<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SONET on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet/</link><description>Recent content in SONET on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Fiber Diet for Business Not Expensive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</guid><description>With business picking up, many companies are hitting a wall – their internet connections can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the increased data flow. The solution? A high-fiber diet for their network.
Fiber optic cables are incredibly efficient. A single strand can handle massive amounts of voice, data, and video simultaneously, far exceeding the needs of most businesses. This capacity can be further multiplied by splitting the light into different wavelengths, each carrying gigabits per second...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Makes the Upgrades Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has always been a popular choice for businesses, particularly those requiring high-speed connections. The good news is that fiber optic service is becoming increasingly accessible to businesses. IT managers and executives now face a decision: stick with their existing copper wireline services or upgrade to fiber optics. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the factors that make fiber optics the preferred choice.
Fiber Optics: The Way of the Future..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Mid-sized and larger businesses that have outgrown the capacity of T1 lines have turned to DS3 Internet Service as the next step in their telecommunications services. Currently, there are more choices for businesses, both small businesses with high bandwidth demands and larger companies seeking this service level.
DS3, short for Digital Signal level 3, is a well-established telecommunications standard for transmitting digital data. It provides a reliable 45 Mbps bandwidth suitable for dedicated point-to-point connections, PBX telephone systems, or internet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Buildings Offer High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Do you want to upgrade your internet speed from slow copper or fixed wireless connections to the rapid speeds offered by fiber optic cables? Are you trying to avoid the high cost of installing new fiber optic cables? If so, you should consider moving into a fiber building.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; a fiber building isn&amp;rsquo;t constructed from exotic materials like carbon fiber. The term &amp;ldquo;fiber&amp;rdquo; refers to the type of telecommunication services already available within the building...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Offers Lower Cost Carrier Grade Fiber Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</guid><description>Large bandwidth consumers, including major corporations, healthcare systems, independent phone companies, video production companies, and internet service providers, now have an affordable alternative for obtaining the reliable bandwidth they require. This shift is thanks to Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet provides metropolitan and long-distance bandwidth services using Ethernet technology rather than conventional telephone company methods. This service is often called Metro Ethernet within a single metropolitan area. These services deliver professional-grade bandwidth solutions characterized by high reliability and dedicated bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Caps: What They Are and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent internet user, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably encountered data caps. This article explains these usage limits and how to navigate them.
OK, What IS a Data Cap? A data cap restricts the amount of data transferred over a connection within a specific timeframe. Usually set monthly, these limits, measured in MB or GB, reset every 30 days. Activities like browsing, file transfers, and cloud backups consume this data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Offers Synchronous Service Transport For Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>Need to move massive amounts of data quickly and reliably? Within a building or campus, fiber optic cables provide sufficient speed and capacity. However, for longer distances, you need robust carrier services. Quest&amp;rsquo;s Synchronous Service Transport (SST) offers a solution.
SST utilizes fiber optics and SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) to provide high-speed, point-to-point data transfer. SONET, a dependable carrier service based on Time Division Multiplexing (TDM), was initially designed for telephone companies and later adopted by large organizations requiring extensive bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is a DS3 Circuit Or T3 Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line often choose DS3. This article explores DS3, its relationship to T3 lines, and competition from Ethernet over Copper.
DS3, or Digital Signal level 3, follows standards set by Bell Labs for the telephone industry. The smallest unit, DS0, has a 64 Kbps bandwidth, enough for one digitized phone call using the original digital standard, PCM (Pulse Code Modulation). Combining 24 DS0s creates a DS1, which runs on a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gig E WAN Comes To The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</guid><description>It may seem surprising, but businesses can now access 10 Gigabit Ethernet connections for their wide area networks. What&amp;rsquo;s even more surprising is how many businesses can actually utilize this bandwidth.
Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular among large corporations and tech companies that need to manage and deliver massive amounts of data quickly. What kinds of companies are we talking about?
For those involved in video production or editing, Gigabit per second connections are essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Everywhere? We’re Almost There!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 20:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</guid><description>By John Shepler
For a while now, experts have predicted a future where all networking standards converge into one: Ethernet. We are nearing a reality where T1, DS3, OCx, and others will be obsolete. How close are we? Very close!
Network Standards Already Favor Ethernet Telecommunications companies are embracing a once-unthinkable idea: they are replacing their proprietary standards with Ethernet services.
The reason is simple: market demand. The past saw many Local Area Network standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-everywhere-we-re-almost-there-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth For Remote Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</guid><description>Businesses need to have a solid plan to safeguard their important data. While basic backups on disks or tapes can help with minor issues like a crashed computer, they are inadequate for major events like natural disasters. Offsite backup is crucial in these situations.
The key is choosing a location geographically distant from your primary site to avoid shared risks. Backing up data across regional offices, separated by significant distances, enhances data protection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-for-remote-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Fiber Replaces Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T1 lines have been a popular connectivity solution for businesses for many years due to their reliability and flexibility in private lines, dedicated internet access, and telephone trunking. However, with the increasing demands of cloud applications and HD video, the fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps has become a significant limitation.
Solution #1: Bonded T1 Lines
One way to increase bandwidth is to combine multiple T1 lines. This can be achieved using a WAN aggregation device or by ordering bonded T1 lines from a provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Video-Film Production Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 18:09:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</guid><description>The shift to digital video and film production has made it possible to work with collaborators across the globe. While physical delivery of tapes and disks is an option, tight production timelines often necessitate electronic file transfer. This, however, raises questions about how to carry out the process and the associated costs.
Bandwidth is the defining feature of digital transfer services, representing the transmission speed in bits per second. It&amp;rsquo;s typically measured in Mbps or Gbps, and generally speaking, a higher bandwidth comes with a higher price tag...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/video-film-production-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>When your business or applications need more bandwidth than T1 lines can offer, even multiple bonded ones, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider fiber optic solutions. But with various options available, how do you choose?
Traditionally, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was the primary fiber optic bandwidth option, pioneered by phone companies. SONET surpasses T-Carrier technology (T1 and T3 lines). While T1 provides 1.5 Mbps over copper and T3 offers 45 Mbps over coaxial cable, SONET scales up to OC-1, OC-3, OC-12, OC-24, OC-48, OC-192, OC-256, and OC-768...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over DS3 Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber are becoming increasingly popular choices for WAN connections. This popularity is driven by competitive pricing and the availability of services like layer 2 switching with direct Ethernet connections. So why would you consider Ethernet over DS3?
It may seem like an unusual combination. DS3, a widely available telecom service, provides 45 Mbps using TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) technology from the T-Carrier standard. Organizations typically use DS3 for dedicated point-to-point connections, high-bandwidth internet access, and high-volume phone lines in contact and call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Connectivity Options For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</guid><description>Most medium to large businesses, and even some smaller ones with high bandwidth needs, can now afford fiber optic bandwidth. This is due to lower prices and a wider range of options, which is great news for those who need a lot of bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these options that you may not be aware of.
Fiber optic bandwidth services generally fall into two categories: traditional time division multiplexed technology, originating from telephone company research, and newer IP-centric networks offered by both competitive service providers and traditional telecom carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Center Services For You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</guid><description>Smaller companies often admire the data centers of larger organizations, but they may not realize that similar services are within their reach.
The key is to only own assets crucial to your business and lease the rest, including data center services. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a massive, secure facility with 24/7 staff, backup generators, and unlimited bandwidth. These services are available on a pay-as-you-go basis.
Two types of data centers are eager to accommodate your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Competitive Fiber Optic Service Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</guid><description>Does your company use a lot of bandwidth? We&amp;rsquo;re talking 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps or more of reliable, commercial-grade bandwidth. If so, bonded T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. You need fiber optic service. But is competitive fiber optic bandwidth an option in your area? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out&amp;hellip;
The reality is that buildings equipped for fiber optic service are appearing faster than ever. Why? Because today&amp;rsquo;s data-heavy applications need increasingly faster network speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DS1 DS3 Relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</guid><description>The terms DS1 and DS3 are frequently used in business telecommunications networking. DS, which stands for Digital Signal level, indicates the capacity of a digital line within the T-carrier system. Essentially, DS1 is associated with T1 service, while DS3 corresponds with T3.
The origins of the T-carrier system can be traced back to the 1950s when Bell Labs recognized the benefits of transitioning from an entirely analog telephone system to digital connections between telephone company offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>