<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>97EBBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/97ebbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 97EBBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:58:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/97ebbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoring the DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the motor. The motor was noticeably loud, a common issue in DC 4002 models often caused by dried lubricant in the sleeve bearings. Addressing this requires disassembling the motor, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubricant.
The first image highlights the upper sleeve bearing after the rotor was removed.
The next image provides a view of the lower bearing, feedback coils, and brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of a Wobbly Carriage Pulley with a New Aluminum Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</guid><description>As I was finishing the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5523), I noticed a concerning noise coming from the carriage when it moved quickly, especially when returning to its starting position. This led me to believe there was an issue with the carriage pulley. Upon inspection, I discovered that the pulley was cracked, which is a common problem with this model. It seems the original plastic can&amp;rsquo;t handle the stress from the setscrew over time and eventually cracks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism, and Tracking Sensor Bulb Replacement and Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</guid><description>The initial step for restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable typically involves reconditioning the arm lowering mechanism and calibrating the tracking system. In this instance, hardened lubricants had affected the mechanical operation, and excessive sensitivity in the tracking sensor led to uncontrolled carriage movement after the arm lowered. The solenoid and damper assembly is depicted below:
The restoration began by disassembling the mechanism, cleaning all parts, and applying fresh lubrication:
A video illustrating the tracking sensor adjustment process is available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A Second Beogram 4002 (5523) Arrived for some TLC - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-second-beogram-4002-5523-arrived-for-some-tlc-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) in need of restoration arrived with its MMC4000 cartridge still attached and transport locks disengaged, causing initial concern about potential damage. The foam meant to support the tonearm had deteriorated, leaving it to swing freely.
Fortunately, the cartridge appeared undamaged, likely due to the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s light weight and protective tape. Testing on a restored Beogram 4000 confirmed its functionality.
The hood was in good condition, showing only minor scratches and signs of polishing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Adjustment of Platter and Sub-Chassis Alignment, Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and Adjustment of the Tonearm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 02:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</guid><description>After restoring the mechanics and electronics of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, it was time to ensure proper alignment of the platter, sub-chassis, and tonearm. The first step was centering the sub-chassis within the transport locks. However, a previous repair attempt had misaligned the transport locks, preventing adjustment. Taking the opportunity, new bushings were installed to replace the deteriorated originals, evidenced by orange plastic fragments within the enclosure.
[Images of deteriorated bushings and new bushings installed]</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Some Final Touches - Replacing Plinth and Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</guid><description>Following the installation of the BeoloverRIAA internal preamplifier and the Commander remote control, this Beogram 4002 (5523) needed a few finishing touches.
The original plinth of the Beogram was damaged. A replacement plinth was sourced, but it also had minor damage, particularly to the corners. Inspired by a previous veneer repair on a Beomaster 8000, a similar approach was taken to address the plinth&amp;rsquo;s corners. Veneer was added and color-matched to the existing finish, significantly improving the appearance, although not completely perfect.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of Beolover RIAA Preamp and 4002 Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (5523), culminating in the installation of gold-plated RCA plugs. My customer opted to have my recently developed internal BeoloverRIAA preamplifier added, along with the 4002 Commander remote control system, which enables control of all functions via a paired Apple remote.
This marks the first 4002 to feature both the Commander and the RIAA preamp – a true fusion of past and present!
Pictures showcasing the installation process of the BeoloverRIAA board and the 4002 Commander are included.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The last step in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5523) was replacing the old and slightly corroded RCA plugs. The picture highlights the original plugs:
This image showcases the new gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs during installation:
The straightforward design of these plugs, which simplifies installation and ensures solid solder connections, is something I appreciate. And here is the finished product:
I need to wait for the PCBs for my new RIAA phono preamp design, so there will be a slight delay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: A New Power Supply Design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous one about the RIAA preamplifier I&amp;rsquo;m building for a Beogram 4002 turntable. This preamp will allow the Beogram to connect directly to a modern amplifier&amp;rsquo;s AUX or TAPE input. While initially pleased with my prototype, I redesigned it for a cleaner layout and had it manufactured.
The new boards arrived, and I assembled a preamplifier, thrilled with its appearance. After installing and testing it, however, I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t tested it thoroughly enough beforehand.</description></item></channel></rss>