<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Family Members on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-members/</link><description>Recent content in Family Members on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-members/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can the Dublin III Regulation strengthen family reunification? The CJEU's ruling on the ability to appeal denials of take charge requests.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Leiden University
Photo credit: DFID
Unaccompanied minors can appeal a receiving EU member state&amp;rsquo;s denial of a request to assume responsibility for their asylum case. This conclusion from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) comes from its judgment in the I. &amp;amp; S. case. Interestingly, the District Court of Haarlem in the Netherlands initially posed the question because the Dublin III Regulation, which governs such transfers, doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly provide for this appeal right.</description></item><item><title>Love triumphs in the CJEU: Equal Marriage and EU Freedom of Movement Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling on same-sex marriage within the framework of EU free movement law in the case of Coman. This case involved a Romanian citizen, Mr. Coman, who married his American husband in Belgium while residing there. When they attempted to return to Romania, the Romanian government, which does not legally acknowledge same-sex marriage, refused residency to Mr.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk.</description></item></channel></rss>