<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Canon has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Canon Singapore has launched FleetnexG, a cloud-based logistics solution providing businesses with real-time delivery tracking and automated scheduling. Designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) that rely on scheduling, delivery, and documentation for their core operations, FleetnexG offers a way to optimize resources and boost efficiency.
Vincent Low, Director &amp;amp; General Manager of Business Imaging Solutions at Canon Singapore, highlights the need for SMEs to go beyond timely order fulfillment. He emphasizes that optimizing resources for greater efficiency and productivity is crucial for success in today&amp;rsquo;s business landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-launched-fleetnexg-a-cloud-based-logistics-solution-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HPE has reduced the entry threshold for its storage portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</guid><description>Hewlett Packard Enterprise (HPE) recently improved its entry storage products to help budget-conscious customers leverage their data and speed up applications. These new HPE MSA Storage options deliver the most budget-friendly dual-controller hybrid flash array from a major vendor while the new HPE StoreEasy 1650 Expanded makes storing large amounts of information more economical.
Being able to quickly and effectively use information is crucial for success. &amp;ldquo;Agility and speed are critical for staying competitive in today&amp;rsquo;s economy, no matter the business size,&amp;rdquo; said Manish Goel, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Storage at HPE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hpe-has-reduced-the-entry-threshold-for-its-storage-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore reviews its accomplishments in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</guid><description>Despite a slowing economy in 2016, SPRING Singapore, a government agency supporting business growth, reported that over 16,000 companies enhanced their capabilities.
These companies participated in projects backed by the Capability Development Grant (CDG) and Innovation &amp;amp; Capability Voucher (ICV) programs. SPRING estimates these projects will generate S$7.8 billion and create approximately 21,400 skilled jobs upon completion, representing a 13% and 43% increase from 2015 respectively.
A record-breaking 2,400 projects received CDG support, almost double the previous year and the highest in five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Helping Your Business Achieve Hyperconnectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It took a whole generation to connect the entire world to the internet. Now, get ready for an even bigger change: we&amp;rsquo;re moving towards hyperconnectivity, and it&amp;rsquo;s happening fast.
Everything, Everywhere, All at Once
Hyperconnectivity means that anything and anyone who can be connected will be connected all the time. We&amp;rsquo;ve already shifted from logging in to having always-on internet for our computers and phones. The next step is to let our devices communicate with each other without us...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-your-business-achieve-hyperconnectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP Helion offers enterprise-level cloud services tailored for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:51:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Helion Managed Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Lean, a service designed to support cloud-based applications for medium and large businesses. This service is suitable for purposes like application development and testing, as well as collaborative work environments.
This managed infrastructure solution allows smaller companies to adopt cloud technology swiftly and scale their usage as needed, all at a lower price point than previous HP Helion managed services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-helion-offers-enterprise-level-cloud-services-tailored-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>