<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>National Parliaments on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/national-parliaments/</link><description>Recent content in National Parliaments on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/national-parliaments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the draft renegotiation deal a legitimate rejection? Tusk's suggestion and the role of national parliaments.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 09:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-renegotiation-deal-a-legitimate-rejection-tusk-s-suggestion-and-the-role-of-national-parliaments/</guid><description>Dr. Katarzyna Granat, Junior Research Fellow &amp;amp; Marie Curie Fellow, Durham Law School Donald Tusk&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A New Settlement for the United Kingdom within the European Union&amp;rdquo; (Draft Decision of the Heads of State or Government), presented on February 2, 2016, provides an initial concrete outline for enhancing the role of national parliaments within the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiation efforts. This note compares the proposed changes with existing mechanisms under the Lisbon Treaty.</description></item><item><title>National legislatures and the "Five Presidents' Report": The extensive journey towards the democratization of Economic and Monetary Union (EMU)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legislatures-and-the-five-presidents-report-the-extensive-journey-towards-the-democratization-of-economic-and-monetary-union-emu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 13:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legislatures-and-the-five-presidents-report-the-extensive-journey-towards-the-democratization-of-economic-and-monetary-union-emu/</guid><description>Ton van den Brink, Associate Professor, University of Utrecht
The &amp;lsquo;Five Presidents&amp;rsquo; Report&amp;rsquo; proposes significant changes to the EU&amp;rsquo;s Economic and Monetary Union (EMU), aiming to deepen its integration. These proposals have substantial implications for national parliaments. A more democratic EMU requires giving these parliaments more authority, going beyond the suggested increased &amp;ldquo;dialogues.&amp;rdquo;
The report advocates for a &amp;ldquo;system of further sovereignty sharing within common institutions,&amp;rdquo; impacting national parliaments by centralizing economic policy coordination within the EU.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule.</description></item><item><title>Can a person be a member of both a national parliament and the European Parliament at the same time?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recently, Geert Wilders, the leader of the Dutch PVV party and a newly elected Member of the European Parliament (MEP), declared his intent to pursue legal action to maintain his position as both an MEP and a member of the Dutch national parliament. This begs the question: does such a right exist?
The crux of the matter lies in Article 39 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, which states that every EU citizen possesses the right to vote in and stand as a candidate for European Parliament elections.</description></item></channel></rss>