<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Worldwide on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/worldwide/</link><description>Recent content in Worldwide on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/worldwide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton guests will enjoy Live Nation experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and Live Nation, a live entertainment company, have launched a new five-year marketing partnership. This collaboration will provide unique experiences, including artist connections and concerts, to Hilton HHonors members, guests, and employees across Hilton&amp;rsquo;s global network of over 4,250 hotels.
Source: Hilton Worldwide. Hilton
aims to motivate a new,
healthier way of thinking - urging
individuals to embrace the unfamiliar,
gain perspective, and learn from daily
life and travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We are all increasing the frequency of washing our hair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</guid><description>The increasing prevalence of hair problems and pollution has led people to shampoo their hair more often, either daily or every other day. This trend has fueled the growth of the shampoo industry, as noted in Technavio&amp;rsquo;s report on the global hair shampoo market from 2015 to 2019. The report highlights that shampoos held over 40% of the global hair care market share in 2014.
Source: Technavio.
The global shampoo market is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investors are increasingly optimistic about placing foreign direct investment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore achieved a top-ten ranking in the 2016 AT Kearney Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) Confidence Index. The city-state climbed five positions, representing the most significant advancement in the rankings, securing the 10th spot.
This index provides a future-oriented assessment of how political, economic, and regulatory shifts are likely to influence FDI inflows into various countries in the coming years. Since its inception in 1998, the study has consistently identified the preferred global destinations for FDI, with the index rankings closely mirroring actual global FDI inflows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The popularity of home remedies for teeth whitening is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 05:27:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</guid><description>Technavio, a research company specializing in technology, found that self-applied teeth whitening products have significantly changed the global oral care market. Consumers are increasingly choosing at-home treatments over professional ones. The firm attributes this shift to the affordability and convenience of oral care products like whitening strips, pens, and trays, which have become popular alternatives to professional whitening procedures.
According to a new Technavio report on the global teeth whitening product market, the industry is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 4% between 2015 and 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple is recalling Beats speakers and offering refunds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</guid><description>Apple initiated a voluntary recall of Beats Pill XL speakers due to a potential fire safety risk. The company determined that in rare cases, the battery in these speakers may overheat.
This recall only affects the specific Beats Pill XL speaker model shown in the images and no other Beats or Apple products.
Apple prioritizes customer safety and urges all Beats Pill XL users to stop using their devices.
To return their speakers and receive a refund of US$325 (or equivalent in local currency) as Apple Store credit or electronic payment, owners can visit www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-is-recalling-beats-speakers-and-offering-refunds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>