<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireline Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireline-services/</link><description>Recent content in Wireline Services on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireline-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle.</description></item><item><title>Future Proofing Your WAN With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Wide area networks (WANs) are changing. While once reliant on telephone technology, core networks are shifting towards packet-switched services to handle the increasing dominance of data and video traffic over voice. This shift raises questions for businesses about adapting their connections to stay current.
Many organizations face growing bandwidth demands. As their service contracts near renewal, they are reevaluating options, considering newer Ethernet services as alternatives to traditional T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Insurance Keeps You in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:32:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-insurance-keeps-you-in-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Constant connectivity has its perks for individuals and businesses, but technology isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof. A broadband outage can be incredibly isolating. Fortunately, there are safeguards against such situations.
Consumers can utilize their mobile data as a backup. Modern smartphones can act as wireless hotspots, allowing devices like computers and printers to connect. While speed and data limits might be concerns, it provides a temporary solution. Another option is using public Wi-Fi hotspots, though availability might be an issue during widespread outages.</description></item></channel></rss>