<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crowdfunding on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crowdfunding/</link><description>Recent content in Crowdfunding on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crowdfunding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A crowdfunding platform has been established to assist victims of human trafficking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</guid><description>Microsoft and the International Organization for Migration (IOM) launched 6Degree.org, a crowdfunding platform that lets individuals directly support the return and reintegration of human trafficking survivors.
This platform, a result of a partnership between Microsoft and IOM, was developed by IOM X. IOM X is an IOM campaign, supported by USAID, that promotes safe migration and aims to end exploitation and human trafficking.
Stefan Sjöström, Microsoft Asia&amp;rsquo;s Vice President for Public Sector, emphasized the potential of technology like cloud computing in addressing migration management challenges and supporting trafficking survivors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-crowdfunding-platform-has-been-established-to-assist-victims-of-human-trafficking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New focus on Kickstarter: A mouse glove as a replacement for traditional computer mice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</guid><description>A new Kickstarter project called the &amp;ldquo;Mouse Glove&amp;rdquo; aims to revolutionize how we interact with technology, potentially replacing touch screens entirely.
Source: Kickstarter website
The creators of the Mouse Glove claim their invention offers a more ergonomic and intuitive user experience compared to traditional mice. By promoting a more natural hand position, they believe it can reduce the risk of repetitive strain injuries like carpal tunnel syndrome.
The glove replicates standard mouse functionalities, including left and right clicks, scrolling, and cursor control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: TwistVolt, the innovative power strip designer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</guid><description>While typical power strips only accommodate standard plugs, the TwistVolt sets itself apart. It features built-in USB outlets and a flexible design that allows for twisting and folding to better suit your power needs.
Source: Kickstarter website
Michael Schroeder, the inventor, explains that their goal was to create a new kind of power strip that prioritizes energy efficiency and provides easy access to all outlets. The result is a product with exceptional energy efficiency, ample USB charging capacity, and a distinctive, patent-pending design that eliminates outlet blockage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-twistvolt-the-innovative-power-strip-designer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Focus of Kickstarter campaign: Sitting cross-legged on a CrossChair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 21:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</guid><description>Dave McClintock designed a chair that lets you comfortably rest with your legs up. Its unique design is so flexible, it even allows for the sukhasana yoga pose while seated.
McClintock explained that the chair caters to millions of workers who experience fatigue, back pain, and stiff muscles from prolonged sitting. While crossing your legs can alleviate these issues, traditional office chairs lack the ergonomics. The CrossChair solves this by enabling various sitting positions, including cross-legged, promoting movement and reducing discomfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An improved chair designed to alleviate back discomfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</guid><description>Simon Hong, a neuroscientist, is seeking funding for his invention, the Chairbot. This robotic chair aims to eliminate back pain by suggesting new positions to the user based on their current posture.
Source: Kickstarter page
The Chairbot&amp;rsquo;s unique design features a split seat that encourages users to alternate between sitting and standing, reducing strain on the spine. Hong explains on the Kickstarter page that this constant shifting prevents the spinal trauma associated with maintaining a single posture for long periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the fast Phone Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</guid><description>The Phone Finder helps locate lost smartphones, even if they&amp;rsquo;re on silent mode, for up to three years. When the Phone Finder device is clicked within 15 meters of the missing phone, the phone will ring, vibrate, and flash, making it easier to find. If the phone is out of range, the Phone Finder website displays its location on a map.
Source: Kickstarter
Creator Gabsow Tom selected Bluetooth 2.1 for its forward and backward compatibility, allowing the Phone Finder to work with any smartphone, regardless of its iOS or Android version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the standing desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 03:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</guid><description>If you need a desk that allows you to work comfortably while standing, Steven Yu might have a solution. His StandDesk is height-adjustable, ranging from 71cm to 114cm, and incorporates design elements that make frequent adjustments easy.
Source: Kickstarter. The all-black StandDesk version.
&amp;ldquo;The StandDesk is more than a product; it&amp;rsquo;s a positive step towards improving people&amp;rsquo;s lives globally,&amp;rdquo; Yu stated on his Kickstarter page.
An intuitive &amp;lsquo;up/down&amp;rsquo; control button effortlessly raises or lowers the desk to the desired height...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: Customizable, reusable clothing in an instant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 13:33:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</guid><description>SiDi Huang, the creator behind ZipSeam, has developed an innovative solution for achieving a tailored look without the need for traditional sewing. ZipSeam offers a quick and easy way to create secure, temporary seams in loose clothing, providing a better fit for the wearer.
This invention has a wide range of applications, from the modeling industry and hand-me-downs to simply adjusting the fit of clothes you love. It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that this project has garnered significant attention and support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-customizable-reusable-clothing-in-an-instant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmoney proudly displays impressive first-year results</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</guid><description>The remarkable first-year performance of Harmoney, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s sole peer-to-peer (P2P) lending platform, highlights a substantial unmet need for crowdfunded microloans.
Established on September 10, 2014, with NZ$100 million in committed capital from prominent institutions like Blue Elephant Capital Management and Heartland Bank, Harmoney has facilitated NZ$100 million in personal loans within its inaugural year. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid expansion has resulted in the creation of 65 new jobs across New Zealand, Australia, and Fiji, with plans underway for an Australian launch...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CrowdsUnite offers convenient crowdsourcing updates all in one location</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</guid><description>CrowdsUnite (crowdsunite.com) aims to be the &amp;ldquo;Yelp&amp;rdquo; for crowdfunding, featuring over 800 platforms in its database. The website provides guidance on crowdfunding and helps startups find the best platforms for their needs.
Alex Feldman, CEO of CrowdsUnite, points out that crowdfunding sites vary in features, customer support, and transparency. He emphasizes the risk of fraudulent campaigns that disappear with investors&amp;rsquo; money.
Source: CrowdsUnite blog. Feldman presents crowdfunding at a July 2014 talk in New York, US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowdonomic is now a registered e-facility for equity crowdfunding in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 14:03:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Crowdonomic. Crowdonomic was one of just a few operators approved as a Registered Electronic Facility (Equity Crowdfunding Platform) by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Securities Commission. From left: Nicola Castelnuovo, Co-founder and Chief Commercial Officer of Crowdonomic; Datuk Ranjit Ajit Singh, Chairman, Securities Commission Malaysia and Leo Shimada, Co-Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Crowdonomic.
Crowdonomic, a leading crowdfunding platform in Southeast Asia, was designated as a registered electronic facility by the Securities Commission Malaysia (SC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdonomic-is-now-a-registered-e-facility-for-equity-crowdfunding-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentrating on Kickstarter: Making Solar Power Accessible to Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</guid><description>Spor Solar Charges aims to make convenient solar-powered battery charging accessible to everyone. Their product, Spor, is a portable battery charger for USB devices that can recharge itself using solar energy. It can also be powered up using a standard AC outlet. The company claims that Spor can charge multiple devices simultaneously and replenish a phone&amp;rsquo;s battery almost as quickly as a wall outlet, according to their Kickstarter page.
Source: Kickstarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>