<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chat on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chat/</link><description>Recent content in Chat on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>StarHub introduces WeChat SIM card for tourists from China visiting Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced two new prepaid SIM cards, named &amp;ldquo;StarHub WeChat Go SIM&amp;rdquo;, specifically designed for Chinese tourists visiting Singapore. This launch is a collaboration between StarHub and WeChat.
The StarHub WeChat Go SIM aims to meet the connectivity needs of the increasing number of Chinese tourists. Data from the Singapore Tourism Board shows a 36% rise in tourists from China in 2016 compared to the previous year. A 2017 Hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-wechat-sim-card-for-tourists-from-china-visiting-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Zhaopin in China introduces chat feature to Highpin recruitment platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</guid><description>Source: Highpin.cn website.
Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform, has introduced Highpin Chat, a desktop-based instant messaging feature for its executive recruitment site, Highpin.cn.
This new chat feature aims to streamline the hiring process on Highpin.cn. Recruiters and employers can now directly connect with candidates, enabling better candidate evaluation and efficient job matching. Similarly, job seekers can use the chat to ask recruiters and employers about specific roles and follow their application status in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The bank in Beirut provides live video conferencing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</guid><description>Bank Audi has established a new flagship branch called &amp;ldquo;Novo&amp;rdquo; in Beirut Central District&amp;rsquo;s Palladium Building. This branch is open every day of the year from 10 am to 10 pm and provides customers with interactive banking services.
In addition to smart ATMs offering services like cash withdrawals, cash and check deposits, and credit card payments, the branch introduces a first-of-its-kind feature in Lebanon: Interactive Teller Machines (ITMs). These ITMs enable customers to connect with personal tellers through live video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>