<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosting/</link><description>Recent content in Hosting on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>How to Get a Web Presence For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</guid><description>Starting a new business or moving an existing one online can feel overwhelming with all the options available. Is it really worth the effort?
Absolutely! Many business owners will attest to the value of establishing an online presence. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be complicated. You can simplify the process by seeking guidance from experienced professionals. Take a look at this engaging introductory video from Network Solutions to see what I mean&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Services With Free Trial Offers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-services-with-free-trial-offers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 02:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-services-with-free-trial-offers/</guid><description>Numerous businesses are turning to cloud services to reduce capital expenses and ongoing operational costs. This rapidly growing field has many vendors vying for market share, making it challenging to determine the ideal services for your needs.
For small businesses with limited budgets, ensuring maximum value for their IT and communication spending is crucial. One effective approach is to test services through free trials before committing. With this in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of cloud-based services offering trial periods.</description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party.</description></item></channel></rss>