<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Visualisation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visualisation/</link><description>Recent content in Visualisation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/visualisation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tableau Public undergoes a makeover as participation increases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 17:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</guid><description>Source: Tableau Public gallery. This Tableau Public visualization displays the world&amp;rsquo;s largest stadiums. Interact with the visualization here.
Tableau reported that 36,000 users joined Tableau Public in 2014, publishing a record number of data stories on the free platform. Tableau Public allows users to create, share, and discover data stories on the web. It comprises a downloadable authoring tool for exploring and visualizing data, a cloud platform for hosting, sharing, and embedding interactive visualizations, and a learning program offering support and training to a global community of data enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-public-undergoes-a-makeover-as-participation-increases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Create interactive data visualizations with our free tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/</guid><description>Source: Tableau Public website.
Unlike print, online content typically benefits from interactivity, often through clickable links. What if we applied this interactivity, similar to interactive infographics, to modern graphics to present more data in the same amount of space?
Tableau Software, a company focused on making data accessible, allows us to create interactive infographics using Tableau Public, a free tool that enables embedding visualizations into web pages. Although not new (videos from 2010 are available online), Tableau Public is poised for increased popularity given the rise of infographics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/create-interactive-data-visualizations-with-our-free-tool/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data-driven alerts are introduced in Tableau 10.3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</guid><description>Tableau Software, a leading provider of visual analytics solutions, has launched Tableau 10.3. This latest release empowers businesses to derive data-driven insights swiftly.
Francois Ajenstat, Chief Product Officer at Tableau, stated that companies are seeking to maximize the value of their data, aiming not just for basic analysis but for the capability to effortlessly and efficiently unlock insights from all their data. Features like smart recommendations enable customers to find the right data quickly, bypassing the need to search for suitable tables and joins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>