<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Infocomm on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infocomm/</link><description>Recent content in Infocomm on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/infocomm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is dedicated to developing talent in the infocomm sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, addressed the rising demand for infocomm professionals in the country. This surge is attributed to the growth of the ICT sector and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiatives. Dr. Yaacob emphasized the need to fill 30,000 infocomm positions by 2020.
He acknowledged the challenge of meeting this demand solely with local talent, stating that while relying on non-Singaporeans might be necessary, the focus should be on equipping Singaporeans with highly competitive skills.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors.</description></item></channel></rss>