<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone Trunk Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-trunk-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone Trunk Lines on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-trunk-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Thirty Carriers, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</guid><description>Are you overwhelmed and frustrated with your current telecommunications services? Do you feel stuck with your local phone or internet provider and dread seeing your monthly bill?
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to endure this! You deserve a wide range of choices for your voice and data communication needs. Imagine having access to 30 different business-grade carriers, offering everything from basic phone lines to high-speed internet options like wireless and satellite.
Whether you need ISDN PRI lines for your office phone system, MPLS networks to connect multiple locations, or Gigabit Ethernet for high-bandwidth applications like video conferencing, you have options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EarthLink Offers Healthcare IT Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</guid><description>The potential for healthcare automation to significantly reduce costs in healthcare settings like doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices, clinics, and hospitals is substantial. However, not all healthcare providers have the necessary IT capabilities to modernize and leverage these new technologies. They might also struggle to meet privacy regulations like HIPAA. This is where large network service providers such as EarthLink Business can bridge the gap. An example of this can be seen in how EarthLink supports Monadnock Community Hospital in Peterborough, New Hampshire, as shown in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>