<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Middle East on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/middle-east/</link><description>Recent content in Middle East on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/middle-east/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Kobo eReader ecosystem is now accessible in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Kobo. The Kobo
Aura H2O eReader.
Kobo, the eBook retailer, and distributor Lionfish have announced that Kobo&amp;rsquo;s digital reading platform is launching in the GCC region. This will give readers access to Kobo&amp;rsquo;s eBookstore, which offers over 4.2 million titles. They will also be able to purchase eReaders and apps compatible with iOS, Android, Microsoft, and BlackBerry platforms.
Kobo products will be sold in 34 stores throughout the region.</description></item><item><title>The demand for online training in the Middle East exceeds the available supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</guid><description>Online professional training courses are gaining popularity in the Middle East, but the availability of suitable courses hasn&amp;rsquo;t matched the increased demand, according to research by GulfTalent, a recruitment firm that operates an online recruitment portal for the region.
GulfTalent’s study shows that one out of five professionals interested in pursuing training prefers online courses. This signifies a significant shift, given that online training was practically nonexistent ten years ago.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals.</description></item><item><title>China has a strong presence in the new City Momentum Index by Jones Lang LaSalle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</guid><description>Five cities in Asia Pacific and the Middle East — Dubai, Wuhan, Shanghai, Hong Kong and Singapore — are among the top 10 in Jones Lang LaSalle&amp;rsquo;s new City Momentum Index (CMI). This index identifies cities worldwide with significant short-term socio-economic and commercial real estate momentum, as well as strong long-term growth potential.
Jeremy Kelly, Director of Global Research at Jones Lang LaSalle, explains that city momentum is not solely determined by GDP growth.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates</description></item><item><title>Fujifilm has launched the X100T premium compact camera in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Fujifilm has introduced the X100T, a high-end compact camera succeeding the successful X100S, to the Middle East market.
Source: Fujifilm. The X100T is available
in black and silver.
&amp;ldquo;The X100, launched in March 2011, established a new market for premium compact cameras. A year later, the second-generation X100S was released, featuring an updated sensor, processor, and an advanced Hybrid Viewfinder,&amp;rdquo; stated Yuta Kawamura, Marketing Manager for the electronic imaging division at Fujifilm Middle East &amp;amp; Africa.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadhan, digital marketing methods need to be adapted in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Think with Google website. Changes in statistics for Musalsalat, a platform for Ramadhan TV series, during the month.
The Think with Google blog highlights the need for specialized digital marketing strategies in the Middle East and North Africa during Ramadhan. Google Analytical Consultants Vrinda Singh and Younis Maqousi, along with YouTube Specialist David Lacklen, observed a significant increase in mobile internet usage, YouTube viewership, and search engine activity throughout the month.</description></item><item><title>Dabur Herb'l Sensitive Toothpaste is designed to combat tooth demineralization in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Dabur International.
Dabur International has introduced its new Herb’l Sensitive Toothpaste to the Middle East market. This toothpaste uses natural ingredients, including cinnamon, mint, licorice root, and potassium ions to quickly and effectively alleviate tooth sensitivity.
The company states that using this toothpaste twice daily will not only reduce sensitivity but also lead to healthier gums. It does this by preventing plaque buildup, gum inflammation, and cavities, all while freshening breath.</description></item><item><title>Expatstoday provides important advice for expatriates living in the Gulf region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</guid><description>Source: Expatstoday
A new online platform, Expatstoday, aims to attract individuals considering a move to Bahrain, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, or the UAE. The website provides insights into living conditions in these Gulf countries.
The company behind the platform emphasizes its commitment to providing accurate, current, and trustworthy information. While the sections dedicated to Gulf countries appear well-established, suggesting an active user base, pages for other countries seem relatively new, often lacking listings in various categories.</description></item><item><title>Hotdesk and Compass provide short-term workspace solutions in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Hotdesk, a platform for finding temporary office space, has teamed up with Compass Offices to provide on-demand workspaces and meeting rooms for professionals on the move. These spaces can be reserved for various durations, including daily, weekly, or monthly.
Studies from IDC indicate that by 2015, there will be a significant increase in the number of mobile workers globally, with over 1.3 billion individuals adopting this work style. Notably, the Asia Pacific region is projected to have the highest concentration, with over 838 million mobile workers.</description></item><item><title>Verizon enhances e-business capabilities with increased support for private IP services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-enhances-e-business-capabilities-with-increased-support-for-private-ip-services/</guid><description>Verizon Communications is expanding its Private IP services network, offering businesses a secure way to deliver e-business applications and conduct business-to-business e-commerce. The expansion includes 10 additional countries across the Middle East, Africa, and Asia-Pacific regions.
Verizon business and wholesale customers in the Middle East and Asia Pacific now have expanded access to Private IP Multiprotocol Private Label Switching (MPLS) services in Bangladesh, Cambodia, Laos, Nepal, Iraq, Lebanon, and Yemen. Chennai, India, gains an additional location, offering customers enhanced network resiliency and reach through increased access to MPLS services.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing.</description></item><item><title>Asian cities have been rearranged in Mercer's Cost of Living Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</guid><description>Five Asian cities—Hong Kong (ranked 2nd), Tokyo (3rd), Singapore (5th), Seoul (6th), and Shanghai (8th)—were named among the top 10 most expensive cities for expatriates in this year&amp;rsquo;s ranking.
Currency fluctuations played a significant role in shaping the rankings of most Asian cities.
While all mainland Chinese cities surveyed experienced a drop in ranking, Tianjin (12th) stood out as an exception, climbing 18 positions.
Mumbai, India made a remarkable jump of 25 places this year, attributed to robust economic growth, inflation, and a stable currency.</description></item><item><title>Aramex is constructing private parcel lockers to meet the demands of the expanding e-commerce industry in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:04:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Aramex, a leading provider of global logistics and transportation solutions, has partnered with InPost, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest parcel locker network. This collaboration aims to provide consumers in the Middle East with convenient access to private, automated parcel lockers for all their e-commerce needs by the end of 2014.
Aramex attributes the significant growth of the e-commerce sector in the region to several factors. These include a growing affluent urban population, increased interest in and demand for online products and services, and a rise in new online retailers entering the market.</description></item><item><title>Five Asian hotels are ranked in the top 25 of Expedia Insiders' Select 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</guid><description>Expedia unveiled its 2014 Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select list in early July. This list highlights the best hotels globally, as determined by almost two million verified customer reviews and Expedia&amp;rsquo;s own travel experts.
Source: Blue Karma Resort website.
Out of over 290,000 bookable properties on Expedia&amp;rsquo;s global websites, 650 hotels received the Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select designation in 2014.
Here are a few of the top 25 hotels from this year&amp;rsquo;s list:
2. Blue Karma Resort - Seminyak, Bali</description></item><item><title>Improve your sleep with the Sleep with Six Senses program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Better sleep with the new Sleep with Six Senses programme.
Six Senses partnered with Sleep Doctor Dr. Michael Breus to launch its improved sleep standard called Sleep With Six Senses. Currently, five resorts offer this standard, with complete implementation across all locations expected by mid-2017. All future resorts will feature this program from their opening day.
The experience begins with a pre-arrival online questionnaire. This allows a designated Sleep Ambassador to understand the guest&amp;rsquo;s relationship with sleep and tailor the room accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:</description></item></channel></rss>