<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Customer Premises Equipment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/customer-premises-equipment/</link><description>Recent content in Customer Premises Equipment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/customer-premises-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true.</description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization</description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased.</description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?</description></item></channel></rss>