<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ECtHR Case Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecthr-case-law/</link><description>Recent content in ECtHR Case Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:35:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecthr-case-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The complex human rights protection system in Europe: facing challenges, embracing opportunities, and managing risks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</guid><description>Lecture at Waseda University Tokyo, 14 March 2016
Jörg Polakiewicz
Professor at the Europainstitut of the University of Saarbrücken and Director of Legal Advice and Public International Law (Legal Adviser), Council of Europe.[1]
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to be presenting at Waseda University in Tokyo. Thank you to Professor Koji Tonami and Professor Kaoru Obata for making this lecture possible.
I am consistently impressed by the comprehensive understanding of fundamental rights protection within Japan&amp;rsquo;s legal system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Workplace Privacy: The Strasbourg Grand Chamber Provides Clarity on Legal Standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The Bărbulescu case examined the permissible extent of employer monitoring of employee communications, including internet usage, particularly when private conversations might be mixed with work-related ones. An employee, dismissed for violating a company policy prohibiting personal use of work equipment, sued his employer in Romania. He lost and appealed under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), which protects privacy rights, arguing that his employer&amp;rsquo;s monitoring of his communications violated the precedent set by Copland v UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Delfi restricting freedom of expression online in Estonia?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Media Law, University of Essex
Under what circumstances can online freedom of expression be restricted? The recent decision from the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber in the case of Delfi v. Estonia tackles this question, focusing on comments made in response to a news article. This ruling presents thought-provoking issues concerning both human rights and EU law, which will be examined in this analysis...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the Big Brother Watch case: part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
(These observations on the judgment follow part 1 of the analysis, which explained the Court’s reasoning).
The Big Brother Watch judgment can be interpreted in two ways: as confirmation that mass surveillance is permissible (para 314) or as an acknowledgment that the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act (RIPA) framework was inadequate. This implies that the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), which inherited some of RIPA&amp;rsquo;s shortcomings, is also lacking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing Celaj and Vélez Loor: The implications of Latin American immigrants' detention in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 18:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</guid><description>Dr Andrea Romano, Research assistant, “Sapienza” University of Rome
Introduction
The recent Celaj judgment and its debatable connection to past rulings of the Court of Justice concerning the Returns Directive has been the subject of much discussion. This analysis will provide a concise comparison between this judgment and the Vélez Loor case, which was decided by the Inter-American Court of Human Rights (IACtHR) in 2010.
The Court of Justice of the European Union’s judgment in the Celaj case stemmed from various preliminary rulings brought forth by Italian judicial bodies regarding the Returns Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-celaj-and-v-lez-loor-the-implications-of-latin-american-immigrants-detention-in-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing religious tolerance with freedom of expression in ECHR case law: Is there a right to insult?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights has reignited the debate about whether freedom of speech should have limitations, particularly when it comes to potentially offensive remarks targeting religious beliefs, such as those of the Muslim faith. This presents an opportunity to analyze the case&amp;rsquo;s background and determine what, if any, restrictions on free speech are justifiable in such instances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Expanding the margin of appreciation: France's prohibition on public face-veiling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 05:03:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</guid><description>The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) has ruled on a highly anticipated case, SAS v France, concerning France&amp;rsquo;s 2010 law prohibiting face coverings in public. The case was brought by a French woman, represented by British lawyers, who argued that the law violated several articles of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), including the right to freedom of religion, expression, and association, as well as protection from discrimination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expanding-the-margin-of-appreciation-france-s-prohibition-on-public-face-veiling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jonathan Sumption's perspective on human rights is not coherent when considering the historical context of gay rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</guid><description>In his Reith Lecture, “Human Rights and Wrongs,” Jonathan Sumption argues that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) has overstepped its boundaries. He believes the court continuously expands its interpretation of the European Convention on Human Rights, creating new rights and encroaching on areas that should be determined by elected officials.
Sumption has raised similar concerns previously, stating in 2016 that the ECtHR is at the forefront of creating fundamental law that goes beyond the original text of the Convention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the Role of the European Court of Human Rights in Addressing Harassment of Human Rights Defenders: Evaluating Democracy, Malicious Intent, and Covert Motives.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:41:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</guid><description>Protecting Critics: The European Court of Human Rights Strengthens its Stance Against Azerbaijan in Aliyev v. Azerbaijan By Dr Marco Antonio Simonelli, PhD, University of Siena, and Alast Najafi, LLM candidate, University of Leiden
Introduction The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) used Article 18 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), a rarely utilized provision, to condemn Azerbaijan for human rights violations in the case of Aliyev v. Azerbaijan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New ECHR ruling on freedom of expression and internet comment liability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 13:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) raises the question of whether internet site providers should be held accountable for comments made by users. This issue gained significance following the court&amp;rsquo;s ruling in MTE v. Hungary.
Considering the importance of intermediaries in the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth, there are arguments for not treating them like traditional publishers. Instead, they could be granted some immunity regarding content posted by others...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the case of Schipani v Italy, under what circumstances is it necessary for national courts to seek guidance from the CJEU as per the ECHR?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo; (ECHR) judgment in the Schipani vs. Italy case, issued on July 21, 2015, revisited a topic of significant interest to EU legal experts: the violation of the ECHR by a national court due to its failure to request a preliminary ruling. This judgment, released just before the summer break, might have slipped under the radar for some...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Commentary on Arlewin v. Sweden: Libel Law, EU Law, and the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 02:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</guid><description>Athanassios Takis: PhD, Special Adviser to General Secretariat of Greek government
The European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruling of March 1, 2016, in the case of Arlewin v. Sweden examined how EU Regulation 44/2001, which decides which Member State&amp;rsquo;s courts hold jurisdiction over civil and commercial disputes, was used (or misused) by Swedish courts. This case highlighted the limitations of the &amp;lsquo;acte clair&amp;rsquo; doctrine – the idea that national courts don&amp;rsquo;t always need to consult the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on EU law matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Appeal ruling in Benkharbouche and Janah: State immunity, remedies, and rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Benkharbouche v Sudan and Janah v Libya delves into significant aspects of public international law, the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, highlighting their interplay within the current British constitutional framework. The cases involved employment law claims brought by two domestic workers against the Sudanese and Libyan embassies, respectively. The embassies invoked state immunity under a UK law based on a Council of Europe Convention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>