<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cable Internet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-internet/</link><description>Recent content in Cable Internet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cable-internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>