<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Party on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/party/</link><description>Recent content in Party on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/party/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is invited to a new year countdown at Clarke Quay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay.
Clarke Quay invites everyone in Singapore to celebrate the end of the year with exciting festivities. Popular radio DJs Glenn Ong from Class95FM and Sonia Chew from 987FM will host the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve countdown. The event will feature live music by the band Goodfellas, a vibrant street parade with a glow theme, and roving percussionists.
The entire event at Clarke Quay will be broadcasted live on 987FM.</description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner.</description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay for the Once Upon a Nightmare free street party to celebrate Halloween</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-for-the-once-upon-a-nightmare-free-street-party-to-celebrate-halloween/</guid><description>Clarke Quay is hosting &amp;ldquo;Once Upon A Nightmare,&amp;rdquo; a street party they&amp;rsquo;re calling the most frightening Halloween event of the year. The event, which is free to attend, will be hosted by popular radio DJs Justin Ang and Vernon A from 98.7FM’s Muttons On The Move.
Source: Clarke Quay.
Attendees can enjoy live music from local band Enigma and participate in themed games for a chance to win prizes. Guests are encouraged to dress up in their most twisted and imaginative interpretations of fairytale characters.</description></item><item><title>The highlight of the Downtown Dubai New Year's Eve Gala is the Burj Khalifa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</guid><description>To celebrate the arrival of 2015, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Khalifa will showcase a dazzling LED display across its 828-meter height, synchronized with a spectacular fireworks show, according to a report from the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
Emaar Properties, the developer behind Downtown Dubai, is orchestrating a six-part extravaganza for their New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Gala. The event will feature a captivating blend of fireworks, laser displays, and a light show. A highlight of the celebration will be a special tribute to Dubai, its leaders, and the UAE&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments over the past 43 years, projected onto the specially designed LED screen.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay to celebrate F1 with special meal promotions and parties at Attica</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 18:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay website.
Clarke Quay is celebrating the Singapore Grand Prix season with special offers and events for both racing fans and those just looking to enjoy the festivities.
Everyone can take advantage of dining deals like buy-one-get-one-free offers at District 10, special Grand Prix menu items at Hooters, and a free meal for every four diners at Peony Jade.
Those with Grand Prix tickets can also enjoy discounts of 10% to 20% at participating restaurants.</description></item></channel></rss>