<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metropolitan Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metropolitan-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Metropolitan Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metropolitan-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>