<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Partner on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/partner/</link><description>Recent content in Partner on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/partner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Chamber partners with Souq.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry and Souq.com, the leading online retail and marketplace platform in the Middle East, have partnered to boost Chamber members’ participation in regional e-commerce.
The agreement grants Dubai Chamber members exclusive benefits from Souq.com, including complimentary access to its Fulfilled by SOUQ services for three months and specialized onboarding training. These benefits also encompass enhanced search visibility, customer support, and promotional opportunities.
In turn, Souq...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ITFC and Catalyst Group collaborate to enhance trade for small and medium enterprises in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>The International Islamic Trade Finance Corporation (ITFC) and Catalyst Group, a Jeddah-based real estate company, have partnered to support small and medium-sized enterprise (SME) trade development in Saudi Arabia. This collaboration will launch ITFC’s KSA SME Program, starting with a pilot SME Trade Development Program (TDP) in Saudi Arabia, with the intention of expanding to other countries.
This agreement aligns with Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Vision 2030 SMEs Trade Development Program, which focuses on supporting businesses&amp;rsquo; export capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guangzhou businesses enter into Letters of Intent with Singapore organizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</guid><description>Source: Guangzhou Municipal Government. Cai.
The city of Guangzhou held a promotional event in Singapore to explore collaboration and innovation between the two business hubs. Two agreements were reached: one between the Sino-Singapore International Joint Research Institute and Chinese Academy of Sciences Holdings Company, and another between Guangzhou Gas Group, Guangzhou Port Group, and the industrial group Royal Golden Eagle.
Guangzhou&amp;rsquo;s Vice Mayor, Cai Chaolin, who also leads the Nansha District&amp;rsquo;s Communist Party and Development Zone, highlighted the shared attributes between Guangzhou and Singapore, such as their size, cultural similarities, and languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Information System for sharing insights on businesses in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced the Business Intelligence Information System (BIIS), a new digital platform designed to revolutionize how business information is accessed and utilized.
This initiative aligns with the UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum&amp;rsquo;s vision of transforming Dubai into a smart city. BIIS provides a centralized hub for users to obtain crucial information about local and international businesses, empowering companies to identify potential partners and make well-informed decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's International Enterprise (IE) and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to collaborate on connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</guid><description>International Enterprise (IE) Singapore, a government agency promoting international trade, and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have established a partnership to boost trade and international expansion for Singaporean companies. This agreement, solidified in a memorandum of understanding (MoU), marks IE Singapore’s first strategic partnership with a Singaporean bank.
The collaboration between IE Singapore and UOB aims to support 200 Singaporean companies in expanding overseas within the next three years. Their focus is primarily on Southeast Asia, China, Japan, and Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Members of Impact Hub have access to resources provided by Google for Entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Impact Hub. Horowitz (left) with Sai (right).
Impact Hub, the largest coworking and entrepreneur-building community in Singapore, has partnered with Google for Entrepreneurs as its first tech hub partner in Southeast Asia. This collaboration grants Impact Hub Singapore members access to Google for Entrepreneurs&amp;rsquo; global network and resources, encompassing numerous coworking spaces and community programs across 135 countries.
Impact Hub Singapore is dedicated to fostering startup growth by offering comprehensive support, ranging from coworking space to essential resources and tools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Japan and Singapore celebrate 50 years of diplomatic relations with the signing of a new Memorandum of Understanding (MoU)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/</guid><description>Source: Takasaki City. From left: Shinichi Aoshima, President, Takasaki Seinenkeieisya Kyogikai (seated); HE the Ambassador of Japan Kenji Shinoda (standing); Low Yen Ling, Parliamentary Secretary of Singapore Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Education and Mayor of South West CDC (standing); Douglas Foo, Singapore Manufacturing Federation (seated); Kenji Tomioka, City Mayor, Takasaki (standing).
The 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between Singapore and Japan (SJ50) was commemorated in Singapore on November 18th at the Japan Business Expo - Takasaki Day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-and-singapore-celebrate-50-years-of-diplomatic-relations-with-the-signing-of-a-new-memorandum-of-understanding-mou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can enjoy Careem services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 14:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</guid><description>Source: Careem website. Emirates Skywards partners with Careem to provide benefits for their members.
Emirates Skywards, the loyalty program for Emirates, has partnered with Careem. This makes Emirates Skywards the only frequent flyer program to provide both earning and redemption opportunities with the leading car booking app in the region.
Careem is a rapidly growing company, currently operating in nine countries. Members can earn and redeem Skywards Miles when using Careem services in the UAE, Qatar, KSA, Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt, Pakistan, Kuwait, and Morocco...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>