<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tracking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tracking/</link><description>Recent content in Tracking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tracking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523) began, as always, with the arm lowering mechanism. The lubricants in these mechanisms often harden with age, preventing the tonearm from lowering correctly. The mechanism is shown here in its original condition:
Each moving part was removed
for cleaning and re-lubrication before reassembly. Next, I lubricated the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point. This required removing the sensor arm, as pictured below from the back:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Germany En Route to California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4000 turntable from Germany, intended for a customer in California. My task is to refurbish the unit and deliver it to its new owner.
The turntable was poorly packaged for shipment, resulting in the keypad plates becoming detached during transit. This led to minor damage to the plates themselves and some cosmetic imperfections on other internal surfaces.
The aluminum surfaces are in surprisingly good shape considering the loose keypad plates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Final Adjustments, Repair of a Damaged Pinth Corner and Test Drive with Bobby Hutcherson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration is nearing completion. Following the installation of new gold-plated RCA plugs, I made adjustments to the sub-chassis, platter height, and meticulously cleaned the aluminum surfaces. To prevent the needle from contacting the platter ribs if the record detection mechanism fails, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit.
Subsequently, I calibrated the tracking weight scale and enhanced the counterweight adjustment mechanism. The original flimsy circlip was replaced with a more durable M3 nut and washer setup, enhancing its resistance to transport-related stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments, a New Solenoid, and Test Drive with Christoph Spendel &amp; Wolfgang Schlüter Group on MPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</guid><description>The final steps of restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) involved replacing the sensor arm light bulb with an LED assembly and performing standard adjustments. These included calibrating the tracking feedback, platter height, level, sub-chassis height, and arm lowering limit, which prevents stylus damage.
To ensure accurate tracking weight calibration, the C-clip securing the counterweight adjustment screw was replaced with an M3 nut and washer for permanent fixation. This guarantees that the calibration remains consistent during shipping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter Height, Tonearm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>After successfully positioning the top aluminum plates, I could adjust the sub-chassis and platter. This step is crucial as it sets the foundation for adjusting the arm lowering limits and, ultimately, the tracking force. This Beogram will be ready for an initial test run once this is completed. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously provided detailed explanations of the chassis and platter adjustment process on my blog and YouTube channel. Two videos demonstrate the platter bearing adjustment and the subchassis adjustment (using a Beogram 4000 as an example, although the procedure is almost identical for the 4002)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Arrival from Arizona - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) from Arizona. It needed complete functional restoration. The unit arrived without its cover, shipped in a Beolover container, which is a great way to ensure safe transportation.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the unit as it looked when unpacked:
While a little dirty, it&amp;rsquo;s in decent condition except for the worn-out keypad:
Hopefully, these keypads can be professionally refurbished. On a positive note, the base is in good shape, with almost pristine corners:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival From West Virginia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from West Virginia recently arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was in good condition and shipped in a Beolover container.
Initial inspection revealed no significant damage to the dust cover or hinges. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, but the keypad has some wear. This will be addressed by installing a Beolover Commander remote control module, which allows for keypad-free operation.
The plinth is well-preserved, with minimal damage to the front corners, which are prone to wear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddy Hubbard's 1975 Album "Polar AC"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable to its former glory is always fulfilling. This particular restoration involved several meticulous adjustments before I could relish Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s music.
The first crucial step was aligning the platter and arms flawlessly. Next, I had to align the platter with its surrounding aluminum panels while ensuring the chassis remained suspended, delicately balanced on its spring-loaded arms. This procedure requires precision as the tolerances for these adjustments are minimal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) AC-motor turntable purchased from eBay. I had sent the seller specific packaging instructions and a sturdy double-boxed container, which they thankfully followed, resulting in the unit arriving undamaged. Initial observations are as follows:
The aluminum surfaces are generally in good shape, just needing a cleaning. The platter, in particular, has remarkably few imperfections.
The keypad shows typical signs of use, with fingerprints visible on the most frequently pressed keys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, known for its unstable RPM, recently arrived for repair. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in excellent cosmetic condition with only minor blemishes.
The keypad appears barely used. However, the hood has some deep scratches, likely from improper storage. Internally, the turntable looks completely original.
Initial testing revealed the arm lowering mechanism is slow, and the automatic RPM switching from 33 to 45 is not functioning, although manual switching works...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Seattle en Route to Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</guid><description>An Australian customer purchased a Beogram 4002 on eBay from the US and sent it to me for restoration. Upon its arrival, I discovered it was in poor condition, likely due to storage in a basement or attic. The dust cover was particularly damaged, with scratches on the aluminum trim and the surface itself.
Despite the dust cover&amp;rsquo;s condition, the internal components appeared undamaged, including the hinges, suggesting a successful restoration is possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 06:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</guid><description>My work began with the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, as is customary for me. My client had already addressed the cleaning and lubrication of the damper and solenoid linkages, so my task was to detach the linkage connecting the damper and tonearm. This required removing the sensor arm assembly, as shown here:
Extracting the sensor arm involved removing two screws at its base:
The linkage could then be detached:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Platter, Sub-Chassis, Arm Lowering Limit and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>To prepare the Beogram 4002 (5513) for testing, several mechanical adjustments were required. The platter needed to be perfectly aligned with the surrounding aluminum plates. This involved balancing the floating sub-chassis within its support brackets. After aligning the chassis and platter, the arm lowering limit was addressed. Finally, the tracking force was calibrated to match the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s weight dial.
Prior to adjusting the sub-chassis, damaged cabinet guidance washers, crucial for securing the top aluminum plates, were replaced with 3D-printed replicas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Evaluation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived for refurbishment, carefully packaged to prevent damage during shipping. The unit appears to be mostly original and in good cosmetic condition, with the exception of a worn keypad.
The keypad&amp;rsquo;s stamped metal sheet is not scratched, suggesting a straightforward restoration using a specialized technique. Interestingly, the STOP key shows more wear than the START key.
Further inspection revealed minor damage to the plinth corners and non-original screws securing the dust cover...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism, and Tracking Sensor Bulb Replacement and Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 11:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</guid><description>The initial step for restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable typically involves reconditioning the arm lowering mechanism and calibrating the tracking system. In this instance, hardened lubricants had affected the mechanical operation, and excessive sensitivity in the tracking sensor led to uncontrolled carriage movement after the arm lowered. The solenoid and damper assembly is depicted below:
The restoration began by disassembling the mechanism, cleaning all parts, and applying fresh lubrication:
A video illustrating the tracking sensor adjustment process is available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-tracking-sensor-bulb-replacement-and-adjustment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Redesigned Drop-In Tracking Sensor Light Bulb Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 17:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I decided to upgrade the tracking sensor light bulb with a new SMD LED design I had created. My previous design lacked stability with the intensity adjustment trimmer, so I redesigned it to be more secure and visually appealing.
The new design incorporates the trimmer directly onto the circuit board and houses it within the light shield. This required modifications to the 3D printed housing to accommodate the trimmer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-redesigned-drop-in-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Full Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 22:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable originating from California. The restoration process commenced with the reconstruction of the carriage and arm lowering mechanisms, encompassing meticulous cleaning and lubrication of components like the solenoid and damper.
Following the mechanism restoration, focus shifted to the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm. This involved addressing a common issue: a detached copper pad on the sensor arm assembly. The pad was reattached using epoxy to ensure smooth operation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-full-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Another New Arrival - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable that needs some care. After unboxing it, I was pleased to see the effective packing method, similar to what I demonstrate in my 4002 shipping video. The sturdy metal construction of the 4002 makes it relatively easy to ship safely with proper double boxing and precautions.
My initial assessment is positive. The aluminum surfaces are in great shape and will gleam with a thorough cleaning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Idris Muhammad (KU-17) After Platter and Tonearm Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 00:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day at the shop, where another Beogram 4002 (5513) is looking and sounding fantastic! The finishing touches involved adjusting the sub-chassis and platter to ensure they float freely and sit flush with the deck&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface. My YouTube channel features two videos demonstrating these adjustments for a Beogram 4000, which are very similar to the 4002 model.
Afterward, the tonearm lowering limit was adjusted, a crucial procedure given the 4002&amp;rsquo;s control system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent photosensor malfunctions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-idris-muhammad-ku-17-after-platter-and-tonearm-adjustments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): First Contact and Two Dead Transistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 that was already being repaired but needed further troubleshooting. The unit is in good cosmetic condition with minor wear. Upon inspection, the platter motor ran when turned on, but the carriage remained static.
Further investigation revealed that transistor TR20, responsible for the carriage motor control, was faulty. Replacing this component restored carriage movement.
However, the carriage would move only slightly before returning to its starting position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Adjustment of Platter and Sub-Chassis Alignment, Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and Adjustment of the Tonearm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 02:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</guid><description>After restoring the mechanics and electronics of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, it was time to ensure proper alignment of the platter, sub-chassis, and tonearm. The first step was centering the sub-chassis within the transport locks. However, a previous repair attempt had misaligned the transport locks, preventing adjustment. Taking the opportunity, new bushings were installed to replace the deteriorated originals, evidenced by orange plastic fragments within the enclosure.
[Images of deteriorated bushings and new bushings installed]..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-adjustment-of-platter-and-sub-chassis-alignment-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-adjustment-of-the-tonearm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from California with a Bit of Shipping Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived needing some care, but unfortunately experienced additional damage during shipping. Upon opening the box, it was discovered that the carriage had detached from the pulley, which was stuck to tape residue. Thankfully, the tonearm was secured with tape, preventing it from ejecting through the platter opening and causing more severe damage. However, the tonearm did sustain some impact. This highlights the importance of securing the carriage during transport using foam and tape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This article details the refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5504) turntable. An initial assessment of the unit is documented in a previous post here.
The turntable, stripped of its panels and platter, appeared relatively untouched. However, evidence of previous work emerged later.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly, which was quite dirty. After disassembling and cleaning the parts, the platter motor and capacitors were removed for thorough cleaning. The motor housing, including the bearings, underwent an oil infusion process under vacuum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-complete-functional-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From New York</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently purchased on eBay was shipped using a specialized container to protect it in transit. Thankfully, the seller mostly followed the provided packing guidelines, resulting in no damage during shipping. Upon opening, the turntable was in good condition, with only minor issues.
While the blue tape used on the aluminum surfaces didn&amp;rsquo;t cause any damage to the lettering, there were a few scratches on the platter. These were likely caused by attempts to remove it improperly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5501 from Sweden: Full Technical Restoration and Some Interesting Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 turntable (Type 5501 with optical carriage position detection) for a complete technical restoration. The unit arrived without a dust cover. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the Beogram right after unpacking:
Besides a number of loose parts that fell out when I opened the box, I was surprised to see that the cartridge was still mounted on the tonearm:
Fortunately, the MMC4000 cartridge had a small plexiglass guard in place, preventing any damage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5501-from-sweden-full-technical-restoration-and-some-interesting-issues/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free E-Books to Get More Sales Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market, businesses face constant pressure to attract and retain customers. Finding new customers is crucial for growth, as a lack of fresh leads can cause a business to stagnate and eventually fail. Companies that can&amp;rsquo;t adapt to changing market conditions risk being overtaken by more agile competitors or innovative startups.
To help your business thrive, we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of free ebooks offering valuable insights on enhancing sales and marketing strategies in the age of social media:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter and Tonearm Weight and Limits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</guid><description>The final stage of restoring the Beogram 4002 (5503) involved balancing the sub-chassis, setting the correct platter height, and adjusting the tonearm. To ensure the best range of motion, the sub-chassis must be carefully positioned between the transport lock clamps. The platter height and vertical alignment need to be set so that the platter sits level with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s aluminum covers. This allows for the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit to be established and the tracking weight to be calibrated against the adjustment dial located on the arm weight housing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-and-tonearm-weight-and-limits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 11:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>This article details the comprehensive restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The initial evaluation of this unit is detailed in a separate post.
The turntable was first disassembled, revealing the need for bearing lubrication in the platter motor, a common issue in these models. This process typically takes a few days.
While the bearings were being re-lubricated, the intricate carriage mechanism, responsible for raising and lowering the tonearm, was addressed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-a-beolover-commander-remote-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Floating Chassis, Arm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>The next steps were to make adjustments to the platter, sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking weight. Additional information on this process is available on my Beogram 4000 page, which includes posts and videos. Before starting, I needed to replace the cabinet guiding washers because they were either damaged or replaced with unsuitable substitutes.
[Image of a missing cabinet guidance washer]
A video demonstrating this process is available in my Beogram 4002 playlist on my YouTube channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Complete Functional Restoration and a Spin with the Cal Tjader Quartet!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. The restoration began with addressing the motor, a common procedure for these models. After removing and disassembling the motor, the Oilite bearings were submerged in oil and placed under a vacuum for several days to replenish lubrication.
Next, the carriage and arm mechanisms were disassembled, cleaned, and re-lubricated. This included taking apart and servicing the damper. The main PCB was removed, and both power transistors were replaced...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-complete-functional-restoration-and-a-spin-with-the-cal-tjader-quartet-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Linear Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</guid><description>My restoration project of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable started with the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. These mechanisms often require attention because of hardened lubricants and misadjusted tracking sensors.
After taking the mechanism apart for cleaning and lubrication, I addressed the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm, which commonly experiences stiffness due to hardened lubricants.
The sensor arm was then removed for disassembly to further work on the linkage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cartrack tracks vehicles in multiple countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</guid><description>Source: Cartrack website.
Cartrack, a company specializing in fleet management, insurance telematics, vehicle tracking, and recovery services, is expanding its presence.
The company is capitalizing on the rising number of vehicles and the expanding telematics sector. Leveraging its Singapore office as a central hub, Cartrack has established new branches in Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, the Philippines, and Hong Kong this year.
Cartrack Singapore CEO, Evert Ong, highlighted the significant growth originating from both small and medium-sized enterprises and larger corporations aiming to enhance their fleet and workforce operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Michigan - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Michigan for restoration, carefully packaged according to instructions. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, with one minor dent on the platter&amp;rsquo;s surrounding plate. The platter itself, keypads, and small aluminum plate are also in good shape. However, one corner of the plinth is damaged. Fortunately, replacement plinth panels were included, which will be installed.
The hood has noticeable scratches, primarily on the surface, and should polish well...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Herbie Hancock (Secrets)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I just got my hands on a nearly perfect copy of Herbie Hancock&amp;rsquo;s 1976 album &amp;ldquo;Secrets.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s in such great condition, it practically looks untouched! This album holds a special place in my heart, especially the track &amp;ldquo;People Music&amp;rdquo; with its captivating atmospheric interludes and those classic 70s analog synthesizer sounds, likely created on a &amp;ldquo;Maestro Universal Synthesizer System.&amp;rdquo;
To celebrate, I decided to listen to the record on my newly restored Beogram 4002(5513) turntable, which is temporarily hooked up to my Beomaster 6000 4-Channel receiver for testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Completing the Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 10:01:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</guid><description>During the summer of 2019, I had the opportunity to work on a Beogram 4002 turntable from Virginia, specifically restoring its DC platter motor. I recently received the entire unit for a complete overhaul. The arm lowering mechanism had been previously restored and was in excellent condition. My attention turned to the remaining areas needing restoration.
To begin, I tackled the main PCB. The first photo illustrates its original condition:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-completing-the-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulb of the Tracking Sensor with a Drop-In LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 11:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 400x turntable, it&amp;rsquo;s common to replace the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s incandescent bulb with a more durable LED assembly. A drop-in replacement for the Beogram 4002 and 4004 models has been created and documented, while the Beogram 4000 version incorporates a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen-specified intensity trimmer for fine-tuning the tracking feedback system&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recalibrate the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s position after any light source replacement to maintain accurate tracking sensitivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable arrived in need of repair. The packaging was generally good, but the cartridge was not secured properly for transport. Thankfully, the delicate cantilever was undamaged. The first step was to safely store the cartridge in a specialized MMC cartridge box. These boxes are offered to customers who are shipping their Beograms for restoration and are also available for the MMC1-5 cartridges.
An initial assessment showed that the aluminum panels were in good condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with an SMD LED Light Source and Adjustment of the Feedback Sensisitivy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 turntable had a damaged part (the tracking sensor aperture) that was bent and obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. This issue prevented the tracking system from working correctly. The initial setup used an incandescent light bulb:
Upon removing the bulb housing, it was evident that the aperture was bent and rubbing against the optical sensor housing:
The aperture was carefully straightened, and the bulb assembly was replaced with a new SMD LED light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Restoration and a Test Spin with Oscar Peterson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 23:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable from Sweden in very corroded condition. To address the extensive corrosion, I chose to use another 4000 unit as a donor for parts. The donor unit, while missing some components, was free of corrosion.
My restoration process started with the carriage. I disassembled and cleaned the arm lowering system, damper, carriage rods, and spindle in an ultrasonic bath. Additionally, the sensor arm assembly was removed to lubricate the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-oscar-peterson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (5503) for restoration. The 5503 is the North American version of the 5501/5502 models, evident in the non-functional voltage switch included to maintain a consistent appearance.
This Beogram is in excellent overall condition, featuring high-quality veneer on the plinth and a dust cover with typical scratches that can be polished to near-original clarity. Internally, it appears largely untouched, though there are indications of prior work, such as loose bolts in the tracking and tonearm mechanisms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with the Bill Evans Trio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable from a Massachusetts customer. The initial evaluation can be found here.
The restoration began by addressing the carriage system. This involved cleaning hardened lubricants from various parts like the arm lowering mechanism, rods, spindle, linkages, and damper, and applying modern synthetic lubricants.
A key aspect of the Beogram 4000 is its solenoid-activated switches, which frequently experience oxidation and require attention. The contact terminals were removed and re-plated with nickel and gold-cobalt alloy for optimal performance and corrosion resistance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-the-bill-evans-trio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Tracking Force and Replacing the Strange Original Front Center Cabinet Guiding Washer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s playing beautifully. As I write this, I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying &amp;ldquo;Song for My Father&amp;rdquo; by Horace Silver on a reissue, as original pressings are unfortunately outside my budget these days.
One of the final tasks was refining the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s mechanics. I calibrated the tonearm weight and limits and replaced the guiding washer, which ensures the plinth moves smoothly. The original washer, pictured below, has a design flaw that was later corrected in the Beogram 400x series...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>The initial phase of the Beogram 4000 restoration involved the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking mechanisms. The solenoid and damper, essential for the arm&amp;rsquo;s smooth and controlled descent onto the record, were revealed.
Each part was carefully removed, cleaned, and lubricated.
Attention then turned to the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm. Located on the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s side, it required the arm&amp;rsquo;s removal to access and lubricate the linkage&amp;rsquo;s pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Chassis, Platter, Tonearm Limits and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:41:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. After adjusting the sub-chassis and platter, I set the tonearm limits and calibrated the tracking force. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to finalize the platter height before adjusting the arm, ensuring the correct arm-to-platter distance. My YouTube channel has videos demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, particularly for the Beogram 4000, but the 4002 process is similar.
Here’s the result:
The platter is now centered and level within the main aluminum plate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-chassis-platter-tonearm-limits-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>