<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Multiscreen on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiscreen/</link><description>Recent content in Multiscreen on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:19:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiscreen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vizury monitors users on various screens to gain a better understanding of them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vizury-monitors-users-on-various-screens-to-gain-a-better-understanding-of-them/</guid><description>For marketers aiming to cultivate customer relationships, providing a consistent and tailored experience is crucial. In anticipation of ad:tech Tokyo, Vizury, a digital CRM company, has presented insights into developing a comprehensive cross-device targeting strategy.
Understanding a user completely requires gathering data from various touchpoints such as desktop browsers, mobile websites, and apps. Vizury emphasizes that a successful cross-device strategy hinges on accurately identifying users across different devices. This allows marketers to track the customer journey from initial product view to the final purchase.</description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping.</description></item></channel></rss>