<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pro on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pro/</link><description>Recent content in Pro on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series.</description></item><item><title>Intel has introduced solid state drives designed for use in business environments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 23:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-has-introduced-solid-state-drives-designed-for-use-in-business-environments/</guid><description>Source: Intel website.
Intel has introduced the Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series, a new business-class addition to their Solid-State Drive (SSD) Professional family.
The Intel SSD Pro 2500 Series provides robust security features and capabilities designed for businesses of all sizes, giving them peace of mind. These drives offer hardware-based encryption, remote management capabilities, and a lower annual failure rate than traditional hard disk drives (HDDs), reducing the need for on-site IT support.</description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Dell updates tablets, unveils new 5K monitor and smart desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 20:13:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-updates-tablets-unveils-new-5k-monitor-and-smart-desk/</guid><description>Dell has improved its PC selection to boost productivity with new tablet functionalities, a 5K Ultra HD monitor, and a futuristic &amp;ldquo;smart desk&amp;rdquo; workspace.
Jeff Clarke, Dell&amp;rsquo;s Vice Chairman of Operations and President of Client Solutions, highlighted Dell&amp;rsquo;s focus on improving productivity and business outcomes at the recent Dell World Executive Summit.
The Dell UltraSharp 27 Monitor, available in December for US$2,499, offers Ultra HD 5K resolution (5,120 x 2,880), seven times sharper than Full HD.</description></item></channel></rss>