<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-services/</link><description>Recent content in Managed Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Voice over MPLS For High Quality Enterprise Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 00:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations are realizing the financial and operational benefits of MPLS networks. MPLS VPNs are emerging as the go-to solution for connecting multiple sites nationally and globally. But what about voice services?
Traditionally, voice and data are kept separate. Telephone systems rely on a proven infrastructure of switched circuit analog and digital trunking. Most PBX systems are designed to connect to standard copper-pair analog business lines or ISDN PRI digital trunks, which act as gateways to the global PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) connecting every phone on Earth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-voice-over-mpls-for-high-quality-enterprise-telephony/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>