<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>David Cameron on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/david-cameron/</link><description>Recent content in David Cameron on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/david-cameron/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later.</description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law.</description></item><item><title>What would be the effect on the UK's relations with the EU if Scotland gained independence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 00:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-would-be-the-effect-on-the-uk-s-relations-with-the-eu-if-scotland-gained-independence/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the Scottish independence referendum approaches, with the &amp;ldquo;Yes&amp;rdquo; campaign gaining momentum and even leading some polls, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to analyze the potential impact of Scottish independence on the European Union (EU). This analysis will focus on the EU membership of both an independent Scotland and the remaining UK (rUK).
Scottish independence would trigger four significant, near-simultaneous events: negotiations between Scotland and rUK about their future relationship; negotiations for Scotland to rejoin the EU; renegotiation of the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership; and a UK general election.</description></item><item><title>Is Juncker capable of being a reformist Commission President, like Nixon was in going to China?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A common saying in American politics, &amp;ldquo;only Nixon could go to China,&amp;rdquo; suggests that only a politician with a well-established reputation can persuade their base to accept a major policy shift. Nixon, a staunch anti-Communist, was able to convince American conservatives that engaging with Communist China was in their best interest. This principle might apply to the European Union as well. The recent European Parliament (EP) elections saw a rise in support for anti-EU parties in several Member States.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for humans to make a legally binding commitment to Treaty change?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-humans-to-make-a-legally-binding-commitment-to-treaty-change/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British Prime Minister David Cameron has surprised many by securing concessions from the EU, such as a smaller EU budget and a Conservative majority in the House of Commons. However, his goal of renegotiating the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership raises the question: are his demands even achievable?
This question arises from Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recently confirmed intention to secure not immediate Treaty changes, but rather a &amp;ldquo;legally binding&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;irreversible&amp;rdquo; agreement that would commit to future Treaty changes.</description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion.</description></item></channel></rss>