<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Consumer Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/consumer-law/</link><description>Recent content in Consumer Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 12:12:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/consumer-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU consumer's status after Faber v Hazet: no longer "Faber" fortunae suae</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-consumer-s-status-after-faber-v-hazet-no-longer-faber-fortunae-suae/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 12:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-consumer-s-status-after-faber-v-hazet-no-longer-faber-fortunae-suae/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD candidate, King&amp;rsquo;s College London
Background
A recent Court of Justice ruling in the Faber case (C-497/13) determined that purchasers are considered &amp;ldquo;consumers&amp;rdquo; even if they don&amp;rsquo;t explicitly claim this status, as long as the purchase wasn&amp;rsquo;t for business or professional purposes. The Court decided that national courts must independently determine if a purchaser qualifies as a consumer, guaranteeing the application of EU consumer protection laws regardless of the purchaser&amp;rsquo;s awareness of their rights.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Compliance of Alcohol Health Warning Labelling in Member States with EU Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 00:27:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compliance-of-alcohol-health-warning-labelling-in-member-states-with-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Dr. Nikhil Gokani, a lecturer specializing in consumer protection and public health law at the University of Essex, holds key positions in several organizations: Chair of the Alcohol Labelling and Health Warning International Expert Group at the European Alcohol Policy Alliance, Vice President of the Law Section at the European Public Health Association, and a member of the Technical Advisory Group on Alcohol Labelling at the World Health Organization (WHO).</description></item><item><title>Consumer law and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): Case C-319/20 involving Facebook Ireland - Advocate General's opinion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 05:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Facts
The Federation of German Consumer Organisations initiated legal proceedings in German courts against Facebook. They claimed that Facebook violated data protection rules by failing to provide sufficient information about data collection practices related to free, third-party games offered on its platform. The Federation argued that this also infringed upon unfair competition and consumer protection regulations. The case reached the Bundesgerischtshof, which raised concerns about the Federation&amp;rsquo;s legal standing to bring the action following the implementation of the GDPR.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union and Spanish mortgage legislation: safeguarding consumers, addressing floor clauses, and expediting repayment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</guid><description>Juan Carlos Benito Sánchez, PhD Fellow at the University of Louvain (Belgium).
Twitter: @jcbensan
Over recent years, the European Court of Justice has issued several judgments invalidating parts of Spanish mortgage law, both in terms of its content and procedures, and how it’s interpreted by the courts. These rulings were based on the fact that these laws went against EU consumer protection regulations. In particular, the Court based its decisions on Council Directive 93/13/EEC of 5 April 1993 on unfair terms in consumer contracts.</description></item></channel></rss>