<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Social Rights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the UK's limitation on EU workers' eligibility for benefits lawful - and if not, should it be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK government recently established a new income requirement for EU citizens from other Member States to be classified as &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and access certain benefits. This raises the question of whether these rules align with EU law regarding the free movement of workers and if modifications are necessary.
Under these regulations, EU citizens must earn a minimum of £150 weekly for at least three months to be considered &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and qualify for benefits such as child benefit, child tax credit, job-seekers&amp;rsquo; allowance, and housing benefit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it necessary to apply the Charter in reconstructing the hierarchy of employment law norms?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</guid><description>The Uncertain Future of UK Employment Law in a Post-Brexit World Niall O’Connor, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The Charter and Brexit
Boris Johnson famously downplayed the significance of the Charter of Fundamental Rights during the Brexit campaign. He argued in a Telegraph article that the Charter&amp;rsquo;s provisions, such as the right to establish a school or pursue an occupation anywhere in the EU, are not &amp;ldquo;fundamental rights&amp;rdquo; as commonly understood and questioned their enforceability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the European Labour Authority: A New EU Agency Based in Bratislava</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</guid><description>Bartłomiej Bednarowicz, PhD Researcher at the Faculty of Law of the University of Antwerp
Background
Bratislava was chosen by the Council to host the headquarters of the newly established European Labour Authority (ELA). Initially proposed by President Juncker in 2017, the ELA&amp;rsquo;s primary goal is to simplify and enhance the fairness of EU labor mobility within the internal market. This initiative stemmed from the European Pillar of Social Rights (EPSR) and was introduced alongside other measures aimed at promoting social fairness within the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are agency workers adequately protected under EU legislation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 06:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Workers with non-traditional employment arrangements, such as those lacking full-time permanent contracts, frequently face precarious positions in the labor market, making them susceptible to exploitation. Additionally, the utilization of such employment models may negatively impact other workers. Conversely, there are instances where such employment benefits both workers and employers, acting as a significant source of job creation. In balancing these concerns, the EU has implemented measures regulating three specific non-traditional employment categories: agency workers, part-time workers, and fixed-term workers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protection for fixed-term workers against unfair dismissal and mistreatment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union (EU) has increasingly addressed the rise of non-standard employment through measures like agreements on part-time and fixed-term work, and a Directive on agency work. The fixed-term work rules, in particular, have spurred many legal cases in the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). However, until recently, the court had not fully considered the connection between these rules and national laws on unfair dismissal, particularly for university researchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Referendum Briefing 6: The Impact on EU Employment and Equality Law Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers suggests that while some claim there would be a &amp;ldquo;bonfire of rights&amp;rdquo; if the UK left the EU, particularly in employment and equality, others argue that the EU has no bearing on these laws in the UK. This post will demonstrate that EU law has significantly improved employment and equality rights in the UK, especially for women in the workplace.
A study of all UK cases reaching the EU court concerning these issues reveals that 60% of cases involving equal treatment for women resulted in findings that UK law was inadequate, leading to improved workplace protections for women...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Returning from Austerity to Legitimacy: An Overview of the European Pillar of Social Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</guid><description>This piece explores how Juncker can use ‘The European Pillar of Social Rights’ to convey a strong message: that the EU champions dignity, autonomy, and social justice.
Claire Kilpatrick (EUI), Elise Muir (Veni Fellow, Maastricht) and Sacha Garben (College of Europe, Bruges)
The EU has faced skepticism from its citizens about its commitment to prosperity and better living and working conditions, especially since the financial crisis and the subsequent implementation of austerity measures in various countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>