<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic/</link><description>Recent content in Economic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:17:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IMF has finished its 2017 Article IV consultation with Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its regular economic review of Vietnam, finding that the country&amp;rsquo;s economy remains in good shape, supported by strong underlying economic conditions. Despite a slowdown in 2016 to 6.2% growth due to agricultural challenges from drought and saltwater intrusion, as well as reduced oil production, Vietnam’s economy has shown resilience.
While the oil sector continued to struggle in early 2017, strong manufacturing and foreign direct investment, healthy domestic demand, and a resurgence in agriculture are driving overall economic momentum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMF provides suggestions for economic policy in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 03:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/</guid><description>Japan&amp;rsquo;s economic growth has decelerated due to subdued private consumption and investment, leading to a loss in inflationary momentum, as per the International Monetary Fund&amp;rsquo;s (IMF) Executive Board&amp;rsquo;s assessment following a consultation in late July. Despite favorable financial conditions, declining stock prices and a strengthening yen have contributed to a slight tightening of financial conditions.
In response to the weakening domestic and global economic landscape, Japanese authorities have implemented additional monetary and fiscal measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-provides-suggestions-for-economic-policy-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF mission has stated that Pakistan's economic reform efforts must extend beyond the EFF program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</guid><description>An IMF team, led by Harald Finger, visited Dubai between July 26th and August 4th, 2016, to discuss the final review of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic program supported by a three-year IMF Extended Fund Facility (EFF). The team met with key officials, including Finance Minister Ishaq Dar and State Bank of Pakistan Governor Ashraf Wathra.
The mission concluded with a staff-level agreement on the completion of the twelfth and final review under the EFF, subject to approval by IMF management and the Executive Board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>