<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cuisine on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cuisine/</link><description>Recent content in Cuisine on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cuisine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Asia will be able to watch a Hong Kong food series on Discovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</guid><description>Discovery Channel has released a new show, Kung Food! Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Grandmasters of Cuisine. This show delves into the intricate and special world of Hong Kong cuisine from the viewpoint of Michelin-starred chefs.
Source: Discovery Channel. Chef Chaneton of Mono at a market in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong dominates Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2021 list with 11 restaurants featured. Chefs David Lai, Guillaume Galliot, Hideaki Sato, Ricardo Chaneton, Richard Ekkebus and Vicky Cheng, all recognized by Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, were chosen to discuss their passion for Hong Kong and illustrate how they craft their culinary masterpieces.</description></item></channel></rss>