<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AboveNet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/abovenet/</link><description>Recent content in AboveNet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/abovenet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Network Connections Into Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</guid><description>Although many businesses only require domestic WAN connections, a growing number are seeking global connectivity, particularly with European markets for financial trading, sales, and support. This raises the question of how US-based companies can establish cost-effective connections with Europe.
Fortunately, several carriers offer transatlantic connectivity to major European cities. Some US carriers have partnerships for traffic handover to European data centers, as illustrated by AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement with ancotel GmbH in Frankfurt, Germany.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary.</description></item></channel></rss>