<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FUTA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/futa/</link><description>Recent content in FUTA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 02:06:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/futa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Additional Payroll Troubleshooting Scripts for Your Enjoyment!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-payroll-troubleshooting-scripts-for-your-enjoyment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 02:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-payroll-troubleshooting-scripts-for-your-enjoyment/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into more FUTA and SUTA insights. These scripts can help pinpoint inconsistencies in your configuration and uncover potential reasons for incorrect FUTA and SUTA wage calculations. You can run each script against your company database to find records with potential problems.
&amp;ndash; This script finds employees without a default SUTA state (accessible in the system through Cards&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Employee)
select EMPLOYID as EmployeeID from UPR00100 where SUTASTAT=''
&amp;ndash; This script identifies employee pay code records (accessible in the system through Cards&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Pay Code) that aren&amp;rsquo;t flagged for FUTA or SUTA, or lack a SUTA state despite the pay code setup (accessible in the system through Setup&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Pay Code) requiring it.</description></item><item><title>Did you forget about FUTA? Falling behind on SUTA? Take care of it immediately!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find payroll errors, particularly with FUTA and SUTA taxes, even with careful planning. Issues arise when pay codes aren&amp;rsquo;t correctly classified for these taxes at setup or when employee payroll details are changed. Unlike other taxes, FUTA and SUTA discrepancies aren&amp;rsquo;t immediately obvious because they are calculated during period-end processing.
Manual correction of such errors, especially across multiple payrolls or employees, is tedious and error-prone. It involves reversing incorrect entries and re-entering them with the correct FUTA and SUTA classifications.</description></item></channel></rss>