<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grab on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grab/</link><description>Recent content in Grab on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:02:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get a ride and offset your carbon emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</guid><description>Grab users will soon have the option to lessen the environmental impact of their trips by utilizing a new carbon offset feature integrated into the Grab app.
Source: Grab.
Explaining the carbon
offset feature.
A recent study across six Southeast Asian countries revealed that 82% of Grab users are concerned about climate change and are taking steps to minimize their environmental impact. However, 44% of those concerned but not actively addressing it cited a lack of knowledge on how to act, while 31% found it too challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grab for Work assists businesses in managing transportation costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</guid><description>Grab, a Southeast Asian ride-hailing company, has introduced Grab for Work, a complimentary transport expense management tool for businesses in Southeast Asia. Designed for business leaders, managers, HR, and finance professionals in both SMEs and MNCs, Grab for Work provides a streamlined approach to handling company transportation costs.
Developed with feedback from over 150 companies in the region during its beta phase, Grab for Work is currently utilized by a similar number of businesses across Southeast Asia, including notable names such as Chope Group (Singapore), Park Hotel Group (Singapore), Rainmaker Labs (Singapore), Yesboss (Indonesia), and Malaysian Airlines (Malaysia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>