<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Council of Europe on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/council-of-europe/</link><description>Recent content in Council of Europe on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:14:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/council-of-europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Does the new Council of Europe treaty on match-fixing comply with EU internal market regulations?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-the-new-council-of-europe-treaty-on-match-fixing-comply-with-eu-internal-market-regulations/</guid><description>Tom Serby, a Senior Law Lecturer at Anglia Law School, Anglia Ruskin University, discusses the escalating problem of betting-related match-fixing in sports. He highlights the Council of Europe&amp;rsquo;s recent Convention aimed at tackling this issue, while also pointing out Malta&amp;rsquo;s legal challenge against it at the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). Malta argues that the treaty clashes with internal market rules, particularly the freedom to provide services, underscoring the difficulties in achieving a unified international response to match-fixing.</description></item><item><title>A Story of Two Institutions: Regulation of Hate Speech in Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</guid><description>Clotilde Pégorier, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The regulation of hate speech has recently resurfaced as a crucial legal and political topic in Europe. While the complexity of this issue and the varying views on balancing legislation with rights protection are well-known, the contrasting approaches of the EU and the Council of Europe, two closely linked entities, is notable. This difference raises questions about its underlying reasons and broader legislative ramifications in Europe.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item></channel></rss>