<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>POTS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pots/</link><description>Recent content in POTS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pots/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>Circuit Switched vs Packet Switched Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Over the past few decades, two primary network technologies have been vying for dominance. The first is the traditional telephone system, which served us well throughout the industrial age. The second is the computer-based architecture that has driven the information age. You might recognize these as circuit switching and packet switching.
While both technologies will likely coexist for a while longer, we are at a turning point. From now on, packet switching will be the dominant force in every network, from copper lines to fiber optic cables to wireless connections.</description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out.</description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>Voice over Internet Protocol Phone Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-over-internet-protocol-phone-services/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) suggests it will likely replace traditional phone services, including landlines and ISDN PRI. This shift is primarily driven by the transition from traditional telephone networks to computer-based networks, further complicated by the emergence of wireless voice and data services.
Telephone networks, largely analog during their long history, were initially designed solely for voice communication. While attempts were made to use them for data transfer with analog modems, the limited bandwidth of these networks proved insufficient for anything beyond low-speed data.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century.</description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized.</description></item><item><title>Types of Business Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-business-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Over time, business phone lines have evolved from a single analog option to a variety of choices. While you can still get traditional analog lines, various digital options offer potential cost and performance benefits.
The standard business phone line remains largely unchanged from its origins over a century ago, using a single twisted pair of copper wires to carry signals. This analog line, also called POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is the basis for multi-line phones connecting to multiple POTS lines, commonly seen in small office phone systems with one to four lines.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system.</description></item></channel></rss>