<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireless Modem Aircards on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-modem-aircards/</link><description>Recent content in Wireless Modem Aircards on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-modem-aircards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cellular Netbooks Are Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Do you spend most of your computing time on the go? If so, a computer designed for mobility might be perfect for you, like one of the new netbooks with built-in 3G cellular internet access.
You might be thinking laptops aren&amp;rsquo;t that bulky and work fine at a coffee shop.
That&amp;rsquo;s true. A laptop with a wireless modem aircard would be comparable to a netbook in functionality. However, laptops are heavier and often carry unnecessary extras.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Plans With Aircards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</guid><description>Wireless modem aircards liberate you from the constraints of WiFi hotspots, transforming your laptop into a truly mobile computer. But how do they work, and what kind of service plans are necessary?
Essentially, an aircard functions as a specialized two-way radio, transmitting and receiving digital computer data instead of voice calls.
While they might resemble them, aircards don&amp;rsquo;t operate on cell phone networks. Currently, the majority adhere to either EVDO (Sprint and Verizon Wireless) or EDGE and HSPA (AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile) standards for cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach.</description></item></channel></rss>