<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bonus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonus/</link><description>Recent content in Bonus on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bonus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs.</description></item><item><title>40% of employees in Malaysia are willing to change jobs if they do not receive a bonus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-employees-in-malaysia-are-willing-to-change-jobs-if-they-do-not-receive-a-bonus/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 05:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-employees-in-malaysia-are-willing-to-change-jobs-if-they-do-not-receive-a-bonus/</guid><description>Randstad, a global staffing and HR services firm, recently conducted its second annual Bonus Expectations survey in Malaysia. The purpose of this survey was to gain insights into employee perspectives on year-end bonuses and how they influence their commitment to their employers. This year&amp;rsquo;s survey also included, for the first time, feedback from companies on their bonus plans to determine if employer and employee expectations are aligned.
The survey revealed that while 98% of employees believe receiving a bonus is important for their engagement, 59% stated that it wasn&amp;rsquo;t the only reason they would consider a job change.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions.</description></item></channel></rss>