<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CDN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cdn/</link><description>Recent content in CDN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cdn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Need a Content Delivery Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The way we deliver content online is evolving rapidly. While you could once manage a website with just a computer and a few phone lines, today&amp;rsquo;s high-definition video and nationwide audiences demand far more resources. This is where content delivery networks (CDNs) come in.
Think of a CDN as a specialized web hosting service. Just as you can host your website on your own server or outsource it, you can also choose between managing your content distribution or relying on a CDN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You Can Afford a Content Delivery Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The internet is great for communication, allowing businesses to connect with anyone globally at a low cost and creating countless opportunities. However, this popularity has led to congestion, potentially slowing down websites.
You can work around this issue without sacrificing connectivity. Large content providers use Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) to bypass internet congestion. CDNs don&amp;rsquo;t connect directly to users but deliver content through servers near service providers, resulting in faster speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T Sees the Video Tsunami Coming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</guid><description>Video streaming is predicted to consume massive amounts of bandwidth, pushing the limits of what&amp;rsquo;s available. Even the concept of &amp;ldquo;unlimited&amp;rdquo; bandwidth offered by providers today comes with hidden caps due to network strain.
AT&amp;amp;T is one company actively addressing this challenge, not just by increasing general internet capacity but by adding 400 Gbps to its Content Delivery Network (CDN).
Think of a CDN as a dedicated express lane running parallel to the public internet highway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Content Delivery Networks Need More Capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</guid><description>A significant media shift is underway, marked by a technological revolution since the days of broadcast dominance. Concerns about antenna reception have been replaced by anxieties over 3G and 4G coverage for accessing videos on mobile devices. Cable and satellite TV, which succeeded over-the-air broadcasting, now face competition from the internet as the preferred medium for audio and video content. As over-the-air delivery declines, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are emerging as its replacement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Content Delivery Networks Transformed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth is steadily growing, largely due to the rise of IP video streaming, downloads, and more sophisticated websites with larger graphics and interactive features. To keep up with this demand, networks and websites themselves need to change.
While increasing WAN bandwidth is a given, it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete solution. Despite significant growth in WAN bandwidth, internet traffic congestion persists, leading to the emergence of Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) as a bypass...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>