<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dublin Rules on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dublin-rules/</link><description>Recent content in Dublin Rules on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dublin-rules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.</description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President.</description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services.</description></item><item><title>Could a third phase of the Common European Asylum System bring wisdom and goodness to those who are considered vile?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
The EU is looking to overhaul its Common European Asylum Policy, and the Commission has laid out its suggestions in a new discussion paper. These proposals, which are expected to lead to further legislation, aim to address the flaws in the current system. This blog post will break down these proposals and analyze their potential impact.
The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum policy has been developed in phases, with the initial legislation implemented between 2003 and 2005 and the second phase between 2011 and 2013.</description></item></channel></rss>