<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beijing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beijing/</link><description>Recent content in Beijing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beijing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Air China provides flights from Beijing to Vienna and Barcelona four days a week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:07:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</guid><description>As a prominent member of Star Alliance, the largest global airline network, Air China is actively expanding its flight schedule in Europe. The airline aims to bridge the gap in nonstop flights between East Asia and Barcelona and increase flight frequency between Beijing and Vienna.
Source: Air China
This new Beijing-Vienna-Barcelona route will be Air China&amp;rsquo;s 23rd European route, creating a direct link between East Asia and Central and Southern Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China have partnered on a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China, China&amp;rsquo;s national airline, have partnered to provide travelers with expanded options and easier connections. This agreement comes after Hawaiian launched its new non-stop service to Beijing, operating three times a week.
&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to collaborate with Air China to expand our reach beyond Beijing, allowing our customers to conveniently explore more Chinese cities with a single ticket from Honolulu,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Dunkerley, Hawaiian Airlines President and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beijing is the first place outside of the Americas to experience Starbucks Nitro Cold Brew</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</guid><description>The China World Trade Centre Starbucks in Beijing is the first location outside of the US and Canada to offer Nitro Cold Brew on tap in addition to their regular Cold Brew. Starbucks plans to introduce this in more locations over the coming months. This follows a very successful launch of Starbucks Cold Brew across China.
&amp;ldquo;We are dedicated to achieving perfection in our coffee expertise, and Nitro Cold Brew shows our significant investment in coffee innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-is-the-first-place-outside-of-the-americas-to-experience-starbucks-nitro-cold-brew/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Bitcoin conference in China will take place in May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</guid><description>Bitfund.pe, a private equity firm focused on Bitcoin, and UBM China have jointly revealed plans for the first international Bitcoin conference in China. This event, the Global Bitcoin Summit 2014 (GBS), is scheduled for May 10-11 in Beijing.
Source: GBS
The summit will be structured around eight key themes, featuring conversations on Bitcoin trends both within China and globally. Additionally, there will be exploration of how to leverage Bitcoin for new business creation and expansion of existing ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in October, Air China will offer nonstop flights from Beijing to Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</guid><description>Air China will commence nonstop flights between Beijing and Mumbai starting October 25, 2015. This decision comes as a response to the growing travel demand between these two BRICS nations, driven by strengthening political and economic ties.
Source: Air China.
The route will operate four times a week, with flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays, and Sundays. The seven-hour journey departs Beijing at 7:40 PM local time and arrives in Mumbai at 1 AM the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>