<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Acquired Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/acquired-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Acquired Rights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/acquired-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Questions &amp; Answers about EU Free Movement Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We shouldn&amp;rsquo;t create a misleading impression of the law.&amp;rdquo;
(Measure for Measure, 2.1.1)
Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School, University of York
Laurent Pech, Professor of European Law, Jean Monnet Chair of EU Public Law at Middlesex University London
This article clarifies common misunderstandings about EU free movement rules, often found in British media. We believe much criticism targets a distorted view of the actual system.
The UK shows a desire to restrict EU freedom of movement, yet misinterpretations about these rules persist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Protocol Proposal for Brexit and the Rights of EU27 Citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</guid><description>Stijn Smismans, Professor of Law, School of Law and Politics, Director of the Centre for European Law and Governance, Cardiff University
While a draft Withdrawal Agreement (WA) between the EU and UK, partially agreed upon in March 2018, aims to address the post-Brexit status of EU27 citizens in the UK and British citizens in the EU, concerns remain about the process of securing residency rights. Although the EU has made efforts to safeguard these rights, the focus has been on the scope rather than the process of obtaining them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-protocol-proposal-for-brexit-and-the-rights-of-eu27-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gazing into the Void: The Future of Citizens' Rights in the Event of a No Deal Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
After resisting guarantees for EU27 citizens&amp;rsquo; rights in the UK for over two years, the UK government has finally issued a plan outlining the treatment of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 in a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit scenario. This comes as the UK Parliament prepares to vote on the withdrawal agreement and after the European Commission published its own position on this matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Returning from Austerity to Legitimacy: An Overview of the European Pillar of Social Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</guid><description>This piece explores how Juncker can use ‘The European Pillar of Social Rights’ to convey a strong message: that the EU champions dignity, autonomy, and social justice.
Claire Kilpatrick (EUI), Elise Muir (Veni Fellow, Maastricht) and Sacha Garben (College of Europe, Bruges)
The EU has faced skepticism from its citizens about its commitment to prosperity and better living and working conditions, especially since the financial crisis and the subsequent implementation of austerity measures in various countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>