<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beverage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beverage/</link><description>Recent content in Beverage on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:35:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beverage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Heineken 0.0 promotes inclusivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 19:35:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/</guid><description>Heineken 0.0 is available in Singapore.
Heineken 0.0, a non-alcoholic malt beverage with a unique recipe, launched in the US on January 9th. It boasts a distinct, balanced taste and contains only 69 calories per bottle (70 calories per 330ml can). Although announced back in May 2017, it is also currently available in Singapore. Heineken&amp;rsquo;s Master Brewers created this alcohol-free option using only natural ingredients.
Jonnie Cahill, CMO of HEINEKEN USA, believes Heineken 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heineken-0-0-promotes-inclusivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces Cauca Terroir Roast &amp; Ground Coffee in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 07:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</guid><description>According to Cafédirect, their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee pairs well with sweet and fruity flavors. Ideal pairings in Colombia include pan de queso (cheese bread) and alfajores (caramel cookie sandwiches). &amp;ldquo;Terroir&amp;rdquo; encapsulates the unique environmental and geographic factors of a region that influence a beverage&amp;rsquo;s taste.
Cafédirect recently introduced their Cauca Terroir Roast &amp;amp; Ground Coffee to Singapore. Colombians describe this high-altitude coffee as &amp;ldquo;black as night, hot as hell and sweet as love&amp;rdquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-cauca-terroir-roast-ground-coffee-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new Medium Roast Freeze-Dried instant coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 13:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect.
Cafédirect, a British beverage company, has introduced a new premium instant coffee in Singapore. This medium roast, freeze-dried coffee offers a convenient solution for those seeking a flavorful cup on the go, featuring a smooth, vibrant taste with hints of caramel.
Interestingly, a growing number of Singaporean coffee drinkers who typically prefer milk in their coffee are developing a taste for black coffee. This shift is attributed to Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s master blender, who has crafted a unique blend using sweet and chocolatey Arabica beans from South America, well-rounded beans from Central America, and robust Robusta beans from East Africa (60%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-medium-roast-freeze-dried-instant-coffee/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks Teavana is now offered in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 06:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Starbucks has launched Starbucks Teavana, its line of handcrafted tea drinks and whole leaf tea sachets, in over 6,200 stores across 16 markets in the China and Asia Pacific region. This marks the global availability of Starbucks Teavana. Starbucks Teavana offers unique, layered flavor experiences in both iced and hot formats.
John Culver, Group President of Starbucks Global Retail, highlighted the growing consumer demand for new and unique taste experiences and positioned the Teavana launch as a way to leverage Starbucks&amp;rsquo; expertise in crafting beverages and sourcing premium ingredients to become a leader in the tea category...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces Nespresso-compatible coffee capsules in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 16:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Cafédirect. Cafédirect launches premium coffee capsules that are compatible with Nespresso Machines.
Cafédirect, a UK-based company known for its award-winning Fairtrade hot drinks, has introduced its premium coffee capsules to supermarkets in Singapore. These capsules, compatible with Nespresso machines, offer a convenient way to enjoy Cafédirect&amp;rsquo;s signature coffee.
Crafted from 100% Arabica beans, each capsule boasts an intensity level of 8 out of 12. The 5.3g blend combines Tanzanian and Mexican coffee beans, resulting in a rich flavor profile...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-nespresso-compatible-coffee-capsules-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The turmeric latte mix simplifies the process of enjoying golden milk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</guid><description>A sample pack of turmeric latte mix.
Nature&amp;rsquo;s Harvest Turmeric Latte Mix, produced in Western Australia and available in Singapore and Malaysia through distributor 1000Tsuru via their website Goldenmylk, leverages the increasing consumer interest in turmeric&amp;rsquo;s health advantages.
Andre Lim, based in Australia, and Paul Ong, in Singapore, co-founded 1000Tsuru to expand the reach of this vegan, naturopath-endorsed blend beyond Australia. &amp;ldquo;We are the primary distributor for Singapore and Malaysia, but we are aiming to introduce it to the broader Asian market soon,&amp;rdquo; Lim stated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-turmeric-latte-mix-simplifies-the-process-of-enjoying-golden-milk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improving heart health with cranberry juice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</guid><description>Drinking cranberry juice every day could potentially lead to healthier blood sugar and cholesterol levels, according to recent research.
In a study involving overweight but otherwise healthy participants, those who drank two glasses (450ml) of a cranberry-based beverage daily for two weeks showed improvements in blood sugar stability, reducing spikes and dips often associated with cravings and fatigue. These benefits continued when the two-glass intake was maintained.
After eight weeks of daily consumption, the same cranberry beverage was also linked to higher levels of &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; HDL cholesterol, known for promoting artery health by removing &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; cholesterol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>