<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Telephones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-telephones/</link><description>Recent content in IP Telephones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-telephones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>