<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t3/</link><description>Recent content in T3 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DS1 DS3 Relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</guid><description>The terms DS1 and DS3 are frequently used in business telecommunications networking. DS, which stands for Digital Signal level, indicates the capacity of a digital line within the T-carrier system. Essentially, DS1 is associated with T1 service, while DS3 corresponds with T3.
The origins of the T-carrier system can be traced back to the 1950s when Bell Labs recognized the benefits of transitioning from an entirely analog telephone system to digital connections between telephone company offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>