<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GoDaddy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/godaddy/</link><description>Recent content in GoDaddy on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:53:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/godaddy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You can now get .cn domain names from GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 09:53:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a company that provides technology specifically to small businesses, now offers a total of 421 domain name extensions. This increase is due to the addition of the &amp;ldquo;.cn&amp;rdquo; domain, China&amp;rsquo;s country code. This expansion targets the growing number of Chinese residents seeking to establish an online presence.
China boasts over 1.6 billion internet users, with over 600 million residing within the country itself. While China has registered over 16 million &amp;ldquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-get-cn-domain-names-from-godaddy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Down In The Face of Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</guid><description>At the end of 2011, major companies like GoDaddy and Verizon Wireless faced significant public backlash that caused them to reverse recently announced decisions. GoDaddy quickly backpedaled on their support for SOPA after online outrage, while Verizon abandoned their plan to charge a $2 payment fee due to public outcry and potential FCC involvement. These incidents, while seemingly isolated, point to a larger pattern found in other events from the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy is dedicated to creating impressive and impactful business identities for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>GoDaddy: Expanding Beyond Domains to Empower Small Businesses While GoDaddy is known for domain names, it has evolved into much more. CEO Blake Irving emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on supporting small businesses, a demographic often overlooked despite representing a significant portion of most economies.
Irving highlights that small businesses, even those with a single employee, present a vast untapped market. Traditional solutions often cater to either large enterprises or individual consumers, leaving small businesses underserved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy has expanded its presence to 11 Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a global technology provider for small businesses, has expanded its reach into 11 Asian markets. This expansion brings GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based products and customer support services to millions of small and medium enterprises (SMEs) within the region.
With these 11 new markets, GoDaddy now operates in 14 markets across Asia, encompassing 10 languages. These markets include Hong Kong (English and Traditional Chinese), Indonesia, Japan, Malaysia (English and Malay), Philippines (English and Filipino), Singapore (English and Simplified Chinese), South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>