<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regulation 1612/68 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-1612/68/</link><description>Recent content in Regulation 1612/68 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-1612/68/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk.</description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends.</description></item></channel></rss>