<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LCC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lcc/</link><description>Recent content in LCC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lcc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Budget airline flyadeal plans to extend its reach to more destinations in the Middle East in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s new low-cost airline, flyadeal, was officially launched on August 23 at King Abdulaziz International Airport in Jeddah. The event showcased flyadeal&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft, named &amp;ldquo;Al-Nayyir&amp;rdquo; (meaning &amp;ldquo;bright star&amp;rdquo;), which arrived from the Airbus delivery center in Hamburg, Germany.
Source: flyadeal. The budget airline flyadeal was inaugurated at a ceremony on August 24. The airline’s colors – a distinct palette of purple and lime – was on full display at the delivery event, along with members of the cabin crew, which gave guests a tour of the unique features onboard.</description></item></channel></rss>