<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bangkok on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bangkok/</link><description>Recent content in Bangkok on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bangkok/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration.</description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok.</description></item><item><title>The River Wing at the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok is undergoing renovations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-river-wing-at-the-mandarin-oriental-bangkok-is-undergoing-renovations/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is embarking on a renovation project for the River Wing of the Mandarin Oriental, Bangkok, aiming to solidify the historic hotel&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top-tier establishment.
Starting in March 2019, the seven-month renovation will encompass all rooms and suites within the River Wing, as well as the lobby, swimming pools, and dining venues: Lord Jim’s, The Verandah, and Riverside Terrace. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s Authors’ and Garden Wings will remain operational throughout.</description></item><item><title>The fourth akyra hotel in Sukhumvit, Bangkok has been launched by Akaryn</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-akyra-hotel-in-sukhumvit-bangkok-has-been-launched-by-akaryn/</guid><description>Akaryn Hotel Group, a Thai hospitality company known for its luxurious hotels and resorts, will open its fourth akyra property, akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok, in December 2017.
The upscale boutique hotel is situated on Sukhumvit Soi 20, a vibrant area in the heart of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s main tourist zone, known for its excellent dining, lively nightlife, high-end shopping malls, spas, and green spaces.
akyra Sukhumvit Bangkok offers 50 rooms, ranging from 30 to 60 square meters, with city views.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No.</description></item><item><title>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park in Bangkok provides a versatile indoor-outdoor option for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-garden-lounge-at-sukhumvit-park-in-bangkok-provides-a-versatile-indoor-outdoor-option-for-mice-events/</guid><description>The Garden Lounge at Sukhumvit Park, Bangkok – Marriott Executive Apartments is a unique venue for gatherings in the Sukhumvit area. Combining indoor and outdoor elements, it offers a versatile space for 30 to 160 guests. High ceilings and comfortable furniture create a welcoming atmosphere.
This lounge seamlessly blends several design concepts, creating a space that is both modern and traditional, as well as casual and elegant. Featuring lawn and garden views, the Lounge covers over 400 square meters and can host a variety of events from meetings to cocktail receptions.</description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for.</description></item><item><title>The Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 will commence operations on January 1, 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-well-hotel-bangkok-sukhumvit-20-will-commence-operations-on-january-1-2016/</guid><description>Source: Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20 website.
Well Hotel Bangkok Sukhumvit 20, a lifestyle hotel focused on health and wellness, will softly open its doors on January 1, 2016. The hotel provides tailored food and drinks, spa treatments, fitness facilities, and wellness activities.
Conveniently situated on Sukhumvit 20, the hotel is a short walk from the BTS Asok Skytrain, MRT Sukhumvit Subway, Terminal 21 Mall, The EmQuartier, and the Emporium.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-radisson-blu-hotel-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group is celebrating the expansion of its Radisson Blu brand with the debut of its first Radisson Blu hotel in Bangkok.
The Radisson Blu Plaza Hotel Bangkok, boasting 290 rooms, is strategically situated in Sukhumvit, a vibrant area known for its numerous offices, corporate headquarters, and retail outlets. This property marks Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s first Radisson Blu establishment in the city and is owned by G&amp;amp;P Asset Holding Company.</description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn in Bangkok is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-in-bangkok-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Bangkok has reopened with a new focus on natural elements.
The traditional lobby is gone, replaced with an open space that blends the front desk, restaurant, bar, lounge, and business center in a modern style. This design approach extends to the 379 guest rooms, each envisioned as a home away from home.
Two new dining options are available: Ginger, offering all-day dining, and Beer Republic, a bar designed to evoke a 1920s European industrial warehouse.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>Experience Silom in a whole new way at the newly elevated ibis Styles Bangkok Silom</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-silom-in-a-whole-new-way-at-the-newly-elevated-ibis-styles-bangkok-silom/</guid><description>Accor Hospitality Group has launched a stylish hotel, ibis Styles Bangkok Silom, in Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s lively Silom neighborhood. The hotel boasts a playful design inspired by Thai festivals and features a vibrant mural by Thai artist Tikkywow, reflecting Silom&amp;rsquo;s rich history.
Located near Sala Daeng BTS Skytrain and Silom MRT subway stations, the hotel provides convenient access to the city. Garth Simmons, CEO of Accor Southeast Asia, Japan &amp;amp; South Korea, expressed excitement for the opening, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s fit with Silom&amp;rsquo;s dynamic atmosphere.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility.</description></item><item><title>Dusit Thani Bangkok will reopen in September 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 00:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dusit-thani-bangkok-will-reopen-in-september-2024/</guid><description>Dusit Hotels and Resorts, a prominent Thai hotel and property development company, will reopen the famous Dusit Thani Bangkok on September 27, 2024, as a key component of Dusit Central Park.
Starting May 1, 2024, reservations for the new Dusit Thani Bangkok can be made through their website, with early birds receiving a US$75 nightly credit for dining and spa treatments, among other benefits. Rates begin at US$330++ per night. Bookings made by October 31, 2024, for stays between September 27, 2024, and March 31, 2025, are eligible for this promotion.</description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet.</description></item></channel></rss>