<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Business Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary.</description></item><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator).</description></item><item><title>Comprehensive Network Services From Telarus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</guid><description>Creating and managing a network can be a significant challenge for businesses of all sizes. Small businesses find it distracting, while larger companies view it as a costly endeavor that can either help or hurt their efficiency. Integrating local and wide area networks seamlessly is a particularly difficult problem.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: Telarus. Regardless of your size or technical expertise, Telarus provides a range of services to address your networking needs.</description></item><item><title>Welcome To The Big Bandwidth Era</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/welcome-to-the-big-bandwidth-era/</guid><description>Remember the days of big band music? While many may not be familiar with that era, technology has dramatically changed since then. We&amp;rsquo;ve moved from radio and kilocycles to the digital age with bandwidth measured in Mbps and Gbps. This is the era of big bandwidth.
But what exactly qualifies as &amp;ldquo;big bandwidth&amp;rdquo;? NuVox, a leading telecommunications company, defines it as any bandwidth exceeding 10 Mbps. This speed is the target for home internet providers as video streaming gains popularity.</description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Connection Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</guid><description>Businesses require internet access for both customer communication and internal operations. Unlike residential internet, business connections demand higher reliability because downtime directly translates to financial losses, especially for online businesses. Cost-effectiveness is also crucial.
Ethernet Internet is a relatively new technology that offers advantages in both cost and reliability. Additionally, it may provide bandwidth options previously unavailable in your area. A quick search with this Ethernet Internet Finder can reveal your options.</description></item><item><title>The Stunning Truth About Metro Ethernet Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/</guid><description>In recent years, a new type of network connection called Metro Ethernet (MetroE) has emerged, offering significantly more bandwidth at lower costs compared to traditional options.
This cost-effectiveness is driven by two main factors: technological advancements and the rise of competitive service providers. This combination provides businesses, especially in challenging economic times, an opportunity to enhance their network capabilities without increasing expenses or even reduce costs while maintaining the same bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>How MPLS Network Bursting Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 19:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>The standard method of ordering bandwidth for last-mile connections or MPLS networks involves committing to a specific rate or line speed. For instance, a T1 line provides a constant 1.5 Mbps, while a 10 Mbps Ethernet service delivers precisely that speed. In multi-tenant networks like MPLS VPNs, you purchase a committed information rate representing the maximum speed your connection will achieve. However, what happens if business needs change or your initial estimate is inaccurate?</description></item></channel></rss>