<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Civil Jurisdiction on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/civil-jurisdiction/</link><description>Recent content in Civil Jurisdiction on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:45:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/civil-jurisdiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Litigation in England involving business and human rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Anil Yilmaz Vastardis, Lecturer in Law, Human Rights Centre, University of Essex
Following the UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union, there is widespread uncertainty about the future. While political questions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit dominate the discussion, the consequences extend far beyond, impacting individuals worldwide, including victims of human rights abuses perpetrated by British corporations. A key concern revolves around the fate of EU laws implemented in the UK, either through legislation or direct application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the UK government's proposals for cross-border civil litigation post-Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re a well-known UK politician who spends most of their time speaking on British radio or working in the US, only occasionally attending their primary job in France or Belgium. Imagine this politician is divorcing their German spouse. Which court and legal system would handle the divorce and child custody matters?
This scenario falls under the larger subject of international civil litigation, also known as private international law, which is the focus of the UK government&amp;rsquo;s most recent position paper on Brexit negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Commentary on Arlewin v. Sweden: Libel Law, EU Law, and the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 02:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</guid><description>Athanassios Takis: PhD, Special Adviser to General Secretariat of Greek government
The European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruling of March 1, 2016, in the case of Arlewin v. Sweden examined how EU Regulation 44/2001, which decides which Member State&amp;rsquo;s courts hold jurisdiction over civil and commercial disputes, was used (or misused) by Swedish courts. This case highlighted the limitations of the &amp;lsquo;acte clair&amp;rsquo; doctrine – the idea that national courts don&amp;rsquo;t always need to consult the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on EU law matters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>