<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transport/</link><description>Recent content in Transport on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dubai's RTA announces transport service timings for Eid al Fitr holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA) has released the operating schedules for its services during the Eid al-Fitr holidays. The schedule covers various services, including customer service centers, parking, public buses, Dubai Metro and Tram, marine transit, driving institutes, and vehicle testing and registration centers.
Source: RTA. Al Marri.
Moaza Al Marri, RTA&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing &amp;amp; Corporate Communication, stated that Customer Service Centers will be closed for the Eid al-Fitr holiday from Sunday, July 3rd, 2016, and will reopen on Sunday, July 10th, 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-announces-transport-service-timings-for-eid-al-fitr-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the ability to hail a cab using Hailo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 21:10:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</guid><description>Hailo, a highly-rated taxi app boasting more five-star reviews than any other similar service, launched in Singapore on October 29th. With a global network of over 60,000 drivers and a strong user base exceeding 1.4 million, Hailo reports a ride request every two seconds somewhere in the world.
Source: Hailo. From left: Benny Lim, Managing Director, SMRT Road Holdings; Ron Zeghibe, Co-Founder &amp;amp; Executive Chairman, Hailo Global, and Yu Hsiang Wong, General Manager, Hailo Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-ability-to-hail-a-cab-using-hailo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings with 3D Printed Replacement Parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5523) arm lowering mechanism, I removed the circuit boards for refurbishment. This presented an ideal opportunity to swap the deteriorated transport lock bushings with 3D-printed replacements. The old bushings tend to break down, scattering fragments within the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s casing, often lodging beneath the floating chassis. These fragments can obstruct the chassis&amp;rsquo;s movement, hindering its ability to isolate the turntable and tonearm from the enclosure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cainiao will collaborate with Ethiopian Airlines to provide cold chain air freight services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</guid><description>Source: Alibaba Group. Cainiao will distribute temperature-sensitive medications, including COVID-19 vaccines, globally, excluding Africa, via Dubai in partnership with Ethiopian Airlines.
Cainiao Smart Logistics Network, the logistics branch of Alibaba Group Holdings, has partnered with Ethiopian Airlines. Their collaboration will establish a specialized cold chain air freight system to transport temperature-controlled medical supplies. These shipments will originate from Shenzhen Airport, recognized as China&amp;rsquo;s first medical cross-border cold chain facility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travel to Banwa Private Island with Ascent Flights Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</guid><description>Banwa Private Island, a secluded island in Northeast Palawan known for its pristine beaches, has joined forces with Ascent Flights Global to provide exclusive and secure travel options for its guests. This collaboration aims to create a protected travel environment through personalized on-demand flights using seaplanes, helicopters, or private jets based on individual preferences.
Source: Banwa Private Island. Banwa Private Island has partnered Ascent Flights Global to offer guests safe, private transport to their accommodation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-to-banwa-private-island-with-ascent-flights-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poor drivers and European Union legislation: The Court of Justice of the European Union takes the wrong approach.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</guid><description>Steve Peers
There&amp;rsquo;s a humorous anecdote about national stereotypes, where an American, a Canadian, a Brit, and a Frenchman are asked to write about elephants. The punchline highlights their different perspectives: the Frenchman focuses on the elephant&amp;rsquo;s mating habits, the Brit on its colonial significance, the American on its military uses, and the Canadian on whether the elephant falls under federal or provincial jurisdiction. This humorous scenario underscores how jurisdictional issues are central to Canadian identity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ACN and MENA Cargo will be providing enhanced services in the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:43:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</guid><description>The Asia Cargo Network (ACN), a Southeast Asian air cargo charter provider, is expanding its reach globally through a new partnership with Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s MENA Aerospace. This agreement will see ACN stationing six cargo planes in Bahrain and the GCC to better serve the Middle East, North Africa (MENA) region and beyond.
These operations will fall under the MENA Cargo brand, a subsidiary of MAE specializing in freight cargo. The rollout will occur over the next year and a half, with the first of the six aircraft scheduled to arrive and begin operations within the next two months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acn-and-mena-cargo-will-be-providing-enhanced-services-in-the-gulf-cooperation-council-gcc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Uber for Business is growing with a new transportation solution for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/</guid><description>Uber for Business is a platform designed to help companies enhance their operational efficiency through streamlined billing, reporting, and management tools. Initially focused on business travel, the platform has expanded to encompass various facets of customer transportation.
This expansion is facilitated by UberCENTRAL, a solution integrated into the Uber for Business platform. UberCENTRAL enables companies to elevate the customer experience by offering on-demand, door-to-door transportation.
UberCENTRAL empowers organizations to modernize customer transportation in several ways:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-for-business-is-growing-with-a-new-transportation-solution-for-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, the Brunei freight and logistics market had a value of US$157.25 million</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</guid><description>A new report by Mordor Intelligence, titled &amp;ldquo;Brunei Freight &amp;amp; Logistics Market Study - Market Trends, Analysis &amp;amp; Forecasts to 2023,&amp;rdquo; has been added to ResearchAndMarkets.com&amp;rsquo;s collection.
The Brunei freight and logistics market, valued at US$157.25 million in 2017, sees its biggest opportunity in the multi-trillion dollar halal industry. Mordor Intelligence highlights Brunei&amp;rsquo;s positive image within the Islamic world, where it is regarded as a hub of Islamic culture.
Brunei&amp;rsquo;s strategic location for China, along with its alignment with the Belt and Road project, presents significant opportunities for its halal certification industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can book Mwasalat taxis without using the mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Mwasalat. Taxi Butler devices will offer taxi booking
services.
Mwasalat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Taxi Butlers,&amp;rdquo; kiosks that streamline taxi bookings. This initiative is part of the public transportation company&amp;rsquo;s ongoing plan to modernize Oman&amp;rsquo;s taxi services.
Taxi Butlers eliminate the hassle of individual driver contact by allowing users to pre-book taxis. The kiosks offer the convenience of booking multiple taxis and provide passengers with real-time updates on arrival times, driver information, and vehicle arrival alerts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's RTA has entered into a partnership with Careem for ride-hailing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</guid><description>Source: RTA. HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of RTA and Mudassir Sheikha, Founder and Managing Director of Careem, signed the agreement on behalf of the two respective entities. RTA executives attending the signing included Mohammed Obaid Al Mulla, Member of Board of Executive Directors, Abdullah Yousef Al Ali, CEO of Public Transport Agency, and Adel Shakri, Director of Transportation Systems. Bassel Al Nahlaoui, VP of Business Development &amp;amp; Government Relations attended on behalf of Careem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-rta-has-entered-into-a-partnership-with-careem-for-ride-hailing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Science Park 1 will be testing a program for sharing personal mobility devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</guid><description>Ascendas-Singbridge Group, a leading provider of sustainable urban and business space solutions in Asia, has partnered with Neuron Mobility, a smart transportation solutions provider, to pilot a personal mobility device (PMD) sharing program at Singapore Science Park 1. This six-month trial reflects the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing accessibility and convenience for tenants, employees, and visitors within the park.
Starting June 14, 2017, fifty GPS-equipped e-scooters and twenty bicycles will be available for rent at six designated parking zones throughout Singapore Science Park 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A Broken Off Solenoid Plunger and New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 16:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, recently serviced and returned to a customer, unexpectedly came back with a faulty tonearm. The culprit was a broken solenoid plunger, a part responsible for lowering the tonearm. This unusual breakage was likely due to material fatigue.
To fix the issue, the solenoid was replaced with one from a donor Beogram 4002. During the repair, it was discovered that the transport lock bushings had also deteriorated and needed replacement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-broken-off-solenoid-plunger-and-new-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Packaging for Shipping: An Update on How to Secure the Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</guid><description>This article outlines a packaging update for the Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 turntables. Instead of taping the arm cover to the platter, the author now advises using an M3 screw to secure the carriage directly to the chassis.
This change is due to the risk of damaging the arm cover&amp;rsquo;s labeling with tape during shipping. While the author previously suggested using paper to protect the lettering, damage continued to occur...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China Telecom is conducting a trial of a connected car concept in partnership with Gemalto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</guid><description>Gemalto, a digital security company, and China Telecom, a major Chinese mobile operator, are collaborating on a connected car project. They are using Gemalto&amp;rsquo;s LinqUs On-Demand Connectivity (ODC) subscription management solution.
The companies recently demonstrated at Mobile World Congress Shanghai how remote provisioning can securely connect mobile devices. They plan to apply this ODC solution to vehicles. This would allow China Telecom&amp;rsquo;s automotive clients to provide their customers with instant in-car connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grab for Work assists businesses in managing transportation costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</guid><description>Grab, a Southeast Asian ride-hailing company, has introduced Grab for Work, a complimentary transport expense management tool for businesses in Southeast Asia. Designed for business leaders, managers, HR, and finance professionals in both SMEs and MNCs, Grab for Work provides a streamlined approach to handling company transportation costs.
Developed with feedback from over 150 companies in the region during its beta phase, Grab for Work is currently utilized by a similar number of businesses across Southeast Asia, including notable names such as Chope Group (Singapore), Park Hotel Group (Singapore), Rainmaker Labs (Singapore), Yesboss (Indonesia), and Malaysian Airlines (Malaysia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grab-for-work-assists-businesses-in-managing-transportation-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>