<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Citizens' Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/citizens-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Citizens' Rights on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/citizens-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In what way can the courts enforce Part Two of the Withdrawal Agreement regarding citizens' rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</guid><description>Ensuring the Enforceability of EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Rights in the UK Post-Brexit Professor Tamara Hervey, Natalia Miernik and James C Murphy (UG students), University of Sheffield
Acknowledgement is given to the ESRC for its support of Health Governance after Brexit and UK in a Changing Europe.
1. Introduction
Approximately 3.6 million EU citizens and their families reside in the UK. A significant number, estimated to be over 185,000, contribute to the health and social care sector.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 3 of the updated Brexit Withdrawal Agreement focuses on dispute resolution.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
This post examines the dispute settlement mechanisms outlined in the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement, specifically addressing the role of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). It is part of a series analyzing the updated agreement, which includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship. Previous posts have provided an overview of the agreement and examined the transition period.</description></item><item><title>It's finally here - the CJEU has confirmed that UK citizens have officially lost their EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has affirmed that UK citizens lost EU citizenship due to Brexit, as per a recent judgment. This aligns with the earlier Advocate-General’s opinion. While other similar cases exist, the CJEU is unlikely to deviate from this decision.
This judgment is notable for its dismissal of arguments advocating for the retention of EU citizenship for British citizens, marking a significant shift.</description></item></channel></rss>