<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Integra Telecom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integra-telecom/</link><description>Recent content in Integra Telecom on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integra-telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Networks Interconnect in Arizona</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</guid><description>Ethernet is quickly gaining popularity as the preferred protocol for metropolitan and wide area networks. It&amp;rsquo;s predicted that IP networks using standard Ethernet services will eventually replace the outdated Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). The main obstacle to this is the fragmented nature of Ethernet service providers, comprising a mix of established and newer carriers with limited service areas. However, E-NNI technology is emerging as the solution to connect these disparate networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Security Moves To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud services are expanding beyond the familiar Infrastructure, Platform, and Software as a Service to include Security as a Service. Integra, for example, now offers a suite of Cloud Security Services, including a Cloud Firewall Service.
Many companies find managed security appealing because it removes the need for dedicated IT staff or investments in security hardware. Traditionally, this involved a monthly service fee and an on-premises security device. Cloud-based security takes it further, eliminating the need for physical hardware altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Services to 400 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</guid><description>Bandwidth requirements are clearly increasing. Small companies are upgrading from 1.5 Mbps T1 lines to 10 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, while medium-sized companies are moving towards 50 or 100 Mbps connections. Large companies are continuously seeking even faster Gigabit connections.
While bandwidth typically peaks at 5 or 10 Gbps, some providers offer up to 40 Gbps as they transition to 100 Gbps. However, one provider is setting a new standard with 400 Gbps availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>