<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gigabit Internet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-internet/</link><description>Recent content in Gigabit Internet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gigabit-internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item></channel></rss>