<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tableau on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tableau/</link><description>Recent content in Tableau on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:05:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tableau/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visualizations in the style of Tableau help to make content more memorable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visualizations-in-the-style-of-tableau-help-to-make-content-more-memorable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 09:05:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visualizations-in-the-style-of-tableau-help-to-make-content-more-memorable/</guid><description>Ben Jones, Director of Marketing, Outreach Programs at Tableau Software, highlights the numerous advantages of data visualizations for content creators. During a media workshop introducing Tableau Public, a free version of Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization platform, Jones outlined several key benefits:
Data visualizations are attention-grabbing, providing a visual anchor within text and effectively conveying the story&amp;rsquo;s central theme.
They simplify the presentation of trends compared to using words alone.
Visualizations make comparisons clear and effortless.</description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering.</description></item><item><title>Tableau 9.3 offers quicker data analysis and additional advantages in the cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-9-3-offers-quicker-data-analysis-and-additional-advantages-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 14:24:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tableau-9-3-offers-quicker-data-analysis-and-additional-advantages-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>Tableau Software has launched an updated version of its data visualization software, Tableau 9.3. The new release features an &amp;ldquo;always connected&amp;rdquo; version of Tableau Desktop, allows direct connection to the Snowflake Elastic Data Warehouse, and provides more comprehensive global map coverage.
“Tableau 9.3 makes sharing and collaboration much easier. Users will notice how central these features have become,” remarked JY Pook, Tableau’s Senior Vice President for the Asia Pacific region. “The ‘always connected’ feature makes it simpler to share work as you go – which is essential for our increasingly digital and data-driven region.</description></item><item><title>Data-driven alerts are introduced in Tableau 10.3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-driven-alerts-are-introduced-in-tableau-10-3/</guid><description>Tableau Software, a leading provider of visual analytics solutions, has launched Tableau 10.3. This latest release empowers businesses to derive data-driven insights swiftly.
Francois Ajenstat, Chief Product Officer at Tableau, stated that companies are seeking to maximize the value of their data, aiming not just for basic analysis but for the capability to effortlessly and efficiently unlock insights from all their data. Features like smart recommendations enable customers to find the right data quickly, bypassing the need to search for suitable tables and joins.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is urging the public to take an active role in digital defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 02:35:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</guid><description>Source: Tableau. Minister Maliki addresses the audience.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for Defence &amp;amp; Foreign Affairs, Dr. Mohamad Maliki Bin Osman, was the guest of honor and keynote speaker at Tableau Software&amp;rsquo;s 5th annual Public Sector Day. During his speech, he emphasized the importance of digital defense in the digital age.
Dr. Maliki highlighted how digital technology&amp;rsquo;s interconnected nature has increased vulnerability to cyberattacks, disinformation campaigns, and the spread of fake news.</description></item></channel></rss>