<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kuala Lumpur on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kuala-lumpur/</link><description>Recent content in Kuala Lumpur on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kuala-lumpur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IdeaLab gives power to startups in ASEAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</guid><description>IdeaLab 2016, a focused two-day startup conference, will highlight ASEAN startup collaboration and the Malaysian startup scene. It also features the Malaysian Business Angels Network (MBAN) Summit, attracting investors globally. The organizers aim to bring together 500 top startups, investors, and corporations from the ASEAN ecosystem.
Attendees can participate in various stages. The Ideation Stage features industry leaders discussing critical issues faced by startups in ASEAN. At the IdeaPad Stage, the best ASEAN startups compete before a panel of judges.</description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites.</description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment.</description></item><item><title>Experience the enchanting Arabian nights under the stars at the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar until July 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</guid><description>From June 21st to July 16th, 2015, the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar is excited to present a delectable Ramadhan buffet. The culinary team at LINK All Day Dining has crafted a special &amp;ldquo;Starry Arabian Nights&amp;rdquo; themed dinner, featuring a wide selection of traditional Arab and Malay dishes. The restaurant will be adorned with exotic, Arabian-inspired starry lights, and live ‘ghazal’ performances will entertain guests throughout their meal.
Source: Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service.</description></item><item><title>The KL Journal provides a unique boutique option for accommodations in Kuala Lumpur, as an alternative to traditional hotel chains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 01:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kl-journal-provides-a-unique-boutique-option-for-accommodations-in-kuala-lumpur-as-an-alternative-to-traditional-hotel-chains/</guid><description>Source: The KL Journal. This hotel blends industrial design, diverse local touches, and vintage pieces to create a stylishly modern yet retro atmosphere.
Located near Bukit Bintang, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s primary shopping and entertainment area, the Kuala Lumpur Journal (KL Journal) is a boutique hotel designed for the modern traveler seeking an alternative to large chains. It offers all the necessary modern amenities while retaining a unique sense of style and personality.</description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan.</description></item></channel></rss>