<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT Resources on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-resources/</link><description>Recent content in IT Resources on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs Dedicated Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 03:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</guid><description>There are many ways to host your emails, websites, and software applications. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the pros and cons of each option to help you determine the best fit for your business.
You might be tempted to manage your own hosting, which is how many companies started and how some large companies still operate. The basic requirement is a computer that functions as a file server and a bandwidth connection. Internally, this connection can be your Local Area Network (LAN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-dedicated-hosting/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>