<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Converged IP Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/converged-ip-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Converged IP Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/converged-ip-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>