<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Passports on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/passports/</link><description>Recent content in Passports on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/passports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's confusion on biometric data and data protection law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Growing concerns about the protection of biometric data have led the EU to propose a data protection regulation classifying such data as sensitive, thus providing it with a higher level of protection. However, until this proposal is enacted, existing EU regulations address this issue, although not always effectively, as demonstrated by the recent CJEU ruling in the Willems case, which falls short in its application of existing regulations to biometric data.</description></item></channel></rss>