<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Video Transport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-video-transport/</link><description>Recent content in IP Video Transport on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-video-transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Content Delivery Networks Need More Capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</guid><description>A significant media shift is underway, marked by a technological revolution since the days of broadcast dominance. Concerns about antenna reception have been replaced by anxieties over 3G and 4G coverage for accessing videos on mobile devices. Cable and satellite TV, which succeeded over-the-air broadcasting, now face competition from the internet as the preferred medium for audio and video content. As over-the-air delivery declines, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are emerging as its replacement.</description></item><item><title>Content Delivery Networks Transformed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth is steadily growing, largely due to the rise of IP video streaming, downloads, and more sophisticated websites with larger graphics and interactive features. To keep up with this demand, networks and websites themselves need to change.
While increasing WAN bandwidth is a given, it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete solution. Despite significant growth in WAN bandwidth, internet traffic congestion persists, leading to the emergence of Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) as a bypass.</description></item></channel></rss>