<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Referendum on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/referendum/</link><description>Recent content in Referendum on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/referendum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty.</description></item><item><title>The process of withdrawing from the EU: Examining the uses and abuses of Article 50 TEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 07:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-process-of-withdrawing-from-the-eu-examining-the-uses-and-abuses-of-article-50-teu/</guid><description>If the UK decides to hold a referendum on leaving the EU, also known as &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; Article 50 of the Treaty on the European Union (TEU) will be a focal point. This article outlines the exit process for member states. While some suggest using Article 50 to renegotiate UK membership, its legal and political limitations make this challenging.
The Details of Article 50 Article 50 allows any EU member state to withdraw according to its constitution.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take.</description></item><item><title>Will Brexit be unavoidable? The UK's EU membership post-General Election.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 07:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-brexit-be-unavoidable-the-uk-s-eu-membership-post-general-election/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Conservative majority win in the UK brings up significant questions regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued membership in the European Union. This piece will initially address concerns surrounding the referendum and the renegotiation process.
The Brexit Referendum
What are the main issues surrounding the approaching referendum?
The new government&amp;rsquo;s plan to renegotiate the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership followed by a referendum (Brexit) based on the renegotiation&amp;rsquo;s results by the end of 2017 is paramount.</description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?</description></item></channel></rss>