<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Health Care on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/health-care/</link><description>Recent content in Health Care on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/health-care/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>The Dublin system: Balancing Mutual Trust and Human Rights Protection in the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated to the Centre of Interdisciplinary Research in Constitutional Law of Saint-Louis University (USL-B) and the Centre of European Law of the Free University Brussels (ULB). The author wishes to thank the Professors E. Bribosia and S. Van Drooghenbroeck for their valuable advice.
Introduction
On February 16th, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) issued a significant judgment in the case of C.</description></item><item><title>The EU’s Patients’ Rights Directive in practice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-patients-rights-directive-in-practice/</guid><description>Tamara Hervey, Professor of Law and Head of Law School, University of Sheffield
As Europe focuses on the immense refugee crisis, discussing other migration matters can seem trivial. However, this week also saw the release of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s report on the &amp;ldquo;Patients&amp;rsquo; Rights Directive.&amp;rdquo; This report reveals that the directive&amp;rsquo;s name is misleading, as its primary goal appears to be safeguarding national health systems instead of patients&amp;rsquo; rights.</description></item><item><title>Part 1 of the European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement text explores the impact on health, focusing on patients and reciprocal healthcare.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 06:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-of-the-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-text-explores-the-impact-on-health-focusing-on-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law, University of Sheffield
This article provides an initial examination of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s draft Withdrawal Agreement and its effects on health-related issues, particularly concerning individuals.
The focus here is on patient rights, specifically reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the remaining 27 EU members post-Brexit. Two significant issues are explored:
The future of UK pensioners residing in or planning to retire in other EU countries.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The Impact of the Revised European Commission Draft Withdrawal Agreement on Health - Patients and Reciprocal Healthcare (Updated as of March 18, 2018)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-impact-of-the-revised-european-commission-draft-withdrawal-agreement-on-health-patients-and-reciprocal-healthcare-updated-as-of-march-18-2018/</guid><description>Tamara K Hervey, holding the Jean Monnet Chair in EU Law at the University of Sheffield, has reviewed the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s revised draft legal text on the Withdrawal Agreement (WA) as of March 15, 2018. Her analysis focuses on how the revised text impacts reciprocal healthcare between the UK and the EU-27 post-Brexit, particularly for UK pensioners residing in other EU countries and the use of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) for emergency care.</description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 1: Examination of Healthcare Entitlements in the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield examines the healthcare entitlements, if any, provided by the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) that was provisionally agreed upon on December 24, 2020.
Introduction
The TCA includes provisions for social security coordination, similar to EU law but considerably weaker. These provisions are found in Heading Four and are not typical of standard trade agreements like CETA.
Many are interested in the future of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) scheme, as private travel insurance is often expensive or inaccessible, particularly for the elderly.</description></item></channel></rss>