<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cognizant on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cognizant/</link><description>Recent content in Cognizant on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cognizant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant outlines three key strategies for remaining employed in the coming decade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 02:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</guid><description>Cognizant&amp;rsquo;s Jobs of the Future Report highlights a three-part theme, Coaching, Caring, and Connecting, which prioritizes human skills and predicts their importance in the future job market, regardless of technological advancements.
Coaching Coaches can transform work by making it more engaging, humane, and meaningful. Individuals with a knack for mentoring and helping others improve in areas like finance or personal well-being should focus on developing these skills further.
Caring Future-oriented organizations will prioritize employee well-being alongside technological advancement.</description></item></channel></rss>