<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Google on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/google/</link><description>Recent content in Google on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>Google Drive prices have been significantly reduced by Google</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-drive-prices-have-been-significantly-reduced-by-google/</guid><description>A blog post published on March 13 revealed that Google significantly reduced prices for cloud storage. The monthly fees have been adjusted to US$1.99 for 100GB (previously US$4.99), US$9.99 for 1TB (previously US$49.99), and US$99.99 for 10TB, with the option to purchase additional terabytes as required.
A 15 GB plan remains free of charge. This storage space can be utilized across Drive, Gmail, and Google+ Photos.
Source: Google
Existing paying users will be automatically transitioned to the corresponding updated plan without incurring additional costs.</description></item><item><title>Starting today, Singtel will be accepting preorders for the Google Pixel 2 XL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</guid><description>Singtel announced a partnership with Google to become the official telecommunications provider for the highly anticipated Google Pixel 2 XL in Singapore. Starting November 15th, Singtel customers will have the exclusive opportunity to be the first in Southeast Asia to purchase this new device.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, expressed excitement about bringing the Pixel 2 XL to Singapore, highlighting its innovative features that have been eagerly awaited by Android fans.</description></item><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology.</description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering.</description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G2 With Google is 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</guid><description>T-Mobile is raising the bar for smartphones with its new G2, a Google phone that seamlessly integrates with Google Voice. This allows for voicemails to be converted to text and read like emails or texts.
Powered by Android 2.2, the G2 boasts a 3.7-inch full touch screen with seven customizable home panels. Users can personalize their experience with thousands of apps and widgets from the Android Market.
One of the G2&amp;rsquo;s standout features is its Adobe Flash Player, unlike a well-known competitor.</description></item><item><title>According to BrandZ, Tencent is currently the most valuable brand in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</guid><description>Tencent, a Chinese company, has become the most valuable brand in Asia and the fastest growing brand globally, achieving a brand value of US$54 billion in the 2014 BrandZ Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands ranking. This success propelled Tencent to the 14th spot globally, surpassing China Mobile.
Source: Millward Brown website.
Deepender Rana, Managing Director of Millward Brown Greater China, emphasized the significance of a market-driven Chinese brand like Tencent taking the lead over state-owned enterprises.</description></item><item><title>Google Tango experiences were introduced as a part of the Visual SG festival</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 12:32:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/</guid><description>To celebrate its 40th anniversary, the Science Centre Singapore has introduced an augmented reality (AR) experience powered by Google Tango technology.
This immersive experience is available at the Science Centre&amp;rsquo;s recently updated E3 exhibition (E-mmersive Experiential Environments), specifically designed for virtual and augmented reality. Visitors with Tango-enabled phones, like the Lenovo Phab 2 Pro or Asus ZenFone AR, can view moving objects and information overlaid onto their surroundings.
One notable Google Tango exhibit at E3 is Space Adventurer.</description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadhan, digital marketing methods need to be adapted in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Think with Google website. Changes in statistics for Musalsalat, a platform for Ramadhan TV series, during the month.
The Think with Google blog highlights the need for specialized digital marketing strategies in the Middle East and North Africa during Ramadhan. Google Analytical Consultants Vrinda Singh and Younis Maqousi, along with YouTube Specialist David Lacklen, observed a significant increase in mobile internet usage, YouTube viewership, and search engine activity throughout the month.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>Word Lens assists travelers in translating signs instantly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/word-lens-assists-travelers-in-translating-signs-instantly/</guid><description>Quest Visual, the company behind the augmented reality app Word Lens, has decided to offer the app and all of its language packs for free for a limited time. This includes languages like English, French, Italian, Portuguese, and Russian. This gesture of thanks to their users comes as the company transitions to new ownership under Google.
Source: Word Lens page on Play Store.
You can download the Glass, Android, and iOS versions of Word Lens from the Quest Visual website.</description></item><item><title>Google prefers websites that are optimized for mobile devices. Have you taken any steps to ensure your site is mobile-friendly?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</guid><description>World Markets Korea, a Seoul-based online marketing firm, has outlined some of the factors Google now considers when evaluating websites for mobile friendliness. These include text size, spacing between links, and whether the content fits comfortably on a mobile screen. Google uses these criteria to determine if a website is &amp;ldquo;Mobile Friendly.&amp;rdquo;
The company recommends that businesses engage their web designers to update their sites accordingly. World Markets Korea also provides services to optimize websites for mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory.</description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Members of Impact Hub have access to resources provided by Google for Entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-impact-hub-have-access-to-resources-provided-by-google-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Impact Hub. Horowitz (left) with Sai (right).
Impact Hub, the largest coworking and entrepreneur-building community in Singapore, has partnered with Google for Entrepreneurs as its first tech hub partner in Southeast Asia. This collaboration grants Impact Hub Singapore members access to Google for Entrepreneurs&amp;rsquo; global network and resources, encompassing numerous coworking spaces and community programs across 135 countries.
Impact Hub Singapore is dedicated to fostering startup growth by offering comprehensive support, ranging from coworking space to essential resources and tools.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Google is revealing how it plans to increase your productivity in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Google&amp;rsquo;s annual developer conference, I/O, brought a wave of announcements for Apps, Android, Chromebooks, and the Cloud Platform.
As highlighted on the official Google blog, Android now boasts a staggering one billion users who send an estimated 20 billion text messages and 93 million selfies daily. Key introductions include:
Android Wear
Expanding Android&amp;rsquo;s reach to wearable devices, Android Wear allows users to perform tasks or ask questions simply by saying &amp;ldquo;Ok Google.</description></item></channel></rss>