<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WIEF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wief/</link><description>Recent content in WIEF on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>