<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Seminar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/seminar/</link><description>Recent content in Seminar on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/seminar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seminar on Intellectual Property and Legal Issues by the RHT Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</guid><description>RHT Academy and RHTLaw Taylor Wessing are holding a half-day seminar titled &amp;ldquo;Commercial Contracts: Latest Case Law Developments, Negotiation Strategies and Intellectual Property&amp;rdquo; on March 4, 2015, at the Suntec Convention &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre in Singapore.
Designed for legal professionals, business development executives, company secretaries, and compliance officers, this seminar aims to:
Offer a practical, business-focused overview of recent key case law developments related to commercial contracts in Singapore and the UK.</description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate.</description></item></channel></rss>