<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2024 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2024/</link><description>Recent content in 2024 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IWG: The Transformation of the World of Work in 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iwg-the-transformation-of-the-world-of-work-in-2024/</guid><description>This image, created using the AI tool Dream by WOMBO, depicts a concept of modern office work.
As the leading global provider of flexible workspaces, IWG, known for brands like Regus and Spaces, has identified ten significant workplace trends anticipated to influence global work dynamics in 2024. The company predicts the continuation of hybrid work models, citing ongoing research by institutions like Stanford University that suggests a significant portion of white-collar workers will maintain this approach.</description></item><item><title>Experience the global culinary journey at THAIFEX Anuga Asia 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 16:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</guid><description>THAIFEX - Anuga Asia 2024, scheduled for May 28th to June 1st, 2024, is set to be the largest and most diverse edition yet, featuring exhibitors from 45 countries and regions and completely booked booth spaces.
_
Source: THAIFEX-Anuga Asia. Hosted buyer programme participants posing for a group picture during THAIFEX-Anuga Asia 2023.
This premier food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) trade show in Asia Pacific has experienced an unprecedented increase in global participation.</description></item><item><title>Exciting pre-game activities at Shangri-La hotels before the Hong Kong Sevens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 03:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-pre-game-activities-at-shangri-la-hotels-before-the-hong-kong-sevens/</guid><description>Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Shangri-La Group is offering rugby enthusiasts special hotel and experience packages for the Hong Kong Sevens. Fans can choose to stay at the Island Shangri-La, Kowloon Shangri-La, or Kerry Hotel, with each offering exclusive day passes to the event. Packages include pre-game accommodations and breakfast. Additional breakfast and day passes are available for a bundled price.
Source: Shangri-La Group Hong Kong. The Hong Kong Rugby Sevens.
Island Shangri-La, Hong Kong</description></item><item><title>Experience the joyous abundance at PARKROYAL COLLECTION Marina Bay, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/</guid><description>PARKROYAL COLLECTION Marina Bay, Singapore, celebrates the Year of the Dragon with &amp;ldquo;Jubilant Abundance,&amp;rdquo; featuring traditional feasts and an array of Chinese New Year delicacies.
Peach Blossoms
Peach Blossoms presents modern Chinese cuisine rooted in classic Cantonese flavors. For Lunar New Year, enjoy six special set menus, including the seven-course &amp;ldquo;Blessings&amp;rdquo; menu at S$2,388 per table of 10, and the six-course &amp;ldquo;Year of the Dragon Imperial&amp;rdquo; menu at S$398++ per person.</description></item><item><title>IHH Healthcare, NUS, Otis, and PSA set new standards for leadership and workplace mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</guid><description>WorkWell Leaders (WWL), a Singapore-based non-profit focused on workplace wellbeing and mental health, has revealed the winners of the WorkWell Leaders Awards 2024. These awards acknowledge exemplary practices in promoting positive change within workplaces. WWL emphasized that these awards are unique in their recognition of specific elements of workplace wellbeing that drive business results, as well as leadership behaviors that foster cultural transformation within organizations.
Anthea Ong, Founder and Chairperson of WorkWell Leaders, stressed the importance of addressing mental health proactively in the workplace, stating, &amp;ldquo;With 70% of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s population employed and spending a significant portion of their day at work, workplaces must serve as catalysts to support employees and their families.</description></item><item><title>In 2024, 80% of service professionals in Singapore anticipate that customer service will play a larger role in generating revenue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:37:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2024-80-of-service-professionals-in-singapore-anticipate-that-customer-service-will-play-a-larger-role-in-generating-revenue/</guid><description>A recent Salesforce report highlights the growing expectation for customer service to become a significant revenue driver in 2024. The report suggests that AI-powered personalized customer experiences empower service teams to capitalize on upselling, cross-selling, and customer retention to boost revenue.
This new &amp;ldquo;State of Service&amp;rdquo; report is based on insights from over 5,500 service professionals globally, including 100 from Singapore. It examines current trends, challenges, and strategies shaping the customer service landscape, emphasizing how service teams utilize AI and data to enhance revenue, efficiency, and customer satisfaction amidst rising customer expectations.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the Taste The World Dining Series is to demonstrate that food serves as a universal form of communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</guid><description>Gourmet Trails, a luxury travel company, presents the first-ever Taste The World culinary series, taking place from May 4th to 26th, 2024. This festival showcases the unifying power of food, emphasizing its ability to connect people and foster understanding.
Taste The World partners with acclaimed restaurants like Appetite, Hashida, CURE, Canchita, Esquina, Ummi Beirut, and ANJU to offer a diverse range of global cuisines. Proceeds from this event will support the United Nations World Food Programme.</description></item><item><title>Soar to new heights with Lunar New Year festivities at the Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Pan Pacific Singapore. The image displays two of the yusheng choices offered for the Lunar New Year in 2024.
From January 1st to February 25th, 2024, Pan Pacific Singapore presents Lunar New Year specialties designed to bring prosperity.
Hai Tien Lo (海天楼)
This acclaimed restaurant serves refined Cantonese cuisine with modern influences. Throughout the Lunar New Year season, Hai Tien Lo will emphasize its celebratory menus: Set menus - January 22nd to February 25th</description></item><item><title>The Carlton Hotel Singapore reveals its promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Source: Carlton Hotel Singapore. The Carlton Hotel is offering special dining options for the 2024 Lunar New Year celebration.
The Carlton Hotel Singapore welcomes the Lunar New Year with exclusive dining experiences available at Wah Lok Cantonese Restaurant, take-away options, and more.
Wah Lok Cantonese Restaurant presents six Lunar New Year set menus from January 29th to February 24th, 2024. Prices begin at S$468++ for four people. A new menu, &amp;ldquo;Happiness 年年有余,&amp;rdquo; is available for S$1,348++ for eight guests.</description></item><item><title>Observe the fireworks display on February 11 at the Regent Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</guid><description>For the Lunar New Year, The Regent Hong Kong offers various culinary experiences:
Hong Kong Cuisine 1983
Celebrate with symbolic à la carte dishes (HK$468 to HK$980) like Lohei (HK$580) for prosperity, prawns in salted egg yolk (HK$580) for wealth, and braised Wagyu beef cheek (HK$980) for strength. Their HK$438 Good Fortune Turnip Cake Gift Box contains two 800g turnip cakes, one traditional and one smoked with tea leaves, sugarcane, imperatae, and brown sugar.</description></item><item><title>Kramnik will face Alcántara in a rematch on Chessarena.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</guid><description>Source: World Chess. Vladimir Kramnik (pictured left) is set to have a rematch against José Alcántara (Jospem, pictured right) in August 2024.
World Chess, an organization dedicated to increasing the popularity of chess worldwide, is organizing &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims 2.&amp;rdquo; This event is a rematch following a controversial first &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims&amp;rdquo; match between chess players Vladimir Kramnik and José Alcántara. The event will be broadcasted live with commentary from well-known chess personalities and include interactive elements for viewers.</description></item></channel></rss>