<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Future Relationship on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/future-relationship/</link><description>Recent content in Future Relationship on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/future-relationship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the Prime Minister hinting at a potential shift in Brexit stance with his unexpected mention of competition policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</guid><description>Andreas Stephan, Professor of Competition Law &amp;amp; Head of UEA Law School, University of East Anglia*
In a speech delivered on March 2, 2018, Prime Minister Theresa May aimed to clarify the UK&amp;rsquo;s Brexit objectives. She proposed aligning UK State Aid and Competition rules with those of the EU, while allowing UK courts to consider European Court of Justice (ECJ) judgments. However, she emphasized that the ECJ would not have jurisdiction over the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-prime-minister-hinting-at-a-potential-shift-in-brexit-stance-with-his-unexpected-mention-of-competition-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 1: Examination of Healthcare Entitlements in the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield examines the healthcare entitlements, if any, provided by the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) that was provisionally agreed upon on December 24, 2020.
Introduction
The TCA includes provisions for social security coordination, similar to EU law but considerably weaker. These provisions are found in Heading Four and are not typical of standard trade agreements like CETA.
Many are interested in the future of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) scheme, as private travel insurance is often expensive or inaccessible, particularly for the elderly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>