<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unionpay on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unionpay/</link><description>Recent content in Unionpay on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unionpay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UnionPay is expanding its presence in Turkey through partnerships with ZIRAAT BANK and Garanti Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</guid><description>Ziraat Bank in Turkey has partnered with UnionPay International to enable UnionPay card acceptance across all its ATMs and POS terminals within the year. This initiative aims to broaden the reach of UnionPay cards within Turkey and enhance the experience for visiting UnionPay cardholders.
UnionPay anticipates that this collaboration will increase the acceptance rate of UnionPay cards at Turkish ATMs from 50% to nearly 70% by year-end. Similarly, POS terminal acceptance is projected to rise from 80% to almost 90%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay cardholders in Singapore can now enjoy exclusive visa privileges for travel to China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</guid><description>UnionPay International (UPI), a branch of China UnionPay, partnered with Chinese Visa Application Service Centre to offer special VIP treatment to UnionPay cardholders in Singapore applying for a Chinese visa. This express service features a dedicated VIP counter and a faster queue for UnionPay cardholders (card numbers starting with 62).
UnionPay is currently the only international card brand offering expedited Chinese visa applications at Chinese embassies, consulates, and participating visa processing centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The acceptance of UnionPay is expanding globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 19:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</guid><description>UnionPay has successfully expanded its network, brand, and products globally, advancing the international use of Chinese financial technology standards. UnionPay International is now present in over 50 markets involved in the Belt and Road Initiative.
Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International, emphasized their strategy of adapting to each local market, fostering personnel exchange between China and other regions, and supporting the globalization of Chinese financial standards.
In Kazakhstan, over 1.3 million UnionPay cards have been issued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay International introduces a new cross-border marketing campaign with global promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</guid><description>Source: UnionPay International. Ge Huayong, Chairman of China UnionPay (sixth from the right), Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International (fifth from the right), and representatives from initial partners were present at the ceremony.
UnionPay International, in collaboration with Bank of China, China Merchants Bank, CYTS, Ctrip, Spring Airlines, SaSa Hong Kong, Prince Jewellery &amp;amp; Watch, LUKFOOK JEWELLERY, and ISA, has introduced 优计划 (Youjihua), translating to &amp;lsquo;a beneficial strategy&amp;rsquo; and playing on the &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; in UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s Chinese name...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>