<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Locate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/locate/</link><description>Recent content in Locate on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/locate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the fast Phone Finder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-fast-phone-finder/</guid><description>The Phone Finder helps locate lost smartphones, even if they&amp;rsquo;re on silent mode, for up to three years. When the Phone Finder device is clicked within 15 meters of the missing phone, the phone will ring, vibrate, and flash, making it easier to find. If the phone is out of range, the Phone Finder website displays its location on a map.
Source: Kickstarter
Creator Gabsow Tom selected Bluetooth 2.1 for its forward and backward compatibility, allowing the Phone Finder to work with any smartphone, regardless of its iOS or Android version.</description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate.</description></item></channel></rss>