<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transition Period on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transition-period/</link><description>Recent content in Transition Period on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/transition-period/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement Analysis 2: Transition Period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Now that a revised Brexit withdrawal agreement is available, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to revisit my prior analyses of the initial agreement. This post, updating my spring 2018 analysis, focuses on the transition period outlined in the agreement. (The revised agreement includes changes to the Irish border protocol and the political declaration on the future relationship.) This post will provide context for the transition period and then break down the text...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the revised Withdrawal Agreement: Is Empire 2.0 making a comeback?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 09:33:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</guid><description>Commentary on the Draft Withdrawal Agreement - Version of February 21, 2018 This post provides an updated analysis of the draft Brexit withdrawal agreement, taking into account the UK&amp;rsquo;s response to the EU Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposed text.
The withdrawal agreement, if successfully negotiated, will be the key legal framework for Brexit. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember this agreement will be separate from future treaties governing the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-revised-withdrawal-agreement-is-empire-2-0-making-a-comeback/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Data Protection Bill and UK-EU Data Transfers: A Story of Brexit and Data Protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 13:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Elif Mendos Kuşkonmaz, PhD student at Queen Mary, University of London[*]
Introduction
A Bosnian folk song tells the story of a Pasha who died from a severe illness. When his wife heard about his passing, she died from grief. Similarly, now that the UK has chosen to leave the European Union, will the same fate befall data protection laws once the UK exits the EU?
The UK&amp;rsquo;s current data protection law, the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), incorporates the EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 Data Protection Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing and Annotating the Brexit Transition Period: Is it a Bridge Leading to Nowhere?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 20:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent weeks have seen significant progress in the Brexit negotiations. The EU27 and the UK reached an agreement on a substantial portion of the withdrawal agreement, including a transition period from March 2019 to the end of 2020, a key concern for the UK. This agreement follows earlier drafts and sets the stage for defining the future relationship between the UK and the EU, to be formalized in separate treaties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-and-annotating-the-brexit-transition-period-is-it-a-bridge-leading-to-nowhere/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preventing the UK from facing another Brexit crisis: Prolonging the Transition Period beyond 1 July 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</guid><description>René Repasi, Associate Professor of EU Law at Erasmus University Rotterdam, Netherlands
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the EU on January 31st, 2020, marked the completion of the initial &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo; phase, focused on resolving the implications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s past membership. This followed the UK general election, which saw Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s Conservative Party secure a significant majority in the House of Commons, leading to the swift ratification of the Withdrawal Agreement (WA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preventing-the-uk-from-facing-another-brexit-crisis-prolonging-the-transition-period-beyond-1-july-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phase 2 of Brexit negotiations: analysis of the EU27's stance in negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU Council is anticipated to establish its negotiating directives for the second stage of Brexit discussions on January 29th. These talks will primarily focus on a transition period after Brexit Day, during which existing EU law would still be applicable in the UK. A leaked version of these directives has surfaced, providing an opportunity to analyze them in detail. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is subject to change pending final approval...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phase-2-of-brexit-negotiations-analysis-of-the-eu27-s-stance-in-negotiations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>