<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Enterprise VoIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise-voip/</link><description>Recent content in Enterprise VoIP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/enterprise-voip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sipping on the Trunk Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sipping-on-the-trunk-lines/</guid><description>The history of telephone trunks goes back to the early days of telephones. Trunks are lines that carry multiple phone conversations, initially connecting switchboards and switching offices. They&amp;rsquo;ve evolved from wire bundles to analog and now digital circuits, with T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and SONET being common digital trunking services. However, SIP trunking is emerging as a popular alternative.
Telephone trunking saves money by combining multiple phone lines into a single high-bandwidth connection.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls.</description></item><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>Telephony In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>When we think about cloud networking, we often picture data networks moving information between locations. However, many businesses are also transitioning their phone systems to the cloud. This shift brings both benefits and hurdles.
The traditional phone network is essentially a large cloud network. This system is designed for reliability and high-quality service, handling countless users at once. Users connect to this cloud through a direct line to their nearest local central office, unconcerned with the complexities of the system.</description></item><item><title>Why Such a Stampede to The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is everywhere you turn. This raises the question: are businesses truly shifting from traditional data centers to cloud-based solutions? And if so, what motivates this transition and what are their objectives?
Unveiling the Hidden Potential of Cloud Technology
Cloud storage receives significant attention, but the vast server capacity offered by the cloud is equally compelling. One often overlooked application is Hosted PBX or Hosted VoIP, which replaces traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible.</description></item><item><title>IP Exchange - The Final Piece For VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</guid><description>The shift from circuit-switched to packet-switched telephone networks is undeniable. While large companies have adopted enterprise VoIP to enhance efficiency, cut expenses, and prepare for the future, small and medium businesses are considering SIP trunking for bundled high-quality telephone and broadband services. Consumers are switching to cable broadband-telephone packages or third-party VoIP options. However, the PSTN remains.
Currently, VoIP systems and services operate in isolation. On-net calls, meaning calls within the same service regardless of location, are often free.</description></item><item><title>XO Communications Nears Tbps National Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 01:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</guid><description>Any lingering doubts about the supposed overabundance of bandwidth in the late &amp;rsquo;90s telecom boom should be dispelled by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; recent announcement. Despite upgrading their national backbone just last year, XO is increasing its capacity again. This upgrade will boost major coast-to-coast network routes from 400 Gbps to a staggering 800 Gbps, putting them within reach of terabit-per-second speeds.
This massive capacity increase is driven by a fivefold surge in demand for high-capacity inter-city network services over the past year, according to XO.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market.</description></item><item><title>E911 For Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>The transition from traditional phone lines to internet-based calling has brought about some unexpected issues, particularly with emergency services. We often take 911 for granted, assuming help will always be on the way. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case with internet-based phone systems.
Imagine a scenario where a fire breaks out in your office. You dial 911, report the emergency, and evacuate. However, the fire department ends up at your company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters instead of your current location.</description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking Providers Want Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 12:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-providers-want-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>The telephone industry is undergoing a transformation. Previously, businesses typically relied on in-house PBX systems to manage their phone networks and utilized ISDN PRI trunk lines for external calls. However, this is changing rapidly.
Two significant trends are emerging: cloud-based hosted PBX telephone systems and SIP trunking. While these technologies complement each other, it&amp;rsquo;s possible to implement SIP trunking without cloud services.
A telephone trunk consists of multiple phone lines grouped together, either physically or electronically.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Phone Lines For PBX Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 16:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</guid><description>Many modern business phone systems utilize T-1 lines to link their buildings to the local telephone company. This is because merging multiple individual lines into one or two T-1 lines is more cost-efficient. This holds true whether your internal phone system is analog or digital, as even most VoIP systems rely on T-1 lines for external calls.
Smaller setups like basic one or two-line phones or key systems with 4-6 lines typically use analog lines.</description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Shows How The Converged Business Network Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</guid><description>Larger organizations have been moving towards network convergence since IP became the standard network protocol. However, smaller companies, often lacking substantial IT departments, haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted this approach as readily. This is changing. Convergence is now a viable option for businesses of all sizes.
What&amp;rsquo;s driving this shift? The answer, as always, is cost savings. In today&amp;rsquo;s business climate, reducing expenses is crucial. The real game-changer is the availability of managed convergence services.</description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line as an On Ramp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</guid><description>You might know about T1 lines as dedicated connections for digital data or PBX phone lines, but they also serve as excellent access points for various other services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Most businesses maintain a Local Area Network (LAN) and a Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect with the wider world. Your WAN connection often acts as an entry point to larger public or private networks.
A prime example is &amp;ldquo;T1 dedicated Internet.</description></item><item><title>Transforming the WAN Into The Smart WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</guid><description>People tend to think of WAN connections as basic channels for data, similar to how Senator Ted Stevens once described the internet. However, with the shift from on-site data centers to cloud-based systems, VoIP, and video streaming, our needs have outgrown this simple model. This is where the concept of a Smart WAN comes into play.
Instead of treating all data equally, a Smart WAN prioritizes different types of data through a system called Class of Service (CoS).</description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century.</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation.</description></item><item><title>To VoIP or Not to VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/</guid><description>Companies are constantly searching for ways to reduce expenses, especially during economic downturns. Phone bills are often a target for cost-cutting measures, as businesses seek to lower this expense without compromising value.
While achieving this might require careful consideration, the ideal solution depends on your specific requirements and existing infrastructure.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), frequently presented as an alternative phone service. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s more accurate to call it an alternative phone system.</description></item><item><title>Rise Of The Cloud Hosted PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</guid><description>Traditional, in-house PBX systems might be nearing obsolescence with the emergence of cloud-hosted solutions like AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s AirePBX. This innovation signifies a return to an older model where the service provider manages the switching system, but with modern technological advancements.
This shift back to provider-managed systems, reminiscent of early telephone networks, offers significant cost advantages due to increased competition and the use of existing network infrastructure for VoIP services. Businesses no longer need to invest in separate wiring or proprietary equipment, leading to more competitive offerings and feature-rich options.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities.</description></item><item><title>PRI Phone Line Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 18:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</guid><description>Analog business phone lines are suitable for small offices and retail spaces that don&amp;rsquo;t need many outside lines. If you require more than six lines, an option like ISDN PRI might be a better fit.
ISDN PRI, which stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is a standard for transmitting calls digitally over regular phone lines. It&amp;rsquo;s the larger of two primary options, with the smaller being BRI (Basic Rate Interface).</description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap.</description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider.</description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker.</description></item><item><title>A New Edge On Private IP Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</guid><description>With the increase in businesses operating from multiple locations, IP network solutions have become more affordable and accessible. New Edge Networks, a key player in this domain, specializes in private IP-based WANs, offering enhanced quality and performance for connecting multiple business sites by bypassing the public internet.
While the internet has revolutionized global communication, its ubiquity and open nature pose limitations for businesses. Network neutrality principles treat all data equally, regardless of its importance.</description></item><item><title>Toshiba Strata CIX Does SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 12:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toshiba-strata-cix-does-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Business phone systems have transitioned from analog lines to digital T1 and T1 PRI trunks. With the rise of Enterprise VoIP, SIP Trunking has emerged as a popular all-IP option, supported by a growing number of carriers. SIP trunking eliminates the need for on-site PSTN termination by sending voice and data packets to a service provider, leading to cost savings through economies of scale.
Toshiba&amp;rsquo;s Strata CIX IP Business Communication Systems have integrated SIP trunking, removing the need for a separate VoIP gateway.</description></item><item><title>Will 2013 Be Your Year of the Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing was a major trend in 2012, with numerous vendors offering a wide range of solutions. Cloud services are no longer limited to powerful supercomputers; they&amp;rsquo;ve become accessible and practical for everyday resources, often surpassing the benefits of in-house solutions. This raises the question: will 2013 be the year you transition to the cloud?
For many businesses, the answer is a clear &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Cost-effectiveness, support, and accessibility are key drivers.</description></item></channel></rss>