<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Retirement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retirement/</link><description>Recent content in Retirement on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:07:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retirement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The economy has an impact on retirement and emergency savings plans in Singapore, according to OCBC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</guid><description>Source: OCBC. Average retirement ages by age cohorts.
Retirement and emergency planning have taken a backseat in Singapore. OCBC&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that &amp;ldquo;planning for retirement&amp;rdquo; experienced the most significant decline among financial priorities, with the index score dropping from 47 in 2022 to 40 this year. This finding comes from the fifth edition of the annual OCBC Financial Wellness Index, which surveyed 2,000 working adults in Singapore aged 21 to 65 in August 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-economy-has-an-impact-on-retirement-and-emergency-savings-plans-in-singapore-according-to-ocbc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Poland violating the principle of effective judicial protection? Recent developments in the CJEU suggest so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</guid><description>Femke Gremmelprez, PhD Researcher and Academic Assistant, Department of European, Public and International Law, Research group Ghent European Law Institute
While the Court of Justice plays a significant role in enforcing EU law through infringement and preliminary ruling procedures (Articles 258 and 267 TFEU, respectively), it has largely been excluded from enforcing EU values, particularly the rule of law. The EU Treaties lack explicit provisions granting the Court of Justice the power to address rule of law breaches by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Technology Enables The 4-Hour Workweek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</guid><description>Timothy Ferriss&amp;rsquo; book, &amp;ldquo;The 4-Hour Workweek,&amp;rdquo; captivated my attention with its intriguing title and concept. It challenges the conventional 40-hour workweek and suggests a lifestyle where individuals can achieve personal and financial freedom by working less.
Ferriss, who identifies as a &amp;ldquo;vagabond,&amp;rdquo; emphasizes embracing technology and shifting perspectives to design a fulfilling life filled with travel and adventure. He challenges the traditional notion of working tirelessly for decades before retirement, proposing instead a series of &amp;ldquo;mini-retirements&amp;rdquo; interspersed with periods of work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The FIRE movement is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fire-movement-is-gaining-popularity-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fire-movement-is-gaining-popularity-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>The FIRE (Financial Independence, Retire Early) movement is gaining traction in Southeast Asia. A Milieu Insight study discovered that over 60% of Southeast Asians anticipate retiring between the ages of 50 and 69.
Source: Milieu Insight. Different FIRE strategies across Southeast Asia.
Retiring before the age of 50 is a possibility for 60% of those surveyed, yet only 14% feel they are on track. Singaporeans are the most doubtful, with only 9% believing they are on track for early retirement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fire-movement-is-gaining-popularity-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fire-movement-is-gaining-popularity-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Henley &amp; Partners has been selected as the worldwide concessionaire for the Thai residency program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</guid><description>Henley &amp;amp; Partners, a global firm specializing in residence and citizenship advisory, has been chosen to promote Thailand&amp;rsquo;s residence visa program, Thailand Elite. This program allows foreigners to reside in Thailand for up to 20 years.
Thailand&amp;rsquo;s welcoming atmosphere has made it a desirable destination in Southeast Asia. Individuals and families from affluent nations are increasingly drawn to its climate, scenery, and recreational opportunities. The 2017 &amp;ldquo;Best Countries&amp;rdquo; report highlighted Thailand as a prime location for starting a business due to its affordability, efficient bureaucracy, and accessible capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>