<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Humor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/humor/</link><description>Recent content in Humor on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clod Computing Challenges The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing is gaining popularity as a cost-effective alternative to traditional data centers. However, a new competitor called &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; computing is emerging, boasting even lower costs.
](http://www.sysnito.com/?crid=11591&amp;linkID=145&amp;refid=Telexplainer-Clod)Clod computing minimizes infrastructure expenses by utilizing readily available, discarded computers. Chip-On-A-Shingle, a clod computing startup, defines a &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; as a network of interconnected old computers and devices that collectively provide impressive processing power.
This approach is viable due to the abundance of still functional computers being discarded simply because they are outdated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Happy 4th of July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-4th-of-july/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-4th-of-july/</guid><description>Hey there! T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer and the Founding Fathers wish you a happy Independence Day!
Have a safe and enjoyable 4th of July!
Best,
John..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-4th-of-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-4th-of-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Economic Woes Drive Rural Telegraphy Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</guid><description>The recent economic downturn has forced a reevaluation of strategies for providing digital communication to rural communities. Access to the internet and even cell phone service is notoriously limited in these areas. While the Rural Broadband Initiative, part of the economic stimulus plan, aimed to address this issue by funding fiber optic cable installation, those funds have unfortunately been redirected.
Robb M. Blihnd, a hedge fund manager, explained that the funds were considered more essential for urban and suburban areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>