<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YouGov on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yougov/</link><description>Recent content in YouGov on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/yougov/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The flag-carrier airline of Dubai is the most popular brand among women in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. 2019 Women&amp;rsquo;s Choice Rankings, top 10 for the UAE.
For the third consecutive year, Emirates secured the top spot in the UAE YouGov BrandIndex Women&amp;rsquo;s Rankings. The airline achieved the highest positive &amp;ldquo;Impression&amp;rdquo; score, reaching +70.0 among women in the UAE. WhatsApp maintained its second-place position, while Carrefour climbed to third place, surpassing Apple, which descended to fourth.
These rankings were determined using data from YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex, a daily brand tracker.</description></item><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products.</description></item><item><title>YouGov is tracking the impact of the haze</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</guid><description>Southeast Asia faced significant haze this year, mainly due to regional forest fires. A YouGov survey reveals a high level of awareness about this issue within the region.
Nearly 80% of Asian respondents are aware of the haze originating from Indonesian landscape fires. This awareness is lower in Hong Kong (48%) and Mainland China (44%). However, in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Singapore, the three countries most affected, only 2% of respondents in each country reported being unaware of the haze.</description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia has the highest number of brand advocates for Garuda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia, the national airline, has earned the highest level of brand advocacy among Indonesian consumers, according to a YouGov BrandIndex analysis.
With a score of 87.5, Garuda secured the top position, surpassing Singapore Airlines (77.2) and Bank Central Asia (76.5).
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s rankings utilize a net promoter score methodology to determine which brands have the highest percentage of current and former customers who would recommend them to family or friends. The top 10 list includes several automotive brands, with Toyota ranking 4th (75.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's top business travel destinations are Tokyo and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 01:50:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-top-business-travel-destinations-are-tokyo-and-bangkok/</guid><description>A recent Samsonite survey explored the preferences of Singaporean business travelers, revealing Tokyo and Bangkok as the top choices for both business and leisure.
The survey, conducted by YouGov, involved over 500 Singaporean respondents who travel for business frequently. It found that Tokyo was the top business destination overall, particularly favored by those aged 35 to 44. Bangkok was the preferred choice for those over 45. Among younger travelers (under 34), Tokyo and London tied for the top spot.</description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines has been ranked as the airline with the highest positive buzz in Singapore, according to YouGov</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</guid><description>Source: Yougov.
YouGov, a market research firm, has identified the leading brands in Singapore across various sectors based on their &amp;ldquo;buzz.&amp;rdquo; These rankings, reflecting average &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo; scores from January to December 2015, offer insights into brands that garnered the most positive attention from the general public.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the top-ranking brands:
Ecommerce and mCommerce: Q0010 leads the pack, followed by Groupon and Carousell. Retail: Fashion: Uniqlo secures the top spot, with H&amp;amp;M and Robinsons trailing behind.</description></item><item><title>YouGov's ranking of the top brands in Hong Kong for the first half of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</guid><description>In the first half of 2016, Mannings was the most talked-about brand among Hong Kong respondents, according to YouGov&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Mid-Year Best Brand Ranking for Hong Kong. Nike and Adidas secured the second and third positions, respectively. This ranking, drawn from YouGov BrandIndex data, reflects the brands generating the most positive buzz.
The leading brands across various industries in Hong Kong are:
Source: YouGov. The top 10 brands by buzz.</description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings.</description></item><item><title>Japanese consumers prefer domestic brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Japan.
YouGov Brandindex&amp;rsquo;s 2016 rankings reveal that Japanese brands are the most popular in Japan. Rakuten and Rakuten Card secured the top two spots, followed by clothing retailer Uniqlo in third place.
These brands were assessed using BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents if their exposure to the brand through advertising, news, or word of mouth in the past two weeks was positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>According to a global survey by YouGov, body confidence increases with age</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</guid><description>A recent global survey by YouGov revealed that most adults feel content with their weight and body image, and this satisfaction generally increases with age. However, the survey also highlighted a widespread concern that celebrity culture negatively impacts young people&amp;rsquo;s body image across almost all countries surveyed.
The survey, spanning the US, Australia, and most of Europe and the Asia Pacific region, found that older individuals are considerably more likely to feel satisfied with their bodies compared to those in their twenties and thirties.</description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Singapore welcomed technology and locally-made brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Brand rankings for 2016.
The 2016 YouGov Brandindex rankings show that Singaporeans have a strong preference for both local and digital brands. Singapore Airlines, DBS bank, The Straits Times newspaper, WhatsApp, and the Apple iPhone (in the top three) all made the list. Other popular tech brands included Facebook, Google, e-commerce platform Qoo10, and YouTube.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score, which asks respondents whether their exposure to the brand in the previous two weeks, through advertising, news, or word of mouth, was positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines is the top-ranked brand in terms of recognition in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 02:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</guid><description>YouGov, a polling and research company, has released its mid-year rankings of the best brands in Singapore for 2015. Singapore Airlines secured the top spot, while Apple appeared twice on the list. Technology brands dominated the top 10, with WhatsApp, e-marketplace Qoo10, Facebook, and Google all making appearances.
Source: YouGov.
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex is a daily metric of public brand perception that monitors numerous brands across various sectors. The company compiles its data every six months and publishes the Best Brand Rankings globally.</description></item><item><title>Indonesian brands are at the top of the Brandindex 2016 rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Indonesia.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 reveal a diverse range of popular brands in Indonesia. Garuda, the national airline, claims the top spot, followed by tech giant Samsung and Danone&amp;rsquo;s mineral water brand, Aqua.
These brands were evaluated based on BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which gauges public perception by asking respondents whether their exposure to a brand in the past two weeks, whether through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth, was positive or negative.</description></item></channel></rss>