<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telco Wiring on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telco-wiring/</link><description>Recent content in Telco Wiring on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telco-wiring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Find Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses currently using T1 lines for dedicated internet or point-to-point connections might be seeking ways to increase bandwidth without the high costs of upgrading to DS3 fiber optic cable. Metro Ethernet offers a solution. But how can you find it?
Locating Metro Ethernet service is straightforward with the right approach. Similar to finding anything else, the key is knowing where to look. A specialized tool designed to locate and map available Ethernet bandwidth in your vicinity is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Thrives In The 21st Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:59:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>For over a century, copper wire has been the backbone of telecommunications, connecting homes and businesses. While fiber optic technology has advanced, copper remains dominant, even in the 21st century.
Despite the rise of fiber optics, copper persists due to its widespread availability and established infrastructure. Connecting to existing copper is often more cost-effective than installing new fiber optic lines.
While copper-based systems were designed for analog signals, they can still handle today’s high-speed digital demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-thrives-in-the-21st-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>