<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>New Zealand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new-zealand/</link><description>Recent content in New Zealand on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/new-zealand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Innovators under 35 in Singapore are looking for applicants from Southeast Asia and Australia/New Zealand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</guid><description>EmTech Singapore is searching for ten innovative individuals under 35 from Southeast Asia, Australia, and New Zealand. These individuals should embody innovation in business and technology and will be featured in the Innovators Under 35 Singapore competition. The competition seeks those responsible for significant advancements, innovations, and impactful contributions to their target audiences.
Organized by MIT Technology Review since 1999, Innovators Under 35 has acknowledged some of the world&amp;rsquo;s brightest minds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces the first non-stop flight between Bali and Auckland that operates year-round</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced a new daily flight route connecting Dubai, UAE to Auckland, New Zealand, with a stop in Bali, Indonesia. This decision comes as a response to the growing popularity of Bali as a travel destination and aims to enhance connectivity options for travelers flying to New Zealand.
This addition brings the total number of daily Emirates flights to New Zealand to three. It complements the existing non-stop daily Airbus A380 service from Dubai to Auckland and another daily A380 service from Dubai to Christchurch, New Zealand, which includes a stopover in Sydney, Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmoney proudly displays impressive first-year results</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</guid><description>The remarkable first-year performance of Harmoney, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s sole peer-to-peer (P2P) lending platform, highlights a substantial unmet need for crowdfunded microloans.
Established on September 10, 2014, with NZ$100 million in committed capital from prominent institutions like Blue Elephant Capital Management and Heartland Bank, Harmoney has facilitated NZ$100 million in personal loans within its inaugural year. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid expansion has resulted in the creation of 65 new jobs across New Zealand, Australia, and Fiji, with plans underway for an Australian launch...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>