<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accelerator on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accelerator/</link><description>Recent content in Accelerator on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:18:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accelerator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Australian government, in collaboration with Microsoft and MassChallenge, aims to enhance the local startup ecosystem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</guid><description>The Australian government is investing A$280,000 to bring MassChallenge, a leading global startup accelerator, to Australia. The goal is to support the growth of local startups.
MassChallenge, in partnership with Microsoft Australia and the Australian government, will offer resources such as idea-pitching competitions, boot camps, and mentoring to strengthen the Australian startup ecosystem. As a non-profit, equity-free accelerator, MassChallenge provides promising startups with the opportunity to compete for millions of dollars in cash awards.</description></item><item><title>The fourth group of entrepreneurs successfully complete the eFounders Fellowship program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</guid><description>Thirty-eight entrepreneurs from Asia have successfully finished the fourth eFounders Fellowship program. This joint effort between the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) and Alibaba Business School equips entrepreneurs with valuable skills and encourages them to share their knowledge.
This initiative stems from a commitment made by Jack Ma, Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s founder and former Executive Chairman, as UNCTAD Special Adviser for Young Entrepreneurs and Small Business. This commitment aims to empower 1,000 entrepreneurs in developing countries over five years, creating leaders for inclusive and sustainable economic development through the digital economy.</description></item><item><title>HubSpot for Startups simplifies the onboarding process for new businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</guid><description>HubSpot, a company that provides marketing and sales technology, has launched a new program called HubSpot for Startups. This program is specifically designed to support startups that are working with accelerators, incubators, and entrepreneurial organizations.
The program aims to help these small businesses gain momentum in their marketing and sales efforts by offering a substantial 90% discount on HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s products. These products include tools for customer relationship management (CRM), sales, and marketing.</description></item><item><title>Fikra Labs aims to speed up innovation in the travel and tourism industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</guid><description>In February, during UAE Innovation Month, which promotes the country&amp;rsquo;s global innovation hub status and recognizes innovators, four Abu Dhabi groups are collaborating with Wamda, an entrepreneurship platform, to launch the Fikra Labs acceleration program. The partners, including the Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi, Miral Asset Management, Etihad Aviation Group, and Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company (ADNEC), with support from Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), aim to boost innovation and entrepreneurship in Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s travel and tourism industry.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud introduces the Create@Alibaba Cloud startup program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing branch of Alibaba Group, has launched its first international startup program, Create@Alibaba Cloud. The program was announced in Singapore, home to Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s international headquarters, which will also serve as the regional hub for the initiative.
Singapore was selected as the regional hub due to its strong ties and access to other ASEAN markets, such as Thailand, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The company explained that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s robust connectivity and reputation as Asia&amp;rsquo;s most entrepreneurial economy enable participating startups to easily connect within Singapore and expand into neighboring markets.</description></item></channel></rss>