<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Southeast on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/southeast/</link><description>Recent content in Southeast on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/southeast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%.</description></item><item><title>Bosch is advocating for an increase in the number of vehicles in Southeast Asia to be equipped with safety features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</guid><description> Road traffic deaths in ASEAN countries are estimated at 117,000 annually, with over half involving motorcycles.
 An increasing number of countries and territories, including Japan, Taiwan, and India, are making motorcycle antilock braking systems (ABS) mandatory for new motorcycles.
 Malaysia is the first and only ASEAN nation to require all new cars to have electronic stability control (ESC) as of 2018.
Bosch believes Southeast Asia can do more to enhance road safety.</description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is a region where digital marketing is effective</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</guid><description>Source: Adobe website.
Recent research from Adobe highlights the growing importance of mobile devices for marketers in Southeast Asia, emphasizing its effectiveness in customer interaction and engagement. This shift toward mobile-first business strategies is particularly prominent in the Asia Pacific region.
Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Digital Index &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Benchmark&amp;rdquo; for 2015 analyzed website performance across eight regions, including Southeast Asia. By comparing the top 20% of websites (&amp;ldquo;best of the best&amp;rdquo;) with the overall average across six key performance indicators, the research provides valuable insights into the strategies of high-performing digital marketing organizations.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices.</description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year.</description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art.</description></item></channel></rss>