<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intercontinental on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intercontinental/</link><description>Recent content in Intercontinental on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intercontinental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item></channel></rss>