<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Taipei on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taipei/</link><description>Recent content in Taipei on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/taipei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Miramar Hotel Group offer now available with Asia Miles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</guid><description>Source: Miramar Hotel Taipei website.
Miramar Hotel Group is now part of the Asia Miles rewards program. This means members can earn 250 Asia Miles for every qualifying stay at either the Miramar Garden Taipei or Miramar Hotel Hsinchu.
To earn miles, members should provide their membership number during booking and show their card upon arrival. Note that this offer applies to deluxe room reservations.
For reference, the Miramar Garden Taipei first opened its doors in 2006, followed by the Miramar Hotel Hsinchu in 2013.</description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers.</description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has added Fukuoka to its list of destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</guid><description>Cebu Pacific Air (CEB) initiated flights between Manila and Fukuoka on December 17th, adding a third weekly service to their existing routes in Japan. This marks their fourth destination in Japan, including direct flights from Manila to Osaka, Tokyo (Narita), and Nagoya, as well as flights from Cebu to Tokyo (Narita).
Japan is a top destination for travelers from the Philippines. Data from the Japan National Tourism Organization indicates a 44% increase in Filipino arrivals, reaching over 211,000 between January and October 2015, compared to the same period the previous year.</description></item></channel></rss>