<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Domains on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domains/</link><description>Recent content in Domains on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:45:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domains/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LDRF.com Domain Auction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ldrfcom-domain-auction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 17:45:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ldrfcom-domain-auction/</guid><description>The domain name LDRF.com was previously up for auction on SEDO, a global domain marketplace. While that auction concluded on January 12, 2016, SEDO offers many other domains. Explore their selection!
var _sedoq = _sedoq || {}; _sedoq.partnerid = &amp;lsquo;19315&amp;rsquo;; // enter your partner id _sedoq.locale = &amp;rsquo;en-us&amp;rsquo;; // language locale (en-us, en-uk, de-de, es-es, fr-fr, pt-br, zh-cn) (function() { var s = document.createElement( &amp;lsquo;script&amp;rsquo; ); s.type = &amp;rsquo;text/javascript&amp;rsquo;; s.async = true; s.</description></item><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry.</description></item><item><title>The Easy Way To Host Lots Of Domains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:44:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-easy-way-to-host-lots-of-domains/</guid><description>As more businesses establish an online presence, they&amp;rsquo;re discovering that a single domain name is often insufficient. Companies may desire individual domain names for each product line, and online marketers might create separate websites tailored to specific products or demographics. This then raises the question of how to host multiple domains effectively.
While purchasing separate hosting services for each domain is an option, it can become costly. This approach might be suitable for a limited number of domains, but it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for businesses with larger websites or multiple online presences.</description></item><item><title>1&amp;1 makes 1.99</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:20:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</guid><description>Choosing 1&amp;amp;1 for web hosting is like getting a steal of a deal. They&amp;rsquo;re a leading web hosting company, even internationally recognized, and their starting price is incredibly low at $1.99 per month for the first three months, then $3.99 monthly.
You might think this means low quality, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. This entry-level package is comparable to professional hosting services. Here&amp;rsquo;s what your $1.99 gets you: a free domain name (that you choose!</description></item><item><title>Save Elephants By Transferring Your Domain Names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-elephants-by-transferring-your-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 01:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-elephants-by-transferring-your-domain-names/</guid><description>This is a limited-time chance to save money on domain names and support a good cause.
Namecheap, a reputable domain and hosting provider, has a special offer today (August 15, 2014). Transfer your .com, .net, or .org domain to Namecheap for just $7.88 for the first year using the code SAVEDUMBO. This is a significantly lower price than most hosting companies.
Renewal prices are also competitive. For example, a .com domain renewal costs $10.</description></item></channel></rss>