<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coup on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coup/</link><description>Recent content in Coup on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd.</description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways releases statement regarding military coup in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has recommended that passengers on flight EY407 from Bangkok to Abu Dhabi be prepared to show their passports and tickets if asked by military personnel. This applies when traveling to Suvarnabhumi Airport during the curfew, which is in effect from 10:00 PM to 5:00 AM local time. The airline advises, &amp;ldquo;Guests are advised to allow extra time to reach the airport.&amp;rdquo;
Due to the suspension of public transportation starting at 9:00 PM local time and possible limited taxi services, Etihad suggests that hotel guests consider booking airport limousine services through their hotels.</description></item></channel></rss>