<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Du on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/du/</link><description>Recent content in Du on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/du/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users.</description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle.</description></item></channel></rss>