<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Crypto on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crypto/</link><description>Recent content in Crypto on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/crypto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There has been an increase in crypto giveaway scams</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. A screen capture from a fake YouTube video that appears to show Elon Musk.
Group-IB, a cybersecurity firm based in Singapore, has detected a significant surge in websites promoting cryptocurrency giveaway scams using fake YouTube live streams during the first half of 2022. These scams have become increasingly organized, evolving into a distinct market segment with various services supporting fraudulent activities.
The firm&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that while 63% of these new scam domains are registered with Russian registrars, they primarily target English and Spanish-speaking individuals interested in cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the BTSE Debit Card is to provide worldwide access to funds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-btse-debit-card-is-to-provide-worldwide-access-to-funds/</guid><description>Source: BTSE. The BTSE Debit Card.
There&amp;rsquo;s a new player in the crypto debit card arena. Accepted at over 53 million MasterCard merchants and compatible with over a million ATMs globally, the BTSE Debit Card sets itself apart by allowing users to fund it with various fiat and cryptocurrencies without needing a traditional bank account.
BTSE, a fintech company focused on financial freedom, designed this card to give users more control over their money.</description></item><item><title>Investors demonstrate trust in the cryptocurrency investment platform CoinMENA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-demonstrate-trust-in-the-cryptocurrency-investment-platform-coinmena/</guid><description>CoinMENA, a cryptocurrency exchange based in Bahrain, has successfully raised US$9.5 million in its initial seed funding round. Major investors included BECO Capital, Kenetic, Arab Bank Switzerland, and others.
Founded in early 2021 by Dina Saman, Talal Tabbaa, and Yazan Barghuthi, CoinMENA aimed to simplify and enhance the safety of cryptocurrency investments in the region. The platform is officially licensed by the Central Bank of Bahrain and has partnered with the Dubai World Trade Centre to establish a prominent blockchain and cryptocurrency hub in the UAE.</description></item></channel></rss>