<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iran on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iran/</link><description>Recent content in Iran on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:35:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iran/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Country Holidays is introducing new Signature Departures for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Luxury travel agency Country Holidays has launched new &amp;ldquo;Signature Departures&amp;rdquo; trips for discerning travelers based in Singapore. Established in 2011, Signature Departures offers a fresh approach to group travel, steering clear of crowded buses, generic hotels, large-scale dining, and tourist traps.
Theng Hwee Chang, Managing Director of Country Holidays, explains: &amp;ldquo;We created Signature Departures four years ago to address the increasing demand for more enriching group travel experiences that go beyond the ordinary.</description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice in Bank Refah Kargaran making a groundbreaking decision by allowing action for damages in relation to CFSP decisions regarding restrictive measures?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</guid><description>Professor Dr. Peter Van Elsuwege and Joyce De Coninck (PhD Researcher), Ghent European Law Institute
The recent Grand Chamber judgment in the case of Bank Refah Kargaran v Council, issued on October 6, 2020, sheds further light on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) jurisdiction concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Drawing on previous judgments such as Elitaliana, H v. Council, Rosneft, and SatCen vs.</description></item></channel></rss>