<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SOHO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soho/</link><description>Recent content in SOHO on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soho/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ESET introduces security solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a company that provides proactive digital protection, has launched two new security products: ESET Multi-Device Security Home Office and ESET Small Office Security. These products are designed for small office/home office (SOHO) users.
&amp;ldquo;Cybercriminals often target small and home offices because they assume these businesses lack strong security measures,&amp;rdquo; said Andrew Lee, CEO of ESET North America. &amp;ldquo;There are 28 million businesses in this sector, and they need security solutions tailored to their unique needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Super Cheap Business Phone Service for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the economy slowly recovers, controlling business expenses, including phone bills, remains crucial. Many businesses find themselves overspending on phone services.
Businesses often begin with a single traditional phone line. As they expand, they might add cordless phones sharing that line or install a second line. While sufficient for small offices, this setup lacks the features and cost savings of PBX or enterprise VoIP systems.
Fortunately, small businesses can utilize network voice solutions, also known as VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), to reduce phone costs significantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>