<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Southeast Asia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/southeast-asia/</link><description>Recent content in Southeast Asia on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/southeast-asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Economic Community has the potential to be a goldmine for B2C businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, has published a white paper outlining a strategic framework for marketing to ASEAN consumers.
The establishment of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) in December 2015 will unify the ten ASEAN member states into a single market and production hub. This development is anticipated to draw significant attention from multinational corporations that have traditionally focused on China and India. Euromonitor suggests that the AEC is on track to become a global economic powerhouse due to its projected robust economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-economic-community-has-the-potential-to-be-a-goldmine-for-b2c-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov is tracking the impact of the haze</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</guid><description>Southeast Asia faced significant haze this year, mainly due to regional forest fires. A YouGov survey reveals a high level of awareness about this issue within the region.
Nearly 80% of Asian respondents are aware of the haze originating from Indonesian landscape fires. This awareness is lower in Hong Kong (48%) and Mainland China (44%). However, in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Singapore, the three countries most affected, only 2% of respondents in each country reported being unaware of the haze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia's unique focus on talent management sets it apart as a hub for talented individuals in the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 12:51:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/</guid><description>PageUp People, a global talent management solutions company, has introduced &amp;ldquo;Talented Southeast Asia,&amp;rdquo; a publication dedicated to talent management in Southeast Asia. The book tackles significant challenges and future trends for employers, drawing from insights gathered from over 100 interviews with business and HR leaders over a year.
Sylvia Vorhauser-Smith, PageUp People’s Senior Vice President of Global Research and co-author, highlights the region&amp;rsquo;s distinct characteristics and the varying approaches to talent management...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-s-unique-focus-on-talent-management-sets-it-apart-as-a-hub-for-talented-individuals-in-the-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Innovators under 35 in Singapore are looking for applicants from Southeast Asia and Australia/New Zealand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</guid><description>EmTech Singapore is searching for ten innovative individuals under 35 from Southeast Asia, Australia, and New Zealand. These individuals should embody innovation in business and technology and will be featured in the Innovators Under 35 Singapore competition. The competition seeks those responsible for significant advancements, innovations, and impactful contributions to their target audiences.
Organized by MIT Technology Review since 1999, Innovators Under 35 has acknowledged some of the world&amp;rsquo;s brightest minds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The last adidas Originals = PHARRELL WILLIAMS collection of 2014 will be released on November 28th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</guid><description>The last adidas Originals and Pharrell Williams collaboration of 2014 features a playful use of polka dots. More releases are planned for 2015. The bold and cheerful polka dot motif symbolizes energy and happiness.
Source: adidas Originals. The Polka Dot Pack includes Stan Smith sneakers.
Launching in Southeast Asia on November 28th, the Polka Dot Pack features leather Stan Smith sneakers. This collection embodies the profound joy of love. The youthful and optimistic designs aim for a relatable and authentic feel, representing the collaboration&amp;rsquo;s core value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>