<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Start on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/project-start/</link><description>Recent content in Project Start on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/project-start/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Beogram 4002 Bonanza!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:24:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</guid><description>We seem to be inundated with Beogram 400x turntable restorations.
Beolover is occupied with multiple projects, and I have two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 projects that I began examining back in February of 2020. In those previous posts, I had sent four Beogram 400x platter motors to Beolover for his restoration expertise. He has since completed those motors, and they are now back in my possession, ready to be used.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Second Unit From Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</guid><description>A few weeks back, I completed the first of two Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable restorations for a client in Houston. I&amp;rsquo;m now starting work on the second one. Both turntable platters had their motors removed before being sent to Beolover for refurbishment. He has since finished these and documented the process on his blog.
I believe that refurbishing the platter motor is an essential step in any Beogram 400x restoration project.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Floating Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 18:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</guid><description>This short post will illustrate an intriguing difference in the suspension systems of two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntables.
The first Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1312615, used a stack of concave washers to secure the floating suspension to the top plate. These washers were also present on the bottom lock.
The second Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1311076, features a slightly different suspension mechanism. This earlier production model employs a single, concave metal piece between the suspension lock and the top plate.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Initial Assessment of the Second One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-second-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 07:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-second-one/</guid><description>This is the second Beomaster 1900 receiver that needs restoration.
Similar to the first receiver, I started by inspecting the indicator lamps when powered on.
[Images of indicator lamps]
All the indicator lamps on this Beomaster are working.
Cosmetically, it&amp;rsquo;s missing the cabinet feet, a common issue with these models.
[Image of missing cabinet feet]
The control panel lid&amp;rsquo;s rubber bumpers have degraded.
[Image of deteriorated lid bumpers]
The cabinet trim veneer isn&amp;rsquo;t peeling, but the finish is quite dull.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Initial Assessment of the First One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-first-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 07:55:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-initial-assessment-of-the-first-one/</guid><description>After a short break from posting on the Beolover Blog, I&amp;rsquo;m starting a new restoration project. An owner sent me two Beomaster 1900 receivers, which I completely understand as a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen collector who owns multiple units of the same component.
Both Beomaster 1900 units appear to be in good cosmetic condition.
Let&amp;rsquo;s begin with the first one.
As previously mentioned, the Beomaster 1900&amp;rsquo;s exterior looks quite good. However, there are a few common issues present.</description></item></channel></rss>