<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Traveller's Choice on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/travellers-choice/</link><description>Recent content in Traveller's Choice on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/travellers-choice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Three of the top 25 hotels in the world, as listed by TripAdvisor, are located in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</guid><description>TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Choice awards highlights 25 diverse hotels worldwide. Notably, three hotels from Asia secured spots within the top 10. Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s The Upper House claimed the second position, while India&amp;rsquo;s Oberoi Udaivilas and Oberoi Mumbai ranked fifth and ninth, respectively.
The Upper House, nestled in Pacific Place, holds the top spot among hotels in Hong Kong. One reviewer praised it as their &amp;ldquo;best hotel experience,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing its flawlessness. A remarkable 97% of the reviews for this hotel are positive.</description></item></channel></rss>