<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telco on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telco/</link><description>Recent content in Telco on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circles.Life introduces a range of new services centered around unlimited usage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 07:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</guid><description>For S$3, enjoy unlimited on-demand data at 4G+ speeds.
For the first time, get unlimited WhatsApp roaming in 18 countries for S$1 per day.
Source: Circles.Life. Poster for Unlimited
Data on Demand. Circles.Life, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fourth mobile operator, argues that the current unlimited data plans are actually quite restrictive. They believe that these plans should not be limited to weekends, slowed down after a small data limit, or tied to yearly contracts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circles-life-introduces-a-range-of-new-services-centered-around-unlimited-usage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>du offers corporate mobile plans for SMEs in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Du offers five corporate mobile plans designed for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These plans include data and free calls to colleagues within the business.
Ranging from AED 50 to AED 450 per month, the plans provide data, national calling minutes, national text messages, and free calls to numbers within a designated &amp;lsquo;business calling circle&amp;rsquo;. Three of the plans also include free international minutes and texts. Businesses can purchase additional &amp;lsquo;packs&amp;rsquo; to add more minutes, texts, or members to their calling circle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/du-offers-corporate-mobile-plans-for-smes-in-the-uae/</a></p></description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>