<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wobbly on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wobbly/</link><description>Recent content in Wobbly on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wobbly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Aluminum Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all spring terminals in the switches, this Beogram 4000 received another upgrade: a replacement for the old, unstable plastic carriage pulley, now made from aluminum. The original pulley is shown below:
And here it is equipped with one of Nick&amp;rsquo;s well-crafted aluminum pulleys:
Contact me if you need a pulley for your Beogram; I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to connect you with Nick. These pulleys are compatible with the 4002 and 4004 models as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Pulley, Hood Bumpers and Shipping Back to Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 14:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-pulley-hood-bumpers-and-shipping-back-to-italy/</guid><description>A Beolover always aims for perfection, and I realized my restoration of the Beogram 4000 wasn&amp;rsquo;t quite finished. Working on a Beogram 8000 reminded me of the importance of rubber hood bumpers for a smooth, quiet closing action. I discovered these bumpers were missing on the Beogram 4000, leaving only remnants of degraded rubber.
To fix this, I carefully removed the old rubber with a small drill bit by hand, avoiding any damage to the plexiglass.</description></item></channel></rss>