<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Makeup on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/makeup/</link><description>Recent content in Makeup on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/makeup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Check out Shopee Malaysia's Christmas gift ideas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, offers a convenient way to shop for Christmas.
Here are some gift ideas available in Malaysia:
Stay Connected
[Image of PINENG PN966 power bank]
This power bank, available in blue and green, ensures you stay connected all day.
[Buy now]
Capture the Moment
[Image of OPPO F1s phone]
The OPPO F1s, dubbed &amp;ldquo;The Selfie Expert,&amp;rdquo; boasts a 5.5&amp;quot; display with 1,280 x 720 pixels resolution, a 13-megapixel rear camera, and a 16-megapixel front camera.</description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals, a brand that is committed to being cruelty-free, has launched a new range of eyeshadows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</guid><description>Everyday Minerals (EM) prioritizes using the purest natural ingredients to create all-natural, vegan, and cruelty-free makeup. Their products are handmade in Texas and packaged in eco-friendly, recyclable materials.
Source: Everyday Minerals blog.
Vegan makeup is characterized by its exclusion of animal-derived ingredients and its non-reliance on animal testing. Ingredients like lanolin and collagen are examples of animal-derived components. A growing number of cosmetics companies are introducing vegan product lines or, like EM, adopting a fully vegan approach.</description></item><item><title>Bourjois eyeshadows are available in matte, pearl, and shimmer finishes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bourjois-eyeshadows-are-available-in-matte-pearl-and-shimmer-finishes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bourjois-eyeshadows-are-available-in-matte-pearl-and-shimmer-finishes/</guid><description>Launched in 1912, Bourjois makeup is recognized for its signature small round compacts. The brand&amp;rsquo;s newest eyeshadows come in these iconic compacts and are offered in a range of matte, pearl, and shimmer finishes.
The eight new eyeshadows glide onto eyelids smoothly when applied dry. If applied damp, the eyeshadows can be used to create precise lines, similar to eyeliner.
01 INGENUDE
This shade is a delicate, slightly pearly off-white. It can be used to even out the look of eyelids.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals introduces a new line of mineral color correctors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</guid><description>Source: Everyday Minerals website.
Everyday Minerals claims to have formulated its finest mineral color correctors to date. These all-natural correctors feature jojoba esters, enabling them to conceal imperfections seamlessly without appearing heavy.
The new Jojoba Color Correctors are offered in four shades, each formulated for a specific purpose. The pink-hued Brighten Color Corrector utilizes light-diffusing pigments to instantly illuminate dark circles under the eyes. The Cover Color Corrector, in a natural skin tone, can be used after foundation for concealing blemishes.</description></item><item><title>Arbonne is launching new product collections that are based on botanical ingredients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arbonne-is-launching-new-product-collections-that-are-based-on-botanical-ingredients/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 04:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arbonne-is-launching-new-product-collections-that-are-based-on-botanical-ingredients/</guid><description>Arbonne International, a Swiss company known for its botanically-based personal care and wellness products, has introduced three new collections.
Arbonne Intelligence Nourishing Facial Oil This light, dry oil is formulated with omega-3 and omega-6 fatty acids and potent antioxidants for radiant skin. The oil delivers exceptional hydration and acts as a nourishing &amp;ldquo;superfood&amp;rdquo; for your skin.
RE9 Advanced for Men Set This comprehensive men&amp;rsquo;s skincare line features a Micro-Exfoliating Cleanser, Shave Cream, After-Shave Soothing Lotion, Anti-Aging Moisturizer with SPF 15, and Eye Repair Cream.</description></item><item><title>15 beauty tips for 2015 to celebrate the 15th anniversary of Giorgio Armani Beauty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-beauty-tips-for-2015-to-celebrate-the-15th-anniversary-of-giorgio-armani-beauty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 12:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-beauty-tips-for-2015-to-celebrate-the-15th-anniversary-of-giorgio-armani-beauty/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oreal.
Giorgio Armani Beauty is commemorating the 15th anniversary of its makeup line with a series of 15 instructional videos. Released periodically throughout the year, these short clips will feature Linda Cantello, Giorgio Armani&amp;rsquo;s International Make-Up Artist, sharing simple makeup techniques and expert advice.
While the professional tips are specifically tailored for Armani products, the company asserts that anyone can easily understand and implement them.
Curious? Check out the videos:</description></item></channel></rss>