<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article 10 ECHR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-10-echr/</link><description>Recent content in Article 10 ECHR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-10-echr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the Big Brother Watch case: part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
(These observations on the judgment follow part 1 of the analysis, which explained the Court’s reasoning).
The Big Brother Watch judgment can be interpreted in two ways: as confirmation that mass surveillance is permissible (para 314) or as an acknowledgment that the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act (RIPA) framework was inadequate. This implies that the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), which inherited some of RIPA&amp;rsquo;s shortcomings, is also lacking.</description></item><item><title>Balancing religious tolerance with freedom of expression in ECHR case law: Is there a right to insult?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights has reignited the debate about whether freedom of speech should have limitations, particularly when it comes to potentially offensive remarks targeting religious beliefs, such as those of the Muslim faith. This presents an opportunity to analyze the case&amp;rsquo;s background and determine what, if any, restrictions on free speech are justifiable in such instances.</description></item><item><title>Halet vs. Luxembourg: The Triumph of the Overlooked Champions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/halet-vs-luxembourg-the-triumph-of-the-overlooked-champions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/halet-vs-luxembourg-the-triumph-of-the-overlooked-champions/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kafteranis* and Stelios Andreadakis**
Photo credit: CherryX, via Wikimedia Commons
*Assistant Professor in Law, Centre for Financial and Corporate Integrity, Coventry University
** Reader in Corporate and Financial Law, Brunel University London
The recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) Grand Chamber in the case of Halet v. Luxembourg signifies a win for whistleblower rights and freedom of expression. This decision concludes a decade-long legal struggle for Raphael Halet, overturning prior judgments by the Luxembourg Court of Appeal and the ECtHR&amp;rsquo;s Third Chamber.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US.</description></item></channel></rss>