<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pacific on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pacific/</link><description>Recent content in Pacific on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pacific/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BenQ introduces new digital signage, projectors, and interactive flat panels, creating a buzz</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</guid><description>BenQ, a leading provider of visual display technology, has introduced a range of new projectors, digital signage, and interactive flat panels, all emphasizing high quality and innovative design. The company highlighted its commitment to delivering excellent visual experiences across various sectors, including business, retail, and food &amp;amp; beverage.
Business The MX666+ projector.
The MX666+ is the first wireless business projector to feature Near Field Communication (NFC) technology and USB connectivity, making it ideal for bring-your-own-device environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globetrekker Challenge creates a wellness portal for Garmin in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Globetrekker Challenge, a Singapore-based corporate wellness software company, will provide their corporate wellness platform to Garmin for distribution across Asia and the Pacific. This collaboration leverages each company&amp;rsquo;s strengths, allowing them to focus on their core offerings.
Globetrekker&amp;rsquo;s platform offers customizable wellness programs, real-time analytics reporting, and health risk profiling for employers. Through this partnership, Garmin&amp;rsquo;s clients can access these features and integrate them with Garmin&amp;rsquo;s wearable devices, creating a comprehensive employee health improvement solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bankers in the APAC region predict a decrease in M&amp;A activity under President Trump's administration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</guid><description>A recent survey of 300 Asia Pacific mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) professionals conducted by Intralinks, a secure platform used by dealmakers for content sharing, found that 75% of respondents believe a potential presidency under Donald Trump would negatively impact M&amp;amp;A activity in the region. This mirrors the global sentiment revealed by Intralinks&amp;rsquo; survey of 1,500 M&amp;amp;A professionals worldwide.
Intralinks&amp;rsquo; Global M&amp;amp;A Sentiment Survey shows 75% of Asian dealmakers consider Trump the most detrimental presidential candidate for M&amp;amp;A activity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Compass Index indicates a positive business outlook in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Despite a global economic downturn, the Compass Index shows optimism in the Asia Pacific (APAC) business sector, with Australian businesses reporting the highest confidence levels. However, the Index emphasizes that maintaining growth requires agility and innovation in business practices.
Source: Compass Index infographic. Australia is particular optimistic on business growth. Compass Offices, a provider of Asian serviced offices, virtual offices, and meeting rooms, surveyed their global clientele for the Compass Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC experienced a 12.3% increase in new company registrations in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</guid><description>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC), a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, demonstrated strong performance across all financial sectors in 2014. These sectors include banking, insurance, leasing, wealth management, and Islamic finance, with a 12.3% rise in new company registrations compared to the previous year.
The organization highlights that 70% of companies registered in Labuan IBFC come from Asia, with 57% from Southeast Asia, particularly Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JLL reports that tech startups are a significant driver of real estate demand in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>New types of office users are emerging in the form of startups, with more tech companies exploring unconventional spaces such as coworking facilities and industrial properties, according to JLL, a real estate and investment management firm.
The technology sector in the Asia Pacific region has experienced significant growth, driven by mobile technology, e-commerce, and the rise of fintech. This growth has fueled demand for both traditional office spaces and business parks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 5-Min Video Challenge has been introduced by the Singtel Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</guid><description>Source: The 5-Min Video Challenge website. Invitation to enter the local rounds.
Singtel Group launched The 5-Min Video Challenge to promote creative content across its global markets. The competition is a collaborative effort among Singtel&amp;rsquo;s associates, including Optus, AIS, Airtel, Globe, and Telkomsel. Winning videos will be shared with over 600 million customers within the Singtel Group.
Content creation is a key element of the Group&amp;rsquo;s strategy for customer engagement in a world where mobile devices are everywhere and demand for online video entertainment is high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks Teavana is now offered in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 06:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Starbucks has launched Starbucks Teavana, its line of handcrafted tea drinks and whole leaf tea sachets, in over 6,200 stores across 16 markets in the China and Asia Pacific region. This marks the global availability of Starbucks Teavana. Starbucks Teavana offers unique, layered flavor experiences in both iced and hot formats.
John Culver, Group President of Starbucks Global Retail, highlighted the growing consumer demand for new and unique taste experiences and positioned the Teavana launch as a way to leverage Starbucks&amp;rsquo; expertise in crafting beverages and sourcing premium ingredients to become a leader in the tea category...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has added Fukuoka to its list of destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</guid><description>Cebu Pacific Air (CEB) initiated flights between Manila and Fukuoka on December 17th, adding a third weekly service to their existing routes in Japan. This marks their fourth destination in Japan, including direct flights from Manila to Osaka, Tokyo (Narita), and Nagoya, as well as flights from Cebu to Tokyo (Narita).
Japan is a top destination for travelers from the Philippines. Data from the Japan National Tourism Organization indicates a 44% increase in Filipino arrivals, reaching over 211,000 between January and October 2015, compared to the same period the previous year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotdesk and Compass provide short-term workspace solutions in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Hotdesk, a platform for finding temporary office space, has teamed up with Compass Offices to provide on-demand workspaces and meeting rooms for professionals on the move. These spaces can be reserved for various durations, including daily, weekly, or monthly.
Studies from IDC indicate that by 2015, there will be a significant increase in the number of mobile workers globally, with over 1.3 billion individuals adopting this work style. Notably, the Asia Pacific region is projected to have the highest concentration, with over 838 million mobile workers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>