<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Full Duplex on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/full-duplex/</link><description>Recent content in Full Duplex on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:04:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/full-duplex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Is The Real T1 Line Speed?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-real-t1-line-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-real-t1-line-speed/</guid><description>A T1 line is often described as a 1.5 Mbps dedicated bandwidth connection, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually a bit more nuanced than that. The true speed is 1.544 Mbps, with a usable payload of 1.536 Mbps.
The reason for this difference lies in the T1 line&amp;rsquo;s structure and history. Developed by Bell Labs for telephone companies in the 1950s, T1 lines aimed to improve upon the limitations of analog systems. While utilizing existing copper wiring, T1 lines transmit digital signals, unlike the analog signals used in older phone systems.</description></item><item><title>USB 3.0 Offers Gbps Data Transfers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</guid><description>The arrival of USB 2.0 as a replacement for 1.1 nearly achieved the universal connectivity goal of its name. With a tenfold speed increase, USB 3.0, or &amp;ldquo;SuperSpeed,&amp;rdquo; aims to further solidify USB&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
While the existing 480 Mbps speed of USB 2.0 serves many devices well, surpassing the original USB 1.0&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 to 12 Mbps, the need for faster data transfer, especially for video, is evident. This need prompted the shift from FireWire to mini-USB in most video cameras.</description></item><item><title>20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>If you need a significant bandwidth upgrade but find traditional options limited or excessively expensive, consider 20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper (EoC). This technology delivers a symmetrical 20 Mbps upload and download speed over readily available twisted pair copper cable.
This professional-grade service provides dedicated, full-duplex bandwidth, allowing simultaneous uploads and downloads at maximum speed. In contrast, T1 lines offer a base speed of 1.5 Mbps and require bonding multiple lines to achieve higher bandwidth, becoming cost-prohibitive beyond 10-12 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item></channel></rss>