<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2020 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2020/</link><description>Recent content in 2020 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap provides insights on the metal rat year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-provides-insights-on-the-metal-rat-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-provides-insights-on-the-metal-rat-year/</guid><description>Thriving in the Year of the Metal Rat: A Guide by Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap [Image of a golden rat with the caption &amp;ldquo;Year of the Metal Rat feng shui advice 2020&amp;rdquo;]
Source: The Joey Yap Group. Dato&amp;rsquo; Yap.
Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap, renowned expert in Chinese Metaphysics and founder of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics, has created a comprehensive guide for navigating the year of the rat. This resource, Everything About The Year of The Metal Rat 2020 All In One Place, is available on his portal.</description></item><item><title>Singtel has declared the champions of Season 1 for the PVP Esports Corporate Championship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</guid><description>Teams from Singapore and Indonesia emerged victorious in the corporate category of Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 2020 PVP Esports Community Championships (Season 1).
Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s team, DeloitteOne, and DBS&amp;rsquo;s team, TurretHeist, secured the top spots in the Dota 2 and Mobile Legends: Bang Bang Corporate Championships, respectively. The Indonesian team, HZL Legion (RM Djamiah Putra), claimed victory in PlayerUnknown&amp;rsquo;s Battlegrounds (PUBG): Mobile.
Each winning team received over S$5,000 in cash and prizes. The grand finals, held online from September 5th to 6th due to the COVID-19 pandemic, saw teams competing remotely.</description></item><item><title>The Stevie Awards for Women in Business welcome participants and organizations from all around the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</guid><description>The Stevie Awards, a leading business awards organization, is accepting entries for the 2020 Stevie Awards for Women in Business. This global competition is open to all female entrepreneurs, executives, and employees, as well as the organizations they lead.
The Stevie Awards recognize exceptional workplace achievements worldwide across various organizations. The Stevie Awards for Women in Business specifically honor the accomplishments of working women in over 100 categories, such as Entrepreneur of the Year, Executive of the Year, and Innovator of the Year.</description></item><item><title>Azerai reveals special promotions for Chinese New Year in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</guid><description>Source: Azerai. Exterior, Hue. Constructed in 1930 as the residence of the French Resident Superieure, this colonial mansion forms the hotel&amp;rsquo;s heart. The mansion&amp;rsquo;s noticeable facade, characterized by its elongated horizontal lines and nautical motifs, is a testament to Art Deco architectural style. Its two harmonious wings, home to a vast tropical garden and a saltwater pool, were constructed in 2005, reflecting a modern take on Art Deco.
Azerai has unveiled special offers and activities for Chinese New Year at its Vietnamese properties.</description></item><item><title>Quick guide for Chinese New Year in the year of the rat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</guid><description>The rat is associated with a new 12-year cycle in the Chinese zodiac. Legend has it that a race among all the animals determined which twelve would be featured in the zodiac. The animals finished in the following order: rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon, snake, horse, goat, monkey, rooster, dog, and pig. This sequence dictates the order of the animals in the zodiac.
The rat is generally agreed to be very clever.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race.</description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is preparing for Chinese New Year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Source: The Sanya EDITION.
In anticipation of the Chinese New Year, The Sanya EDITION presents two unique offerings that provide a genuine experience of Chinese culture.
Guests can immerse themselves in culture and history through The Sanya EDITION&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with the Forbidden City. This partnership features a temporary shop and exhibit highlighting fine arts and teas. Those with a passion for cuisine will enjoy the luxurious interpretations of Chinese dishes prepared by world-renowned Michelin-starred chefs, specially invited by The Sanya EDITION for the celebratory period.</description></item><item><title>The 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards are now accepting submissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</guid><description>Source: GCSA organizers. GCSA winners for 2019 at the GCSF in 2019.
If your company demonstrates a strong dedication to sustainability, we encourage you to apply for the 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards (GCSA).
The Alliance for Sustainable Development Goals (A•SDGs) is hosting the 2020 GCSA in collaboration with the Taiwan Academy of Corporate Sustainability (TACS), the Taiwan Institute for Sustainable Energy (TAISE), and the Center for Corporate Sustainability (CCS).</description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%).</description></item><item><title>2020 Christmas Gift Guide: Must-Have Gadgets for the Holiday Season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>As the year ends, it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to treat yourself. Check out these gadgets for relaxation and maybe even work:
OPPO Find X2 Pro smartphone
The OPPO Find X2 Pro blends technology and elegant design. Marketed as &amp;ldquo;a cinema in your hand,&amp;rdquo; it boasts a 120 Hz QHD+ Ultra Vision screen with exceptional resolution, color, refresh rate, and brightness. Enjoy immersive audio and video with its powerful dual speakers and Dolby Atmos.</description></item><item><title>Entries are now being accepted for the inaugural HUAWEI Film Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</guid><description>Filmmakers in the Asia Pacific region can win prizes for films made on Huawei smartphones.
The top prize includes $20,000 and a trip to Bangkok for the awards ceremony.
An event in Singapore on December 21 will showcase a film by local director Boris Boo.
Source: Huawei. Poster for the HFA.
Huawei has launched its first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), in the Asia Pacific region. The competition aims to encourage filmmakers and content creators to use Huawei smartphones to demonstrate their creativity.</description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs.</description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be expanding in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</guid><description>A Nestle Sjora mural was a key feature at the Nestle booth during Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia 2018.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), the largest biennial trade show in the region for food and hospitality, will be split into two separate shows starting in 2020. FHA-HoReCa will take place in early March, and FHA-Food &amp;amp; Beverage will follow at the end of March.
This cake was on display at the Qingdao Kesong Food Company (KFI) booth.</description></item><item><title>Huawei joins Singaporeans in celebrating National Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 01:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/</guid><description>In honor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 55th birthday, Huawei collaborated with five local photographers: Bryan van der Beek, Don Lee, Junaidi Lim, Zipeng Lee, and Jovanne Amolat. These photographers used the HUAWEI P40 Series smartphones to capture the spirit of Singapore by showcasing unique perspectives on everyday scenes.
Fresh Perspectives of the Familiar
Through thoughtful composition and utilizing the depth of field capabilities of the HUAWEI P40 Series, these photos provide a fresh perspective on common sights.</description></item><item><title>CEOs anticipate a deceleration in economic growth in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-anticipate-a-deceleration-in-economic-growth-in-2020/</guid><description>Global CEOs are expressing unprecedented pessimism regarding the economic outlook for 2020, according to PwC&amp;rsquo;s 23rd Annual Global CEO Survey. 53% of CEOs anticipate a decline in economic growth, a significant increase from 29% in 2019 and a stark contrast to the mere 5% who held this view in 2018. This marks the highest level of pessimism since the survey began in 2012, with only 22% of CEOs predicting economic growth in 2020, down from 42% in 2019.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Chinese New Year with Amazon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</guid><description>Preparing your office for Chinese New Year might be easier with a little help from Amazon.sg&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Chinese New Year store.
Finding the right gifts for clients is made simpler with choices like an abalone gift set, priced at S$310.80 for two 454g cans, or bird&amp;rsquo;s nest, available for S$39.90 for six jars. To help everyone in the office get into the spirit, festive treats are a must-have:
Source: Amazon. Snacks for the office for Chinese New Year.</description></item><item><title>Residents of Hong Kong can enjoy an additional complimentary night at New World Millennium Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</guid><description>The New World Millennium Hong Kong Hotel, a prominent five-star establishment situated on the Victoria Harbour waterfront in Tsim Sha Tsui East, is offering a special &amp;ldquo;1+1 Bonus Night&amp;rdquo; room package to Hong Kong residents. Until September 30th, residents booking a one-night stay can enjoy an additional night free of charge.
This promotion is exclusively available to Hong Kong residents and requires HKID verification upon check-in. By reserving a City View room or a higher category for a single night, guests will automatically receive a second night&amp;rsquo;s stay complimentary.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Office Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:04:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</guid><description>Stationery The Scenic Route 2021 calendar
Victoria McGrane, an illustrator and textile designer, collaborated with Rainforest Rescue, an organization dedicated to rainforest protection and restoration since 1999, to create a 2021 calendar. McGrane, the talent behind The Scenic Route brand, is known for her hand-illustrated designs and stationery that showcase the beauty of Australian nature. Her work has garnered attention and partnerships with prominent brands.
“Protecting and restoring Australia&amp;rsquo;s valuable rainforests is incredibly important to me, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that my illustrations and travel inspiration can contribute to safeguarding these ancient forests and their wildlife,” shared McGrane.</description></item><item><title>Is the trend for 2020 sustainable red packets?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 19:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Orange/bottle carrier (left) with sustainable
hongbaos middle and right.
For the year 2020, Singtel chose to prioritize sustainability with their red envelope (hongbao) design. Instead of traditional paper, they opted for a material derived from sugarcane stalks after juice extraction.
Two designs were created. The first displays the character 欣, signifying &amp;ldquo;happiness and prosperity&amp;rdquo;. The second features a Chinese couplet, 竞发无极添新彩, 欣荣丰盛增辉煌, translating to &amp;ldquo;delight, happiness, progress with superior competitive advantage, bursting with exciting changes and new opportunities&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>LG will be unveiling its 2020 laptops at CES 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:23:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</guid><description>Source: LG. The LG gram 14T90N in action.
LG&amp;rsquo;s 2020 gram laptops maintain their focus on lightweight, compact design and long battery life, with the added benefit of improved performance. This refreshed lineup boasts a sleek, minimalist aesthetic and enhanced features.
Leading LG&amp;rsquo;s new gram series are the LG gram 17 (model 17Z90N), LG gram 15 (model 15Z90N), LG gram 14 (model 14Z90N), and the 14&amp;quot; LG gram 2-in-1 (model 14T90N).</description></item><item><title>Improve your filmmaking abilities using a smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 05:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</guid><description>Boo (left) with Tan (right).
While using mobile phones for filmmaking only emerged around 2008, recent technological advancements have empowered many phone owners to become filmmakers.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), aim to raise awareness about this potential in the Asia Pacific region and cultivate local talent. Their latest phone, the HUAWEI Mate 30 Pro, boasts features like 4K video recording, ultra-wide angle lens, and ultra slow motion capabilities, making it a capable filmmaking tool.</description></item><item><title>The Emirates Literature Foundation introduces a new digital discussion series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</guid><description>The Emirates Literature Foundation has launched a new project, Literary Conversations Across Borders. This digital initiative aims to promote global cultural understanding by connecting Emirati writers and thinkers with internationally recognized experts for live discussions on significant issues.
The series commences on May 30, 2020, with Indian politician and writer Shashi Tharoor and HE Zaki Nusseibeh, UAE Minister of State for the Office of Cultural Diplomacy. They will examine how the events of 2020 will shape the future, both positively and negatively.</description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Xero thoroughly examines the effects of COVID-19 on small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 17:55:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</guid><description>Xero, a global platform for small businesses, has published two reports examining the economic and emotional effects of the COVID-19 pandemic on small businesses worldwide.
Source: Xero&amp;rsquo;s Emotional metrics: small business mindsets during the pandemic report. From January to August 2020, small business owners experienced a range of emotions, from feeling &amp;ldquo;worn down&amp;rdquo; to a sense of loss.
The Xero Small Business Insights (SBI) Special Report, Pandemic Insights: Small Business Experience, was created in collaboration with AlphaBeta (part of Accenture) and utilizes anonymized and aggregated data from over 300,000 Xero subscribers.</description></item><item><title>The top four visual trends for 2020 according to Adobe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</guid><description>Adobe has predicted the biggest visual trends for 2020, sharing four key themes brands should embrace in a recent blog post.
_Inclusivity for All Ages _
Marketing is moving away from solely youth-focused campaigns. Recognizing the influence and engagement of older demographics, brands are showcasing diverse, energetic individuals from various age groups.
_Authenticity in Expression _
Consumers are increasingly drawn to genuine representations of themselves and their experiences. This desire for authenticity extends to brands, public figures, and politicians, who are expected to reflect real life in their messaging.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Expo CNY Fair offers daily discounts of S$380 to the first 888 customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</guid><description>Red envelopes containing discounts, called angbaos, can be redeemed for certain products in addition to existing promotions (terms and conditions apply).
Items will be offered at up to 88% off.
The Singapore Expo CNY Fair will distribute complimentary lucky angbao gift packages, each valued at S$380, to the initial 888 attendees daily from January 10th to 12th. The event will be held at Singapore Expo Hall 6, open from 12 pm to 9 pm each day.</description></item></channel></rss>