<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Voice on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-voice/</link><description>Recent content in Network Voice on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-voice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does a VoIP Call Work?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</guid><description>VoIP is often called a network service, not a phone service, which matters for technical folks and business owners, but less so for everyday users. After all, a phone is a phone; you expect it to work the same way.
The aim with VoIP has been to closely replicate the experience of traditional landlines. Now that this is largely accomplished, the focus is shifting towards making VoIP calls sound even better than traditional calls, aiming for what&amp;rsquo;s called HD or high-definition voice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>To VoIP or Not to VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:39:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/</guid><description>Companies are constantly searching for ways to reduce expenses, especially during economic downturns. Phone bills are often a target for cost-cutting measures, as businesses seek to lower this expense without compromising value.
While achieving this might require careful consideration, the ideal solution depends on your specific requirements and existing infrastructure.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), frequently presented as an alternative phone service. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s more accurate to call it an alternative phone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/to-voip-or-not-to-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SOHO VoIP Phone Service With Two Lines at $8.33/mo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</guid><description>Looking for affordable business or home phone service with great features? Imagine paying just $8.33 a month for a two-line system! This incredible price is possible through VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol) technology, which uses your existing broadband connection for phone calls.
Competitive providers like Phone Power offer this technology at unbeatable rates. You don&amp;rsquo;t need special equipment—simply plug your existing phones into an adapter that allows two simultaneous calls. This means no more waiting for someone to hang up!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional ISDN PRI For Telephone Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</guid><description>ISDN PRI is a great option for businesses that need a robust phone system. It provides 23 digital lines with features like fast call switching and Caller ID on a single, cost-effective line. However, not all businesses need that many lines.
Smaller businesses or those with lower call volumes can opt for Fractional ISDN PRI, which offers the same features but with fewer lines. This option allows businesses to customize the number of lines they need, typically around 12, leading to significant cost savings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving Call Quality Momentum With Cloud Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 15:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated by your outdated in-house phone system? Perhaps you&amp;rsquo;ve had a negative experience with VoIP, finding it unreliable and offering poor call quality. It might be time to consider a modern cloud communication solution, such as one from Momentum.
If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with IP-based voice communication, you might not be aware of potential issues that can impact network voice systems, or the solutions that are simply inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-call-quality-momentum-with-cloud-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Puts Your Complete Office In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:47:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>You might be interested in cloud services, but the process of ordering and integrating them can be overwhelming. Now, a new solution offers a comprehensive bundle of IT services tailored for small businesses at an affordable price.
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
Small businesses often don&amp;rsquo;t need or can&amp;rsquo;t afford large-scale IT infrastructure. Expensive VoIP phone systems and on-site data centers are impractical for companies with limited staff and resources. While cost savings were previously linked to scale, hosted solutions have revolutionized this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>