<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Common Commercial Policy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-commercial-policy/</link><description>Recent content in Common Commercial Policy on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-commercial-policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and the trade relations between the European Union and the United Kingdom with other countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:46:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</guid><description>Some Brexit supporters have a relaxed view of European Union (EU) law. However, their assertions about trade after Brexit, specifically the notion that existing agreements would simply continue, require closer examination. They argue that global trade regulations would prevent the EU from hindering the UK&amp;rsquo;s trade relationships. This overlooks the possibility that, absent a transitional agreement, the UK&amp;rsquo;s participation in the World Trade Organisation (WTO) and other trade agreements could be at risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-the-trade-relations-between-the-european-union-and-the-united-kingdom-with-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The debate between free trade and freedom of association: Analyzing the EU/South Korea free trade agreement and the panel report regarding the EU's objection to South Korean labor laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
This post explores whether global trade liberalization through agreements like the World Trade Organization (WTO) and related free trade agreements promotes economic growth for all or widens the gap between rich and poor. It also examines if and how labor standards and environmental concerns should be considered in pursuing freer trade.
These concerns are increasingly debated in trade policy discussions, making some nations hesitant about new free trade deals or prompting calls to renegotiate existing ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-debate-between-free-trade-and-freedom-of-association-analyzing-the-eu-south-korea-free-trade-agreement-and-the-panel-report-regarding-the-eu-s-objection-to-south-korean-labor-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's upcoming trade policy is beginning to form with the release of the Opinion on the EU/Singapore FTA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s authority regarding trade agreements has been debated for years in the European Court of Justice (ECJ), as it significantly affects the balance of power between the EU and its Member States concerning international economic policies. Treaty revisions, especially the Treaty of Lisbon, have altered these rules, making this issue even more important due to recent controversies surrounding EU trade negotiations (notably with Canada and the USA) and the UK-EU trade talks post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ clarifies EU's authority over copyright law in the Marrakesh Treaty ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</guid><description>Gesa Kübek, PhD candidate at the law faculty of the University of Passau.
In its February 14, 2017 Opinion 3/15, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) determined that the European Union (EU) possesses exclusive competence to enter into the Marrakesh Treaty to Facilitate Access to Published Works for Persons Who Are Blind, Visually Impaired, or Otherwise Print Disabled (hereafter: Marrakesh Treaty). This decision aligns with Advocate General (AG) Wahl’s prior Opinion, which similarly argued for exclusive EU competence in this domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>