<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LED Replacement Lamp on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/led-replacement-lamp/</link><description>Recent content in LED Replacement Lamp on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:26:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/led-replacement-lamp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>Slow response times from the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control panel buttons pointed to potential oxidation on the keypad contacts. This was confirmed upon opening the keypad assembly, revealing dull key contacts.
The contact pads were unsoldered and removed for a closer look. While they seemed okay, the leaf contacts engaged by the actuators showed signs of oxidation.
To address the oxidation, a fiberglass brush and Deoxit were used, restoring the contacts to a shiny and clean condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Finishing Up The Tangential Arm Position Sensor &amp; The Fixed Arm Platter Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</guid><description>I was pleased to discover that Beolover successfully refurbished the platter motor for my Beogram 4002. During the packing process for the motor&amp;rsquo;s return, I took the opportunity to calibrate the voltage for two newly installed sensor lamps within the Beogram.
The recently added LED replacement light for the tangential arm position sensor was insufficiently bright. While it functioned, even at maximum output (with the 1R88, 25K ohm trimmer at its highest setting), the voltage measured at the 1TR17 base only reached 0.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Checking the Forward/Reverse Scanning LDR Devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-checking-the-forwardreverse-scanning-ldr-devices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-checking-the-forwardreverse-scanning-ldr-devices/</guid><description>My previous work on this Beogram left me concerned about a potential issue with one of the forward/reverse scanning LDRs (Light Dependent Resistors).
Testing the resistance of both LDRs with +15 VDC on the light source, I noticed a significant difference between them, leading me to believe one was faulty. However, upon removing and re-testing them, the resistance values were much closer.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that my testing method involved a simple setup with an LED work light as a light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Progress Update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</guid><description>The next stage of the restoration involved removing parts from the Beogram chassis. This was necessary to access the tangential arm for repairs and to thoroughly clean the disintegrated transport bushings.
Fragments of the old bushings were scattered throughout the chassis, even within the tonearm cover.
This image shows the Beogram chassis after a thorough cleaning.
Next, 3D-printed replacement bushings from Beolover were installed.
The new bushings fit perfectly. When reattaching the floating chassis, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to align the top and bottom locking washers on their respective threads.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some additions for a previous Beogram project from Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntable I previously restored in 2018 was returned for a sensor lamp replacement. This turntable had also visited in 2020 for a broken tonearm cartridge mount.
During both prior repairs, the owner opted to retain some original, functioning components, including the sensor lamp, tracking sensor lamp, and output phono muting switch. Since the sensor lamp has now burned out, it will be replaced with a modern Beolover LED assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 19:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>In addition to working on the tangential arm assembly, the RPM trimmer panel was also restored. Testing by Beolover has demonstrated that this upgrade reduces the heat affecting the platter motor control circuit and improves the motor&amp;rsquo;s stability.
The original trimmer assembly is shown here with its two original lamps.
The Beolover replacement LED lamp assemblies are designed to be connected to the same solder pads as the original lamps, eliminating the need for board modifications.</description></item></channel></rss>