<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Landlines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/landlines/</link><description>Recent content in Landlines on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:21:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/landlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>$8.33/mo Small Business &amp; Residential VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</guid><description>Forget expensive phone plans advertised on TV, there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for homes and small businesses. For just $8.33 a month, Phone Power offers unlimited calls within the US and Canada, plus a free hour of international calls.
This Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) service works with your existing internet connection. Phone Power provides a free adapter that connects to your modem and lets you use two phones on a single line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Capability To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 04:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of wireless phones allows mobile professionals to stay connected consistently. However, international calls remain a challenge due to expensive rates. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: international dial-around services.
These services, such as TEL3Advantage, seamlessly integrate with existing cell phone plans. Essentially, they allow users to make international calls at significantly reduced rates by routing them through the dial-around service instead of their regular carrier.
For example, TEL3Advantage offers a rate of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>866 Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 18:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>Everyone knows about 800 numbers; they were the original toll-free option. But did you know there are others, like 866? Is it truly toll-free?
Yes, 866 is indeed toll-free. It functions identically to 800; the difference is simply in the prefix. Just like area codes (202 for Washington, DC, 302 for Delaware), these prefixes are assigned nationwide.
This highlights a key difference: toll prefixes are location-specific (area codes), while toll-free prefixes are not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/866-toll-free-numbers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Visual Guide To Enterprise VoIP Justification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</guid><description>Thank you to MegaPath Broadband Service Providers for this interesting infographic.
Is your company missing out on the advantages of enterprise VoIP technology, which can potentially reduce costs and increase productivity? A variety of on-site and hosted options are available to accommodate businesses of all sizes. Explore business VoIP solutions and pricing from MegaPath and other providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>