<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Self-Employment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/self-employment/</link><description>Recent content in Self-Employment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/self-employment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finally, a Directive safeguarding platform work - What's next?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</guid><description>Catherine Jacqueson, Professor of EU law and Alberto Barrio, postdoctoral researcher on the WorkWel-project, Law Faculty, University of Copenhagen
Photo credit: conceptphoto.info, via Flickr On April 24th, the European Parliament officially approved the directive designed to protect platform workers. Although formal endorsement from the Council is still pending, this is largely a formality. The directive&amp;rsquo;s passage, despite the challenges and last-minute negotiations, signifies a victory. Initially, the Council presented resistance, making its unexpected adoption of the compromise agreement on March 11th surprising...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that self-employed workers are protected from discrimination, including on the basis of sexual orientation, under anti-discrimination and labor rights laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</guid><description>A Closer Look at Worker Protections: Analyzing the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in Case C-356/21 By Chiara De Capitani, linguist agent at the European Commission and PhD candidate and honorary fellow in European law at the University of Naples “L&amp;rsquo;Orientale”. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Photo credit: Silar, via Wikimedia Commons..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New mothers who are self-employed and the EU free movement law: the CJEU reaches the expected decision.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
* For further information on EU free movement law issues, refer to the upcoming second edition of the commentary on the EU Citizenship Directive, authored by Elspeth Guild, Steve Peers, and Jonathan Tomkin – available soon
A pertinent question arises when an EU citizen relocates to another Member State and gives birth: do new mothers risk losing their rights under EU free movement law?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-mothers-who-are-self-employed-and-the-eu-free-movement-law-the-cjeu-reaches-the-expected-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the gig economy protected by EU law? Conflicting opinions in the CJEU's legal decisions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/</guid><description>Dr Maria Tzanakopoulou, Teaching Fellow, King&amp;rsquo;s College London and University College London
BACKGROUND
The expanding gig economy is sparking debates about working conditions, including issues like working hours, pay, parental leave, and the crucial classification of gig workers. The case of King is the first time the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has ruled on business conduct and worker rights in this sector. The CJEU upheld the right of self-employed individuals to retain unused paid leave indefinitely and affirmed Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-gig-economy-protected-by-eu-law-conflicting-opinions-in-the-cjeu-s-legal-decisions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>$2 Toll Free Numbers Help Professionals Go Independent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s challenging economy, many skilled professionals are thinking about becoming independent and leaving traditional employment. While it&amp;rsquo;s a significant decision, resources are available to help with this transition. One such resource is an affordable toll-free service that provides the flexibility of working independently.
Individuals starting their own businesses often work from home offices and are frequently on the move, particularly those in service industries or consulting roles. This raises the question of how to maintain communication with clients and prospects regardless of location, using only a cell phone and laptop...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>