<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accounting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accounting/</link><description>Recent content in Accounting on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 19:05:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intuit Singapore is set to release a popular expense management application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 19:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</guid><description>Intuit, a leading provider of accounting software for small businesses worldwide, is getting ready to introduce QuickBooks Self-Employed in Singapore. This software helps users efficiently monitor their business expenditures. Launched in the US back in 2015, QuickBooks Self-Employed has gained significant traction, boasting a global customer base of 180,000, a considerable increase from 50,000 just a year ago, including users in Australia.
The QuickBooks Self-Employed mobile app, expected to be released later this month, aims to support the expanding freelance workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intuit-singapore-is-set-to-release-a-popular-expense-management-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xero creates cloud-based accounting software specifically tailored for business owners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 14:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/</guid><description>Fitzgerald.
Despite the significant benefits, small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs) are slow to embrace cloud computing.
Kevin Fitzgerald, FCCA, Regional Director for Asia at cloud accounting software provider Xero, noted that cloud adoption remains a hurdle, particularly in accounting. Speaking at the recent Accounting &amp;amp; Finance Show Asia 2018 in Singapore, Fitzgerald shared that Xero&amp;rsquo;s potential clients often express concerns about security and privacy.
He pointed out the irony, stating, &amp;ldquo;They don&amp;rsquo;t realize they are already in the cloud if they use a banking app or an email server...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-creates-cloud-based-accounting-software-specifically-tailored-for-business-owners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Readsoft Online version 9 has been released by Kofax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 01:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</guid><description>Kofax, a company that produces software to streamline and transform the initial stages of business operations, has introduced the 9th release of ReadSoft Online, a cloud-based solution for capturing and processing invoices.
ReadSoft Online provides small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) with a cost-effective and adaptable way to automate their accounts payable procedures. The solution captures invoices, extracts invoice data, and exports verified data to enterprise resource planning (ERP) systems, accounting software, and other applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/readsoft-online-version-9-has-been-released-by-kofax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Important Contribution of Small Business [Infographic]</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 23:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</guid><description>..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-important-contribution-of-small-business-infographic-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accounting solution in the cloud specifically created for individuals without accounting expertise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 03:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</guid><description>Asian Business Software Solutions (ABSS) has introduced Financio, a cloud-based accounting software designed for micro and small businesses in Singapore. This secure solution simplifies financial tracking without requiring accounting expertise.
Developed by ABSS and utilizing Microsoft Azure, Financio allows users to easily monitor sales, purchases, and other transactions through a user-friendly dashboard. It automates tasks like generating financial reports, tax records, and sending invoices, and enables seamless collaboration and document sharing through Financio Connect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>