<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EoC Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eoc-technology/</link><description>Recent content in EoC Technology on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eoc-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3x3 Mbps Ethernet Doubles Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t benefit from additional internet speed? Websites, software, and files continue to grow larger, but unfortunately, technology budgets haven&amp;rsquo;t kept pace. Imagine doubling your internet speed without increasing your current expenses – an appealing proposition, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
It might sound illogical to suggest that doubling your internet speed wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cost more, especially since internet providers aren&amp;rsquo;t known for giving things away for free. The secret lies in adopting newer, more cost-effective technology instead of simply replacing your existing service with an identical one from another provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>