<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GPS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gps/</link><description>Recent content in GPS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149.</description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones.</description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>Tile's tiles bring the Internet of Things to life, even without an internet connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tile-s-tiles-bring-the-internet-of-things-to-life-even-without-an-internet-connection/</guid><description>You may have heard of the Internet of Things, but dismissed it as irrelevant to you. However, consider the startup Tile, which aims to become a global &amp;ldquo;lost and found&amp;rdquo; system.
Tile isn&amp;rsquo;t about internet-connected refrigerators spamming people. Instead, it involves small, attachable devices that can be placed on keychains and other items to prevent them from getting lost.
[Image of Tile device]
Source: Tile website.
Technically, Tile devices don&amp;rsquo;t directly connect to the internet.</description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces three new fēnix 5 multisport GPS wearables</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-three-new-f-nix-5-multisport-gps-wearables/</guid><description>Source: Garmin. The fēnix 5 family of multisport GPS watches.
Garmin International has released the fēnix 5, fēnix 5S, and fēnix 5X multisport GPS watches. These wearables are designed for adventurers of all sizes.
Each fēnix 5 model offers 24/7 wearability, extended battery life, daily activity tracking*, Garmin Elevate wrist heart rate technology, and various connected features**. At 47mm, the fēnix 5 is more compact than past models like the fēnix 3HR, while still providing extensive multisport features.</description></item><item><title>The TomTom Golfer 2 GPS Watch is created to assist golfers in enhancing their game</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</guid><description>TomTom has introduced the TomTom Golfer 2, a slim GPS watch designed for golfers. The watch uses automatic shot detection to provide detailed analysis after a round, aiming to improve users&amp;rsquo; games.
The TomTom Golfer 2 eliminates uncertainty on the course by measuring distances to greens and hazards. This automatic shot detection helps golfers understand their distance potential by displaying distances for drives and approach shots at a glance. After the game, golfers can analyze their strokes in detail using TomTom MySports.</description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player.</description></item></channel></rss>