<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MPLS Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-network/</link><description>Recent content in MPLS Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone IP Communications offers Polished VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses usually don&amp;rsquo;t spend much effort on their telecommunication systems, often starting with basic necessities like desk phones, internet service, and maybe a simple VoIP system. It&amp;rsquo;s manageable for the owner or an office manager. However, as these businesses grow, their communication needs change. Suddenly, managing communication among numerous employees and locations becomes challenging. Reaching colleagues becomes difficult, and clients experience poor connection quality, leading to apologies. This situation calls for a &amp;ldquo;forklift upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Best VoIP Providers For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 14:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-voip-providers-for-business/</guid><description>Thinking about switching from traditional phone lines to VoIP, but unsure about its effectiveness? This guide provides insights and advice for a smooth transition.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, is also known as “network voice” because it operates on computer networks, unlike traditional phone systems. Essentially, voice becomes another service on your network, alongside data, video, and audio streaming. Each service transmits packets routed through the network.
This setup offers significant cost savings for larger businesses by consolidating telephone and data networks.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions.</description></item><item><title>Broadview Networks OfficeSuite Brings The Cloud To SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadview-networks-officesuite-brings-the-cloud-to-smb/</guid><description>Smaller companies often want to adopt money-saving technologies like VoIP, private networks, and cloud services, but the initial investment can be daunting. While internet-based options seem appealing, their quality and reliability are often a concern. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for businesses of all sizes to access these advanced tools without breaking the bank.
Broadview Networks&amp;rsquo; OfficeSuite offers a comprehensive solution, effectively serving as a company&amp;rsquo;s central office across multiple locations. This enterprise-grade PBX system provides the functionality of a traditional system with the convenience of easy administration through a web browser.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost.</description></item><item><title>Using T1 Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:54:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/using-t1-between-offices/</guid><description>T1 lines have diverse applications, including linking offices within a city or across the country. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how this is achieved and the available options.
The fundamental interoffice connection is a point-to-point T1 line, a circuit connecting two specific locations. It runs from one business site to the nearest telecom central office, then between central offices, and finally to the other location.
You might wonder why not directly connect locations with wires.</description></item><item><title>Insatiable Demand For Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>10 Gbps used to be a bandwidth amount so large that only major telecommunications companies needed it. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer true, as businesses are now using that much WAN bandwidth and wanting even more.
Beyond internet providers, who could need 10 Gbps? According to Carrier Ethernet News, the finance, streaming entertainment, and medical industries are leading the demand for high bandwidth. Some are even hoping for 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps!</description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added.</description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network.</description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions.</description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item></channel></rss>