<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtual Private Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Virtual Private Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-private-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Choose An MPLS VPN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Businesses need secure communication between their different locations. While private networks offer the highest level of security, they are expensive to build and maintain. Using the public internet is cheaper but raises security concerns.
A fully private network, offering top-notch security and performance, requires significant investment. Building a central hub and connecting each location with dedicated lines like T1 or Ethernet can become very costly, especially with increasing bandwidth demands and staffing for maintenance.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of SSL VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</guid><description>Cybersecurity is a significant concern for all internet users. With frequent news of hacking, data breaches, identity theft, and malicious bots, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that people are anxious about the security of their sensitive information, especially with the move towards cloud-based storage. This has led to a surge in interest in virtual private networks (VPNs).
Why would one choose a virtual private network over a traditional one?
The answer lies in our need for widespread connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Why International MPLS Connections Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 14:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple branches, even those with only two, are realizing the benefits of MPLS network services for domestic and global connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS offers, particularly for international connections, and why it&amp;rsquo;s a practical solution even for single-link setups.
Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS) is a network technology designed to carry data for numerous users while maintaining security, service quality, and crucial network attributes such as bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss.</description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems.</description></item><item><title>Telephone and Internet for Chain Stores</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</guid><description>Cost-conscious small businesses need reliable communication systems. They can&amp;rsquo;t risk losing customers due to failed credit card transactions or dropped calls. Businesses with multiple locations also need efficient ways to connect their operations. Integrated T1 offers a solution that addresses these needs while staying budget-friendly.
Integrated T1 merges voice and data services onto a single line, combining the reliability of T1 phone lines with the efficiency of T1 internet connections. This approach minimizes costs without sacrificing quality.</description></item></channel></rss>