<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HMH on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hmh/</link><description>Recent content in HMH on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hmh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coral Beirut Al Hamra now offers two additional Ambassador Suites as part of its room options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 18:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</guid><description>The Coral Beirut Al Hamra Hotel recently introduced a new suite category featuring expansive rooftop terraces with outdoor seating areas. Situated on the 11th floor, the 87 square meter Ambassador Suites offer fully equipped kitchens, large living rooms, and luxurious bathrooms, complete with high-end amenities.
Hartmut Grauel, General Manager of the hotel, stated that these new suites cater to the preferences of discerning travelers. He noted a consistent demand for spacious accommodations akin to full-size apartments, complete with kitchens and living rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-beirut-al-hamra-now-offers-two-additional-ambassador-suites-as-part-of-its-room-options/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>