<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international/</link><description>Recent content in International on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing the most rapid growth for SWIFT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</guid><description>SWIFT, a financial messaging service, has announced a significant increase in new corporate clients from the Asia Pacific region between May and December 2015, with 29 new companies joining the network.
SWIFT provides a unified platform for corporations to communicate financial information with their banks globally, leading to enhanced visibility and more efficient treasury operations. This connection allows for greater automation and standardization of financial processes. Currently, over 1,500 corporate groups, representing roughly 30,000 entities, utilize SWIFT to manage their banking relationships worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's International Enterprise (IE) and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to collaborate on connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</guid><description>International Enterprise (IE) Singapore, a government agency promoting international trade, and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have established a partnership to boost trade and international expansion for Singaporean companies. This agreement, solidified in a memorandum of understanding (MoU), marks IE Singapore’s first strategic partnership with a Singaporean bank.
The collaboration between IE Singapore and UOB aims to support 200 Singaporean companies in expanding overseas within the next three years. Their focus is primarily on Southeast Asia, China, Japan, and Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-international-enterprise-ie-and-united-overseas-bank-uob-have-signed-a-memorandum-of-understanding-mou-to-collaborate-on-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dabur Herb'l Sensitive Toothpaste is designed to combat tooth demineralization in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Dabur International.
Dabur International has introduced its new Herb’l Sensitive Toothpaste to the Middle East market. This toothpaste uses natural ingredients, including cinnamon, mint, licorice root, and potassium ions to quickly and effectively alleviate tooth sensitivity.
The company states that using this toothpaste twice daily will not only reduce sensitivity but also lead to healthier gums. It does this by preventing plaque buildup, gum inflammation, and cavities, all while freshening breath...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flickr Wall Art is now available worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 16:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</guid><description>Yahoo has expanded its Flickr wall art service to global markets, enabling businesses worldwide to adorn their walls with photographic artwork from Flickr artists.
Initially introduced in October, the Flickr Wall Art service allows the transformation of photographs from licensed artists within the Flickr Marketplace into high-quality wall prints available for purchase directly on Flickr.
The Flickr team has curated a collection of licensed photographs from popular categories such as abstract, landscapes, travel, and animals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flickr-wall-art-is-now-available-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sunway's Resort Cafe provides a range of dining options from breakfast to dinner, perfect for business meetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</guid><description>Source: Sunway.
The recently opened Resort Cafe, situated on the lobby level of the luxurious Sunway Resort Hotel and Spa, accommodates 362 guests and showcases the diverse culinary heritage of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Malay, Chinese, and Indian populations.
Spanning 17,588 square feet, the restaurant presents eight distinct culinary themes: the impressive Monumental Fruit and Salad Towers, Malay Archipelago (featuring dishes from Malaysia, Singapore, and Indonesia), Indo-Chine (showcasing cuisine from Thailand and Vietnam), Oriental Far East (highlighting dishes from Japan, Korea, and China), Spices of India, Mirage of the Gulf (offering dishes from the Middle East), Best from the West (featuring Western comfort food, grills, rotisserie, and churrasco), and a dedicated dessert section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>