<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Withdrawal Agreement Act on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/withdrawal-agreement-act/</link><description>Recent content in Withdrawal Agreement Act on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/withdrawal-agreement-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In what way can the courts enforce Part Two of the Withdrawal Agreement regarding citizens' rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</guid><description>Ensuring the Enforceability of EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Rights in the UK Post-Brexit Professor Tamara Hervey, Natalia Miernik and James C Murphy (UG students), University of Sheffield
Acknowledgement is given to the ESRC for its support of Health Governance after Brexit and UK in a Changing Europe.
1. Introduction
Approximately 3.6 million EU citizens and their families reside in the UK. A significant number, estimated to be over 185,000, contribute to the health and social care sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Allister Round 2: Exploring the depths of UK constitutional law in the Mariana Trench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD student, Queen’s University Belfast School of Law
Photo credit: Dom0803, via Wikicommons
Introduction
It&amp;rsquo;s a common observation in UK constitutional law that complex issues rarely have simple solutions. Instead, they often result in multiple, overlapping interpretations. This is certainly the case with the recent Allister and others v Prime Minister and others [2022] NICA 15 ruling from the Northern Ireland Court of Appeal (NICA). It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that this case is headed to the UK Supreme Court on appeal, ensuring further analysis and discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allister-round-2-exploring-the-depths-of-uk-constitutional-law-in-the-mariana-trench/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the Northern Ireland Protocol in question? Examination of the High Court ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:09:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</guid><description>Sarah Kay, human rights lawyer
Brexit has negatively impacted Northern Ireland, as was anticipated. Five years after the Brexit referendum, the High Court in Belfast issued a significant political decision regarding a legal challenge to the Northern Ireland Protocol. This challenge mirrors the Miller 1 case concerning Brexit&amp;rsquo;s constitutionality. Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s fragile political landscape, exacerbated by Brexit, has exposed existing systemic issues.
The legal challenge was brought forward by two main parties: Clifford Peeples, who opposed the Irish Sea border, and unionist members, including former First Minister Arlene Foster, who argued that the Protocol weakens Northern Ireland&amp;rsquo;s ties with Great Britain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-in-question-examination-of-the-high-court-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How can the issue of Suella be resolved? Exploring the legal implications of breaching and terminating the withdrawal agreement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent news suggests the UK may plan to violate the Brexit withdrawal agreement, with new Attorney-General Suella Braverman potentially seeking legal justification. This makes examining the repercussions of such a breach crucial. While the dispute resolution mechanisms within the agreement and the UK&amp;rsquo;s Withdrawal Agreement Act have been analyzed separately, this piece aims to provide a comprehensive overview, encompassing international law perspectives. This blog post summarizes the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution clauses and the international law principles concerning treaty termination, exploring their interplay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>