<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Server Colocation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/server-colocation/</link><description>Recent content in Server Colocation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/server-colocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Bandwidth is Cheap Downtown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</guid><description>Want to increase your business internet speed without breaking the bank? Head downtown! The city center offers more competition and cheaper prices than anywhere else. Can&amp;rsquo;t relocate for better bandwidth deals? There&amp;rsquo;s a comparable solution that works for many businesses.
Why is bandwidth cheaper downtown when real estate is so expensive? The answer is density. Imagine real estate as a pie: limited supply and high demand for the best slices drive up prices.</description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching.</description></item><item><title>TelePacific Takes Business Continuity Seriously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications, a telecommunications company serving California and Nevada, emphasizes a thorough approach to disaster preparedness and business continuity.
Their Business Continuity Services aim to keep your voice and data operational, even if a trunk line or your entire facility goes down. But how is this achieved?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with telephone service. Many businesses utilize digital trunk lines like T1 PRI and SIP Trunks, which offer cost savings compared to individual lines but pose a single point of failure risk.</description></item></channel></rss>