<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payments on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payments/</link><description>Recent content in Payments on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:07:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payments/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Warrior Forum has introduced a new e-marketplace that leverages the existing reach of its members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:07:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</guid><description>Warrior Forum, a prominent online community and marketplace for internet marketers, has introduced Warrior Payments. This comprehensive platform aims to revolutionize online sales by combining payments, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution tools.
Matt Barrie, CEO of Freelancer.com, which acquired Warrior Forum in 2014, highlights the platform&amp;rsquo;s value for entrepreneurs and startups looking to launch and sell products or services online.
Warrior Payments streamlines the sales process by integrating payment processing, digital product delivery, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instarem introduces recurring transfers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-recurring-transfers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 13:31:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-recurring-transfers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Instarem, a digital payments company specializing in international transfers, has launched a recurring payments feature in Singapore. This new offering aims to simplify the user experience by saving time and reducing hassle.
Users have the flexibility to schedule payments weekly or monthly, aligning with their individual needs. They can also manage their scheduled payments with options to modify, pause, or cancel at any time. Setting up recurring transfers is straightforward, either through the transaction history or directly after completing a transaction...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-recurring-transfers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-recurring-transfers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>