<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Civil Liability on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/civil-liability/</link><description>Recent content in Civil Liability on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:47:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/civil-liability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EC is proposing an AI Liability Directive to provide assistance.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ec-is-proposing-an-ai-liability-directive-to-provide-assistance/</guid><description>Ida Varošanec (PhD student, University of Groningen) and Nynke Vellinga (post-doc researcher, University of Groningen)
Photo credit: Cryteria, via Wikimedia commons
1. Proposal Goals
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposal for an AI Liability Directive, published on September 28, 2022, alongside an updated Product Liability Directive, aims to address the risks posed by artificial intelligence (AI) while acknowledging its potential benefits. The proposal stems from a report recognizing the potential harm AI systems can cause due to their connectivity, unpredictable nature, and opacity, which makes it difficult to assign responsibility for AI-related incidents.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling in McFadden: Public Wi-Fi and Responsibility for Unauthorized Downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-in-mcfadden-public-wi-fi-and-responsibility-for-unauthorized-downloads/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case, McFadden, examined whether businesses offering free wi-fi are responsible for customers&amp;rsquo; illegal downloads. This case centered around Article 12 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s eCommerce Directive, which protects &amp;ldquo;mere conduits&amp;rdquo; of information from liability. While generally aligning with existing laws, the ruling raised potentially significant points regarding injunction costs and internet access provision requirements.</description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters.</description></item><item><title>Unresolved concerns regarding the regulations for trusted flaggers under the Digital Services Act regime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giorgia Lo Tauro, FratiniVergano European Lawyers
Photo credit: ** Lobo Studio Hamburg**, via Wikimedia Commons
1 Introduction
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services Act (DSA) formally establishes the roles and responsibilities of &amp;ldquo;trusted flaggers,&amp;rdquo; important entities in the online world that have operated with varying degrees of influence since the early 2000s. This new framework aligns with the DSA&amp;rsquo;s goals: creating consistent, effective, and balanced rules across the EU to improve the online marketplace.</description></item><item><title>Commentary on Arlewin v. Sweden: Libel Law, EU Law, and the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 02:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-arlewin-v-sweden-libel-law-eu-law-and-the-echr/</guid><description>Athanassios Takis: PhD, Special Adviser to General Secretariat of Greek government
The European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruling of March 1, 2016, in the case of Arlewin v. Sweden examined how EU Regulation 44/2001, which decides which Member State&amp;rsquo;s courts hold jurisdiction over civil and commercial disputes, was used (or misused) by Swedish courts. This case highlighted the limitations of the &amp;lsquo;acte clair&amp;rsquo; doctrine – the idea that national courts don&amp;rsquo;t always need to consult the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on EU law matters.</description></item></channel></rss>