<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Android Smartphone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/android-smartphone/</link><description>Recent content in Android Smartphone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:10:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/android-smartphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What To Do With Old Cell Phones and Electronics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 04:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</guid><description>So, you&amp;rsquo;ve finally upgraded to the latest smartphone but now you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with your old one. It&amp;rsquo;s useless without a service plan but you hesitate to get rid of it.
Years pass and you stumble upon it again, completely forgotten. It&amp;rsquo;s just an outdated piece of technology now, the battery long depleted. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe it was once worth hundreds of dollars, leaving you wondering if you could have sold it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-with-old-cell-phones-and-electronics/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Here’s Why Companies Actually Want BYOD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The concept of &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Device&amp;rdquo; (BYOD) can be a real headache for IT managers. While employees may enjoy the convenience, it poses a significant risk to a company&amp;rsquo;s sensitive data. When personal devices connect to the company network, carefully constructed security protocols are often bypassed. So, what can be done?
Many companies address this issue by drawing a hard line. Recognizing the challenges of managing diverse personal devices, they prohibit their use for business purposes altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/here-s-why-companies-actually-want-byod/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Intercept Brings Free Android Smartphone to Sprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 05:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</guid><description>A popular new smartphone design combines a 3-inch touchscreen, a slide-out QWERTY keyboard, and the Android operating system. Sprint offers this package in their Samsung Intercept model. Amazingly, you can get this phone for free when you order it online with a new Sprint PCS service plan. There are no additional costs; even shipping is free, and the plans are the same price as in stores.
The Samsung Intercept M910 is a fantastic deal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC ThunderBolt Screams On LTE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:58:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</guid><description>The HTC ThunderBolt, a smartphone with lightning-fast speed, embodies the next generation of mobile connectivity. It operates on Verizon&amp;rsquo;s LTE network with exceptional performance.
Not long ago, having a smartphone with cutting-edge 3G broadband was a status symbol. Technology evolves rapidly, and the speed that impressed us a few years ago seems archaic compared to today&amp;rsquo;s standards.
While 3G seemed remarkably fast at the time, its approximate speed of 1 Mbps pales in comparison to 4G&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-thunderbolt-screams-on-lte/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pink Android Intercept Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pink-android-intercept-means-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 03:55:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pink-android-intercept-means-business/</guid><description>The Samsung Intercept, with its stylish satin pink exterior, could easily be described as &amp;ldquo;Pretty in Pink,&amp;rdquo; much like the classic 80s movie. This phone is more than just attractive; it&amp;rsquo;s also a highly capable device.
This pink Android phone boasts a large 3-inch touchscreen display, providing access to a vast library of apps from the Android Market. What sets it apart from other touchscreen phones is its full slide-out QWERTY keyboard, enabling swift emailing, instant messaging, and texting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pink-android-intercept-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pink-android-intercept-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FREE HTC Wildfire S White For The Holidays</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-htc-wildfire-s-white-for-the-holidays/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-htc-wildfire-s-white-for-the-holidays/</guid><description>The HTC Wildfire S, a stylish white smartphone available from T-Mobile, is a popular choice for the holidays. This sought-after Android phone can be yours for free, making the season even brighter.
What makes the Wildfire S so appealing? It might be the way this smart device focuses on people, organizing communication by individuals instead of apps. Its multi-window browsing feature allows for efficient multitasking. The Wildfire S stands out for its compact size, measuring a mere 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-htc-wildfire-s-white-for-the-holidays/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-htc-wildfire-s-white-for-the-holidays/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free 6-Way Desktop and Mobile Video Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all used conference calls to connect with people in different locations. While audio conferencing has been the traditional method, video conferencing has become a popular alternative.
Although video conferencing was initially associated with formal corporate meetings, it has evolved into a more versatile tool. The previous cost barrier of video equipment and connections has significantly decreased since most devices now come equipped with built-in cameras, allowing for affordable video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-6-way-desktop-and-mobile-video-calls/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>