<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Suhoor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suhoor/</link><description>Recent content in Suhoor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suhoor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Golf introduces special promotions for Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Golf website.
During Ramadan, Dubai Golf has several special iftar and suhoor packages perfect for corporate events.
QD&amp;rsquo;s
QD&amp;rsquo;s has a special Ramadan tent where they serve both iftar and suhoor. The daily iftar buffet features a variety of traditional hot and cold Arabic mezze, soups, Middle Eastern and international main dishes, and desserts. This comes with your choice of juice and traditional Arabic sweets and dates.</description></item><item><title>Special discounts are available for group bookings for iftar and suhoor at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp; Hotel in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Source: Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is offering special group rates for iftar and suhoor.
The iftar buffet, which includes Ramadan juices, is priced at AED 180*, with a discounted rate of AED 170 per person for groups of 10 or more. Using the coupon system**, the price drops to AED 150 per person. The suhoor buffet, also with Ramadan juices, costs AED 90 per person.</description></item><item><title>Atlantis Dubai offers a diverse selection of options for iftar dining</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</guid><description>This Ramadan, Atlantis is offering three unique dining experiences for iftar and suhoor: Asateer, Nobu, and Kaleidoscope, each providing a taste of Arabian culture.
Asateer, meaning &amp;ldquo;legends&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, provides a traditional tent setting overlooking the Arabian Sea, accommodating up to 900 guests. A customary iftar buffet is available at sunset for AED195, featuring Ramadan juices and followed by an à la carte suhoor menu starting at 9:30 pm.
During iftar, guests can enjoy classic dishes like foul moudammas and balila, complemented by a variety of Ramadan beverages such as jallab, laban, kamr al deen, and karkadeh.</description></item><item><title>During this Ramadan, the Corp Amman will offer Iftar dining and entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Corp Amman Hotel website.
The 4-star Corp Amman Hotel has put together a special offering for iftar and suhoor during Ramadan, showcasing traditional Jordanian hospitality. Guests can enjoy evenings filled with food and music for JD18 per person, not including services and taxes.
The celebration starts with an iftar menu at the Boulevard Restaurant &amp;amp; Poolside Terrace, available all day. The menu features Ramadan favorites such as juices, dried fruits, Arabic breads, soups, salads, pickles, and mezze.</description></item></channel></rss>