<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Removal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/removal/</link><description>Recent content in Removal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/removal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Keyboard Keys - Video About Removal and Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</guid><description>After restoring a Beogram 4000, I shipped it to a customer, but two keypad keys came loose during transport. To secure them, I had used tape and foam, but the shipping stress was too much for the delicate leaf spring mechanism holding the keys.
To prevent this from happening again, I created special tools that make it easier to install the keys and shared a video demonstrating their use. These tools, designed to avoid damaging the aluminum, are available to other enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Restoring the Plexiglass Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I recently restored had a very scratched dust cover.
[Image of scratched dust cover]
If I can feel the scratches with my fingernail, the first restoration step is sanding with 220 grit sandpaper. This creates a smooth surface for polishing. This is what the surface looks like after sanding:
[Image of dust cover after sanding]
It looks a bit like wood at this stage. After approximately 10 polishing steps using progressively finer sandpaper and then micro-mesh polishing cloths, the surface is restored:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The final step in restoring my Beogram 4000 involved replacing the damaged dust cover with one from a donor unit. While the replacement had some typical scratches, it was in good condition overall.
I began by sanding the surface with 320 grit sandpaper to remove the scratches. The next step was to polish it back to its original shine and clarity. Here&amp;rsquo;s the dust cover after polishing with 800 grit:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Polishing of the In- and Outside of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</guid><description>After installing a new remote control and internal pre-amplifier, the final touch on this Beogram 4002 (5523) was polishing its dust cover. While the outside showed typical scratches, the inside had an unusually large scratch as well.
Polishing the inside is more challenging because the polishing tool can hit the corners. However, because this scratch was situated away from the edges, it could be addressed. The technique involved gradually widening the polished area with each step...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>The final touch in restoring a Beogram turntable is typically polishing its plexiglass cover. This particular Beogram 4002 had noticeable scratches on its cover, including a branded logo above the platter&amp;rsquo;s center.
Deep scratches that can be felt by hand require an initial sanding with 220-grit sandpaper to level the surface, creating a temporarily rough appearance. If the scratches are less pronounced, starting with 320 or 400-grit sandpaper might suffice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Plexiglass Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 18:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) I recently refurbished had a very scratched lid. Fortunately, the hinges were undamaged, and the inside of the lid was in good condition, with only a few minor cleaning marks. This made it worthwhile to try to restore the lid to an acceptable condition. The photo below shows the condition of the lid when I received the Beogram:
Because some scratches were deep enough to feel with a fingernail, I began by using 400-grit sandpaper to smooth the surface:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>