<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1938DNBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1938dnbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 1938DNBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1938dnbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Massachusetts - First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from a Massachusetts customer for a complete restoration. Thankfully, it was properly packaged and arrived without damage.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s dust cover shows typical signs of use, but it will be replaced with a new one. The aluminum surfaces are in good shape overall.
However, there are some minor flaws. The keypad has a corner ding, suggesting it might have come loose during past transportation. Additionally, there are small scratches on the aluminum, possibly from the keypad moving around.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</guid><description>During a recent Beogram 4000 restoration, my customer opted for a brand new reproduction hood from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These hoods mark a significant advancement in Beogram 400x restoration. Crafted through injection molding, they perfectly mirror the original hoods, eliminating the seams found in laser-cut and fused alternatives.
Simply put, these hoods are identical in appearance to the originals. Developed by Beoworld&amp;rsquo;s Dillen, their availability has greatly benefited Beogram 400x restorations.</description></item></channel></rss>