<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Managed Security on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-security/</link><description>Recent content in Managed Security on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 23:22:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/managed-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telnes Broadband for T1 Dedicated Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 23:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</guid><description>Reliable, always-on internet connectivity has transitioned from a convenient business tool to a necessity. Companies of all types rely on consistent bandwidth for communication with customers, suppliers, and even phone services. Dedicated connections, like T1 data lines, offer the highest reliability with guaranteed uptime.
Telnes Broadband is an Internet Service Provider (ISP) catering specifically to businesses and government entities, constituting over 99% of their clientele. Their reputation for dependable WAN connections, especially for businesses with multiple locations, has made them a popular choice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Security Moves To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud services are expanding beyond the familiar Infrastructure, Platform, and Software as a Service to include Security as a Service. Integra, for example, now offers a suite of Cloud Security Services, including a Cloud Firewall Service.
Many companies find managed security appealing because it removes the need for dedicated IT staff or investments in security hardware. Traditionally, this involved a monthly service fee and an on-premises security device. Cloud-based security takes it further, eliminating the need for physical hardware altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>