<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>122KSBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/122ksbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 122KSBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/122ksbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding a Noisy DC Motor with Oil Infused Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 11:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-a-noisy-dc-motor-with-oil-infused-bearings/</guid><description>The majority of Beogram 4002 turntables equipped with a DC motor require motor refurbishment. Indicators of this need include abrupt drops in revolutions per minute (RPM) or audible motor noise during operation. This specific Beogram 4002 (5514) exhibited significant noise during unloaded operation. As part of my restoration process for all 4002 turntables, I comprehensively rebuild the DC motors to preemptively address these common issues.
The primary contributor to these performance issues lies in the brass sleeve bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Restoring the Plexiglass Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I recently restored had a very scratched dust cover.
[Image of scratched dust cover]
If I can feel the scratches with my fingernail, the first restoration step is sanding with 220 grit sandpaper. This creates a smooth surface for polishing. This is what the surface looks like after sanding:
[Image of dust cover after sanding]
It looks a bit like wood at this stage. After approximately 10 polishing steps using progressively finer sandpaper and then micro-mesh polishing cloths, the surface is restored:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): RPM Performance Measurement after Restoration of DC Motor and Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</guid><description>Following the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable&amp;rsquo;s DC motor and control system, a 24-hour RPM performance test was conducted using a custom-built RPM monitoring device.
The initial performance, measured before the restoration, revealed noticeable, abrupt drops in RPM, indicating typical wear and tear in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings. These dips, while moderate in this instance, would have been audible due to their 1% magnitude.
After the restoration, which included rebuilding the motor and replacing RPM-related components, the significant RPM fluctuations were eliminated.</description></item></channel></rss>