<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Traffic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traffic/</link><description>Recent content in Traffic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traffic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The TomTom City portal offers real-time traffic and travel updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 05:33:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</guid><description>TomTom (TOM2) introduces TomTom City, a digital platform providing real-time traffic data and travel details to both individuals and traffic management professionals.
This new service showcases the wide array of traffic information available for specific cities and acts as a hub for connecting traffic authorities, businesses, and citizens to collaborate on sustainable and efficient mobility solutions. Building on the traffic information already available through TomTom navigation devices and partners in automotive, consumer, and government sectors, TomTom City expands upon the historical congestion data provided in reports like the TomTom Traffic Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-city-portal-offers-real-time-traffic-and-travel-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fake clicks and pageviews can artificially boost digital marketing metrics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve invested in online ads on a platform known for its excellent results, and you&amp;rsquo;re seeing those clicks increase week after week. People are clearly interested enough to visit your store locations, but actual sales remain stagnant. So, what&amp;rsquo;s the deal?
This could be a sign of ad fraud, and not necessarily originating from the platform itself.
The Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB), based in the US, emphasizes the need for greater awareness surrounding non-intentional traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>