<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Originals on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/originals/</link><description>Recent content in Originals on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/originals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adidas Originals is reintroducing the Superstar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</guid><description>Source: adidas.
This year, adidas Originals launches a campaign exploring the meaning of being a superstar, coinciding with the anniversary of the iconic Superstar shoe, first released in 1969.
A short film by adidas Originals, directed by Karim Huu Do, examines what it means to be a superstar in 2015. Footballer David Beckham states, &amp;ldquo;It’s not about trying to be the next big thing.&amp;rdquo; Entertainer Pharrell Williams believes &amp;ldquo;It’s not about the number of views, likes or shares...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mary Katrantzou, known as the "Queen of Prints," is featured in the adidas Originals fall/winter collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 09:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Shoes from the Mary Katrantzou collection.
Renowned fashion designer Mary Katrantzou, often called the “Queen of Prints,” has partnered with sportswear giant adidas. Their collaboration, the adidas Originals by Mary Katrantzou collection, features apparel and footwear inspired by Katrantzou&amp;rsquo;s signature style.
Katrantzou&amp;rsquo;s designs are known for their fusion of vibrant graphics, structural silhouettes, and cutting-edge technologies, resulting in a contemporary and feminine aesthetic. For this collection, she drew inspiration from classic adidas shoe designs, incorporating elements like outsoles, laces, and iconic brand details into her unique pieces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mary-katrantzou-known-as-the-queen-of-prints-is-featured-in-the-adidas-originals-fall-winter-collection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The YEEZY BOOST 350 will be released on August 22nd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</guid><description>On August 22, 2015, Kanye West and adidas Originals will launch a new all-black version of the YEEZY BOOST 350 sneaker in select stores worldwide. This release follows the successful June launch of the white YEEZY BOOST 350.
This is the third shoe model designed collaboratively by West and adidas. The low-top YEEZY BOOST 350 in black features a one-color upper made from adidas Primeknit, a material engineered to feel like a second skin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas Originals celebrates originality with the Born Original fragrance pair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/</guid><description>Source: adidas Originals.
Adidas Originals, the renowned streetwear brand, introduces a new fragrance pair: Born Original. These dynamic scents, one for men and one for women, embody the spirit of embracing individuality and authenticity.
Born Original reflects the energetic and empowering essence of the adidas Originals brand, grounded in individuality, authenticity, and imagination. The Born Original fragrances, For Him and For Her, present a vibrant blend of contrasting notes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces new Stan Smith designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</guid><description>This summer, the Stan Smith shoe gets a bold update with the Wrapped Animal Pack. Available in three color combinations, the pack keeps the Stan Smith&amp;rsquo;s famous shape while incorporating textured snake, alligator, and crocodile leather around the outsole.
Source: adidas.
Complementary heel tab accents in green, red, and black add a fashionable touch to this classic preppy sneaker. The Adidas Originals Stan Smith, originally a tennis shoe, has become a timeless classic thanks to its all-leather design and simple aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The last adidas Originals = PHARRELL WILLIAMS collection of 2014 will be released on November 28th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</guid><description>The last adidas Originals and Pharrell Williams collaboration of 2014 features a playful use of polka dots. More releases are planned for 2015. The bold and cheerful polka dot motif symbolizes energy and happiness.
Source: adidas Originals. The Polka Dot Pack includes Stan Smith sneakers.
Launching in Southeast Asia on November 28th, the Polka Dot Pack features leather Stan Smith sneakers. This collection embodies the profound joy of love. The youthful and optimistic designs aim for a relatable and authentic feel, representing the collaboration&amp;rsquo;s core value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>