<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ramadhan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ramadhan/</link><description>Recent content in Ramadhan on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ramadhan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buffets for Iftar are available at 21 on Rajah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</guid><description>Source: 21 on Rajah.
The buffet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a venue to hold a corporate Iftar gathering in Singapore during Ramadan, consider the halal-certified 21 On Rajah. Situated within Days Hotel Singapore at Zhongshan Park, this all-day dining restaurant is presenting a selection of Mediterranean and Asian Iftar buffets each evening.
Chef de Cuisine Faustino Picardo Ines Jr and his culinary team have crafted diverse menus throughout the week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Golf introduces special promotions for Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Golf website.
During Ramadan, Dubai Golf has several special iftar and suhoor packages perfect for corporate events.
QD&amp;rsquo;s
QD&amp;rsquo;s has a special Ramadan tent where they serve both iftar and suhoor. The daily iftar buffet features a variety of traditional hot and cold Arabic mezze, soups, Middle Eastern and international main dishes, and desserts. This comes with your choice of juice and traditional Arabic sweets and dates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-golf-introduces-special-promotions-for-ramadan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Grand Millennium Dubai is providing daily iftar buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</guid><description>During Ramadan, the Grand Millennium Dubai, located near Sheikh Zayed Road, is hosting nightly iftar buffets at their Atrium restaurant. For AED 145 per person, guests can enjoy live cooking stations, along with Arabic and international dishes.
Source: Grand Millennium Dubai website. The Atrium restaurant.
The restaurant offers special group rates for iftar. The Silver package, priced at AED 165 per person, accommodates up to 50 guests. The Gold package, for a maximum of 100 people, costs AED 155 per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-grand-millennium-dubai-is-providing-daily-iftar-buffets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xpress Money introduces a daily raffle for customers sending money in 11 countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</guid><description>Xpress Money, a money transfer company, has introduced a 49-day promotion called &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday.&amp;rdquo; This program is open to customers sending money from Malaysia and ten other countries, including several in the Middle East.
Source: Xpress Money website.
The World Bank reported that in 2012, individuals sent $2.3 billion from Malaysia to other countries. Xpress Money anticipates a 15% increase in money transfers during Ramadan. Sudhesh Giriyan, Xpress Money&amp;rsquo;s Vice President and Business Head, stated that the &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday&amp;rdquo; program is a gesture of goodwill towards customers during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the enchanting Arabian nights under the stars at the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar until July 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</guid><description>From June 21st to July 16th, 2015, the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar is excited to present a delectable Ramadhan buffet. The culinary team at LINK All Day Dining has crafted a special &amp;ldquo;Starry Arabian Nights&amp;rdquo; themed dinner, featuring a wide selection of traditional Arab and Malay dishes. The restaurant will be adorned with exotic, Arabian-inspired starry lights, and live ‘ghazal’ performances will entertain guests throughout their meal.
Source: Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Special discounts are available for group bookings for iftar and suhoor at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp; Hotel in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Source: Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is offering special group rates for iftar and suhoor.
The iftar buffet, which includes Ramadan juices, is priced at AED 180*, with a discounted rate of AED 170 per person for groups of 10 or more. Using the coupon system**, the price drops to AED 150 per person. The suhoor buffet, also with Ramadan juices, costs AED 90 per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Atlantis Dubai offers a diverse selection of options for iftar dining</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</guid><description>This Ramadan, Atlantis is offering three unique dining experiences for iftar and suhoor: Asateer, Nobu, and Kaleidoscope, each providing a taste of Arabian culture.
Asateer, meaning &amp;ldquo;legends&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, provides a traditional tent setting overlooking the Arabian Sea, accommodating up to 900 guests. A customary iftar buffet is available at sunset for AED195, featuring Ramadan juices and followed by an à la carte suhoor menu starting at 9:30 pm.
During iftar, guests can enjoy classic dishes like foul moudammas and balila, complemented by a variety of Ramadan beverages such as jallab, laban, kamr al deen, and karkadeh...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atlantis-dubai-offers-a-diverse-selection-of-options-for-iftar-dining/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bay Hotel is now offering a Ramadhan buffet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 21:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</guid><description>Rumah Rasa, a restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bay Hotel, is known for its &amp;ldquo;home-style with a twist&amp;rdquo; Indonesian cooking, using herbs freshly picked from its own garden. During the month of Ramadan, Rumah Rasa offers a special &amp;ldquo;Ramadan Iftar Menu&amp;rdquo; featuring unique and less common Indonesian dishes.
Indonesian-born Chef Esa Hassim, the mastermind behind these culinary creations, shared that he sources these distinctive dishes by inquiring about Indonesian delicacies that are not readily available in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During Ramadhan, digital marketing methods need to be adapted in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Think with Google website. Changes in statistics for Musalsalat, a platform for Ramadhan TV series, during the month.
The Think with Google blog highlights the need for specialized digital marketing strategies in the Middle East and North Africa during Ramadhan. Google Analytical Consultants Vrinda Singh and Younis Maqousi, along with YouTube Specialist David Lacklen, observed a significant increase in mobile internet usage, YouTube viewership, and search engine activity throughout the month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AFOCH invites businesses to gather for iftar during Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: AFOCH website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is hosting Iftar celebrations ideal for gatherings with business associates.
Peter Freeman, the Deputy Director General of the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, highlighted that the hotel&amp;rsquo;s leading chefs will once again prepare a grand Iftar buffet. The buffet will feature exquisite Arabic delicacies alongside international dishes.
&amp;ldquo;Here at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, we provide the most authentic Arabic cuisine, meticulously crafted with the freshest ingredients by our highly skilled culinary team,&amp;rdquo; Freeman stated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big discounts on Honda vehicles in the UAE during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Honda cars are on Ramadan offer in the UAE.
This Ramadan, Al-Futtaim Honda, the exclusive distributor of Honda vehicles, motorcycles, marine engines, and power products in the UAE, is offering reduced starting prices and complimentary service and warranty coverage across their car lineup. Ramadan is typically a popular time for purchasing new vehicles in the GCC region, and various brands offer promotions during this period.
Honda Civic..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iftar gatherings at AquaMarine, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 03:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</guid><description>Originally from the Marina Mandarin Singapore website, this photo displays the Bakar Station&amp;rsquo;s offerings of chicken, oxtail, prawns, and sea bass cooked in banana leaves.
AquaMarine, a Halal-certified buffet restaurant, has recently renovated its Terrace@AquaMarine space. Now fully air-conditioned, it&amp;rsquo;s an ideal location for larger gatherings.
The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s current iftar menu, available until July 17th, features dishes like dates, slow-roasted baby lamb seasoned with Moroccan spices, bulgur wheat with raita, and a traditional Indonesian oxtail soup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During this Ramadan, the Corp Amman will offer Iftar dining and entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Corp Amman Hotel website.
The 4-star Corp Amman Hotel has put together a special offering for iftar and suhoor during Ramadan, showcasing traditional Jordanian hospitality. Guests can enjoy evenings filled with food and music for JD18 per person, not including services and taxes.
The celebration starts with an iftar menu at the Boulevard Restaurant &amp;amp; Poolside Terrace, available all day. The menu features Ramadan favorites such as juices, dried fruits, Arabic breads, soups, salads, pickles, and mezze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us at the Pullman Jakarta Indonesia to celebrate the holy month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>The Pullman Jakarta Indonesia hotel has a special offer for corporate groups during Ramadan. For groups of 50 or more, they offer a deluxe Iftar (breaking the fast) package for Rp450,000 per person. This package features a selection of traditional Iftar snacks and drinks, along with an Indonesian buffet.
To make a reservation or get more details, you can contact Ms. Sarat via email at H8491-SM4@accor.com or by phone at +62 21 3192 1111...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>