<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gas/</link><description>Recent content in Gas on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin.</description></item><item><title>Airswift Holdings, a global recruiting company, operates in 57 locations worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 05:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Airswift Holdings. From left, Duncan Gregson, CEO of Air Energi; Janette Marx, COO, Airswift, Ian Langley, Chairman, Airswift; Peter Searle, CEO, Airswift; and Tobias Reed, CEO of Swift Worldwide Resources.
Air Energi Group and Swift Worldwide Resources combined to establish Airswift Holdings, a global staffing company. Airswift specializes in placing contract and permanent employees, providing resource consultation, assisting with global mobility, and developing managed solutions for companies in the energy, process, and infrastructure sectors.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>