<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Type 5513 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/type-5513/</link><description>Recent content in Type 5513 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/type-5513/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some Cabinet Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I made progress reassembling the Beogram 4002, focusing on the cabinet trim and deck cover. To prevent damage, I had previously removed the rosewood trim.
The trim is attached to a metal frame that slides in and out to lock and unlock the cabinet. This frame relies on five guide washers, which are commonly broken in Beogram 4002 units. This one was no different. These washers have a unique design, as detailed in a past Beolover blog post.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Fit and Finish Rework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</guid><description>Restoring Beogram 4002 turntables is a fulfilling endeavor, though it often necessitates revisiting steps multiple times. Despite getting this particular Beogram functioning properly, I was dissatisfied with the fit of some components.
The tonearm cover wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting flush, as evidenced by its crooked appearance in the photo, with the center divider visibly off-center between the fixed arm and tonearm.
A head-on perspective further highlights this issue, along with the misaligned deck trim, showing an undesirably wide gap between the panels.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Main Board Rework and Start of Speed Test #3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</guid><description>I visited Mouser to acquire some components for my Beogram project. However, upon commencing work on the main board, I realized I lacked a couple of 5KΩ multi-turn trimmers, essential for the 45 RPM and 33 1/3 RPM speed control (labeled 1R14 and 1R15). While I could order the parts, delivery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be possible until Monday, and I was eager to keep the project moving.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a photo of the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main board before removal:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Finishing Up The Tangential Arm Position Sensor &amp; The Fixed Arm Platter Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</guid><description>I was pleased to discover that Beolover successfully refurbished the platter motor for my Beogram 4002. During the packing process for the motor&amp;rsquo;s return, I took the opportunity to calibrate the voltage for two newly installed sensor lamps within the Beogram.
The recently added LED replacement light for the tangential arm position sensor was insufficiently bright. While it functioned, even at maximum output (with the 1R88, 25K ohm trimmer at its highest setting), the voltage measured at the 1TR17 base only reached 0.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Progress Update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</guid><description>The next stage of the restoration involved removing parts from the Beogram chassis. This was necessary to access the tangential arm for repairs and to thoroughly clean the disintegrated transport bushings.
Fragments of the old bushings were scattered throughout the chassis, even within the tonearm cover.
This image shows the Beogram chassis after a thorough cleaning.
Next, 3D-printed replacement bushings from Beolover were installed.
The new bushings fit perfectly. When reattaching the floating chassis, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to align the top and bottom locking washers on their respective threads.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: First Listening Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</guid><description>I finished the mechanical adjustments on the Beogram today. After turning on my digital scale, I calibrated and locked the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s tracking force counterweight. Following Beolover&amp;rsquo;s method, I secured the calibrated setting by replacing the M3 counterweight adjustment screw on the back of the tonearm with a tightening nut. This prevents accidental changes during transport or handling.
With the counterweight set, I secured the locking nut and added a touch of glue for extra stability.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Changing out the tonearm phono cartridge connector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project was paused until a new batch of Beolover replacement parts for the Beogram 400x tonearm cartridge mounts became available. With the parts in hand, the installation process could begin.
One of the cartridge connector contacts on this particular Beogram 4002 was defective. Whether this was a factory issue or a result of wear and tear is unclear, but the owner&amp;rsquo;s prior problems with cartridge mounting made replacing the connector a necessary step.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Results of Initial Platter Motor Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-results-of-initial-platter-motor-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 04:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-results-of-initial-platter-motor-test/</guid><description>I ran the Beogram for slightly more than a day and then analyzed the logged measurement data. As shown in the graph, which plots RPM over time, the turntable speed remained relatively stable at the target 33 1/3 RPM, but there were noticeable drops, reaching as low as 30.324 RPM after about three and a half hours.
This result aligns with Beolover&amp;rsquo;s initial findings when testing similar motors. Based on other Beogram DC motor tests conducted by Beolover, it will be revealing to observe the performance of this Beogram after re-lubricating the platter motor bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 19:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>In addition to working on the tangential arm assembly, the RPM trimmer panel was also restored. Testing by Beolover has demonstrated that this upgrade reduces the heat affecting the platter motor control circuit and improves the motor&amp;rsquo;s stability.
The original trimmer assembly is shown here with its two original lamps.
The Beolover replacement LED lamp assemblies are designed to be connected to the same solder pads as the original lamps, eliminating the need for board modifications.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Service Manual Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 04:24:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-adjustments/</guid><description>The replacement platter motor from Beolover has arrived, and I&amp;rsquo;ll be putting it through its paces soon. Meanwhile, I&amp;rsquo;ve nearly finished the service manual adjustments on this Beogram turntable.
The most time-consuming adjustments on these turntables involve the platter height and leveling. This particular Beogram wasn&amp;rsquo;t level, and the platter height, measured from the top of the fixed arm, was less than the specified 23mm.
To fine-tune these, the platters are removed, and the central threaded bearing is adjusted vertically as needed.</description></item></channel></rss>