<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Effective on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/effective/</link><description>Recent content in Effective on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/effective/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facebook claims that only native and video advertisements provide substantial value</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Head of Ad Tech, Dave Jakubowski, recently stated that exchanges and banners lack significant value in a blog post. He highlights that Facebook conducted a test using &amp;ldquo;a buying platform&amp;rdquo; within Atlas, their ad solution. The test revealed that despite reaching real people accurately, many ads were low-quality or fraudulent.
Although effective in removing these poor ads, Facebook was surprised by the sheer volume of ineffective inventory. The test also demonstrated that only native and video ad formats yielded substantial value.</description></item><item><title>HubSpot uncovers the true desires of buyers when it comes to salespeople</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</guid><description>HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s recent report, Asia Pacific Buyers Have Spoken: Sales Needs to Evolve, reveals what Asia Pacific buyers desire in a sales experience, from initial call topics to the best time for sales interactions.
The report suggests that sales isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily becoming more challenging, but rather traditional sales strategies are losing their effectiveness. The mismatch between current sales tactics and buyer expectations is the root of the problem. HubSpot asserts that conversions will increase if salespeople align their approach with buyer preferences.</description></item></channel></rss>