<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Austria on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/austria/</link><description>Recent content in Austria on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/austria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the special status of minority religious groups, stating "You are all individuals!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice recently issued five significant decisions regarding Directive 2000/78&amp;rsquo;s provisions on religious discrimination, a topic it hadn&amp;rsquo;t addressed in many years. This surge in rulings signifies the Court&amp;rsquo;s renewed focus on this area.
The latest case originated from Austria&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court and concerned a law granting paid holidays on Good Friday to members of three minor Christian denominations, excluding others.</description></item><item><title>DHL introduces new freight service from Taiwan to Austria for shipments smaller than a full container</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding has introduced a new weekly Less-than-Container-Load (LCL) service originating in Taiwan and arriving in Vienna, Austria, by way of Koper, Slovenia. This service, departing every Monday from Keelung or Kaohsiung, allows Taiwanese exporters to ship cargo with a 35-day transit time to Vienna.
Kelvin Leung, CEO, Asia Pacific at DHL Global Forwarding, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to understanding industry trends and supporting exporters. He highlighted the increasing demand for Asian products in Eastern Europe and positioned the new service as a way to strengthen trade partnerships and improve the speed and efficiency of services for Taiwanese businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>