<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2016 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2016/</link><description>Recent content in 2016 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EZVIZ introduces new action cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</guid><description>Source: EZVIZ. The FIVE action cam.
EZVIZ, a company specializing in Wi-Fi cloud cameras and video surveillance equipment, will introduce a new action camera series at CES 2016, designed for sports enthusiasts and content creators.
Priced at US$299.99, the EZVIZ FIVE action camera boasts an Ambarella A12 chipset, a built-in 2-inch IPS touchscreen with 320x240 resolution, a 900mAh battery, and the capability to record continuously at 4K resolution at 15 frames per second...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Stylus 2 will make its first appearance at MWC 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</guid><description>LG will introduce the LG Stylus 2 at the upcoming Mobile World Congress 2016 in Barcelona, Spain.
Source: LG. The LG Stylus 2.
The LG Stylus 2 is slimmer and lighter than its predecessor, measuring 7.4mm thick and weighing 145g. This follow-up to the G4 Stylus boasts a 5.7&amp;quot; HD display for an enhanced viewing experience.
Using the LG Stylus 2 mimics the experience of writing with a traditional pen and notepad...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should Brazil be considered a cyber security threat?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 04:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</guid><description>Cybercriminals frequently target major events like the Olympics to spread malware, and the 2016 Rio Games were no exception. While it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to stay vigilant against phishing attempts that exploit current events, a report from Fortinet, &amp;ldquo;FortiGuard Eye of the Storm,&amp;rdquo; highlights why the 2016 Olympics warranted particular concern.
Although cyberattacks at the Olympics are not a recent phenomenon, with incidents dating back to the 2004 Athens Games, Fortinet raised concerns about the Rio Games for two key reasons that could impact attendees and have a ripple effect on those back home:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers award in Thailand for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</guid><description>Leading employers in Thailand boast engagement scores that are 24 points higher than the average company. This trend is particularly noticeable among Gen Y employees (born between 1979 and 1990), who report engagement levels 22 points higher when working for a top employer. A striking 89% of employees at these leading companies would recommend their workplace to job seekers, significantly surpassing the 68% market average. Among the top performers, Advanced Info Services earned the distinguished title of &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Employers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The perspectives of Gen Z differ from those of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</guid><description>A panel discussion at the Global Islamic Economy Summit focused on the characteristics of Generation Z, the generation following Millennials. Growing up with the internet and mobile phones, Gen Z is not only tech-savvy but also possesses a distinct perspective.
Sunil John, CEO of ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller, pointed out that governments are increasingly paying attention to this generation, questioning if current education and employment systems meet their needs. Citing the ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey 2016, John highlighted that 58% of young Arabs desire higher education, and 36% aim to start businesses, a departure from the traditional reliance on government jobs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-perspectives-of-gen-z-differ-from-those-of-millennials/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarivate Analytics states that global innovation is shifting its focus from quantity to quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 07:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</guid><description>Source: Clarivate Analytics infographic.
Clarivate Analytics, previously known as the Intellectual Property &amp;amp; Science division of Thomson Reuters, has announced its 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators. Utilizing unique proprietary data analysis, the report recognizes the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative companies and institutions.
Now in its sixth year, the 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators report highlights a significant change in approach among leading global innovators, according to Clarivate Analytics. The report shows a decline in patent filings coupled with an increase in grant rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks in Asia is offering merchandise for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 05:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>To commemorate the 2016 Lunar Year of the Monkey, Starbucks has introduced a special collection of limited-edition items available in Asian markets. This merchandise includes:
[Image of Starbucks Monkey Mug]
Lunar New Year Monkey Mug
This red ceramic mug features a three-dimensional white monkey. Its body wraps around the side, its tail forms the handle, and its playful expression peeks out from the mug&amp;rsquo;s surface. The design is enhanced with a glossy red glaze, a contrasting yellow interior, and gold-colored vines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-in-asia-is-offering-merchandise-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check out Shopee Malaysia's Christmas gift ideas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, offers a convenient way to shop for Christmas.
Here are some gift ideas available in Malaysia:
Stay Connected
[Image of PINENG PN966 power bank]
This power bank, available in blue and green, ensures you stay connected all day.
[Buy now]
Capture the Moment
[Image of OPPO F1s phone]
The OPPO F1s, dubbed &amp;ldquo;The Selfie Expert,&amp;rdquo; boasts a 5.5&amp;quot; display with 1,280 x 720 pixels resolution, a 13-megapixel rear camera, and a 16-megapixel front camera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yahoo has published its 2016 Year in Review for Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 02:37:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</guid><description>Yahoo, a popular online platform, has released its &amp;ldquo;2016 Year in Review&amp;rdquo; (YIR) for Singapore. This yearly recap highlights the major search trends and events that captivated Singaporean internet users, based on their search history and online activity on Yahoo throughout 2016.
Topping the list of &amp;ldquo;Top 10 Singapore Headlines&amp;rdquo; is swimmer Joseph Schooling winning Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first Olympic gold medal. Significant political events like changes to the Elected Presidency and MP David Ong&amp;rsquo;s resignation also feature prominently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-has-published-its-2016-year-in-review-for-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Schroders predicts that the second half of 2016 will be challenging, but still an improvement over the first half</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</guid><description>Schroders Investment Management believes the global economy will improve after weak growth in the first half of 2016.
Keith Wade, Chief Economist &amp;amp; Strategist at Schroders, states that there are indicators of increasing growth in the next two quarters of 2016, with previous economic obstacles diminishing. Consumer spending is also rising due to renewed credit growth. However, Wade cautions that 2016 will likely not see robust global growth.
Wade attributes much of the sluggishness to the aftermath of the global financial crisis, with various economic actors still adapting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schroders-predicts-that-the-second-half-of-2016-will-be-challenging-but-still-an-improvement-over-the-first-half/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google is ranked first in the Brandindex Australia rankings for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</guid><description>Source: YouGov BrandIndex. Overall brand rankings for 2016 in Australia.
YouGov BrandIndex has released its 2016 rankings for Australia. Having monitored brands in Australia since mid-2015, BrandIndex currently tracks over 260 brands. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Google secured the top position, followed by YouTube, another Alphabet subsidiary, and then ALDI, the discount retailer.
Here are some other notable findings:
In the automotive sector, Toyota, Mazda, and Mercedes-Benz secured the top three spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF is analyzing the economy of the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 21:56:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) mission, headed by Chikahisa Sumi, has assessed the Philippine economy&amp;rsquo;s performance as positive but believes there&amp;rsquo;s room for improvement.
During their visit to Davao and Manila from June 28 to July 12, the mission engaged with various stakeholders, including the Governor of the Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP), economic ministers, high-ranking government representatives, private sector leaders, and financial experts. Sumi&amp;rsquo;s post-mission statement highlighted the following:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-is-analyzing-the-economy-of-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore National Administrative Professionals Week is here. If you need someone to talk to, I'm here for you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</guid><description>A recent survey conducted by Zyllem, a delivery service, in honor of Singapore Administrative Professionals Day 2016, showed that 93% of respondents believe that Administrative Professionals are the unsung heroes of Singaporean businesses.
However, the survey also revealed that 64% of coworkers admitted to taking their Admin Professionals for granted. They frequently rely on them to perform tasks outside their job description, including delivering umbrellas to colleagues stuck in the rain, sending forgotten passports to colleagues at airport check-in, performing first aid, and even providing early morning wake-up calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals its list of 25 talented individuals under the age of 25 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</guid><description>Spotify has unveiled the top 25 most influential artists under 25 who are currently dominating the music scene in Singapore.
Shawn Mendes, an 18-year-old singer-songwriter from Canada, takes the top spot. He boasts 25 million monthly listeners on Spotify and over 500 million streams for his hit song, &amp;ldquo;Stitches.&amp;rdquo; Following closely behind Mendes are Ariana Grande, Martin Garrix, Justin Bieber, and Alessia Cara. Popular artists Gentle Bones and Fifth Harmony are also included in the list...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vivid Sydney will once again enchant audiences starting on May 27th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</guid><description>The longest-running Vivid Sydney will illuminate Sydney Harbour and other beloved locations for 23 nights, from May 27 to June 18, 2016. This year marks the eighth anniversary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest festival of light, music, and ideas. The festival is owned, managed, and produced by Destination NSW, the NSW Government&amp;rsquo;s tourism and major events agency.
Sandra Chipchase, Destination NSW Chief Executive Officer and Executive Producer of Vivid Sydney, stated that this year&amp;rsquo;s Vivid Sydney promises an incredible program where art, creativity, and innovation converge, captivating both local and international visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is leading the way in digital transformation and digital leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 05:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</guid><description>Source: SAP. Agree or disagree? Management and staff in Southeast Asia and globally share their thoughts in the Leaders 2020 study.
Almost 25% of Southeast Asian companies are considered digital leaders, according to a recent study by SAP and Oxford Economics. This figure surpasses the global average of 16% reported in the Leaders 2020 study.
This new category of high-achieving companies reports greater profit increases, improved employee engagement, and more inclusive workplace environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-leading-the-way-in-digital-transformation-and-digital-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IdeaLab gives power to startups in ASEAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</guid><description>IdeaLab 2016, a focused two-day startup conference, will highlight ASEAN startup collaboration and the Malaysian startup scene. It also features the Malaysian Business Angels Network (MBAN) Summit, attracting investors globally. The organizers aim to bring together 500 top startups, investors, and corporations from the ASEAN ecosystem.
Attendees can participate in various stages. The Ideation Stage features industry leaders discussing critical issues faced by startups in ASEAN. At the IdeaPad Stage, the best ASEAN startups compete before a panel of judges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Source: The Ascendas-Singbridge Group. From left: Ho Kheng Lian, Venture Partner, Vectr Ventures; Natalie Loh, Vice President of Products, Vanitee; Kuik Xiao Shi, Co-Founder, Vanitee; Pocket Sun, Founding Partner of SoGal Ventures; Adrianna Tan, Founder, Wobe; Virginia Tan, Co-founder and Managing Director of Lean In China; Adeline Quek, Head of Regional Business Development, Grabtaxi; Mrs Nina Yang, Chief Operating Officer of Singbridge.
The Ascendas-Singbridge Group selected two startups from Singapore to compete in the finals of the Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 competition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The demand for online training in the Middle East exceeds the available supply</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 02:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</guid><description>Online professional training courses are gaining popularity in the Middle East, but the availability of suitable courses hasn&amp;rsquo;t matched the increased demand, according to research by GulfTalent, a recruitment firm that operates an online recruitment portal for the region.
GulfTalent’s study shows that one out of five professionals interested in pursuing training prefers online courses. This signifies a significant shift, given that online training was practically nonexistent ten years ago...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-online-training-in-the-middle-east-exceeds-the-available-supply/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The exclusive offers available at the 26th edition of The PC Show</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</guid><description>The PC Show, celebrating 26 years of IT and consumer electronics in Singapore, is back. Major brands like Best Denki, Canon, Courts, Creative, Dell, Epson, Harvey Norman, HP, Lenovo, M1, Newstead, Samsung, Seagate, Singtel, and Toshiba will offer exciting products, deals, and competitive prices.
Gillian Loh, Project Manager at Lines Exposition and Management Services, highlighted that attendees often look for great deals and the latest technology at the show. Organizers aim to continually improve the visitor experience, and this year they are introducing dedicated zones for specific interests and providing online updates on deals and new products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>L’Oréal introduces a flexible skin sensor that tracks sun exposure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</guid><description>Source: L’Oréal. Model wearing a My UV patch.
L’Oréal recently introduced My UV Patch at the Consumer Electronics Show. It is the first flexible skin sensor designed to track UV exposure and promote sun-safety awareness among consumers. This innovation arrives as sun exposure has become a significant health concern, with 90% of non-melanoma skin cancers linked to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from the sun, in addition to skin pigmentation and premature aging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Dell EMC was recognized as one of the top companies to work for in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell EMC Singapore has been recognized as the 8th best company to work for in Singapore in 2016. This ranking comes from a comprehensive study conducted by the Great Place to Work Institute Singapore, which evaluates workplace culture.
The study utilizes 58 metrics from employee surveys and company audits to measure the factors that contribute to a positive and successful work environment. Only organizations where a majority of employees consider it a great place to work are eligible for inclusion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian venture capital investments have remained stable in the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 05:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Venture capital (VC) investment experienced a global decline in 2016, following a strong 2015, according to the Venture Pulse Q4 2016 report by KPMG Enterprise.
Global VC investment decreased by 24% year-over-year, totaling US$127.4 billion. Despite a promising start to the year, investor confidence waned in the latter half of 2016 due to uncertainties in the market. Events like Brexit and the US presidential election furthered this uncertainty.
Chia Tek Yew, Head of Financial Services Advisory at KPMG in Singapore, noted that this period of uncertainty allowed VCs to refine their portfolios, focus on high-potential deals, and guide their portfolio companies towards further growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-venture-capital-investments-have-remained-stable-in-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DBS Marina Regatta is filled with exciting activities spread out over two weekends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest water sports festival, the DBS Marina Regatta, returns for its fifth year with an expanded format spanning two weekends, May 28-29 and June 4-5. The event, which drew over 24,000 attendees last year, will feature regional dragon boat races set against the Marina Bay skyline, the return of Singapore’s only pop-up urban beach, and the debut of Southeast Asia’s tallest inflatable water slide.
This year&amp;rsquo;s regatta will premiere several new features, including themed dragon boat races and competitive kayak races...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Nongsa Regatta took place in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Nongsa Regatta Facebook page.
The first Nongsa Regatta will take place at Nongsa Point Marina &amp;amp; Resort in Batam, Indonesia, from January 27th to 31st, 2016. This period coincides with the strongest point of the northeast monsoon. The competition welcomes yachts, sporting boats, and racing multihulls. Additionally, there will be races for dinghies and traditional &amp;ldquo;kolek&amp;rdquo; boats.
Having hosted the Singapore Straits Regatta for almost two decades, the resort possesses extensive experience in regattas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Chinese New Year promotion by Digi highlights the importance of family and tradition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</guid><description>Source: Digi website.
For many Chinese individuals, the Chinese New Year signifies the only opportunity to reconnect with distant family members. Malaysian telecommunications company Digi is capitalizing on this tradition with a new promotional campaign designed for a global audience.
Recognizing that in today&amp;rsquo;s world, many individuals simply use titles like &amp;lsquo;aunt,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;uncle,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cousin&amp;rsquo; for relatives beyond their immediate family, Digi&amp;rsquo;s campaign encourages the use of more precise family titles within Chinese families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tough Mudder Bali event will take place in the green hills of Jimbaran</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Bali. Event poster.
The ultimate test of physical and mental strength, stamina, and teamwork will premiere in Asia on October 1, 2016, at Jimbaran Hijau (Bali International Park), a multifaceted development in South Bali.
Established in 2010 and known as &amp;ldquo;probably the toughest event on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder is an obstacle course challenging participants to collaborate and conquer physical and mental hurdles in an extreme endurance event...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reserve a spot for a handicraft workshop at the Etsy Craft Party 2016 - Summer Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 15:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/</guid><description>Individuals with a creative spirit or those seeking engaging team-building exercises might be interested in three craft workshops featured at the &amp;ldquo;Etsy Craft Party 2016 - The Summer Edition&amp;rdquo; on June 18, 2016. The Singapore edition of this annual Etsy event is organized by Crafty Singapore, with support from Etsy.
Source: Crafty Singapore. Finished embroidery on tiny &amp;lsquo;mini&amp;rsquo; embroidery hoops.
Needlework on a Miniature Hoop
Presented by Wish I Were Stitching (two sessions, eight participants per session)..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-spot-for-a-handicraft-workshop-at-the-etsy-craft-party-2016-summer-edition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There was a significant increase in early-stage M&amp;A activity in the APAC region during the fourth quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>The Intralinks Deal Flow Predictor, which forecasts future merger and acquisition (M&amp;amp;A) announcements, anticipates a 6% rise in the total number of global M&amp;amp;A deals announced in the first half of 2017 compared to the same period in 2016. This would establish a new record for global announced deals in the first six months of a year.
The Asia Pacific (APAC) region leads in early-stage M&amp;amp;A activity, demonstrating 44% year-over-year growth in the fourth quarter of 2016, and is positioned to significantly contribute to the projected record deal count in the first half of 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-was-a-significant-increase-in-early-stage-m-a-activity-in-the-apac-region-during-the-fourth-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Tough Mudder event in Asia will take place in Bali, Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 06:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Indonesia. Chairi Ibrahim, Project Manager at Seroja Partners (left), Gandrasta Bangko, Business Director at Mesa Race (middle), and Ridzki Syahputera, Partner at Seroja Partners (right) at the launch of Tough Mudder Indonesia.
The world-renowned endurance series, Tough Mudder, has officially launched in Indonesia. Known as &amp;ldquo;Probably the Toughest Event on the Planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder has attracted 2.5 million participants across 200 events in six countries. Its Asian debut will take place on October 1st and 2nd, 2016, in Bali, Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is something for everyone on Jane's Walks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global initiative of free walking tours led by community members, is making a comeback from May 6th to 8th. The walks are inspired by Jane Jacobs (1916-2006), an urban planner and advocate who championed community-driven city development. Grounded in the belief that everyone possesses knowledge about their surroundings, these walks celebrate Jacobs&amp;rsquo; ideas worldwide. Participants share stories about their neighborhoods, discover hidden gems, and connect with their neighbors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei P9 and India Photo Project introduce Monochrome award in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</guid><description>Source: Instagram. Top Instagram posts for the contest hashtag #ipp_ma2016 at the time of writing.
Huawei, in partnership with the Instagram-based India Photo Project, has introduced the &amp;ldquo;Monochrome&amp;rdquo; award to commemorate World Photography Day on August 19th. This competition, running from August 20th to August 31st, aims to discover India&amp;rsquo;s top black and white Instagram photographer.
The judging panel comprises Sumit Dayal, recognized as CNN&amp;rsquo;s Indian Instagrammer of the Year in 2015, Tara Bedi, the first Instagram employee from India, Devika Daulet Singh, Director of PHOTOINK, a prominent photography gallery, and Neeraj Priyadarshini, the Photo Editor at the Indian Express...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF has identified key policy priorities for Cambodia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, led by Sonali Jain-Chandra, visited Cambodia from July 6 to July 20, 2016, for their yearly review of Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy. The team analyzed economic data and discussed policies with Cambodian government officials, business leaders, and other stakeholders. They concluded that Cambodia&amp;rsquo;s economy is strong, with high growth projected to continue due to exports, real estate, and construction. However, they cautioned that this growth could slow in the long term and emphasized the risk of financial instability from rapid credit growth, particularly in real estate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-identified-key-policy-priorities-for-cambodia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai ranks in the middle of the global innovation push, according to the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has published the findings from the inaugural Dubai Innovation Index. Introduced last year, this index is part of the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s plan to encourage innovation and global best practices in the private sector. The index identified medical care, media, marketing, IT, and retail industrial sectors as the most innovative, while professional services, agriculture, fisheries, construction, and energy were identified as the least innovative in Dubai...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TAKAUD will be hosting its first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</guid><description>Source: _Middle East Pensions Conference _website.
With the support of the Central Bank of Bahrain, TAKAUD, a leading provider of savings, investment, and pension solutions in the MENA region, is gathering government officials and financial service leaders to discuss the development of robust pension plans for citizens and foreign workers across the region.
The first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference will occur in Bahrain on October 18, 2016. The conference aims to raise awareness and encourage action towards bringing Middle Eastern pension standards in line with developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment commitments in Singapore remain in a positive trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</guid><description>Global companies continued to view Singapore as a crucial base in Asia for expansion and innovation in 2016, with investment commitments meeting or exceeding the Economic Development Board (EDB)&amp;rsquo;s projections. The EDB remains committed to pursuing opportunities in thriving sectors to foster sustained economic growth and create quality employment prospects for Singaporeans.
Attracting S$9.4 billion in fixed asset investments, Singapore exceeded its forecast of S$8 billion to S$10 billion. Total business expenditure reached S$8...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The second edition of Food and Hotel Penang is back!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</guid><description>Source: FHP 2016 website.
The second Food and Hotel Penang (FHP 2016) event is poised to solidify its standing as the premier trade-only platform in Northern Malaysia. This event will host a curated buyer program, offering access to key figures in the food and hospitality sectors within Penang and nearby northern states like Kedah, Perak, and Perlis.
Supported by the Penang state government and the Malaysian Association of Hotels, FHP aims to build upon the achievements of its 2014 edition, which saw participation from 240 companies spanning 30 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SITEX 2016 guarantees an immersive and educational experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</guid><description>Source: SITEX website. Scene from SITEX 2015.
SITEX, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s yearly consumer technology showcase, aims to bridge the gap between individuals and technology. This year, it promises an elevated experience with new interactive activities like a technology-infused dance competition, a dedicated space for children&amp;rsquo;s technology (IMDA Pixel Labs), displays of intelligent systems from NTU, and the SITEX Innovation Alley presented by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SITF). These additions are designed to educate, entertain, and captivate visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Art Stage Singapore will be back in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 06:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Art Stage Singapore.
Art Stage Singapore, the leading art fair in Southeast Asia, will take place from January 21st to 24th, 2016, with a preview day on January 20th. This year&amp;rsquo;s event aims to showcase a new perspective on contemporary art from the region, highlighting the fair&amp;rsquo;s role in its development.
The sixth edition of Art Stage Singapore draws inspiration from ancient gathering places like the Roman Forum and the Greek Agora, aiming to be a hub for the exchange of both art and ideas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-stage-singapore-will-be-back-in-january-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alcatel IDOL 4 Series offers enhanced multimedia features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:42:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/</guid><description>Boom Key provides personalized features for taking pictures, enjoying music, and improving user experience.
Audio experience powered by Waves and JBL, including high-quality JBL headphones included in the box.
Three-way reversibility: sound travels from left to right or front to back, and the user interface adapts when flipped upside down.
VR-in-the-box: VR goggles create an immersive virtual reality experience anywhere, anytime*
ALCATEL has introduced its premium IDOL 4 and IDOL 4S smartphones, offering an enhanced multimedia experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-idol-4-series-offers-enhanced-multimedia-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis has released updated versions of Acronis True Image Cloud and True Image 2016 for backup purposes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 06:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</guid><description>Source: Acronis.
Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, has released updates for its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 software. These comprehensive backup solutions, designed for individuals, families, and home offices, incorporate user feedback. Key improvements include simplified cloud storage options to address limited device space, a redesigned user interface for ease of use, and enhanced features for managing backups across multiple devices like PCs, Macs, smartphones, and tablets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The premium image of cheese is advantageous in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesian families, especially those residing in major urban areas, are anticipated to increasingly incorporate cheese as a staple ingredient in their meals. This trend is linked to a growing consumer preference for preparing Western dishes, such as pizzas, pastas, cakes, pastries, and toast, which often feature cheese, within their own homes, as indicated by research conducted by Euromonitor. A notable shift in preference is the rising popularity of cheese paired with white bread, replacing traditional spreads like chocolate sprinkles, jam, or honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-premium-image-of-cheese-is-advantageous-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia is showing support for breast cancer awareness by going pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Malaysia, is partnering with the Pink Ribbon Deeds (PRIDE) Foundation for a &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; campaign throughout October to raise awareness about breast cancer. The campaign involves both online and offline initiatives.
Shopee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Goes Pink&amp;rdquo; collection features pink and white products across various categories like mobile accessories, beauty products, and home goods, encouraging users to purchase and show their support. With over 2 million app installs in Malaysia, Shopee aims to leverage its platform to spread awareness nationwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-is-showing-support-for-breast-cancer-awareness-by-going-pink/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intralinks APAC respondents predict that waves in China will have an impact on M&amp;A</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</guid><description>Dealmakers in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region believe that China&amp;rsquo;s economic and market activity will be the biggest influence on mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in the region over the coming six months.
This insight comes from a survey of over 1,600 global M&amp;amp;A professionals conducted by Intralinks, a leading provider of M&amp;amp;A deal management and secure collaboration solutions. The survey, conducted between October 4 and 11, 2016, gathered responses from dealmakers across APAC, Europe, the Middle East and Africa, North America, and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, come to DiverseCity in KL to experience a diverse range of performing and visual arts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</guid><description>DiverseCity 2016, also known as the Kuala Lumpur International Arts Festival, ran from August 31st to October 2nd, 2016. The festival showcased a diverse range of artistic expressions, including visual arts, crafts, music, dance, and literature at various locations around Klang Valley in Malaysia. Many events were free to attend.
Taking place annually for five weeks at multiple venues in and around Kuala Lumpur, DiverseCity highlights the rich cultural tapestry of Malaysia and explores the country&amp;rsquo;s close relationship with the ASEAN community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore ranks second in global competitiveness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</guid><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) recently published its Global Competitiveness Report for 2016.
The report determined that a global trend of decreasing openness in countries is negatively impacting growth and prosperity. Financial stimuli like quantitative easing are insufficient for sustained growth and must be paired with reforms that bolster competitiveness. For emerging markets, modernizing business practices and investing in innovation are now just as crucial as infrastructure, skilled workforces, and efficient markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG has released an updated version of the TONE INIFINIM around-the-neck wireless headset just in time for CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</guid><description>Source: LG. The TONE INFINIM HBS-910 headsets will debut at CES 2016.
LG Electronics (LG) will introduce its latest LG TONE INFINIM (HBS-910) headsets at CES 2016. The wireless neckband headset boasts a modernized design and exceptional audio quality.
As the next generation of the HBS-900, the new TONE INFINIM retains key features of its predecessor, like retractable earbuds and Harmon/Kardon audio. It also introduces upgraded Quad-Layer Speaker Technology for a top-tier audio experience with enhanced balance across the entire sound spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore reviews its accomplishments in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</guid><description>Despite a slowing economy in 2016, SPRING Singapore, a government agency supporting business growth, reported that over 16,000 companies enhanced their capabilities.
These companies participated in projects backed by the Capability Development Grant (CDG) and Innovation &amp;amp; Capability Voucher (ICV) programs. SPRING estimates these projects will generate S$7.8 billion and create approximately 21,400 skilled jobs upon completion, representing a 13% and 43% increase from 2015 respectively.
A record-breaking 2,400 projects received CDG support, almost double the previous year and the highest in five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean CFOs are struggling to manage an overwhelming amount of data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 10:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chief Financial Officers (CFOs) face difficulties due to evolving stakeholder expectations and reporting timelines. CFOs anticipate changes in how reporting operates. CFOs are finding it difficult to provide boards with timely and accurate insights due to the increasing amount and speed of data. This issue is highlighted in a new report by EY Financial Accounting and Advisory Services (FAAS): 66% of global respondents say this significantly impacts corporate reporting effectiveness, up from 57% in 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF mission has stated that Pakistan's economic reform efforts must extend beyond the EFF program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</guid><description>An IMF team, led by Harald Finger, visited Dubai between July 26th and August 4th, 2016, to discuss the final review of Pakistan&amp;rsquo;s economic program supported by a three-year IMF Extended Fund Facility (EFF). The team met with key officials, including Finance Minister Ishaq Dar and State Bank of Pakistan Governor Ashraf Wathra.
The mission concluded with a staff-level agreement on the completion of the twelfth and final review under the EFF, subject to approval by IMF management and the Executive Board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-mission-has-stated-that-pakistan-s-economic-reform-efforts-must-extend-beyond-the-eff-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Within the next five years, one-third of young Arabs intend to launch their own businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</guid><description>According to the 2016 ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey, over one-third of young Arabs plan to launch their own businesses within the next five years. The survey indicates that young Arabs believe governments could do more to support them, such as promoting affordable lending, enhancing training and education opportunities, and reducing bureaucratic hurdles.
When asked if their generation is more likely to start businesses than previous ones, 54% agreed. GCC youth were the most optimistic at 62%, compared to 54% in North Africa and 44% in the Levant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Compass Index indicates a positive business outlook in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Despite a global economic downturn, the Compass Index shows optimism in the Asia Pacific (APAC) business sector, with Australian businesses reporting the highest confidence levels. However, the Index emphasizes that maintaining growth requires agility and innovation in business practices.
Source: Compass Index infographic. Australia is particular optimistic on business growth. Compass Offices, a provider of Asian serviced offices, virtual offices, and meeting rooms, surveyed their global clientele for the Compass Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is dedicated to developing talent in the infocomm sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, addressed the rising demand for infocomm professionals in the country. This surge is attributed to the growth of the ICT sector and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiatives. Dr. Yaacob emphasized the need to fill 30,000 infocomm positions by 2020.
He acknowledged the challenge of meeting this demand solely with local talent, stating that while relying on non-Singaporeans might be necessary, the focus should be on equipping Singaporeans with highly competitive skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Once a month until October 2016, the Mount Faber Loop in Singapore will be closed to cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</guid><description>Beginning August 6th, Mount Faber Loop will transform into a car-free zone every first Saturday of the month, from 4 pm to 7 pm. This initiative, named &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Lepak at Mount Faber,&amp;rdquo; marks the first car-free event in a Singapore park and will run for three months, ending in October.
Organized by Mount Faber Leisure Group through the &amp;ldquo;Streets for People&amp;rdquo; initiative and supported by NParks, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Lepak at Mount Faber&amp;rdquo; aligns with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s goal of becoming a &amp;ldquo;car-lite&amp;rdquo; city...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FHA2016 ends on a positive note</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</guid><description>Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), the leading trade show for Asia&amp;rsquo;s food and hospitality sector, concluded successfully.
Source: Singapore Exhibition Services. The showfloor at FHA2016.
Lindy Wee, Chief Executive of Singapore Exhibition Services, noted that as consumer preferences change, so do buyer demands. She expressed satisfaction that FHA remains a crucial platform for exhibitors to introduce innovative products and for global buyers to source them, effectively serving the food and hospitality sectors.
FHA featured a comprehensive range of products and services, from ingredients and equipment to hotel amenities and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 provides a boost to talented young entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: GES 2016. President Obama waves as he walks off the stage with Mark Zuckerberg, Chairman, CEO, and co-founder of Facebook with successful young entrepreneurs from Africa and South America after a panel discussion that he moderated. This is the occasion where he famously said he still had some time to go before he could wear a t-shirt like Zuckerberg, but could at least remove his jacket.
Former US President Barack Obama believes entrepreneurship is a driving force for economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bare Your Sole 2016 barefoot walkathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 14:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</guid><description>Source: Habitat for Humanity Singapore.
&amp;ldquo;Bare Your Sole,&amp;rdquo; the annual barefoot walkathon organized by Habitat for Humanity Singapore, returns to raise funds and awareness for those in need within Singapore. Now in its tenth year, the event will be held at OCBC Square on September 10th at 7:30 am.
The 2.5km and 5km charity walkathon will benefit Project HomeWorks, a local initiative dedicated to improving the living situations of the elderly, ill, and disabled individuals facing challenging conditions across Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit will span two days and focus on the future of commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Millennial 20/20.
From September 7th to 8th, 2016, Singapore will be the site of the Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit. This two-day event will feature discussions centered around understanding the millennial consumer, with over 130 speakers, interactive exhibits, 50 panel discussions, and 24 keynote presentations and interviews.
Rupa Ganatra, Founding Partner of Millennial 20/20, emphasizes the rapid changes in the marketplace driven by millennials, stating that the summit will be crucial for brands to adapt and remain relevant in this influential movement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover Clark by participating in the CLARK BIKE TOUR this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</guid><description>Source: PDOT.
The Philippines Department of Tourism (PDOT), alongside the Clark Development Corporation, announced the upcoming CLARK BIKE TOUR happening in July. This bike tour aims to raise awareness about the significance of health and wellness as a way of life while promoting travel and tourism. It also seeks to highlight Clark as a bike-friendly area.
The event, scheduled for July 30 at the parade ground, anticipates around 400 road bikers, forming 100 teams of four members each, to engage in a non-competitive day-long tour of different attractions within the freeport zone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The fourth bootcamp for 1Malaysia Entrepreneurs has begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 15:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/</guid><description>Source: 1MET. Over 500 participants attended the 1MET bootcamps in Kota Kinabalu.
The 1Malaysia Entrepreneur (1MET) program, an initiative of the National Entrepreneurship Development Office (NEDO) within the Malaysian Ministry of Finance, has initiated its fourth round of two-day entrepreneurial bootcamps. Utilizing an experiential model, these bootcamps offer a six-month mentoring and coaching opportunity for 500 chosen business concepts. The first group to benefit from this follow-up program commenced in August 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-bootcamp-for-1malaysia-entrepreneurs-has-begun/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Automotive industry continues to export to China as its third-largest destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</guid><description>The Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) recently released data revealing that Britain is exporting more cars than ever. The number of British-built cars shipped globally increased by 10.3%, reaching a new record of 1,354,216 units. This marks the second year in a row that this record has been broken.
China, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest car market, maintained its position as the UK&amp;rsquo;s third largest trading partner, after the EU and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tmall Global report showcases the preferences of Chinese consumers in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</guid><description>A recent report on import consumption in China, the Annual Report on Tmall Global Data 2016, was released by Tmall Global, an online platform allowing businesses outside China to connect with Chinese consumers, and CBNData. The report reveals the strength of e-commerce in China, showing a growing customer base, expanding product interest, and notable trends influenced by significant events.
The report highlights several key findings. First, cross-border e-commerce is entering a new phase, supported by favorable policies from both the Chinese government and global trade organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During Ramadhan, digital marketing methods need to be adapted in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Think with Google website. Changes in statistics for Musalsalat, a platform for Ramadhan TV series, during the month.
The Think with Google blog highlights the need for specialized digital marketing strategies in the Middle East and North Africa during Ramadhan. Google Analytical Consultants Vrinda Singh and Younis Maqousi, along with YouTube Specialist David Lacklen, observed a significant increase in mobile internet usage, YouTube viewership, and search engine activity throughout the month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadhan-digital-marketing-methods-need-to-be-adapted-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will provide direct charter flights to Okinawa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/</guid><description>To encourage travel between Singapore and Okinawa, SilkAir, the Okinawa Prefecture government, Japan, and Changi Airport Group are collaborating on seven direct SilkAir charter flights. These flights will operate between June 1st and 25th, 2016, connecting Singapore and Okinawa, Japan&amp;rsquo;s southernmost prefecture.
Travelers can book these full-service flights through Singapore travel agents. SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s Boeing 737-800 aircraft, featuring Business and Economy class cabins, will service the route. Passengers will enjoy a comprehensive range of full-service offerings, including a baggage allowance of 30kg for Economy and 40kg for Business class, inflight meals, and complimentary inflight entertainment through SilkAir Studio...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingPost honors Team Singapore's accomplishments in Rio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-honors-team-singapore-s-accomplishments-in-rio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-honors-team-singapore-s-accomplishments-in-rio/</guid><description>Source: SingPost.
Singapore Post, or SingPost, is releasing two limited-edition stamp sheets on August 29, 2016, to honor Team Singapore&amp;rsquo;s performance at the 2016 Rio Olympics. This project is a collaboration with the Singapore National Olympic Council, and all profits, with a minimum of S$10,000, will be donated to the Singapore Olympic Foundation. This includes Singapore’s first-ever Olympic gold medal.
One sheet, the limited edition “Team Singapore MyStamp” sheet, costs S$20, with a face value of S$6...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-honors-team-singapore-s-accomplishments-in-rio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-honors-team-singapore-s-accomplishments-in-rio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces an improved True Image family and guarantees regular updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</guid><description>Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, recently launched its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 products in Singapore.
During the launch event, Acronis Co-Founder and CEO, Serguei Beloussov, emphasized the increasing importance of data protection, stating that it will soon be as essential as basic necessities. He believes that data represents a comprehensive record of our lives and preserving it should be a top priority, with the goal of eventually retaining all data indefinitely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IMF anticipates that the Kyrgyz Republic's economy will grow by 2.2% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</guid><description>An International Monetary Fund (IMF) team, headed by Edward Gemayel, visited Bishkek, Kyrgyz Republic from July 8th to 14th. The purpose of the visit was to assess the country&amp;rsquo;s recent economic performance and lay the groundwork for the third review mission under the Extended Credit Facility (ECF), tentatively planned for late September.
Preliminary findings from the visit were presented by Gemayel, noting that these do not necessarily reflect the views of the IMF’s Executive Board:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-anticipates-that-the-kyrgyz-republic-s-economy-will-grow-by-2-2-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore emerges victorious at the Culinary Olympics 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</guid><description>Source: the Singapore National Culinary Team. The Singapore National Culinary Team outperformed over 30 countries to become the champions of the Culinary Olympics 2016. The team achieved gold medals in both the Cold Display and Hot Cooking categories, proving the country&amp;rsquo;s chefs are world-class. From left: Teo Yeow Siang, team captain, from Lavish Catering; Triston Fang, team member, from Ocean Restaurant by Cat Cora, Resorts World Sentosa; Alan Wong, team member, from Lavish Catering; team manager Louis Tay from Swissotel Merchant Court; Roy Lim, team member, from Unilever FoodSolutions; and Alex Chong, team member, from The Regent Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Adobe Symposium 2016 will be sharing important digital marketing trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. Logo for Adobe Symposium 2016.
Over 1,000 professionals in digital marketing, publishing, advertising, content management, and marketing executives will come together at the Adobe Symposium in Singapore on July 28, 2016. This event will provide insights into how innovative global brands have successfully utilized digital trends to deeply understand their customers, create personalized campaigns, and effectively manage content and assets.
With over 50 sessions across four tracks, attendees will witness the latest innovations from Adobe Marketing Cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov's ranking of the top brands in Hong Kong for the first half of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</guid><description>In the first half of 2016, Mannings was the most talked-about brand among Hong Kong respondents, according to YouGov&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Mid-Year Best Brand Ranking for Hong Kong. Nike and Adidas secured the second and third positions, respectively. This ranking, drawn from YouGov BrandIndex data, reflects the brands generating the most positive buzz.
The leading brands across various industries in Hong Kong are:
Source: YouGov. The top 10 brands by buzz...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the unique Kampong culinary specials at the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>This June, the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur in Malaysia is offering a special deal for gatherings with colleagues, business contacts, and potential clients. The promotion is valid in their newly renovated ballrooms and private function rooms.
Source: Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur website.
For every ten paying guests, one person can attend for free. The Selera Kampong package is priced at RM155 nett per adult, while the Kampong Boys Special is RM172 nett per adult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMF approves of Singapore's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:52:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its yearly assessment of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy. The IMF noted that while Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy remains strong, it is facing challenges from both global and domestic factors.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economic growth slowed to 2% in 2015, down from 3.3% in 2014, and was 2.2% in the first half of 2016. While unemployment is still low, job creation slowed significantly in 2015, and inflation has remained negative since late 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imf-approves-of-singapore-s-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Bhutan made significant improvements to its business climate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</guid><description>Bhutan has significantly improved its business environment, earning a global ranking of 71st out of 189 countries in the World Bank Group&amp;rsquo;s annual ease of doing business assessment. This achievement places Bhutan at the top spot within the South Asia Region.
The Doing Business 2016: Measuring Regulatory Quality and Efficiency report highlights two key reforms implemented by Bhutan. First, obtaining an electricity connection is now faster, taking only 61 days compared to 93 days five years ago...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-bhutan-made-significant-improvements-to-its-business-climate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buyers who prioritize design are encouraging gift and premium manufacturers to elevate their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</guid><description>Source: SGS website. SGS 2015 was well attended.
This year&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Gifts Show (SGS), taking place from June 29th to July 1st, sees exhibitors raising their game in response to increasingly design-conscious buyers. As the biggest event of its kind in Singapore, SGS is a trade show for gifts, premiums, lifestyle products, and services, targeting both regional and global markets. Established in 2006, this yearly showcase spans three days and encompasses both an exhibition and industry seminars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be larger and improved in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</guid><description>Ting speaking at a media preview for FHA.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), a major food and hospitality trade show in Asia, is approaching its 40th anniversary of serving the industry&amp;rsquo;s needs.
Since its 1978 inception, FHA has attracted a predominantly international exhibitor base (over 80%), underscoring its global reach. FHA provides a platform for showcasing innovative products, technologies, and solutions from around the world, facilitating connections and business opportunities for trade buyers and sellers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Japanese consumers prefer domestic brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Japan.
YouGov Brandindex&amp;rsquo;s 2016 rankings reveal that Japanese brands are the most popular in Japan. Rakuten and Rakuten Card secured the top two spots, followed by clothing retailer Uniqlo in third place.
These brands were assessed using BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents if their exposure to the brand through advertising, news, or word of mouth in the past two weeks was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has revealed a budget for 2016 that is favorable to small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: Budget in Brief document on Singapore Budget website.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, introduced a new program to bolster businesses and industries while stimulating growth through innovation. Building on the Quality Growth Programme from Budget 2013, this initiative, called the Industry Transformation Programme (ITP), seeks to foster innovation and productivity. The goal is to empower Singaporean companies to become more resilient and capitalize on the anticipated global economic upswing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore International Festival of Music is ready for its October shows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 13:56:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</guid><description>The Singapore International Festival of Music (SIFOM), Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first classical music festival, returns for its second year. Centered around the theme &amp;ldquo;Myths and Legends,&amp;rdquo; the festival showcases classical music inspired by folklore and fairy tales. From October 13th to 30th, the festival offers free public programs, masterclasses, and ticketed events including orchestral performances, musical theater, and vocal concerts.
The 2016 SIFOM lineup features the festival&amp;rsquo;s own SIFOM Orchestra and Ensemble, Ding Yi Music Company (showcasing Singapore&amp;rsquo;s finest young musicians), and internationally-renowned guests from the Chamber Orchestra of Europe (COE), a distinguished chamber orchestra...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport is offering mooncakes in a suitcase</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has launched its 2016 mooncake collection, featuring classic baked and contemporary snowskin varieties. These halal-certified treats are packaged in a stylish metal suitcase, making them a great gift for colleagues or loved ones.
For those who prefer a traditional taste, baked mooncakes are available in three flavors: White Lotus Paste with Double Egg Yolk, White Lotus Paste with Single Egg Yolk, and White Lotus Paste with Melon Seeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget prioritizes innovation to capitalize on opportunities in a changing economic landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</guid><description>In his 2016-17 Budget address, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized the need for the city to adapt to a changing global economy driven by technology and the rise of emerging markets. He highlighted robotics, healthy aging, and smart city initiatives as potential areas for Hong Kong to leverage its strengths.
Tsang announced plans to promote smart production and research in the Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate, utilizing robotics and IT to advance the entire value chain, from research and development to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Singapore welcomed technology and locally-made brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Brand rankings for 2016.
The 2016 YouGov Brandindex rankings show that Singaporeans have a strong preference for both local and digital brands. Singapore Airlines, DBS bank, The Straits Times newspaper, WhatsApp, and the Apple iPhone (in the top three) all made the list. Other popular tech brands included Facebook, Google, e-commerce platform Qoo10, and YouTube.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score, which asks respondents whether their exposure to the brand in the previous two weeks, through advertising, news, or word of mouth, was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dictionary.com defines 2016 as xenophobia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dictionary-com-defines-2016-as-xenophobia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 23:55:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dictionary-com-defines-2016-as-xenophobia/</guid><description>Dictionary.com selected &amp;ldquo;xenophobia&amp;rdquo; as its Word of the Year, reflecting significant news events over the past year. The company explained that major news stories in 2016, including Brexit, police shootings, the Syrian refugee crisis, transgender rights, and the US presidential election, all shared a common thread of fear of &amp;ldquo;the other.&amp;rdquo;
The word &amp;ldquo;xenophobia,&amp;rdquo; meaning &amp;ldquo;fear of strangers,&amp;rdquo; originated in the late 19th century from the Greek words xénos (&amp;ldquo;stranger, guest&amp;rdquo;) and phóbos (&amp;ldquo;fear, panic&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dictionary-com-defines-2016-as-xenophobia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dictionary-com-defines-2016-as-xenophobia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee reveals birthday flash sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</guid><description>Shopee, a prominent mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is marking its first anniversary. To commemorate the occasion, they are holding hourly flash sales with discounts of up to 70% on December 12, 2016.
Two products will be discounted every hour on December 12th, from 12 pm to 7 pm.
Along with the hourly flash sales on December 12th, Shopee is running a lucky draw for users who take advantage of daily category vouchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas in Vietnam have been recognized with accolades from TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The master bedroom of an oceanfront three-bedroom villa at Six Senses Con Dao, Vietnam.
TripAdvisor, a leading travel platform, has revealed its highest-rated properties for the fourteenth consecutive year. These rankings are determined by analyzing user reviews and feedback from travelers globally over the past year. Three properties - Evason Ana Mandara, Six Senses Ninh Van Bay, and Six Senses Con Dao - have earned the prestigious Traveler’s Choice award, signifying TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s highest honor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kaspersky provides solutions to combat ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 16:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</guid><description>Ransomware is increasingly targeting businesses, encrypting files and demanding payment for decryption keys.
A Kaspersky Lab report reveals a six-fold increase in ransomware attacks against businesses from 2015 to 2016, affecting one in ten business users.
Cybercriminals are focusing on businesses, particularly small and medium-sized companies. A Kaspersky Lab and B2B International study found that 42% of respondents from these businesses considered ransomware a major threat.
Even brief data unavailability can severely impact small businesses, potentially halting operations entirely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-provides-solutions-to-combat-ransomware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's Global Pension Index score has increased</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</guid><description>Source: Mercer. Where various countries stand on the MMGPI.
Now in its eighth year, the Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI) urges governments worldwide to act quickly to address aging populations, declining birth rates, and inadequate retirement systems. This year, the MMGPI examined the effects of rapidly aging populations and how prepared countries&amp;rsquo; retirement systems are to handle the significant financial strains this presents.
Dr. David Knox, the report&amp;rsquo;s author and a Senior Partner at Mercer, noted that many governments and communities have underestimated the combined effects of longer lifespans and falling global birth rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-global-pension-index-score-has-increased/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instagram outperformed Facebook during the Rio 2016 Olympics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</guid><description>Source: ComScore. Social network interactions between Facebook and Instagram for July 2016 around the Olympic games, which ran from 5 to 21 August.
ComScore, a media measurement company, found that Instagram was the top platform for engagement during the 2016 Rio Olympics, even though Facebook, its parent company, was primarily used for pre-event official content sharing.
In June, the UK ranked third globally in unique visitors to the official Rio Olympics website (RIO2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesian brands are at the top of the Brandindex 2016 rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Indonesia.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 reveal a diverse range of popular brands in Indonesia. Garuda, the national airline, claims the top spot, followed by tech giant Samsung and Danone&amp;rsquo;s mineral water brand, Aqua.
These brands were evaluated based on BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which gauges public perception by asking respondents whether their exposure to a brand in the past two weeks, whether through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth, was positive or negative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry saw an increase in registered activity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.
Member exports and re-exports reached a value of AED273 billion The Dubai Chamber was involved in 78 events spanning 50 cities The Chamber welcomed 681 delegations representing 81 countries The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry in the UAE experienced a 9% growth in its member network during 2016, adding 16,800 companies. This brought the organization&amp;rsquo;s total membership to 201,000 by the year&amp;rsquo;s end, solidifying its standing as a leading global chamber of commerce in terms of membership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-saw-an-increase-in-registered-activity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>