<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dynamics Gp on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dynamics-gp/</link><description>Recent content in Dynamics Gp on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dynamics-gp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Numerous White Papers Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 19:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-white-papers-available/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through a phase where white papers feel incredibly relevant to challenges we face internally and with clients. I wanted to share some of my top picks:
Microsoft Dynamics GP and SQL Server 2008
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/mdgpsqlwhitepaper.htm?printpage=false This paper offers valuable insights into leveraging SQL Server 2008 compression, including performance benchmarks.
Choosing a Development Tool for Microsoft Dynamics GP 10
Partners: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false Customers: https://mbs.microsoft.com/customersource/documentation/whitepapers/gp10_toolswhitepaper.htm?printpage=false A must-read for developers and consultants, this paper provides a comprehensive overview of development tools, licensing costs, required skillsets, and tool capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Should User Account Control be disabled?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 19:57:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-user-account-control-be-disabled/</guid><description>Increasingly, as clients transition to Windows 7 or Vista, user account control issues are becoming more prevalent in Dynamics GP support, particularly with Dynamics GP Utilities. Users frequently encounter BCP utility errors after successfully launching utilities and logging in.
A quick fix is to launch Dynamics GP Utilities as an administrator. While this is straightforward, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed a concerning trend of simply recommending the disabling of user account control altogether. This approach raises concerns for me.</description></item><item><title>What qualities define exceptional training?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:35:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-qualities-define-exceptional-training/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading training sessions, including a Dynamics GP Distribution Partner Academy and a customized Forecaster training. These distinct classes got me thinking about the elements of exceptional training and what makes it truly valuable. I&amp;rsquo;d love to share my thoughts and hear yours!
Relevant Content: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for training content to align with student needs. While this can be challenging with pre-determined classes, instructors can bridge the gap by connecting content to real-world scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Users of Forecaster and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-forecaster-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Have you ever encountered a problem where you vaguely recall a solution but can&amp;rsquo;t seem to locate the specific article or link? This happened to me recently with a client attempting to use their Dynamics GP user ID for Forecaster 7. As expected, it was unsuccessful due to GP&amp;rsquo;s encryption method when generating user IDs in SQL. This encryption prevents the same ID from functioning in Forecaster, even with proper database permissions.</description></item><item><title>Predictor Line Arrangements Over Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/predictor-line-arrangements-over-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 07:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/predictor-line-arrangements-over-time/</guid><description>In the past, using special characters in Forecaster 6.7 often led to problems, so avoiding even periods was recommended. While things have improved in Forecaster 7.0, it&amp;rsquo;s still best to avoid special characters in name and ID fields. Recently, a period caused confusion in Forecaster again.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what happened:
A line set was named with a period at the end (e.g., &amp;ldquo;HR.&amp;rdquo;). This line set was used as an override on an input set.</description></item><item><title>Zero Dollar Checks and Mekorma MICR are both essential tools for managing your finances effectively.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</guid><description>I recently encountered a situation with zero-dollar checks and Mekorma MICR software. To clarify, Dynamics GP software generates zero-dollar checks when an invoice is fully paid through methods like credit memos or manual payments. This often happens before a check run or when opting for automatic application of unapplied documents during check runs.
These zero-dollar checks, appearing on the edit list after a check batch is created, act as placeholders, allowing for a remittance advice to be printed within the check run, confirming the invoice was settled using existing credits.</description></item><item><title>Please don't end my year...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s debunk some common misconceptions about year-end closing in Dynamics GP:
Myth #1: All adjusting entries must be finalized before closing the General Ledger.
This is false. Dynamics GP allows posting to the most recent historical year. After closing 2009, for instance, adjustments can still be made to it, just not to 2008. This requires enabling &amp;ldquo;allow posting to history&amp;rdquo; in GL setup and ensuring the fiscal period is open in Fiscal Period Setup.</description></item><item><title>Solving the Mystery of the Missing Payroll 941 Table</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 02:34:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-mystery-of-the-missing-payroll-941-table/</guid><description>The most crucial advice for payroll professionals is to prioritize backups before finalizing and issuing payroll. Recovering from payroll errors becomes significantly less painful with a readily available backup.
Beyond backups, two additional recommendations are:
Avoid posting payroll if printing or processing issues arise. Instead, cancel the process. The transactions can be included in a new run, eliminating the need to address a partial posting.
When using manual checks for adjustments or corrections, meticulous review of taxable wages and employer FICA taxes is critical.</description></item><item><title>Additional Payroll Troubleshooting Scripts for Your Enjoyment!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-payroll-troubleshooting-scripts-for-your-enjoyment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 02:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-payroll-troubleshooting-scripts-for-your-enjoyment/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s dive into more FUTA and SUTA insights. These scripts can help pinpoint inconsistencies in your configuration and uncover potential reasons for incorrect FUTA and SUTA wage calculations. You can run each script against your company database to find records with potential problems.
&amp;ndash; This script finds employees without a default SUTA state (accessible in the system through Cards&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Employee)
select EMPLOYID as EmployeeID from UPR00100 where SUTASTAT=''
&amp;ndash; This script identifies employee pay code records (accessible in the system through Cards&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Pay Code) that aren&amp;rsquo;t flagged for FUTA or SUTA, or lack a SUTA state despite the pay code setup (accessible in the system through Setup&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Pay Code) requiring it.</description></item><item><title>Uh-Oh: Account Level Security and Advanced Search</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uh-oh-account-level-security-and-advanced-search/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:05:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uh-oh-account-level-security-and-advanced-search/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m continually surprised that even with a decade of training experience, Dynamics GP users still uncover unexpected features. Just recently, during a class, a situation arose concerning account level security and the advanced search within the account lookup window.
For those unfamiliar with account level security, sometimes called organizational structures, this Dynamics GP feature allows you to organize users and general ledger accounts according to your company&amp;rsquo;s structure. This limits which accounts each user can access.</description></item><item><title>TXSHANTY and Tax Sheltered Deductions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/txshanty-and-tax-sheltered-deductions/</guid><description>Coming back from vacation and jumping right into a busy week, I encountered a strange issue with a client&amp;rsquo;s FUTA and SUTA taxable wages in their system. Here&amp;rsquo;s the situation:
We had a deduction set up initially as non-tax-sheltered. Later, this was changed to be tax-sheltered with specific tax boxes checked. While the general setup reflected this change, the existing deduction records for employees did not automatically update to reflect the new tax-sheltered status.</description></item><item><title>Should you report on a 1099 form or not?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-report-on-a-1099-form-or-not/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-report-on-a-1099-form-or-not/</guid><description>Recent Dynamics GP versions offer significant enhancements to 1099 tracking. The ability to track 1099 amounts by type and box at the transaction level enables more detailed tracking, eliminating the assumption that all vendor payments fall under the same 1099 type and box number.
Despite these advancements, comprehensive reporting features for reviewing this information by type and box are limited. While inquiries can be made easily (Inquiry&amp;ndash;Purchasing&amp;ndash;Vendor 1099 Details, Cards&amp;ndash;Purchasing&amp;ndash;1099 Details), these methods have limitations.</description></item><item><title>Did you forget about FUTA? Falling behind on SUTA? Take care of it immediately!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/did-you-forget-about-futa-falling-behind-on-suta-take-care-of-it-immediately/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find payroll errors, particularly with FUTA and SUTA taxes, even with careful planning. Issues arise when pay codes aren&amp;rsquo;t correctly classified for these taxes at setup or when employee payroll details are changed. Unlike other taxes, FUTA and SUTA discrepancies aren&amp;rsquo;t immediately obvious because they are calculated during period-end processing.
Manual correction of such errors, especially across multiple payrolls or employees, is tedious and error-prone. It involves reversing incorrect entries and re-entering them with the correct FUTA and SUTA classifications.</description></item><item><title>Degrees of Activity Tracking in Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/degrees-of-activity-tracking-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/degrees-of-activity-tracking-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>There are many ways to track changes in Microsoft Dynamics GP, and the best method depends on your specific needs and budget.
At a basic level, GP tracks who posted specific transactions, and when certain records were modified. The Human Resources module allows tracking of pay and position changes, including the reason for the change. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t track the values before and after the change. Additionally, you can control who can post transactions and access specific information through posting setup and security settings.</description></item><item><title>SQL Reporting Services, Dynamics GP, and Report Models can be frustrating.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 20:12:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sql-reporting-services-dynamics-gp-and-report-models-can-be-frustrating/</guid><description>I really enjoy using SQL Reporting Services and Dynamics GP, especially the standard reports included with Dynamics GP. However, I feel a slight dread when asked to modify one, and I&amp;rsquo;m not even a developer!
Why the apprehension? I might be revealing my non-technical side, but reports based on report models make me particularly nervous. Sometimes, I&amp;rsquo;m lucky and the necessary field is already there, requiring just minor adjustments. However, a recent request wasn&amp;rsquo;t so straightforward.</description></item><item><title>Dance with the one who brought you - Fixing transactions in Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dance-with-the-one-who-brought-you-fixing-transactions-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>It seems many questions on Dynamics GP forums revolve around fixing transactions, or even worse, how fixing one transaction created more problems. When I train, I emphasize &amp;ldquo;Dance with the one who brung &amp;lsquo;ya,&amp;rdquo; meaning corrections should happen where the transaction originated. During my support shifts, I get asked &amp;ldquo;how do I fix this?&amp;rdquo; a lot. I always start with these questions:
What&amp;rsquo;s been tried already? Often, attempts to fix the issue made it worse.</description></item><item><title>Tax-Free Holiday!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</guid><description>Last week, a client reached out because their employees&amp;rsquo; state taxes weren&amp;rsquo;t being calculated correctly, despite seemingly accurate setup in the system.
Everything appeared properly configured: state tax assignments, default state codes, pay codes subject to state tax, and transaction entries. However, upon examining the build and calculate reports, the state tax was present in the build report but missing from the calculation. The culprit? The default filing status for that state&amp;rsquo;s tax code was set to 0%.</description></item><item><title>Unusual Quick Journal Entry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unusual-quick-journal-entry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unusual-quick-journal-entry/</guid><description>A client recently encountered an unusual problem with quick journals in Microsoft Dynamics GP. It turns out this is a known issue, but the likelihood of Microsoft resolving it is low due to the small number of users affected.
For those unfamiliar with quick journals, they let you create templates for journal entries that automatically balance. You provide all the details except one line, and the system calculates the remaining amount to ensure the entry balances.</description></item><item><title>Resources for supporting partners in Dynamics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-supporting-partners-in-dynamics/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 05:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-supporting-partners-in-dynamics/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely already familiar with various online forums, including those hosted by Microsoft and independent ones like Experts Exchange and Egghead Cafe. However, I wanted to remind you about the specific resources available to Dynamics partners. You can find links to these on https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/resources/discussions/.
Beyond public forums, there are private ones exclusively for partners and, my favorite, the partner online technical communities managed by Microsoft Dynamics support. These communities offer a valuable way to expand your knowledge base and utilize your support plan without submitting a formal case.</description></item><item><title>What is Sustainable Development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-sustainable-development/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 11:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-sustainable-development/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;sustainability&amp;rdquo; is frequently used in business discussions today, often connected to ideas like continuous growth or reducing environmental impact. It seems like everything from snack foods to vehicles is labeled as &amp;ldquo;sustainable.&amp;rdquo; But what does sustainable development mean in the context of Microsoft Dynamics GP?
Before diving in, I have to admit that I&amp;rsquo;m not a developer. I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from developers about their experiences. However, I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in enough functional and technical design processes to recognize patterns in customizations.</description></item><item><title>On Monday, we will be converging in Atlanta.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-monday-we-will-be-converging-in-atlanta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-monday-we-will-be-converging-in-atlanta/</guid><description>Yesterday was a great start to Convergence 2011 in Atlanta! We balanced successful lab work and managing a Sure Step study hall with a fun evening exploring the Georgia Aquarium and the World of Coca-Cola.
Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the labs, especially for GP – they&amp;rsquo;re impressive! There are some excellent demos for the upcoming GP 2010 R2 release, as well as self-guided and recorded labs covering SQL Reporting Services, Management Reporter, and various other analytical and customization tools for Dynamics GP.</description></item><item><title>Headaches at a high level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/headaches-at-a-high-level/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/headaches-at-a-high-level/</guid><description>In my recent work, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering how to best approach &amp;ldquo;high-level&amp;rdquo; project estimates, especially when they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for a client&amp;rsquo;s budget planning. While a &amp;ldquo;ballpark&amp;rdquo; figure is implied, the need for realism remains essential.
One challenge I face is finding the right balance between being overly prepared and providing a rough estimate. When a project is done, how much variance is acceptable from that initial high-level estimate? Is it 10%, 25%, or even 50%?</description></item><item><title>The Dynamics GP window is either not visible or has been hidden.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dynamics-gp-window-is-either-not-visible-or-has-been-hidden/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 15:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dynamics-gp-window-is-either-not-visible-or-has-been-hidden/</guid><description>I recently encountered a strange issue with GP 10 on a remote Terminal Server. After minimizing the main GP 10 window and disconnecting, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resize or maximize the window upon reconnecting. It remained stuck in the taskbar.
Closing and reopening GP 10 didn&amp;rsquo;t resolve the problem, nor did logging out and back in.
I remembered that a configuration file stores window location data, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t encountered this specific problem in years.</description></item><item><title>Do you approve or disapprove? The Setup Checklist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-approve-or-disapprove-the-setup-checklist/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 02:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-approve-or-disapprove-the-setup-checklist/</guid><description>Every Dynamics GP implementation presents the challenge of effectively training users during the configuration phase. I admit, I was hesitant to embrace the setup checklist (Microsoft Dynamics GP&amp;raquo;Tools&amp;raquo;Setup&amp;raquo;Setup Checklist) at first. However, I recently decided to give it another try.
For those unfamiliar, the Setup Checklist grants users access to most setup screens needed for system configuration. This tool is valuable because it presents tasks in the required order, preventing unnecessary jumping between modules.</description></item><item><title>Are local taxes established as deductions?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-local-taxes-established-as-deductions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 22:45:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-local-taxes-established-as-deductions/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common for local taxes like earnings or &amp;ldquo;head&amp;rdquo; taxes to be set up as deductions in payroll systems. These taxes often have income thresholds, like Denver&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;head&amp;rdquo; tax, which only affects individuals earning over $500 monthly.
However, common payroll software may not calculate thresholds based on periods other than per pay period, year-to-date, or life-to-date. This limitation might force you to handle monthly thresholds differently.
Using deductions for tracking local taxes offers flexibility but can cause issues during year-end processing.</description></item><item><title>The benefits of reading old, high-quality reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-reading-old-high-quality-reports/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-reading-old-high-quality-reports/</guid><description>Occasionally, you might come across an old quality report mentioned in a knowledge base article. Often, these reports seem irrelevant to current issues, having been resolved in past software versions. However, my experience today highlighted how these outdated reports can sometimes provide valuable insights into current problems.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the situation: A client contacted me about duplicate records appearing in their RM30501 (Commission History) table. They handle commissions upon invoice posting, not payment.</description></item><item><title>Don't forget to take advantage of your 401k match and ensure you receive all of your money!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-forget-to-take-advantage-of-your-401k-match-and-ensure-you-receive-all-of-your-money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-forget-to-take-advantage-of-your-401k-match-and-ensure-you-receive-all-of-your-money/</guid><description>Dynamics GP has become much better at managing typical 401(k) matching scenarios. However, due to the various components involved, a breakdown might be useful.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with a 50% match up to 5% scenario, where the employer matches half of the employee&amp;rsquo;s contribution, but only up to 5% of their gross wages. Achieving this requires setting up both a deduction (for the employee&amp;rsquo;s contribution) and a benefit (for the employer match).</description></item><item><title>Limits on credit and holds on the sales process</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limits-on-credit-and-holds-on-the-sales-process/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 06:29:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limits-on-credit-and-holds-on-the-sales-process/</guid><description>I recently wrote a blog post about sales process holds and wanted to highlight a useful benefit of using them with customer credit limits. If you&amp;rsquo;re unfamiliar with sales process holds, they are custom rules you can apply to sales documents like quotes, orders, and invoices. These holds can prevent actions such as printing, posting, fulfilling, or transferring and can be applied to individual documents, groups of documents, or specific document types.</description></item><item><title>Remember to bring your keys (and report your taxable wages)!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 08:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/remember-to-bring-your-keys-and-report-your-taxable-wages/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, there have been some recurring support cases related to taxable wages on the manual payroll checks window, particularly when starting with initial balances. Here are a few common issues:
Federal taxes are accurate, but Federal wages are incorrect. FICA/S and/or FICA/M are accurate, but the corresponding wages are incorrect. Federal wages don&amp;rsquo;t match FICA/M or FICA/S wages, and the reason is unclear. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down how these issues occur:</description></item><item><title>Database Dynamics. Information about the company.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/database-dynamics-information-about-the-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 19:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/database-dynamics-information-about-the-company/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s great to hear from you! It sounds like you&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying the fall weather. You&amp;rsquo;ve also reminded me about something crucial: the importance of the Dynamics database when restoring a system. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook the fact that while many settings are stored within each company&amp;rsquo;s database, some vital components reside in the Dynamics database itself.
If the Dynamics database restore point predates a company&amp;rsquo;s setup, you&amp;rsquo;ll encounter some issues.</description></item><item><title>Lesson Learned: Tax Details Importation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lesson-learned-tax-details-importation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lesson-learned-tax-details-importation/</guid><description>A client recently inquired about manually setting up numerous tax details in Dynamics GP during a testing phase. Since this involved both a live and a test database, manual setup would be doubly time-consuming. Opting for a supposedly &amp;ldquo;quick&amp;rdquo; table import, a mistake was made.
While table imports themselves are not problematic, the assumption of speed was. Importing to the Sales/Purchases Tax Master (TX00201) table requires careful attention. Manually setting up a record beforehand is crucial to understand the appropriate settings for all fields, many of which have specific default values needed for the import.</description></item><item><title>Structure, Layout, Goose!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/structure-layout-goose/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 04:19:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/structure-layout-goose/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s break down account frameworks and formats in Microsoft Dynamics GP.
Account Framework: The Big Picture Think of the account framework as the maximum size for your chart of accounts. It&amp;rsquo;s set during the initial Dynamics GP installation, even before all the details are finalized. This is important because changing it later is a hassle. The framework impacts all companies within your Dynamics GP system, so consider everyone&amp;rsquo;s needs.
Technically, it can have up to 66 characters and 10 segments, but there are storage limits detailed in the installation guide.</description></item><item><title>Returned from Convergence 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</guid><description>Looking forward to Convergence 2013 in New Orleans! I enjoyed New Orleans, though San Diego remains my top pick. It was a successful event, even though it seemed to fly by. As always, the hands-on labs were a highlight, and I appreciated connecting with attendees, partners, and familiar faces. We had better access to the product teams this year, which provided valuable opportunities to interact with those who consistently support us.</description></item><item><title>I may not be Sherlock Holmes, but I can help you find missing deductions and benefits.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-may-not-be-sherlock-holmes-but-i-can-help-you-find-missing-deductions-and-benefits/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m in Denver this week providing training on reporting tools for Microsoft Dynamics GP, such as Report Writer, SmartList Builder, and SQL Reporting Services. A client asked for a report to identify employees not set up for Denver&amp;rsquo;s occupational tax. We use a specific benefit and deduction code in the system (&amp;ldquo;head tax&amp;rdquo;) instead of the standard local tax functionality.
Finding employees who are set up is simple. The challenge is identifying those who aren&amp;rsquo;t, especially when they have other benefits and deductions.</description></item><item><title>Sourcing default accounts for project accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:50:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sourcing-default-accounts-for-project-accounting/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently managing multiple project accounting implementations. When dealing with several similar projects simultaneously, I concentrate on common aspects. Recently, my focus has been on the default project account configuration in Dynamics GP (Tools&amp;raquo;Setup&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;Accounts). Explaining this to clients who inquire about how the project determines account usage is interesting. The answer usually depends on their setup.
Default posting accounts in Dynamics GP&amp;rsquo;s core modules are straightforward. The system prioritizes the master record for account specifications.</description></item><item><title>Have you heard about Project Macros?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-heard-about-project-macros/</guid><description>Have you ever been surprised after adding project accounting to Dynamics GP, only to find that users are constantly asked if they want to include project details when entering purchase orders?
You might already know that GP support offers macros for both customers and vendors. These tools automatically set default project settings, eliminating the need for manual entry or repetitive prompts.
For additional information, please reach out to me at christinap@theknastergroup.</description></item><item><title>Incorporating Employer Tax Fields into Payroll Check Register</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 14:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/incorporating-employer-tax-fields-into-payroll-check-register/</guid><description>This month, we encountered a strange issue. A client reported a discrepancy between the payroll Check Register printed immediately after payroll posting and the same report reprinted later using Reports-Payroll-Reprint Journals-Check Register.
Both the standard and reprinted Check Register reports usually combine Employer FICA taxes into a single &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA Owed&amp;rdquo; field. However, the client&amp;rsquo;s reports displayed this amount split into two additional fields: &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA/Social Security&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Employer FICA/Medicare.&amp;rdquo; Since these fields aren&amp;rsquo;t standard, we knew the reports were customized, which we verified through Microsoft Dynamics GP customization tools.</description></item><item><title>Excel Report Extravaganza</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excel-report-extravaganza/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excel-report-extravaganza/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of you already know this, but it&amp;rsquo;s easy to forget about useful features, so I wanted to share a quick reminder.
Dynamics GP 10.0&amp;rsquo;s Excel Reports is a good example. I often train people on it, but it seemed like users weren&amp;rsquo;t adopting it. It turns out, they just needed a little nudge. I used to always look for reports first, but a coworker helped me realize Smartlists could often provide the same information.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of the Troublesome Window and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 11:13:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mystery-of-the-troublesome-window-and-security/</guid><description>It can be frustrating when setting up security in GP 10.0 (or GP 2010). Take limiting access to payroll data, for instance. You disable the Payroll Clerk role, thinking that&amp;rsquo;s enough, but then you test it and find various Payroll windows still accessible.
While the Payroll Clerk role manages transactions and cards, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t cover setup, utilities, routines, reports, Smartlists, or inquiries. Even after removing relevant tasks and roles, like those within the Accounting Manager role, some windows remain stubbornly visible.</description></item><item><title>Basic: Arrears Deductions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 20:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/basic-arrears-deductions/</guid><description>When new software features are released, they are often overlooked or considered too complex for users to implement. One valuable feature that deserves attention is Deductions in Arrears (DIA), introduced in Payroll Extensions for GP 10.0. This feature simplifies payroll processing when dealing with part-time or seasonal employees whose earnings may not cover their deductions.
DIA automatically tracks any deductions that are not fully paid due to insufficient wages. It then recovers these arrears in subsequent payrolls until the obligation is settled.</description></item><item><title>Tips and Tricks for Troubleshooting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-troubleshooting/</guid><description>I often find myself surprised at how effective simple troubleshooting steps can be in resolving problems. When I&amp;rsquo;m stuck on an issue, these five steps are my go-to solutions:
Does the issue affect everyone? This helps determine if the problem originates from a specific workstation or user. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to test both as a regular user and as &amp;lsquo;sa&amp;rsquo;. Does it impact all companies? This helps isolate whether the issue stems from the data or affects the entire system.</description></item><item><title>Were you aware of the Extender Setup process?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-you-aware-of-the-extender-setup-process/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-you-aware-of-the-extender-setup-process/</guid><description>As someone who frequently reviews training materials, I recently came across an interesting note in the Microsoft Dynamics GP Extender manual. The manual advises users to only enable the &amp;ldquo;Auto-Update SmartLists&amp;rdquo; option in a single company within Extender&amp;rsquo;s options.
This recommendation stems from the system-wide nature of SmartLists contrasting with the company-specific design of Extender windows. The suggested approach is to designate a &amp;ldquo;main&amp;rdquo; company where this option is enabled, perform all Extender configurations within that company, and then export and import the necessary windows to other companies as needed.</description></item><item><title>Inadequate Dynamics GP Opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inadequate-dynamics-gp-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 12:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inadequate-dynamics-gp-opportunities/</guid><description>One underappreciated feature in Dynamics GP is the Sales Prospect Maintenance window, found under Cards -&amp;gt; Sales -&amp;gt; Prospects. This feature lets users input potential customers separately from existing customer records. This separation is useful for integrating external CRM systems with Dynamics GP, allowing for review and validation before converting prospects to customers.
Customers are kept in the RM00101 table, while Prospects are in the SOP00200 table. Prospects have fewer fields than customers, lacking details like Address ID, salesperson, territory, and those found in the Customer Options window.</description></item><item><title>The SanScript Library could not be loaded, and Integration Manager is affected.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanscript-library-could-not-be-loaded-and-integration-manager-is-affected/</guid><description>Towards the end of the previous month, a client reached out for help with their Dynamics GP year-end update. After resolving that, they described a separate Integration Manager problem that a previous consultant couldn&amp;rsquo;t fix, even after resorting to completely reinstalling the system. Intrigued, I decided to investigate further.
The client demonstrated that when running an integration on a specific machine, it would initially start but then fail with the error message &amp;ldquo;Unable to load SanScript Library.</description></item><item><title>Templates for Word and Synchronization</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/templates-for-word-and-synchronization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/templates-for-word-and-synchronization/</guid><description>The Developing for Dynamics GP blog came to the rescue once more! A Microsoft Word template field wasn&amp;rsquo;t printing, causing much frustration, until a helpful article on the blog provided a solution. For anyone experiencing similar issues where fields don&amp;rsquo;t appear on the template, but print fine within the GP report, this article is a lifesaver.
http://blogs.msdn.com/b/developingfordynamicsgp/archive/2011/05/06/keeping-word-templates-in-synch-with-report-writer.aspx
Christina Phillips, a Microsoft Certified Trainer and Dynamics GP Certified Professional, is a supervising consultant at BKD Technologies.</description></item><item><title>Identifying a GP 10 security task that is providing unauthorized access to a window.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-a-gp-10-security-task-that-is-providing-unauthorized-access-to-a-window/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:03:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-a-gp-10-security-task-that-is-providing-unauthorized-access-to-a-window/</guid><description>While I appreciate the design of GP 10&amp;rsquo;s security model, I find the process of setting up security roles and tasks to be rather cumbersome. Thankfully, I don&amp;rsquo;t have to do it very often.
GP 2010 has some improvements that make configuring security easier. However, for those still using GP 10, researching specific security settings can be challenging.
I recently addressed a question about GP 10 security where a user wanted to restrict access to particular SmartLists.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy the Payroll FICA Fun!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-payroll-fica-fun/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m sharing Michael Lupro&amp;rsquo;s recent blog post about the changes to FICA rates. The post highlights the different rates for employees and employers, which may require manual adjustments in Great Plains until a system update is available to address this discrepancy.
http://btosteam.blogspot.com/2011/01/manual-employer-fica-tax-calculations.html</description></item><item><title>Changes are happening quickly, including the implementation of "Checks on the fly.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-are-happening-quickly-including-the-implementation-of-checks-on-the-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 06:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changes-are-happening-quickly-including-the-implementation-of-checks-on-the-fly/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss printing &amp;ldquo;checks on the fly&amp;rdquo; in Microsoft Dynamics GP. A &amp;ldquo;check on the fly&amp;rdquo; is printed directly from the Payables Transaction Entry window by entering an amount in the check field and clicking &amp;ldquo;Print Check.&amp;rdquo; This action simultaneously records a check alongside the invoice and adjusts both cash and expense distributions.
Transactions-Purchasing-Transaction Entry
What happens if you need to make a correction after printing? Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can modify:</description></item><item><title>Is More Always Better? Or Less?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-more-always-better-or-less/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-more-always-better-or-less/</guid><description>While I appreciate a wealth of information, sometimes less is more, especially when dealing with large volumes of data. Too much information can lead to wasted time and frustration.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate this with posting in Dynamics GP. In Posting Setup (Tools&amp;raquo;Setup&amp;raquo;Posting&amp;raquo;Posting), you control posting details with the &amp;ldquo;Create a Journal Entry Per&amp;rdquo; setting. Choosing &amp;ldquo;Transaction&amp;rdquo; is akin to posting in &amp;ldquo;detail&amp;rdquo; mode. Every transaction within the chosen series and origin creates a separate journal entry in the General Ledger.</description></item><item><title>Things that I adore about SQL Reporting Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/things-that-i-adore-about-sql-reporting-services/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;ve been rather quiet online lately, I can assure you it&amp;rsquo;s not due to a lack of things to share! My recent travels and the beautiful spring weather have lured me away from my computer.
However, SQL Reporting Services has been on my mind, particularly with recent client projects and an upcoming training session I&amp;rsquo;m delivering on using it with Microsoft Dynamics GP 10.0. Revisiting the material has reminded me of some useful features I tend to overlook.</description></item><item><title>Choose blogs that start with [%] in the Smartlist.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-blogs-that-start-with-in-the-smartlist/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 18:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-blogs-that-start-with-in-the-smartlist/</guid><description>Last week, I encountered a simple but frustrating issue. I needed to find all payables transactions with a document number starting with a percent sign. The client used this to flag specific invoices for further processing.
I created a Payables Transaction SmartList in Microsoft Dynamics GP with the following criteria: Document Number begins with %, Vendor ID is &amp;lsquo;XYZ&amp;rsquo;, Document Amount is between $50 and $5,000, and Document Date is between 01/01/2023 and 01/31/2023.</description></item><item><title>Setting up a Dynamics GP Data Source Name on a 64-bit Windows operating system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-a-dynamics-gp-data-source-name-on-a-64-bit-windows-operating-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:46:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-a-dynamics-gp-data-source-name-on-a-64-bit-windows-operating-system/</guid><description>This article addresses the issue of a Dynamics GP DSN not appearing in the application, even when it&amp;rsquo;s visible in the Data Sources window. This commonly happens on 64-bit Windows systems.
Dynamics GP, being a 32-bit application, needs a 32-bit ODBC Data Source Name (DSN) to connect to SQL Server. While DSN setup is usually straightforward, problems arise on 64-bit Windows versions.
The standard method of setting up a DSN using Administrative Tools &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Data Sources utilizes the 64-bit ODBC Administrator.</description></item><item><title>Including Additional Fields in Word Templates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/including-additional-fields-in-word-templates/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:05:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/including-additional-fields-in-word-templates/</guid><description>Adding fields to a Word Template in Microsoft Dynamics GP is simpler than it might seem. Take adding an order date to an SOP Blank Invoice Word Template as an example.
First, you need to add the order date field to the Report Writer report, which provides the data (XML) for the Word Template. This is done in Report Writer (found under Microsoft Dynamics GP - Tools - Customize). Place the field in the appropriate report section.</description></item><item><title>Avoid Payroll and Tips at all costs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-payroll-and-tips-at-all-costs/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m not a fan of handling payroll, tips, sales tax, and analytical accounting, I recently discovered something interesting in Dynamics GP. Tax-sheltered deductions (TSAs) can affect how tips are taxed. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at an example:
We have Adam Smith, an employee paid hourly with a rate of $15/hr. He also earns tips and has a tax-sheltered health deduction of $10 per pay period, exempt from federal and FICA taxes.</description></item><item><title>Importing tables is not always seen as the less attractive option.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/importing-tables-is-not-always-seen-as-the-less-attractive-option/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/importing-tables-is-not-always-seen-as-the-less-attractive-option/</guid><description>I usually avoid using table imports and prefer alternative methods like Integration Manager, direct SQL queries, or eConnect whenever possible. However, I&amp;rsquo;m reminded from time to time about the simplicity and effectiveness of this approach.
Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a project with a tight deadline, striving to minimize manual data entry. I encountered several instances where Integration Manager wasn&amp;rsquo;t suitable for importing data, making table import a valuable solution. I successfully used it to import data into straightforward tables like:</description></item><item><title>Simplified Sales Tax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-sales-tax/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-sales-tax/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of talk about sales tax on the Dynamics GP forums. Let&amp;rsquo;s break down this complex topic into three manageable steps:
Document Default: This step determines the initial tax schedule that appears on a document. Item or Setup Default: This step considers whether you&amp;rsquo;re working with Receivables or Sales Order Processing to determine the default tax schedule. Tax Schedule Comparison: This step compares the tax schedules from the previous steps to determine the final tax calculation.</description></item><item><title>Hello, I'm Christina and I genuinely enjoy using modifiers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hello-i-m-christina-and-i-genuinely-enjoy-using-modifiers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 09:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hello-i-m-christina-and-i-genuinely-enjoy-using-modifiers/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common for people to complain and strive for perfection, especially when it comes to tools and their functionality. We often find flaws and desire improvements. This reminds me of a situation where I was tasked with reviewing a Dexterity customization. While people often underestimate Modifier, in this case, it proved to be the ideal solution.
The Dexterity customization was simple, consisting of six modified windows with cosmetic changes like field size and header rearrangements.</description></item><item><title>Caution: Implementation Trauma Upcoming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in Indianapolis for work and, despite a looming deadline for my blog post, I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit short on inspiration. It could be the post-holiday slump, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m prepping for a training session tomorrow. Either way, I&amp;rsquo;m hoping my readers will bear with me!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of training and study hall sessions for Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me reflect on some common pitfalls I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered during implementations.</description></item><item><title>Solving the Puzzle: Exploring Report Options and Report Groups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-puzzle-exploring-report-options-and-report-groups/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solving-the-puzzle-exploring-report-options-and-report-groups/</guid><description>(UPDATED 8/9/2011) Thanks to Mariano Gomez for clarifying this!
While user guides mention a 32-report limit per report group (e.g., Reports-Financial-Groups), you can easily create more groups to bypass this.
However, a bigger issue arises with report options within a report. For instance, the &amp;ldquo;Reports-Financial-Trial Balance&amp;rdquo; might have 33 report options:
[Image of Trial Balance Report window with 33 report options]
If you then try adding some of these options, particularly the 33rd, to a new report group (&amp;ldquo;Reports-Financial-Groups&amp;rdquo;):</description></item><item><title>Simplified Sales Tax Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-sales-tax-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:18:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplified-sales-tax-part-2/</guid><description>This post clarifies how inventory impacts sales tax calculations in Sales Order and Purchase Order Processing. We&amp;rsquo;ll build upon the three-step tax calculation process from the previous post: Document Default, Line Item Default, and Tax Schedule Comparison.
While still called a &amp;ldquo;document&amp;rdquo; default, the Shipping Method and Site information influencing the default tax schedule is actually stored by line item because they can differ. For example, in Sales Order Processing, a &amp;ldquo;Shipping Method Delivery&amp;rdquo; would default to the tax schedule associated with the Customer&amp;rsquo;s Ship To Address, while &amp;ldquo;Shipping Method Pickup&amp;rdquo; defaults to the Site&amp;rsquo;s tax schedule.</description></item><item><title>What programming language do Dynamics GP Developers use?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-programming-language-do-dynamics-gp-developers-use/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-programming-language-do-dynamics-gp-developers-use/</guid><description>This blog post is geared towards &amp;ldquo;GP Developers&amp;rdquo;.
The author has been working with Visual Basic since the mid-1990s and transitioned to VB.NET in 2007. While the author has experience in C++ and C#, they primarily used VB.NET for its ease of transition. However, after learning about Object-Oriented (OO) application architecture in .NET, the author sees advantages in using C# for OO programming.
Specifically, the author highlights that VB.NET&amp;rsquo;s method of handling Class Constructors, while convenient, can be less intuitive than the C# approach.</description></item><item><title>The World Order That Isn't So New - Variances in Costs and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-order-that-isn-t-so-new-variances-in-costs-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-order-that-isn-t-so-new-variances-in-costs-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>In the past, Dynamics GP calculated cost variances for FIFO/LIFO perpetual valuation method items during purchase order processing, sales order processing, or inventory control. These variances were not always posted to the general ledger. Users were frequently reminded of the significance of reviewing the Cost Variance Journal. However, this changed with the release of Dynamics GP 9.0.
While articles about cost variances exist, many seem outdated or inaccurate, especially regarding changes introduced in version 9.</description></item><item><title>Tracking activities in Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-activities-in-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 05:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tracking-activities-in-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>This blog has relocated to https://blog.steveendow.com/. All future content will be published there.
It&amp;rsquo;s not unusual for me to get questions about viewing Dynamics GP security and access logs, specifically about who logged in and when. This usually comes up when clients need to investigate a past issue. However, GP doesn&amp;rsquo;t inherently log these events, so this type of data typically doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist.
For those who see the need for such logs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring Dynamics GP&amp;rsquo;s Activity Tracking feature.</description></item><item><title>A brief post on my love for Management Reporter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:56:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-brief-post-on-my-love-for-management-reporter/</guid><description>Stuck in an airport with a four-hour delay on my way to our yearly customer event in Denver, I decided to share some quick thoughts on Management Reporter. I&amp;rsquo;ve been increasingly impressed with it. While some features are still in development, I&amp;rsquo;m confident they will be available soon. In the meantime, here are a few things that make it incredibly useful:
Adding dimensions like account categories or analytical accounting details is incredibly simple.</description></item><item><title>Sales Tax Information is being loaded.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sales-tax-information-is-being-loaded/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 20:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sales-tax-information-is-being-loaded/</guid><description>In a recent project, I needed to create Tax Schedules in Dynamics GP using a spreadsheet containing customer data, zip codes, and their respective city, state, and local tax rates. I developed a series of scripts to import this data from Excel and wanted to share them to potentially benefit others. In this scenario, the tax details were already in Dynamics GP, and the spreadsheet used their corresponding Tax Detail IDs.</description></item><item><title>Are you Sure Step Certified, or just Certifiable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/</guid><description>I came across a helpful blog post by a European Sure Step trainer that offers valuable advice for those preparing for the Sure Step exam. I recommend reading the comments too, as they address common concerns about Sure Step that I often hear.
While Sure Step offers a wide range of tools, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that improvement is a gradual process. Focus on identifying areas within your organization that need enhancement, and then leverage the Sure Step guidance to address those specific areas.</description></item><item><title>Alternative uses for existing products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 13:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-uses-for-existing-products/</guid><description>A client needed a system to track expenses online. They were looking for a basic solution and found the popular options too expensive. While searching for alternatives, I realized they already owned a software called Project Accounting, but weren&amp;rsquo;t using its expense features.
We decided to implement the Time and Expense portion of their existing software to meet their needs. This was a much more affordable option, especially since they didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full functionality of the software.</description></item><item><title>GP Multi-Company SmartLists - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:19:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-2/</guid><description>In the first part of this series, we discussed a scenario where a centralized accounting team could benefit from SmartLists that query data from multiple Dynamics GP company databases. We then covered the fundamentals of creating multi-company views as the foundation for these SmartLists.
Before continuing, let&amp;rsquo;s address the Bonus Quiz from Part 1. The missing step to enable adding a custom view to a new SmartList in SmartList Builder involves SQL Server database security settings.</description></item><item><title>Allocating project costs by unit for accounting purposes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 19:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allocating-project-costs-by-unit-for-accounting-purposes/</guid><description>While stuck in a Denver hotel room during a snowstorm, I finally had a chance to unravel a feature in our project management software.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been curious about the Project Allocation feature since its release last summer but haven&amp;rsquo;t had a project that required it. My initial exploration didn&amp;rsquo;t help me grasp its capabilities compared to the Unit allocation method at the Cost Category level. However, last night&amp;rsquo;s testing session brought some clarity.</description></item><item><title>Error in procedure zDT_UPR00100U: Object name is invalid.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-procedure-zdt-upr00100u-object-name-is-invalid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 05:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/error-in-procedure-zdt-upr00100u-object-name-is-invalid/</guid><description>Creating a test copy of a production database is standard practice for testing with current data.
After restoring a production database copy to a test environment, it&amp;rsquo;s common to run a script to update database name references, ensuring everything points to the test database.
However, while working with a GP 10 test database, I encountered an error related to creating or retrieving employee records, stating that the &amp;lsquo;UPR_MSTR&amp;rsquo; table couldn&amp;rsquo;t be found.</description></item><item><title>Setting up the item: Where it all begins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</guid><description>My recent focus on Sure Step training reminded me how crucial item setup is. Many Sales Order Processing (SOP) and Purchase Order Processing (POP) problems stem from those initial item setup choices. Users might misunderstand how the system works, not realizing their settings are dictating the behavior – settings that are often easy to change. This happens because setup and transaction entry are often done by different people, or so much time has passed that the reasoning behind setup decisions is forgotten (hence the need for good documentation, though I doubt my coworkers would be thrilled to hear that again).</description></item><item><title>One, two, SQL Report Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/one-two-sql-report-security/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 05:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/one-two-sql-report-security/</guid><description>Microsoft Dynamics GP offers a valuable feature: standard SQL Reporting Services (SSRS) reports. These reports are beneficial for several reasons: they can be accessed online by individuals without GP accounts, they can be easily exported to Excel or Word, users can modify them and retrieve extra information, they allow for custom reports using standard report models, and they offer subscription features that send reports directly to your inbox.
While I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of SSRS reports, this post will focus on their security aspects.</description></item><item><title>Modifying PO Distributions in Summary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</guid><description>Since the release of service packs GP 10 (SP2 and later) and GP 9 (SP3 and later), users can no longer make changes to summary distributions in Receivings Transaction Entry and Purchasing Invoice Entry. Instead, they must access the Item Detail expansion and adjust the account assigned to the line item.
While this change makes sense from an inventory management perspective, as reconciling inventory with the general ledger was difficult when summary distributions could be modified, it has made the process more complex for clients who use the POP module without inventory.</description></item><item><title>The trauma of implementation persisted.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-trauma-of-implementation-persisted/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-trauma-of-implementation-persisted/</guid><description>A few weeks back, I promised a deeper dive into the top five implementation mistakes for both clients and consultants. Let&amp;rsquo;s address the biggest misstep for both groups:
For consultants: Assuming you alone determine the project&amp;rsquo;s success or failure.
For clients: Assuming the consulting team solely dictates the project&amp;rsquo;s success or failure.
Taking sole responsibility for a project is problematic for both parties. Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with Suzy&amp;rsquo;s story. Suzy, a stellar consultant, is adored by her clients.</description></item><item><title>Discover this hidden gem by reviewing the distribution report.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 22:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/</guid><description>Need a way to see which invoices were paid by a specific check, or view the payment details for those invoices? Users often ask for this information, but it can be tricky to find in Microsoft Dynamics GP. The SmartList feature isn&amp;rsquo;t ideal (unless you have SmartList Builder and even then, it takes some setup) because one check can pay multiple invoices.
A simple solution, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t have SmartList Builder, is the Check Distribution Report.</description></item><item><title>Increasing the minimum amount for garnishments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 06:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-the-minimum-amount-for-garnishments/</guid><description>It can feel overwhelming trying to understand the numerous ways to calculate garnishments across different agencies. While the standard garnishment feature in Dynamics GP works well for single garnishments, more complex scenarios with multiple garnishments often necessitate the use of the Greenshades Garnishments module.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what Dynamics GP can handle independently. A recent example involved these requirements:
The initial $150 of the employee&amp;rsquo;s eligible earnings are exempt from garnishment. If earnings fall between $150 and $200, only the amount exceeding $150 is subject to garnishment.</description></item><item><title>Why is it important to consider User Classes?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-is-it-important-to-consider-user-classes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:48:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-is-it-important-to-consider-user-classes/</guid><description>In recent Dynamics GP versions, security roles, tasks, and operations have become the preferred way to manage user security, replacing the older user class model. This shift leads many to question the continued relevance of user classes in Dynamics GP.
Microsoft Dynamics GP-Tools-Setup-System-User Classes
Users are assigned to a class in Setup-System-Users
Despite this shift, user classes still offer several advantages within Dynamics GP. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these benefits.</description></item><item><title>SmartList and Year End: A love affair.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-and-year-end-a-love-affair/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 22:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartlist-and-year-end-a-love-affair/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of SmartList, especially with the added power of SmartList Builder. While we save that for later, let&amp;rsquo;s focus on basic SmartList uses for year-end tasks. I&amp;rsquo;m preparing a presentation on this and want to share some of my top SmartLists.
Here they are, in no specific order:
1099 Transaction Audit: Verify 1099 amounts against transaction details.
Use &amp;ldquo;Payables Transactions.&amp;rdquo; Add &amp;ldquo;Document Amount,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;1099 Amount,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;1099 Type&amp;rdquo; columns.</description></item><item><title>I'm not sure if my implementation methodology is working properly.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:59:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</guid><description>Christina and Steve rarely collaborate on blog posts due to the coordination involved, but they decided to team up to address common project failures. They believe that most project issues stem from flawed methodologies rather than individual mistakes. A structured implementation methodology like Sure Step can help avoid these problems.
Steve recounts instances where partners sought his help on troubled projects, needing him to fix integrations or customizations urgently and at discounted rates.</description></item><item><title>Resources for Dynamics GP and SharePoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/</guid><description>Clients are frequently asking about SharePoint, often in conversations about Business Portal and how to share Dynamics GP data with a wider, non-Dynamics GP user group. To help with these discussions, I&amp;rsquo;m sharing some resources I often use. Please feel free to share yours, and I&amp;rsquo;ll update the blog accordingly.
To clarify the differences between Windows SharePoint Services (WSS) and Microsoft Office SharePoint Server (MOSS), and other editions, refer to the SharePoint Edition Comparison: http://office.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible that there are multiple companies with multiple databases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-there-are-multiple-companies-with-multiple-databases/</guid><description>When a customer has multiple companies, it seems logical to assume they would need separate Dynamics GP databases for each. While this is often true, there are exceptions. Determining the best approach requires careful consideration.
There are several factors to analyze when deciding whether to create a dedicated database per company or consolidate them within a single database. Combining companies into one database is less common but can be the ideal solution in certain situations.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions About Year-End Payroll</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 23:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frequently-asked-questions-about-year-end-payroll/</guid><description>This information comes from a Microsoft and Terry Heley webinar and addresses common questions about FICA rate changes:
Q: I already applied the 2011 tax tables before creating the year-end wage file. What should I do? A: Change the FICA/Social Security tax rate back to 6.2% in the Payroll Tax setup. Then, create the year-end wage file and reset the rate to the 2011 value of 4.2%.
Q: Can I rebuild the year-end wage file using the above method if I already processed 2011 payrolls?</description></item><item><title>Quick Payroll Data Entry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 02:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-payroll-data-entry/</guid><description>During a recent payroll implementation and training, I was inspired to share some of my favorite tips for quicker payroll entry in Dynamics GP.
#1: Utilizing Payroll Mass Transaction Entry Many users overlook the Mass Entry window in Dynamics GP (Transactions&amp;raquo;Payroll&amp;raquo;Mass Entry), but it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly useful. Begin by choosing or creating a Batch ID for the transactions. Then, select a pay code, deduction, or benefit, and specify the date range and employee range using criteria like employee ID, class, department, or position.</description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs: Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 08:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about landed costs. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover the three main ways landed costs are used, building on the previous example of setting up insurance costs to connect insurance invoices with product shipments.
Three Ways to Use Landed Costs 1. Landed Costs by Line Item Assign a landed cost group to each line item upon receipt. This can be done by default (from item setup or the purchase order) or manually.</description></item><item><title>Learning Management Reporter Lessons the Hard Way Learning from the mistakes made in managing a reporter.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 20:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learning-management-reporter-lessons-the-hard-way-learning-from-the-mistakes-made-in-managing-a-reporter/</guid><description>Today, I encountered an interesting problem in Management Reporter related to consolidated multi-company reporting. It turns out that for this type of reporting, having identical account segment names across all involved companies is crucial.
Let me illustrate with an example. Imagine two companies, A and B. Both use a 4-2 account structure. However, Company A labels its account segments (accessible via Microsoft Dynamics GP &amp;gt; Tools &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; Company &amp;gt; Account Format) as &amp;ldquo;Main Account&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Department.</description></item><item><title>Buyer (or Surfer) Be Cautious!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 21:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</guid><description>Over the past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a few situations that highlight the internet&amp;rsquo;s potential, both good and bad, for software troubleshooting and learning, especially with Microsoft Dynamics GP.
For instance, I came across a Summit Group Software Blog post about recent changes to US Payroll for form 941. This was perfect timing, as I had just seen an internal email chain about it. The blog had valuable information from a reliable source that I could share, which was a great find.</description></item><item><title>Lessons learned from Management Reporter report distribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lessons-learned-from-management-reporter-report-distribution/</guid><description>Here are some helpful tips for using Management Reporter, especially for distributing reports:
Utilize Security Groups in the Report Viewer for folder security whenever possible. You can create these groups on the Security page in Management Reporter. When setting up a folder in the Reports Library, grant access to the group (right-click on the folder and choose Report Library Permissions). Now, any user added to this group will automatically have access to these folders.</description></item><item><title>Issue with Project Accounting Cost Category and Fee ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</guid><description>Last week, a client contacted me with a peculiar problem in Project Accounting. While their actual billings and payments/receipts matched in summary and detail, running the Cash Apply reconciliation (Tools&amp;raquo;Routines&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;PA Reconcile) incorrectly recalculated the payments/receipts as less than the actual billings. This discrepancy, equal to the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee charged on projects, was especially noticeable on projects with a single invoice and payment.
We investigated the database, comparing the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee setup to other fees, but found no differences.</description></item><item><title>Exciting Updates Ahead for HR and PR in Dynamics GP 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exciting-updates-ahead-for-hr-and-pr-in-dynamics-gp-2013/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic to hear about the exciting updates coming to the Human Resources and Payroll modules in Dynamics GP 2013, as shared by Terry Heley from Microsoft. Here are a few highlights:
A significant improvement is the direct integration of tools for managing deductions, benefits, and pay code modifiers. This user-friendly approach will make it much easier to modify pay codes, deduction codes, and benefit codes, enhancing user satisfaction.
Another valuable enhancement for users is the ability to choose whether or not to print alignments on checks and earnings statements.</description></item><item><title>Affordable Check and Signature Verification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/affordable-check-and-signature-verification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 12:15:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/affordable-check-and-signature-verification/</guid><description>While many third-party products offer enhanced check printing security for Microsoft Dynamics GP, most come with extra features like MICR printing that not all clients need or want. This often comes with additional costs. So, how can you control check printing in Microsoft Dynamics GP without relying on these products?
Enable Batch Posting Control Navigate to Tools &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; Posting &amp;gt; Posting and enable the option for batch approvals. Set a password for Series: Purchasing, Origin: Computer Checks.</description></item><item><title>Cool Free Stuff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cool-free-stuff/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 14:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cool-free-stuff/</guid><description>I frequently encounter questions that make me wonder why they haven&amp;rsquo;t been asked before. While the answers are rarely straightforward, I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that even if Dynamics GP doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a specific feature, there might be a free Professional Services Tool that bridges the gap.
For those unfamiliar, the Professional Services team provides an array of resources and tools to both customers and partners.
Partners can explore these resources at: https://mbs.microsoft.com/partnersource/resources/support/supportinformation/msdy_winwithexpressconsulting.htm</description></item><item><title>Practicing and Opinions on Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</guid><description>I recently co-trained a new course in Atlanta called &amp;ldquo;Project Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations with Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step&amp;rdquo; (Course 80053A). This course was paired with a one-day class, &amp;ldquo;Project Management Skills Essentials for Microsoft Dynamics,&amp;rdquo; developed by Kristi Honey and Scott Mertes.
The first day concentrated on the essential soft skills needed for each stage of an implementation. We had many engaging discussions throughout the day. It was a fantastic opportunity to gain insights from different perspectives on Dynamics implementation project management.</description></item><item><title>Vote now for the top 100 companies in the world!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-now-for-the-top-100-companies-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 10:45:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-now-for-the-top-100-companies-in-the-world/</guid><description>Being nominated for an award is always an honor, even if it&amp;rsquo;s a common sentiment. We want to express our gratitude to the Oscars for the recognition. Voting for Dynamics World&amp;rsquo;s Top 100 Most Influential Dynamics People list is officially open. Both Steve and I were pleasantly surprised and humbled to be nominated this year. Steve received his nomination for his technical blog posts that dive into the core of development issues and Dynamics GP.</description></item><item><title>Strange GL Reconciliation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strange-gl-reconciliation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strange-gl-reconciliation/</guid><description>While the Reconcile to GL feature in Microsoft Dynamics GP is helpful, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered some quirks. This tool simplifies subledger reconciliation by generating a spreadsheet of subledger and general ledger transactions, eliminating the need for manual Excel workarounds.
To use it, select the module (Payables or Receivables Management), specify the date range, and input the relevant accounts. The resulting spreadsheet categorizes transactions as matched, potentially matched, or unmatched, aiding in identifying discrepancies.</description></item><item><title>Directly depositing direct deposit information</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 19:13:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/directly-depositing-direct-deposit-information/</guid><description>When implementing payroll for smaller companies (fewer than 250 employees), manual data entry might be acceptable and even beneficial for data accuracy. However, with larger implementations, like my current project involving over 1500 employees across three companies, manual entry isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible.
While integration tools help import most payroll data, direct deposit information requires extra caution. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to avoid errors in account and routing numbers, making manual entry risky. Therefore, I use table imports for this specific data.</description></item><item><title>What is the Recapture Provision? I am not familiar with it.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-recapture-provision-i-am-not-familiar-with-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 07:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-recapture-provision-i-am-not-familiar-with-it/</guid><description>Several clients have inquired about the recapture provision in the extended payroll tax cut. This provision mandates a 6.2% tax on earnings exceeding a certain limit within the year&amp;rsquo;s first two months. The question arises: how is this implemented?
Fortunately, Terry Heley from Microsoft has written an informative blog post clarifying this provision and explaining why it&amp;rsquo;s not handled within GP.
http://blogs.msdn.com/b/dynamicsgp/archive/2012/01/05/payroll-tax-cut-temporarily-extended-into-2012-translated-so-a-user-can-understand-and-how-it-affects-microsoft-dynamics-gp.aspx
Take a look!
Christina Phillips is a Microsoft Certified Trainer and Dynamics GP Certified Professional.</description></item><item><title>Recommendations for books on accounting for IT professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recommendations-for-books-on-accounting-for-it-professionals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 20:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recommendations-for-books-on-accounting-for-it-professionals/</guid><description>IT professionals who support Microsoft Dynamics GP users often ask me for book recommendations to learn accounting basics. During my Dynamics GP training sessions for IT professionals, I suggest these two books to help them better support and manage their Dynamics GP systems.
McGraw-Hill 36 Hour Accounting Course (http://www.amazon.com/McGraw-Hill-36-Hour-Accounting-Course-Courses/dp/0071486038)
This book offers a comprehensive and concise introduction to accounting. Its structure allows readers to learn at their own pace, focusing on small sections at a time.</description></item><item><title>Is it relevant? Who cares?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 23:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</guid><description>Recently, I discussed staying relevant in a constantly evolving field with a respected colleague. As someone with potentially decades in my career ahead, this is a topic I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering, especially considering my specialization in Dynamics GP and how other technologies intersect with it. While I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with my current skill set, I wonder if I should branch out and explore standalone technologies.
My colleague reassured me that my experience, teaching abilities, and the continued relevance of Dynamics GP contribute to my value.</description></item><item><title>The third instance of Implementation Trauma!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 16:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/</guid><description>Many people have been eagerly anticipating a post about common problems in software implementation. This post addresses the third consulting and customer pitfalls, as identified through personal experience and teaching. The goal is to share these insights to help others avoid similar mistakes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s revisit the list of common pitfalls:
Top 5 Consulting Mistakes:
Believing you are solely responsible for the project&amp;rsquo;s success or failure. Neglecting customer service, even during challenging implementation phases.</description></item><item><title>GP Multi-Company SmartLists - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 08:26:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-multi-company-smartlists-part-1/</guid><description>Part 1: Creating Multi-Company SmartLists in Microsoft Dynamics GP 1. Introduction This series will guide you through creating SmartLists that combine data from multiple Dynamics GP companies. We&amp;rsquo;ll leverage SmartList Builder, custom SQL scripts, and address security considerations. This solution is particularly beneficial for organizations with numerous GP company databases managed centrally, such as Consolidated Property Corporation in our example.
While this solution involves SQL queries and Visual Basic scripting, each step will be broken down to make it manageable for those without extensive programming experience.</description></item><item><title>Tips and Tricks for the End of 2008</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-the-end-of-2008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 11:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-the-end-of-2008/</guid><description>The process of upgrading to GP 10 Service Pack 3 and applying the year-end update can be done from any computer, but it might be faster on the server. As a precaution, back up your reports.dic file before installing the GP 10 SP3/year-end update. After installation, rebuild the reports dictionary. After closing the year 2008, ensure your Dynamics GP user date is set in the new year to perform a check run.</description></item><item><title>Access Denied Party due to Unhandled Object Exception!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-denied-party-due-to-unhandled-object-exception/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 07:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-denied-party-due-to-unhandled-object-exception/</guid><description>Today, I came across a strange problem. A client could log into GP but got &amp;ldquo;Unhandled Object Exception&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Access Denied&amp;rdquo; errors when clicking on home pages or area pages. The &amp;ldquo;Unhandled Object Exceptions,&amp;rdquo; besides saying &amp;ldquo;Access Denied,&amp;rdquo; also mentioned &amp;ldquo;Error Calling Method Save,&amp;rdquo; pointing towards a permissions issue.
Some sources linked similar home page errors to missing files like &amp;ldquo;AreaPage.xsl,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;HomePage.css,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;HomePage.xsl,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;PreviewPane.xsl&amp;rdquo; in the Backgrounds folder. We checked, and the files were present.</description></item><item><title>In Support of Classifications (Inventory)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 16:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</guid><description>During a recent phone support session, I encountered a case that highlighted the often-overlooked advantages of using classes in Dynamics GP. While classes are generally known for providing default values, enabling changes to cascade down to records, and facilitating the grouping of records for tasks like reporting, their practical benefits go beyond these commonly recognized uses.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate this with an example from inventory management. When a new item is created manually (Cards&amp;raquo;Inventory&amp;raquo;Item), the option to maintain history is not enabled by default.</description></item><item><title>Kits, Bills of Materials, and Components - Oh, the Possibilities!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kits-bills-of-materials-and-components-oh-the-possibilities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 04:29:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kits-bills-of-materials-and-components-oh-the-possibilities/</guid><description>When examining the core functions of Kits and Bills of Materials (BOMs) in Dynamics GP, the differences appear straightforward: Kits combine items at the point of sale, while BOMs group items during the production of a finished good. Essentially, Kits are sales-focused, while BOMs are inventory-focused. Kits are assembled upon sale, whereas BOMs are created before the item is even available for sale.
While this seems simple, deciding between Kits and BOMs often sparks debate, even among experienced professionals.</description></item><item><title>Is Use Tax a Perfect Fit for Dynamics GP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-use-tax-a-perfect-fit-for-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-use-tax-a-perfect-fit-for-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>Use tax can be a headache for many businesses. While compliance is crucial, the volume doesn&amp;rsquo;t always justify investing in a dedicated software solution. For those using Dynamics GP with limited budgets, a workaround exists.
Cindy Boersma from BKD developed an effective process, and this article outlines the steps involved.
Step #1:
Within Dynamics GP, create a placeholder tax detail. Go to Tools &amp;gt; Setup &amp;gt; Company &amp;gt; Tax Detail. Configure it as &amp;ldquo;Purchases,&amp;rdquo; with &amp;ldquo;Percent of Sale/Purchase&amp;rdquo; as the basis, leaving the percentage at zero.</description></item><item><title>Forecaster.ini...or possibly outie?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/forecaster-ini-or-possibly-outie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 23:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/forecaster-ini-or-possibly-outie/</guid><description>Even though I have a baby at home who loves a good belly laugh, I wanted to share a helpful tip about Forecaster 7.0. Installing the Forecaster 7.0 client is straightforward, only requiring a few clicks to finish. After that, applying the service pack gets you up and running quickly.
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need to connect to existing Forecaster databases. You start the Forecaster client, but only the Demo database appears in the company list.</description></item><item><title>Differentiating GP Versions with Custom Icons</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differentiating-gp-versions-with-custom-icons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 23:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differentiating-gp-versions-with-custom-icons/</guid><description>I work with many different customers who use various versions of Dynamics GP, ranging from GP 9 to GP 2010 R2. While most rely on the core modules, some utilize Project Accounting, and a few work with Analytical Accounting. This setup requires me to maintain multiple GP versions across several virtual servers.
A minor inconvenience I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered is the identical icons for GP 10 and GP 2010. This makes it challenging to differentiate between them in the start menu, taskbar, and desktop when both versions are installed on the same server.</description></item><item><title>Ouch, Editing Direct Deposit Files</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ouch-editing-direct-deposit-files/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ouch-editing-direct-deposit-files/</guid><description>Generating ACH files in Dynamics GP can be tricky. Providing incorrect information, such as a wrong routing or account number, or voiding a direct deposit after payroll posting, results in an inaccurate ACH file.
The standard solution is voiding and re-running the entire payroll with the correct information. While this works for smaller companies, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for larger companies with substantial payrolls.
Manually editing the ACH file used to be a solution, but recent encoding changes, specifically &amp;ldquo;hash&amp;rdquo; entries created during file generation in GP, make this unreliable.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to use Report Builder 3.0 without SQL Reporting Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-use-report-builder-3-0-without-sql-reporting-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 04:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-use-report-builder-3-0-without-sql-reporting-services/</guid><description>Many people connect SQL Server 2008 R2 Report Builder (Report Builder 3.0) with SQL Server Reporting Services, which makes sense because using Report Builder with SQL Server Reporting Services allows you to share reports you create with others through the Report Manager website. However, many don&amp;rsquo;t realize that Report Builder 3.0 can function similarly to Crystal Reports, enabling you to create and run reports directly on your desktop without needing SQL Server Reporting Services.</description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</guid><description>Landed cost represents the total expense of getting an item to your location. This includes the item price plus charges like shipping, customs fees, and processing. More companies are focusing on landed costs as they increasingly source products from global suppliers and manufacturers. Using landed costs provides a more accurate view of the &amp;ldquo;total&amp;rdquo; cost, reflecting it in inventory value as an asset, rather than treating additional expenses separately.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with an example: you buy 100 widgets from a European supplier at $20 per widget.</description></item><item><title>Where oh where could my overtime be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-oh-where-could-my-overtime-be/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m seeking advice on a specific overtime calculation issue in Dynamics GP. While GP can calculate overtime based on exceeding a set number of hours within a pay period, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t consider daily or weekly overtime rules common in many locations.
For example, with biweekly pay and an 80-hour overtime threshold, exceeding 80 hours triggers overtime. However, GP doesn&amp;rsquo;t recognize situations where an employee works a 14-hour day within an 80-hour pay period, which could still qualify for overtime pay in many jurisdictions.</description></item><item><title>Ramblings on Project Accounting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ramblings-on-project-accounting/</guid><description>It can be lonely being a Microsoft Dynamics GP Project Accounting trainer because there aren&amp;rsquo;t many of us, and clients seem to use the module differently. This highlights a contradiction: Project Accounting is specialized yet serves diverse purposes. Through my experience, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned that thorough discovery, including pre-purchase discussions about realistic expectations and software fit, is crucial for successful implementation.
While Project Accounting fulfills many requirements and boosts productivity, it&amp;rsquo;s vital to understand its limitations, which can be addressed proactively during implementation:</description></item><item><title>The Payroll System Continues to Grow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 11:48:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-payroll-system-continues-to-grow/</guid><description>Over the last few months, many clients have asked me about additional modules for Payroll in Dynamics GP. While the base payroll module works well, companies seeking better efficiency and streamlined processes are looking for ways to expand its capabilities. For example, they might need to automate a previously manual process or switch from paper-based delivery to electronic methods like email or portals.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to share some options for improving payroll processing.</description></item><item><title>A straightforward approach: Managing the ego</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:54:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-straightforward-approach-managing-the-ego/</guid><description>I like to think of myself as a creative problem-solver. Finding ingenious solutions to complex issues is something I take pride in. With enough time and focus, my logic and reasoning skills (and a healthy dose of sarcasm) can usually crack the code.
However, today I encountered a real head-scratcher, a problem that genuinely stumped me (cue the sarcastic surprise). Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of the situation:
The client has been using project accounting since January 1, 2009, with no changes to their fiscal period setup.</description></item></channel></rss>