<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scottish Independence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scottish-independence/</link><description>Recent content in Scottish Independence on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scottish-independence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Scotland and Brexit: Courageous Heart or Fearful Creature?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scotland-and-brexit-courageous-heart-or-fearful-creature/</guid><description>Steve Peers
During the Scottish National Party (SNP) conference, Scotland&amp;rsquo;s First Minister, Nicola Sturgeon, revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to present a draft bill for a second independence referendum. She also announced their intention to introduce an alternate plan ensuring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the EU single market, even if the rest of the UK chooses to leave. This proposal would involve granting the Scottish Parliament substantial new powers, encompassing all current EU-related powers held by Scotland and additional authority to negotiate international treaties and manage immigration.</description></item><item><title>Legal Issues Surrounding Scotland, the EU, and 'Indyref2'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 08:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-issues-surrounding-scotland-the-eu-and-indyref2/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Scottish First Minister Nicola Sturgeon recently revealed the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s desire to pursue a second independence referendum. This announcement follows the UK government&amp;rsquo;s dismissal of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s proposed Brexit alternatives. The timing of this potential referendum, contingent on the UK&amp;rsquo;s final Brexit arrangements, brings Scotland&amp;rsquo;s EU membership into focus. While a second referendum would encompass issues beyond EU relations, this analysis will primarily address the legal complexities surrounding Scotland&amp;rsquo;s potential EU membership, particularly the misconception of budget deficits as a barrier to entry.</description></item></channel></rss>