<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DS3 Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ds3-connections/</link><description>Recent content in DS3 Connections on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ds3-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper DS3 Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</guid><description>Your business needs more bandwidth, but the price of a DS3 connection might seem daunting. While upgrading from a T1 line to a DS3 might have seemed expensive in the past, prices have gone down. Even with the current economic climate, a DS3 connection could now be within your budget.
DS3, or Data Service level 3, is a digital telecommunications standard initially designed for telephone systems. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the T-Carrier system and works seamlessly with SONET fiber optic networks.</description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>GigE For Business Not So Far-Fetched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</guid><description>The increasing demands of online technologies, particularly those using graphics and video, are putting pressure on Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. While ordering a T1 line was once a big decision, businesses may soon need to consider Gigabit Ethernet connections.
While Gigabit Ethernet is often associated with large-scale networks, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly relevant for businesses. With corporate LANs already transitioning to faster speeds, the WAN connection often becomes a bottleneck.</description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent.</description></item></channel></rss>