<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sentiment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sentiment/</link><description>Recent content in Sentiment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sentiment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business sentiment in Singapore for 2017 is characterized by caution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 09:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-sentiment-in-singapore-for-2017-is-characterized-by-caution/</guid><description>The Singapore government has released business sentiment data for 2017, covering both the manufacturing and retail sectors.
In the manufacturing sector, a survey conducted by the Singapore Economic Development Board revealed that a weighted 76% of firms expect business conditions in the first half of 2017 to remain similar to the previous quarter. While 13% anticipate improvement, 11% foresee a decline. Overall, the net weighted balance sits at 2%, indicating a slightly positive outlook for the manufacturing sector in early 2017.</description></item><item><title>Business confidence in China continues to be weak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</guid><description>While overall business confidence in China showed a slight improvement, activity declined in December as large companies continued to face weak demand and an uncertain business climate. According to MNI Indicators, a provider of economic data and analysis, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t anticipate significant improvement in early 2016. This is reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator, which remains close to the previous month&amp;rsquo;s low point.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator, a measure of current business sentiment, rose 5.</description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year.</description></item><item><title>Investment commitments in Singapore remain in a positive trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-commitments-in-singapore-remain-in-a-positive-trend/</guid><description>Global companies continued to view Singapore as a crucial base in Asia for expansion and innovation in 2016, with investment commitments meeting or exceeding the Economic Development Board (EDB)&amp;rsquo;s projections. The EDB remains committed to pursuing opportunities in thriving sectors to foster sustained economic growth and create quality employment prospects for Singaporeans.
Attracting S$9.4 billion in fixed asset investments, Singapore exceeded its forecast of S$8 billion to S$10 billion. Total business expenditure reached S$8.</description></item><item><title>CEOs express optimism about the global economy, according to PwC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 01:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</guid><description>Global business leaders are feeling positive about the economic climate in the near future, according to the 21st annual survey of CEOs conducted by PwC. The survey, which included approximately 1,300 CEOs from around the world, was released at the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland.
A significant majority (57%) of CEOs believe that global economic growth will improve in the next year. This represents a substantial increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 29% and marks the largest surge in positive sentiment since PwC began tracking global growth projections in 2012.</description></item><item><title>The Compass Index indicates a positive business outlook in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Despite a global economic downturn, the Compass Index shows optimism in the Asia Pacific (APAC) business sector, with Australian businesses reporting the highest confidence levels. However, the Index emphasizes that maintaining growth requires agility and innovation in business practices.
Source: Compass Index infographic. Australia is particular optimistic on business growth. Compass Offices, a provider of Asian serviced offices, virtual offices, and meeting rooms, surveyed their global clientele for the Compass Index.</description></item><item><title>Ipsos: More than half of Singaporeans are feeling positive about 2022, but have mixed emotions about 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 06:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipsos-more-than-half-of-singaporeans-are-feeling-positive-about-2022-but-have-mixed-emotions-about-2023/</guid><description>A recent worldwide survey conducted by Ipsos explored global citizens&amp;rsquo; opinions on the past year and their outlook for the future. The survey revealed that 73% of respondents believe their country had a challenging year, marking a slight improvement compared to the previous year (2021).
The Ipsos Global Predictions for 2023 report, which included data from 36 countries, indicated that over half (56%) of respondents globally considered 2022 a difficult year personally.</description></item></channel></rss>