<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Windows XP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/windows-xp/</link><description>Recent content in Windows XP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/windows-xp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CA Technologies is offering a free migration tool for Windows XP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 12:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-is-offering-a-free-migration-tool-for-windows-xp/</guid><description>If you need to upgrade from Windows XP, there&amp;rsquo;s a free tool that can help. Developed by CA Technologies, CA Desktop Migration Manager (CA DMM) is a software solution designed to manage, upgrade, and maintain laptops and desktops. It can also migrate a Windows XP computer to a more secure operating system.
&amp;ldquo;Since Microsoft is no longer providing ongoing technical support and security updates for Windows XP, our customers are exposed to vulnerabilities and significant risks,&amp;rdquo; says Vic Mankotia, VP of Solution Strategy for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies.</description></item><item><title>Are you still using Windows XP? Norton and Qihoo 360 are here to assist you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</guid><description>The AV-Test Institute, located in Germany, tested ten antivirus programs for Windows XP. Out of these, Qihoo 360 Internet Security 9 and Norton Internet Security 2014 proved most effective.
Source: Qihoo 360. AV-TEST Report: Exploit Protection on Windows XP
The institute designed 54 attack simulations using various methods and vulnerabilities to thoroughly test each program. The tested antivirus solutions included products from Qihoo 360, Avast, AVG, Avira, Bitdefender, Eset, Kaspersky, and Norton.</description></item></channel></rss>