<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Organic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/organic/</link><description>Recent content in Organic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/organic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019.</description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives.</description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth.</description></item></channel></rss>