<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chennai on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chennai/</link><description>Recent content in Chennai on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chennai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations.</description></item><item><title>Citadines OMR serviced apartments are now available in Chennai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</guid><description>The Ascott Limited, a fully owned subsidiary of CapitaLand specializing in serviced residences, has expanded its presence in India with the opening of Citadines OMR in Chennai. This 269-unit property marks Ascott&amp;rsquo;s second serviced residence in India, further solidifying its position as a leading international serviced residence operator in the country.
With this addition, Ascott&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in India now encompasses over 1,600 units across nine properties, including those currently operational and under development.</description></item></channel></rss>