<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Update on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/update/</link><description>Recent content in Update on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:50:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/update/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tax-Free Holiday!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 01:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tax-free-holiday/</guid><description>Last week, a client reached out because their employees&amp;rsquo; state taxes weren&amp;rsquo;t being calculated correctly, despite seemingly accurate setup in the system.
Everything appeared properly configured: state tax assignments, default state codes, pay codes subject to state tax, and transaction entries. However, upon examining the build and calculate reports, the state tax was present in the build report but missing from the calculation. The culprit? The default filing status for that state&amp;rsquo;s tax code was set to 0%.</description></item><item><title>Bank Negara Malaysia develops mobile applications for the convenience of consumers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 10:57:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-negara-malaysia-develops-mobile-applications-for-the-convenience-of-consumers/</guid><description>The Central Bank of Malaysia, Bank Negara Malaysia, has launched three new mobile applications designed to empower consumers to make well-informed financial decisions.
These applications – MyBNM, BNM MyLINK, and MyTabung – aim to keep consumers updated on financial developments, provide tools for financial planning and management, and enable them to exercise their financial rights.
MyBNM serves as the official Bank Negara Malaysia mobile application, offering consumers access to the latest financial news.</description></item><item><title>Acronis has released updated versions of Acronis True Image Cloud and True Image 2016 for backup purposes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 06:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-has-released-updated-versions-of-acronis-true-image-cloud-and-true-image-2016-for-backup-purposes/</guid><description>Source: Acronis.
Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, has released updates for its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 software. These comprehensive backup solutions, designed for individuals, families, and home offices, incorporate user feedback. Key improvements include simplified cloud storage options to address limited device space, a redesigned user interface for ease of use, and enhanced features for managing backups across multiple devices like PCs, Macs, smartphones, and tablets.</description></item><item><title>The acceptance of UnionPay is expanding globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 19:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-acceptance-of-unionpay-is-expanding-globally/</guid><description>UnionPay has successfully expanded its network, brand, and products globally, advancing the international use of Chinese financial technology standards. UnionPay International is now present in over 50 markets involved in the Belt and Road Initiative.
Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International, emphasized their strategy of adapting to each local market, fostering personnel exchange between China and other regions, and supporting the globalization of Chinese financial standards.
In Kazakhstan, over 1.3 million UnionPay cards have been issued.</description></item><item><title>The initial significant update is now accessible for Windows 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-significant-update-is-now-accessible-for-windows-10/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Microsoft has released its first significant update for Windows 10, available for both PCs and tablets. This update brings enhancements across the platform, improving user experience according to the company&amp;rsquo;s official announcement. The rollout of Windows 10 has also begun for Xbox One and is expected to reach selected mobile phones shortly.
Terry Myerson, Executive VP of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Windows and Devices Group, expressed confidence in the update, stating that it marks a level of platform maturity suitable for organization-wide deployment.</description></item><item><title>Ouch, Editing Direct Deposit Files</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ouch-editing-direct-deposit-files/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ouch-editing-direct-deposit-files/</guid><description>Generating ACH files in Dynamics GP can be tricky. Providing incorrect information, such as a wrong routing or account number, or voiding a direct deposit after payroll posting, results in an inaccurate ACH file.
The standard solution is voiding and re-running the entire payroll with the correct information. While this works for smaller companies, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for larger companies with substantial payrolls.
Manually editing the ACH file used to be a solution, but recent encoding changes, specifically &amp;ldquo;hash&amp;rdquo; entries created during file generation in GP, make this unreliable.</description></item></channel></rss>