<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Capacitor Replacement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capacitor-replacement/</link><description>Recent content in Capacitor Replacement on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/capacitor-replacement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The first Beomaster 1900 receiver is fully operational and undergoing testing in a listening room. However, the second unit still requires restoration.
Initial assessment of the second Beomaster 1900 has already been completed, and now it&amp;rsquo;s time to begin replacing capacitors on the main circuit board.
The main circuit board houses most of the capacitors that need replacing. Unfortunately, it cannot be removed for servicing and must remain connected to the wire harness.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Capacitor Replacement and Slider Controls on Unit #2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-and-slider-controls-on-unit-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 20:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-capacitor-replacement-and-slider-controls-on-unit-2/</guid><description>The second Beomaster 1900 unit is prepped for reassembly after completing the capacitor replacements and slider control repairs.
The Volume Control board was addressed first, requiring six capacitor replacements. Here&amp;rsquo;s the board before:
And after the replacements:
The Tone Control and FM Tuning board came next. While it only needed ten capacitors replaced, the Bass, Treble, and Balance sliders needed attention. This involved cleaning and repairing the Bass and Treble controls, which had broken slider bridges impacting the switch contacts.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Capacitor Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-capacitor-replacement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 18:57:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-capacitor-replacement/</guid><description>In this Beogram 8002 turntable restoration, I began by replacing the capacitors and the phono muting relay.
I started with the two electrolytic capacitors on the floating chassis, which are part of the +5 VDC power supply regulation. I replaced them with WIMA MKS capacitors (for values 4.7uF and under) and high-quality Japanese 105°C electrolytic capacitors (for values over 4.7uF).
The old muting relay was replaced with a fully sealed Omron relay.</description></item></channel></rss>