<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular Towers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-towers/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular Towers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-towers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent.</description></item><item><title>I Shall Call It Cellular Mini-Me</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</guid><description>The change from landlines to mobile phones is accelerating as 3G networks expand coverage to suburban and rural areas. Smartphones like the BlackBerry and iPhone are becoming ubiquitous, prompting questions about the necessity of laptops. Wireless technology offers liberation from desktops, allowing users to communicate, browse, and enjoy videos on the move. However, this freedom is often hindered indoors.
Indoor spaces present a significant obstacle to wireless transmission. Walls and other barriers weaken high-frequency radio signals, leading to dropped calls and poor connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Access Wireless Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 16:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-access-wireless-internet-providers/</guid><description>Wireless internet isn&amp;rsquo;t just for mobile devices. Businesses can also benefit from fixed wireless services.
One affordable option utilizes existing cell towers to provide broadband similar to a T1 line at nearly half the cost. Accel Networks, for instance, partners with major carriers to leverage their bandwidth, achieving 99.9% reliability and quick installation times. This solution is ideal for businesses requiring PCI-compliant connections, like convenience stores or gas stations, especially those in areas with limited wired options.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Network Expansion Underway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</guid><description>Our society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to bandwidth is evident with the recent launch of a massive dark fiber network project by Allied Fiber. This project will encircle the US with 548 dark fibers and 300 tower sites.
Fiber optic communication is experiencing a resurgence and this time it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. Unlike the failed attempt in the 1990s, the unused fiber optic cables laid then are likely to be utilized soon due to the resurfacing of the telecommunication revolution.</description></item></channel></rss>