<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Miles on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/miles/</link><description>Recent content in Miles on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 15:24:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/miles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FEH has announced a partnership with SIA's HighFlyer business travel program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 15:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feh-has-announced-a-partnership-with-sia-s-highflyer-business-travel-program/</guid><description>Source: FEH. The Clan Hotel Singapore lobby.
Far East Hospitality (FEH) is the first hotel group to join Singapore Airlines’ (SIA&amp;rsquo;s) corporate travel program, HighFlyer. Companies in this program receive discounted airfares and earn HighFlyer points when their staff travel for business. These points can be redeemed for future travel, benefits for their business, or rewards for their traveling employees.
Members of HighFlyer can now accumulate up to 500 points when their employees stay at participating Far East Hospitality hotels in Singapore, Japan, and Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions.</description></item></channel></rss>