<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/networking/</link><description>Recent content in Networking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poken Enhances Face to Face Social Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</guid><description>Is jotting down contact information on scraps of paper your go-to method? Do you find yourself hoping your hand-written notes survive the journey home? Perhaps you rely on traditional business cards?
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, those methods are outdated.
Just like Facebook, MySpace, LinkedIn, and Twitter revolutionized online networking, Poken is ushering in a new era for in-person connections with a device aptly named &amp;ldquo;Poken.&amp;rdquo; Think of it as a modern-day amulet, powered by cutting-edge technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai World Central is pleased to welcome partnerships between the UAE and Japan through the Japan Trade Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</guid><description>Source: Dubai World Central. Khalid Abdulla, Vice President, Licensing, Registration &amp;amp; Permits Approval, Dubai World Central, Usama Saleh, Vice President, Land Planning and Development, Dubai World Central, with Shogo Ishida, Director, JTC DWC LLC, during the inauguration of the Japan Trade Centre at Dubai World Central in January 2015.
The Japan Trade Centre (JTC), a private business-to-business platform promoting Japanese small and medium enterprises (SMEs) internationally, is now operational at Dubai World Central (DWC)&amp;rsquo;s Business Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-world-central-is-pleased-to-welcome-partnerships-between-the-uae-and-japan-through-the-japan-trade-centre/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goose Your Technical Service Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</guid><description>Are you seeing a decline in business lately? You might have just as many inquiries, but customers seem hesitant to commit. This is likely due to the current economic climate, not anything you&amp;rsquo;re doing wrong. However, there are ways to stimulate your business and potentially even increase your income.
While these ideas apply to many businesses, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on those offering telephone or computer networking technical services. If this describes your business, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Founders' Friday session in Singapore by Huawei will showcase Scott Bales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</guid><description>Source: Scott Bales website.
Huawei is launching a new networking series called Founders&amp;rsquo; Friday. The series aims to connect business leaders with professionals to exchange ideas, address difficulties, and develop innovative solutions for advancing the digital world.
The inaugural event, presented alongside the HUAWEI Mate 9, features prominent digital and innovation expert Scott Bales. He will discuss essential principles for fostering a culture of innovation within organizations. Bales, the Managing Director of Singapore-based Innovation Labs Asia, brings over a decade of global experience in innovation, thought leadership, implementation planning, and strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tell Me You're Not PAYING For Equipment Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</guid><description>Stop wasting money on expensive equipment leads that often lead nowhere.
There&amp;rsquo;s a smarter way to generate sales and marketing leads for your telephone systems and IT networking equipment: commission-based leads. This means you receive qualified leads from serious businesses in your area as they emerge, completely free of charge. You then select the leads you want to pursue and focus your efforts on closing the deal. Only after a successful sale and payment from the customer do you share a small percentage with the agency that provided the lead...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new tech and innovation business club has been introduced in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</guid><description>SPECTRUM, a curated tech and innovation business club, has been established in Singapore. The organization, co-founded by Cheryl Lee and Shirley Crystal Chua, aims to create a globally connected ecosystem for businesses seeking to expand into Asia by providing expert advice, necessary resources, and strategic networks.
SPECTRUM has partnered with Golden Equator and Mistletoe to form a collaborative network of seven strategic groups: innovators, learning institutions, executors, backers, enablers, government agencies, and ecosystem builders and partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom Providers Build Their Own Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</guid><description>As cloud computing companies start to establish themselves, internet service providers and similar carriers are developing their own cloud services. This creates a challenge for IT professionals and business owners who need to choose the best option.
It’s important to recognize that cloud computing is still in its early stages. Like any new technology, it will take time for it to fully develop. As the technology progresses, we will see a lot of activity from many different companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Better Than a T3 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 19:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 voice and data lines, once a reliable option for businesses, now offer insufficient speed (45 Mbps) for modern demands, which often exceed 100 Mbps. Businesses today require significantly faster connections, with some even seeking speeds beyond 10 Gbps. If you&amp;rsquo;re still using a T3 line, you might find better bandwidth options at a similar or lower cost.
What is a T3 Line?
Developed by Bell Labs, the T3 line was designed to carry numerous simultaneous phone conversations, a function it still serves in certain settings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-better-than-a-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Work together at a beach resort and form new relationships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</guid><description>While new coworking spaces and startup events are constantly emerging, forging meaningful connections with startups outside of one&amp;rsquo;s immediate location can still be challenging. Coworking Camp aims to bridge this gap with its upcoming six-week program. This program offers startups and digital nomads a chance to network and explore business opportunities with like-minded individuals in a relaxed and comfortable environment.
Source: Coworking Camp website.
Matthias Zeitler, Chief Coworker, highlights the program&amp;rsquo;s focus on fostering valuable connections and providing a space for rejuvenation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces new network switches designed specifically for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>Dell has improved its networking solutions designed for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs). Their new X-series smart managed switches and expanded N-series family provide cost-effective, enterprise-grade network control with user-friendly simplicity.
The Dell Networking X-Series includes web-managed 1 Gigabit Ethernet (GbE) and 10GbE switches with flexible configuration options. SMBs can benefit from advanced network management without specialized IT staff using step-by-step wizards and customizable dashboards. These features allow for quick and accurate configuration, calibration, and troubleshooting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-new-network-switches-designed-specifically-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Come and see! GP Partner Connections Conference</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-and-see-gp-partner-connections-conference/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 14:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-and-see-gp-partner-connections-conference/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m a huge advocate for peer-to-peer learning in the partner community, a fact evident to anyone who&amp;rsquo;s attended my partner training sessions. There&amp;rsquo;s a noticeable lack of opportunities for partners, especially consultants, to connect and collaborate in a non-competitive setting. Sharing ideas, best practices, and brainstorming together are invaluable activities.
Speaking of which, mark your calendars for the GP Partner Connections conference this fall in Orlando! This valuable knowledge-sharing event takes place from Saturday, October 23rd through Monday, October 25th at the Renaissance Resort near SeaWorld...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-and-see-gp-partner-connections-conference/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-and-see-gp-partner-connections-conference/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>