<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BRI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bri/</link><description>Recent content in BRI on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bri/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is ISDN and Why Do I Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</guid><description>You might have encountered the term ISDN in the context of phone services. What does it mean and how can it benefit you?
ISDN stands for Integrated Services Digital Network, a technical term for a digital phone service that adheres to specific standards.
The concept of ISDN emerged when dial-up modems using analog phone lines were the norm for internet access. ISDN aimed to combine phone and internet services on a single line with three channels.</description></item><item><title>What Is a PRI Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-line/</guid><description>Businesses frequently use PRI lines to obtain multiple phone lines. But what exactly are PRI lines, and what choices are there?
PRI is a component of ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network), a telecommunications standard. Its goal was to replace analog phone lines with digital ones for both residential and commercial customers. When ISDN was first introduced, dial-up connections using 56 Kbps modems were the norm for internet connectivity. Many of these modems only achieved speeds of 30 to 40 Kbps due to phone line limitations.</description></item><item><title>So, What Does ISDN Stand For?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</guid><description>If your business uses telephone systems, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the term ISDN. This piece explains what ISDN is and how it can benefit your company.
ISDN, or Integrated Services Digital Network, is a digital telephone standard initially intended to replace analog lines for both residential and business users. While DSL, cable broadband, and VoIP surpassed ISDN in the residential market with their higher bandwidths and lower costs, ISDN found its niche as a popular trunking service for business PBX telephone systems and a few specialized applications.</description></item></channel></rss>