<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>10 GigE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10-gige/</link><description>Recent content in 10 GigE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/10-gige/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>