<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ticket on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ticket/</link><description>Recent content in Ticket on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ticket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Air France provides complimentary newspapers and magazines for tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</guid><description>Air France has launched a new app, Air France Press, allowing Flying Blue members to enjoy complimentary digital media offline.
Flying Blue members can download a selection of French and international newspapers and magazines at no cost. This content is accessible offline before, during, and after their Air France flights. Passengers can download publications with their ticket, starting 24 hours before their flight until departure.
Access to the service is granted by logging into the app using Flying Blue credentials or a reservation number...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>