<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TDM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tdm/</link><description>Recent content in TDM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tdm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item></channel></rss>