<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Port on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-port/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Port on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:42:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-port/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Ports In a Data Storm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</guid><description>Businesses are finding it increasingly challenging to forecast their WAN network needs, especially during uncertain economic times. The traditional long wait times for telecom upgrades add to this uncertainty. What&amp;rsquo;s needed is a solution that allows businesses to pay only for the bandwidth they currently use while retaining the ability to swiftly increase capacity as needed.
Ethernet service ports offer this flexibility. Service providers install these ports, often as RJ45 jacks or fiber optic connectors, on a managed router at the customer&amp;rsquo;s location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>