<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recognition on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recognition/</link><description>Recent content in Recognition on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recognition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience.</description></item><item><title>The speech recognition app can transcribe discussions involving several individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:46:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</guid><description>Source: NVIDIA blog post. The Otter team at AISense.
AISense, a company based in the US, has introduced Otter, an application that uses GPU technology to record and transcribe speech from multiple speakers. Unlike most currently available software that needs to be trained on a single voice, Otter can accurately recognize and differentiate between various speakers.
Sam Liang, AISense co-founder and CEO, highlights in a blog post that capturing human-to-human interactions is significantly more challenging than interactions like those with virtual assistants like Alexa, Siri, or Google Assistant.</description></item><item><title>If you ask LG ThinQ AI TVs, Google Assistant will respond</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</guid><description>LG Electronics has integrated the recently launched Google Assistant into their OLED and SUPER UHD TVs.
This feature, available on all LG ThinQ AI TV models, enables users to search for information, check weather forecasts, and more using voice commands, all without interrupting their TV viewing.
Previously, voice commands were limited to basic functions like changing channels or adjusting volume. Now, users can search for specific content using the TV remote, for example, &amp;ldquo;show me romantic comedy movies on Netflix&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;show me yoga videos&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Solarwinds is advocating for the recognition of IT personnel on September 15th as IT Professionals Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</guid><description>SolarWinds, a company that provides software for managing hybrid IT infrastructures, has declared the third Tuesday of September (starting on September 15, 2015) as IT Professionals Day. This day is meant to show appreciation for IT professionals, recognizing their often-unsung contributions to modern businesses.
To mark IT Professionals Day, SolarWinds published the findings of their IT Pro Value Survey. This research highlights the significant contributions of Singaporean IT professionals. It examines how much end-users value IT departments and explores how valued IT professionals feel within their organizations.</description></item></channel></rss>