<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cryptocurrency on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cryptocurrency/</link><description>Recent content in Cryptocurrency on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:52:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cryptocurrency/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anyone interested in a portfolio of CENNZ?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-interested-in-a-portfolio-of-cennz/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 09:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-interested-in-a-portfolio-of-cennz/</guid><description>Moonstake, a leading staking provider, announced that in March, users staked US$5.5 million worth of CENNZ, the cryptocurrency of Centrality. This achievement makes Moonstake Wallet the world’s largest CENNZ staking pool, just 10 days after it became the first platform to offer CENNZ staking on February 25th.
Founded in 2020 with the goal of creating the largest staking pool network in Asia, Moonstake explains that staking pools let participants combine their resources for staking and receive rewards proportional to their contribution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-interested-in-a-portfolio-of-cennz/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-interested-in-a-portfolio-of-cennz/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new NYNJA app allows you to communicate, make purchases, and utilize cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: NYNJA Group. Screen captures of the NYNJA app, currently in beta.
NYNJA Group, a Hong Kong-based communications and mobile technology firm, has introduced NYNJA, a new communications app with a built-in digital marketplace and cryptocurrency wallet.
The NYNJA app works across multiple platforms and integrates voice, text, and visual messaging with business management and e-commerce tools. Its features are powered by its own financial ecosystem and cryptocurrency, NYNJACoin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aditus is a platform that links high-end retailers with individuals who own cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Aditus is a platform designed to connect wealthy individuals who hold significant Bitcoin and other cryptocurrency assets (crypto-affluents) with luxury goods and service providers.
The company identifies a gap in the market, noting that while few luxury businesses currently accept cryptocurrency, crypto-affluents are eager to use these digital assets for their purchases. Additionally, Aditus recognizes the importance of data privacy to crypto-users, which contrasts with the need for customer data in luxury marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Bitcoin conference in China will take place in May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</guid><description>Bitfund.pe, a private equity firm focused on Bitcoin, and UBM China have jointly revealed plans for the first international Bitcoin conference in China. This event, the Global Bitcoin Summit 2014 (GBS), is scheduled for May 10-11 in Beijing.
Source: GBS
The summit will be structured around eight key themes, featuring conversations on Bitcoin trends both within China and globally. Additionally, there will be exploration of how to leverage Bitcoin for new business creation and expansion of existing ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should you consider investing in cryptocurrency?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: Statista. Bitcoin price index from November 2016 to November 2018 (US$).
Cryptocurrencies experienced substantial growth in 2017, followed by a less impressive 2018. This raises the question: Are we witnessing a classic boom and bust cycle? Several experts in the field share their insights.
Source: Dash. Taylor.
“The total market value of all cryptocurrencies combined is currently at the same level as in September 2017. However, what often gets overlooked is the continued growth in actual usage and the constant innovation happening in the sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible that your computer is generating wealth for someone else?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 07:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</guid><description>Fortinet, a leading cybersecurity company, is warning users to be alert if their computers drastically slow down, as it could be a sign of &amp;ldquo;browser cryptojacking.&amp;rdquo; This new cybercrime involves hackers secretly using victims&amp;rsquo; computers to mine Monero, a type of cryptocurrency.
This is how it works: a malicious script is secretly embedded into a website. When a user visits the site, the script uses their computer&amp;rsquo;s processing power to mine Monero for the cybercriminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-that-your-computer-is-generating-wealth-for-someone-else/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trade cryptocurrency with Wowoo in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-cryptocurrency-with-wowoo-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-cryptocurrency-with-wowoo-in-singapore/</guid><description>Wowoo Exchange, a digital asset trading platform based in Singapore, has been launched. The platform initially targets the local market and enables users to trade cryptocurrency using Singapore dollars (SGD) for deposits and withdrawals.
Initially, three currency pairs are offered: SGD-Bitcoin, SGD-Ethereum, and Bitcoin-Ethereum, with plans to introduce more pairings in the future. New users who sign up on the platform are eligible for sign-up bonuses.
Wowoo Exchange facilitates convenient trading experiences with features such as Singapore-dollar transactions, market and limit orders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-cryptocurrency-with-wowoo-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trade-cryptocurrency-with-wowoo-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>