<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Solutions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Solutions on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768).</description></item><item><title>Yes, There IS Rural Broadband For Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</guid><description>Many people are excited about the economic stimulus plan&amp;rsquo;s promise of expanded rural broadband access. However, you might already be able to get the internet speeds your rural business needs.
Most major internet providers have overlooked rural areas, not because rural businesses are less important, but because the cost of installing infrastructure like coaxial cables or fiber optic cables is difficult to recoup when there are fewer customers. This is why cable and DSL internet services are less common in the countryside.</description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide.</description></item></channel></rss>