<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Female on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/female/</link><description>Recent content in Female on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/female/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 in Singapore have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 02:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</guid><description>Source: The Ascendas-Singbridge Group. From left: Ho Kheng Lian, Venture Partner, Vectr Ventures; Natalie Loh, Vice President of Products, Vanitee; Kuik Xiao Shi, Co-Founder, Vanitee; Pocket Sun, Founding Partner of SoGal Ventures; Adrianna Tan, Founder, Wobe; Virginia Tan, Co-founder and Managing Director of Lean In China; Adeline Quek, Head of Regional Business Development, Grabtaxi; Mrs Nina Yang, Chief Operating Officer of Singbridge.
The Ascendas-Singbridge Group selected two startups from Singapore to compete in the finals of the Ascendas-Singbridge Her Startup 2016 competition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-ascendas-singbridge-her-startup-2016-in-singapore-have-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When size is important</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</guid><description>The market offers a wide variety of feminine hygiene products, each with its own set of claims. While some brands highlight product length as a selling point, ranging from 35cm to 42cm, others leave it unspecified, making comparisons difficult.
Although some brands provide charts illustrating relative product lengths, the lack of specific measurements makes it challenging to determine actual size differences and whether those differences significantly impact usability.
To provide some clarity, here are approximate lengths of various products measured end-to-end:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-size-is-important/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dove encourages women to push boundaries and redefine beauty and success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</guid><description>Women are rejecting the idea that their appearance should limit their potential, sharing empowering stories in Dove&amp;rsquo;s new film, #MyBeautyMySay. The film aims to motivate women to defy stereotypes and societal expectations.
Dove&amp;rsquo;s Global Beauty Confidence Report reveals that women desire the freedom to express themselves authentically but feel restricted by judgments about their appearance. For example, 70% of women receive more compliments on their looks than their work achievements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dove-encourages-women-to-push-boundaries-and-redefine-beauty-and-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The increasing involvement of women in commerce and industry in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>The Technical Education and Skills Development Authority (TESDA) in the Philippines has reported a rise in the number of women participating in skills training programs for traditionally male-dominated fields.
Amelito Cardenas, a supervising specialist at TESDA Pangasinan, mentioned that more women are enrolling in technical-vocational (tech-voc) and private institutions to learn trades such as welding and automotive repair, as reported by the Philippines Information Agency.
Cardenas also shared that TESDA offers a free training program specifically for women who run sari-sari stores and carinderia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-increasing-involvement-of-women-in-commerce-and-industry-in-the-philippines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Female entrepreneurs need more than just determination to succeed, according to Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 22:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</guid><description>The first Mastercard Index of Women Entrepreneurs reveals that strong support systems, such as easy access to financial services and a business-friendly environment, are crucial for women-owned businesses to succeed. These enabling factors are essential in overcoming the two biggest hurdles women face in entrepreneurship: cultural bias and limited opportunities for advancement.
Developed economies lead the index, with New Zealand (74.4), Canada (72.4), and the US (69.9) claiming the top spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/female-entrepreneurs-need-more-than-just-determination-to-succeed-according-to-mastercard/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>