<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exchange on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exchange/</link><description>Recent content in Exchange on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>