<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DED on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ded/</link><description>Recent content in DED on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DED allows for the licensing of eight additional business activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-allows-for-the-licensing-of-eight-additional-business-activities/</guid><description>Source: DED. Bushahab.
Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Economic Development (DED) has expanded its list of permissible business activities, increasing the total to 2,133. This decision stems from regular feedback gathered from various industry sectors regarding local market needs and the balance of supply and demand. The goal is to simplify business operations and offer essential resources for growth.
The new additions encompass several specialized activities. These include assembling industrial robots, providing tax consultancy services, printing secure documents, manufacturing scanners, collecting and transporting hazardous waste, offering health consultancy, brokering financing deals, and developing and managing applications for social media.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item></channel></rss>