<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remittance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remittance/</link><description>Recent content in Remittance on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remittance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instarem introduces a new mobile application for consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Instarem, a digital platform for international payments, has updated its website and mobile app for users in Singapore. The company will also introduce a groundbreaking consumer debit card called Amaze later this year.
Instarem has revamped its brand and released a new app specifically designed for the Singapore market.
This rebranding goes beyond simply improving global consumer remittances. Instarem aims to simplify the complexities of international payments, providing its customers with an intuitive, transparent, and affordable way to manage their money...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dash, the mobile payment service by Singtel, introduces a new rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 22:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</guid><description>Singtel Dash users now have a new incentive to use the app – the Dash Rewards program. This program allows users to earn points for various transactions, including payments and overseas remittances. These points can then be redeemed for rewards such as Singtel mobile services, grocery vouchers, dining options, retail discounts, and lifestyle benefits.
Source: Singtel website. Dash Rewards incentivizes Dash users for making transactions.
Dash Rewards aims to provide more value to users by awarding points for every dollar spent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces digital remittance services for Mobile Prepaid customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 21:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile Prepaid users can now send money internationally to over 40 countries within a day using the updated StarHub Prepaid app. This new feature is possible through a partnership with Singapore fintech company and licensed major payment institution, Pay2Home.
Digital remittances through the app eliminate the need for physical queues or appointments. The StarHub Prepaid app allows users to conveniently manage everything from identity verification and checking updated currency rates to transferring funds and managing prepaid accounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-digital-remittance-services-for-mobile-prepaid-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xpress Money introduces a daily raffle for customers sending money in 11 countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</guid><description>Xpress Money, a money transfer company, has introduced a 49-day promotion called &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday.&amp;rdquo; This program is open to customers sending money from Malaysia and ten other countries, including several in the Middle East.
Source: Xpress Money website.
The World Bank reported that in 2012, individuals sent $2.3 billion from Malaysia to other countries. Xpress Money anticipates a 15% increase in money transfers during Ramadan. Sudhesh Giriyan, Xpress Money&amp;rsquo;s Vice President and Business Head, stated that the &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday&amp;rdquo; program is a gesture of goodwill towards customers during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dash has increased its services in response to the COVID-19 outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</guid><description>Dash, a mobile wallet by Singtel, is introducing new features to assist customers and partners during the COVID-19 pandemic. These features offer more convenient options for sending money, shopping online, and connecting businesses with customers while social distancing measures are in place.
Dash is providing free mobile remittance services to help employers and foreign workers in Singapore affected by stay-at-home guidelines and travel restrictions. This service allows for secure digital money transfers to seven countries: Bangladesh, China, India, Indonesia, Malaysia, Myanmar, and the Philippines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>