<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobility on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobility/</link><description>Recent content in Mobility on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Buying Ernest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations often struggle to manage their telecommunications across the board. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t a single, national provider that understands local needs be ideal? While that might seem contradictory, Ernest Communications offers precisely that solution.
Ernest specializes in serving businesses with widespread locations, such as chain stores, hotels, and restaurants, by providing phone lines, data connections, and wireless services. Essentially, any company with franchises, branches, or service centers across various regions fits their model.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?</description></item><item><title>HP has released a variety of mobile solutions to enhance business productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</guid><description>HP has introduced a suite of commercial mobility solutions aimed at boosting workplace productivity. The offerings include eight new mobile devices and accessories designed to simplify business processes.
Anneliese Olson, HP Asia-Pacific and Japan VP and GM of Personal Computing, highlighted how these products address evolving workplace dynamics, workforce trends, and work styles, ultimately reshaping workflows.
HP has developed a comprehensive mobility solution catering to diverse businesses, including those in specialized sectors like education, field service, healthcare, public safety, and retail.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Science Park 1 will be testing a program for sharing personal mobility devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-science-park-1-will-be-testing-a-program-for-sharing-personal-mobility-devices/</guid><description>Ascendas-Singbridge Group, a leading provider of sustainable urban and business space solutions in Asia, has partnered with Neuron Mobility, a smart transportation solutions provider, to pilot a personal mobility device (PMD) sharing program at Singapore Science Park 1. This six-month trial reflects the group&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing accessibility and convenience for tenants, employees, and visitors within the park.
Starting June 14, 2017, fifty GPS-equipped e-scooters and twenty bicycles will be available for rent at six designated parking zones throughout Singapore Science Park 1.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: EU Commission's Proposal for Long-Term Resident Non-EU Citizens and Poundshop Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 18:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</guid><description>The free movement of people within the EU, a fundamental principle, generally applies to EU citizens and citizens of countries with specific agreements. However, EU immigration law allows for limited mobility of non-EU citizens within member states under stricter conditions. This article explores whether these limitations create a &amp;ldquo;discount&amp;rdquo; version of free movement for non-EU citizens.
One such measure is the EU long-term resident (LTR) status for non-EU citizens, established in 2003 and amended in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>