<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-technology/</link><description>Recent content in IP Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IP T1 Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 21:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-t1-line-service/</guid><description>T1 lines have been around for a long time, initially used by phone companies to carry multiple calls between their facilities. Eventually, businesses adopted them for their phone systems. When the Internet became widespread, T1 lines were adapted to serve as dedicated internet connections. This might seem odd given their history, but in today&amp;rsquo;s internet-centric world, T1 lines can indeed function as IP connections.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/) While T1 technology was originally designed for voice calls, the fundamental principle is that digital data is just a series of ones and zeros.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Leads in High Bandwidth Ethernet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 22:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-leads-in-high-bandwidth-ethernet-connectivity/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a significant change in high-bandwidth services, moving away from older SONET/SDH technology and towards Ethernet IP technology. This shift, driven by the long-term transition from analog to digital communications and the widespread use of Ethernet, could indicate a turning point for Ethernet in fiber optic communication, as argued by AboveNet.
AboveNet, a provider of high-bandwidth services in 15 major U.S. markets and the UK, specializes in fiber optic MAN and WAN connectivity, offering speeds from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps at lower prices than traditional telecom providers.</description></item></channel></rss>