<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EVC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evc/</link><description>Recent content in EVC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/evc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps.</description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services.</description></item></channel></rss>