<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Optical Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optical-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Optical Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/optical-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment.</description></item></channel></rss>