<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Signature on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-signature/</link><description>Recent content in E-Signature on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-signature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adobe and Microsoft software will now collaborate more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</guid><description>Adobe has enhanced Adobe Document Cloud as part of their partnership with Microsoft. Both companies want to provide excellent digital document experiences to their many shared customers.
Adobe Sign is now more integrated with Microsoft Dynamics 365. This provides real-time access to customer information from LinkedIn Sales Navigator and allows for more automated sales processes. New PDF integrations will enable all Office 365 users who subscribe to Adobe Acrobat DC for teams or enterprises to create, edit, and view secure, high-quality PDFs.</description></item><item><title>Adobe Sign simplifies the process of creating digital signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new cloud-based digital signature solutions, Adobe Document Cloud and Adobe Sign, built on an open standard developed with the Cloud Signature Consortium. This new technology, announced following the Consortium&amp;rsquo;s formation last June, allows digital signatures on any browser or mobile device.
Adobe Sign works with over 200 providers from the European Union Trust List (EUTL) and Adobe Approved Trust List (AATL), offering users a wide selection of trusted digital IDs.</description></item><item><title>The Green Way To Get Documents Signed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/</guid><description>The excessive paperwork in business today contradicts early predictions of a paperless office. Despite the rise of computers, high-speed printers led to increased printing, resulting in a cycle of paper consumption and shredding.
Cloud services offer a potential solution by enabling work processes that don&amp;rsquo;t rely on physical documents. While some businesses transition to online operations, others remain partially offline, necessitating physical documents for legal and operational purposes.
This reliance on paper persists due to the need for legally valid signatures on agreements, forms, and contracts, as digital communication methods are often insufficient.</description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet.</description></item></channel></rss>