<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ping on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ping/</link><description>Recent content in Ping on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?</description></item></channel></rss>