<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vyvx and Genesis Offer Worldwide Video Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</guid><description>The Power of Fiber for Video Transport Those working in video production, distribution, news, or sports broadcasting need reliable video transport. While satellites have been the traditional choice, fiber optic networks offer compelling advantages, including vast bandwidth, minimal latency, and accessibility in popular locations. The Level 3 and Global Crossing merger brought together their video transport expertise, resulting in a comprehensive range of services.
Level 3&amp;rsquo;s Emmy Award-winning Vyvx service provides broadcast fiber services, managed video networks, teleport and satellite services, and venue-specific services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Broadband the Next Oil?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</guid><description>Customers are enraged by the escalating prices of gasoline and heating oil. The cost of oil seems to be limitless, as traders frantically outbid each other for future contracts. It feels like a never-ending cycle of increasing prices. And now, prepare yourself: the next crisis might involve broadband internet.
You might be wondering how broadband, especially internet broadband, could resemble oil. Oil is a natural resource with over a century of extraction history, while broadband is a relatively recent technological invention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Even Lower Latency Connections To Chicago</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</guid><description>The significance of network latency is evident in AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s efforts to establish faster fiber optic connections, even within a metropolitan area like Chicago, set to launch by the middle of next year. This begs the question: will other cities follow suit?
Latency is the new frontier, surpassing even bandwidth in importance. It represents the critical factor when exceptional computing performance is non-negotiable. This need is especially acute in the financial sector, where companies engaged in stock and commodity trading demand minimal delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Glass Belt to Transform the Rust Belt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/</guid><description>Hidden beneath the cornfields of Northern Illinois is a unique triangle, often compared to the Bermuda Triangle, but with a positive twist. Unlike its infamous counterpart, this triangle doesn&amp;rsquo;t make things disappear but instead makes poverty, unemployment, and economic decline vanish. It transforms the remnants of the &amp;ldquo;rust belt&amp;rdquo; into a technological hub for the information age.
This modern marvel comprises a network of fiber optic cables buried alongside three major highways: I-88, I-90, and I-39...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Vyvx Connects The Super Bowl</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/</guid><description>Super Bowl Sunday is a time for celebration, but behind the scenes, technology ensures a seamless broadcast experience for millions. Level 3 Vyvx VenueNet+ plays a crucial role in delivering high-quality broadcasts from stadiums like Indianapolis&amp;rsquo;s Lucas Oil Stadium, where their technology is pre-installed and managed by experts.
Remote broadcasting, whether for radio or TV, can be unpredictable. Traditional methods often involve cumbersome equipment and potential signal disruptions. The demand for high-definition broadcasts further complicates matters, requiring substantial bandwidth to maintain picture clarity during fast-paced action...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-vyvx-connects-the-super-bowl/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Networks Need Denser Wavelength Multiplexing To Meet Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</guid><description>Despite the economic downturn, fiber optic network providers are experiencing a surge in demand. However, instead of widespread digging, they are leveraging technology to boost capacity on existing infrastructure.
XO Communications, a leading fiber optic network provider, recently revealed plans to double its capacity per fiber strand using Infinera&amp;rsquo;s optical line equipment. The Infinera Line System 2 increases the channel count for C-band fiber optic systems from 80 to 160, resulting in an extra 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Plus Copper Equals High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 03:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Our appetite for bandwidth is insatiable, growing daily. Businesses and consumers alike are hampered by insufficient bandwidth, preventing them from fully utilizing the latest technologies. Content providers and productivity vendors face similar hurdles, unable to deliver their full potential due to inadequate transport and last-mile bandwidth.
This scenario mirrors the early days of personal computers. For decades, limitations in processor speed, RAM, and hard disk capacity were constant challenges. While advancements in these areas have significantly minimized these bottlenecks, they haven&amp;rsquo;t entirely vanished...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Same Budget, More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 10:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Is Slow Network Speed Affecting Your Business?
Are you experiencing frustrating network issues like slow downloads, choppy calls, interrupted streaming, and sluggish website loading?
Do You Need More Bandwidth?
There&amp;rsquo;s a good chance your internet connection needs more bandwidth. While your internal network might be fast enough, your external connection (WAN) might not be able to handle your current needs.
Signs You Need More Bandwidth
If your internet service hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed in years but your business relies more on multimedia and online tools, you probably need more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/same-budget-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Lit Towers Improving Rural Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 16:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</guid><description>Living outside the city limits often means limited internet options. While options like 3G and satellite exist, they come with slow speeds and download caps. Businesses might have access to slightly better choices like T1 lines, but high-speed options are generally nonexistent.
Rural areas face a digital disadvantage compared to cities where gigabit and even 10 gigabit ethernet connections are readily available. Fixed wireless and cable options also offer much faster speeds in these areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>