<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Y on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/y/</link><description>Recent content in Y on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/y/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New e-book series examines generational disparities in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>The INSEAD Emerging Markets Institute collaborated with employer branding specialist Universum, Singapore-based think tank The HEAD Foundation, and MIT Leadership Centre to release Brave New Workplace, the first in a series of e-books called Generations Series.
As companies aim to create optimal work environments and policies for multigenerational workforces, they may find generational differences to be a significant factor, though this is not always the case. Brave New Workplace examines how Gen X, Gen Y, and Gen Z are transforming the nature of work and workplace culture by looking at their behaviors and attitudes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>