<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call/</link><description>Recent content in Call on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:12:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>COPC releases contact center training schedule for the second half of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</guid><description>COPC, a consulting firm specializing in customer experience enhancement, has announced its training schedule for the latter half of 2015. The firm offers in-person classes focusing on operational areas within customer contact.
Kathleen Jezierski, COO of COPC, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s approach: &amp;ldquo;Customers interact with companies through many touch points such as phone, email, social media, mobile and the web. We take our call center expertise and apply our proven best practices to manage these newer channels to deliver a unified experience.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Halo Smart is designed to enhance both your calling and music experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</guid><description>Jabra Halo Smart headphones are designed for users who prioritize call quality but also enjoy listening to music. Research indicates that 79% of consumers desire headphones suitable for both calls and music, yet find most music headphones lacking in call performance.
These headphones prioritize calls with features like high-quality microphones, wind-noise reduction, and a dedicated button for Google Now or Siri. At the same time, they offer great audio quality for music with 10mm speakers.</description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join.</description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost.</description></item></channel></rss>