<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colour on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colour/</link><description>Recent content in Colour on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:33:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acuvue by Johnson &amp; Johnson excels in tests conducted in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acuvue-by-johnson-johnson-excels-in-tests-conducted-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 03:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acuvue-by-johnson-johnson-excels-in-tests-conducted-in-japan/</guid><description>Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson Vision Care&amp;rsquo;s 1-Day Acuvue Define and Acuvue 2 Define contact lenses were favorably mentioned in a report by Japan&amp;rsquo;s National Consumer Affairs Center (NCAC) concerning popular colored and limbal ring contact lenses in the Asia Pacific region.
The NCAC report, &amp;ldquo;Safety of Color Contact Lenses,&amp;rdquo; highlighted that while some manufacturers falsely claimed their lenses had &amp;ldquo;no pigment on the surface,&amp;rdquo; 1-Day Acuvue Define and Acuvue 2 Define lenses genuinely lacked surface pigments.</description></item><item><title>Lexmark introduces seven innovative laser multifunction models with groundbreaking features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</guid><description>Lexmark has introduced seven new A4 color laser and smart multifunction printers (MFPs). These MFPs feature Kofax TotalAgility from Lexmark to improve omnichannel capture strategies and boost business efficiency.
Amy Machado, Research Manager at IDC, highlighted the strong growth of the A4 color MFP market, projecting a 10.5% increase throughout the forecast period, according to the Worldwide Hardcopy Peripherals Format Forecast from Q3 2015.
These new models, powered by a quad-core processor, boast leading print and copy speeds for their class.</description></item><item><title>The new bronze pink Xperia XZ Premium phones are now on sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The Bronze Pink Sony Xperia XZ.
After the June release of the Sony Xperia XZ Premium, Sony Mobile has launched a third color option in Singapore: Bronze Pink.
This new pink-hued phone will be available at select retailers starting July 8th. The Xperia XZ Premium has a suggested retail price of S$1,098.
Sony claims its Xperia XZ Premium is the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest smartphone, boasting a 4K HDR display.</description></item><item><title>The Pantone color of the year for 2018 is Ultra Violet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:29:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</guid><description>Source: Pantone. PANTONE Ultra Violet 18-3838.
Pantone, a subsidiary of X-Rite and a leading authority on color systems and technology, declared PANTONE 18-3838, Ultra Violet, as its highly anticipated Color of the Year for 2018. According to Pantone, this shade embodies originality, creativity, and forward-thinking.
For nearly two decades, Pantone&amp;rsquo;s Color of the Year has significantly shaped product development and purchasing choices across diverse industries, including fashion, home furnishings, industrial design, packaging, and graphic design.</description></item><item><title>For the fourth year in a row, Konica Minolta has been awarded the prestigious BLI 'Line of the Year' award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>Buyers Laboratory (BLI), a recognized independent evaluator for the imaging industry, has given Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s A3 multifunction printer (MFP) family its &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award for an unprecedented fourth consecutive year.
The &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award is presented annually to companies whose products demonstrate exceptional performance in BLI&amp;rsquo;s rigorous two-month laboratory assessments.
&amp;ldquo;Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s success comes down to consistency,&amp;rdquo; said George Mikolay, BLI&amp;rsquo;s Senior Product Editor for A3/Copier MFPs.</description></item><item><title>AkzoNobel has chosen Denim Drift as the Color of the Year for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 02:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/akzonobel-has-chosen-denim-drift-as-the-color-of-the-year-for-2017/</guid><description>Source: AkzoNobel. From left: Farhan Akhtar, Dulux Brand Ambassador; Rajiv Rajgopal, Director of Decorative Paints, AkzoNobel South Asia Cluster; Jeremy Rowe, Managing Director of AkzoNobel Decorative Paints, South East &amp;amp; South Asia, Middle East; and Shraddha Kapoor, Dulux Brand Ambassador, revealed Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017.
AkzoNobel, a global paints and coatings company, specialty chemicals producer, and the manufacturer of Dulux paints in India, has announced Denim Drift as the Colour of the Year for 2017.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals introduces a new line of mineral color correctors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</guid><description>Source: Everyday Minerals website.
Everyday Minerals claims to have formulated its finest mineral color correctors to date. These all-natural correctors feature jojoba esters, enabling them to conceal imperfections seamlessly without appearing heavy.
The new Jojoba Color Correctors are offered in four shades, each formulated for a specific purpose. The pink-hued Brighten Color Corrector utilizes light-diffusing pigments to instantly illuminate dark circles under the eyes. The Cover Color Corrector, in a natural skin tone, can be used after foundation for concealing blemishes.</description></item></channel></rss>