<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Account on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/account/</link><description>Recent content in Account on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:31:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/account/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing the Al Rabeh salary account by Kuwait Finance House</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-al-rabeh-salary-account-by-kuwait-finance-house/</guid><description>Kuwait Finance House (KFH) has introduced the Al-Rabeh account, a salary account that offers customers chances to win valuable prizes like Range Rovers and gold each quarter. Al-Rabeh is also designed as an investment savings account, providing customers with annual dividends.
This account caters to individuals who want to transfer their salaries and manage their personal finances while benefiting from savings and investment opportunities. The Al-Rabeh account is available in Kuwaiti Dinars (KD) and requires regular salary transfers to be eligible for prize draws.</description></item><item><title>Sections and Accounts for Forecasting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sections-and-accounts-for-forecasting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 20:22:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sections-and-accounts-for-forecasting/</guid><description>Forecaster uses Lines (or Line Sets) to define which accounts appear in input sets or reports. You can assign these lines to specific cost centers, creating an &amp;ldquo;override&amp;rdquo; that tailors the accounts displayed for a particular department&amp;rsquo;s input set. For example, the Accounting department would only see accounts relevant to their work.
We&amp;rsquo;ve already covered these Forecaster navigation paths:
Build&amp;raquo;Lines Build&amp;raquo;Reports or Report Worksheet Setup&amp;raquo;Budgets&amp;raquo;Input Set&amp;raquo;Overrides You can also create Sections (Setup&amp;raquo;Budgets&amp;raquo;Sections) to organize your lines in input sets or reports with headers, improving data presentation.</description></item><item><title>Issue with upgrading Project Accounting and Purchase Order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-upgrading-project-accounting-and-purchase-order/</guid><description>A recent upgrade from GP9 to GP10 resulted in an unexpected issue: purchase order line items were missing account numbers. This was perplexing because previous upgrades, even those involving project accounting, had gone smoothly.
The problem became evident when a user discovered that upon receiving purchase orders, no Cost of Goods Sold account defaulted. This was because the purchase order line items lacked account numbers. Database examination confirmed that the INVINDX field, which stores account indexes for purchase order lines in the POP10110 table, was empty for all 7500 lines.</description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination.</description></item></channel></rss>