<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Roaming on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/roaming/</link><description>Recent content in Roaming on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/roaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel expands ReadyRoam data roaming service to include additional destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 07:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</guid><description>Singtel has improved its ReadyRoam 1GB for 30 days service, making it the first to provide comprehensive multi-destination data roaming across Asia, Europe, the US, and Canada. This enhanced service, which covers 26 countries for S$35 and 11 countries for S$20, offers travelers a convenient way to stay connected.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, highlights that this enhancement caters to the holiday season when many customers travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-expands-readyroam-data-roaming-service-to-include-additional-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cricket Offers Advantages For Urban Dwellers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</guid><description>Are you constantly on your cell phone, talking or texting? Do you live in or around a city and use the internet frequently outside your home or work? If so, Cricket Wireless has cellular service deals that might be perfect for you.
Cricket Wireless operates differently than traditional cell phone providers. First, there are no contracts. Second, most services are unlimited with one exception. Plans range from $30 to $60 per month, all offering unlimited service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel customers enjoy the top roaming experience in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Opensignal. 4G download speed experience in Mbps for Singapore roamers in Malaysia compared to the experience for Malaysian mobile users.
A 2019 Opensignal study on Singaporean 4G users roaming in Malaysia revealed that Singtel subscribers had the best download speeds, upload speeds, and latency.
M1 and StarHub users experienced comparable download and upload speeds while in Malaysia. However, StarHub users enjoyed better latency compared to M1. Although both StarHub and M1 users faced significantly slower latency than Malaysian domestic users, indicating a poorer experience, Singtel users only lagged behind domestic Maxis users by 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-customers-enjoy-the-top-roaming-experience-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mandarin Orchard and Marina Mandarin in Singapore are now providing free local smartphone services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 20:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</guid><description>The Mandarin Orchard Singapore and Marina Mandarin Singapore have added a convenient amenity to all guestrooms: &amp;ldquo;handy,&amp;rdquo; a smartphone solution. This provides registered guests with complimentary unlimited 4G data, local and international calls, online city guides, and ticket booking services for Singapore attractions. Both hotels are managed by Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
With handy now available in all 1,077 rooms at Mandarin Orchard Singapore and 575 rooms at Marina Mandarin Singapore, guests can stay connected while exploring Singapore using their own personalized smartphone outside the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub simplifies mobile customers' ability to browse and travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</guid><description>StarHub Mobile postpaid customers can now subscribe to a Mobile DataTravel plan for S$15. This plan offers 2GB of data valid for 30 days, usable in a single country or across multiple destinations.
DataTravel eliminates the need to manually select or lock phones to specific mobile networks, unlike traditional roaming plans. StarHub highlights this as a unique advantage among Singaporean telcos and plans to expand its list of supported destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-simplifies-mobile-customers-ability-to-browse-and-travel/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>