<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-services/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Exchange - The Final Piece For VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</guid><description>The shift from circuit-switched to packet-switched telephone networks is undeniable. While large companies have adopted enterprise VoIP to enhance efficiency, cut expenses, and prepare for the future, small and medium businesses are considering SIP trunking for bundled high-quality telephone and broadband services. Consumers are switching to cable broadband-telephone packages or third-party VoIP options. However, the PSTN remains.
Currently, VoIP systems and services operate in isolation. On-net calls, meaning calls within the same service regardless of location, are often free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Getting Cavalier About Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</guid><description>Is ignoring Ethernet an option for your business&amp;rsquo;s connection to the world? Can you afford to miss out on its benefits?
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about Cavalier Telephone, a competitive telecom provider, whose Ethernet services are now available on the GeoQuote (tm) search tool within our Shop for Ethernet service. While their name might imply a casual approach, Cavalier is serious about providing the bandwidth your growing business requires.
Cavalier Telephone is a regional Competitive Local Exchange Carrier (CLEC) serving 15 states in the Eastern and Southern US, including Washington D...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ether Rabbit Finds Cheap Ethernet Fast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/</guid><description>Looking for the best deals on Metro Ethernet services? Look no further! We&amp;rsquo;re experts in finding affordable business Ethernet connections.
Curious about our services? Check out our updated website:
Need a quote? Tell us what you need using our inquiry form. Whether you have specific requirements or just want to explore options, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help.
Go ahead and use this inquiry form now. We&amp;rsquo;ll find the right service for you quickly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Sales Support Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in earning money by selling business voice and data services, there&amp;rsquo;s a brokerage service that can simplify the process.
The VAR Network, managed by Telarus, Inc., connects telecom providers with VARs (Value Added Resellers). VARs typically represent manufacturers of business phone systems, network equipment, video conferencing tools, and similar products. They often handle both sales and service, providing clients with complete solutions and ongoing support.
Many VARs, focused on hardware and software, haven&amp;rsquo;t ventured into selling telephone lines or WAN services, which are crucial for a comprehensive business solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Telecom Consulting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, many companies are hesitant to hire consultants due to budget constraints. While consultants can potentially save money in the long run, the initial expense can be difficult to justify. So, how can businesses access consulting services without breaking the bank? The answer is free consulting.
One company offers free technical consulting specializing in business telecommunications. By submitting an online inquiry or calling their toll-free number, businesses can connect with a consultant for immediate assistance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thirty Carriers, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</guid><description>Are you overwhelmed and frustrated with your current telecommunications services? Do you feel stuck with your local phone or internet provider and dread seeing your monthly bill?
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to endure this! You deserve a wide range of choices for your voice and data communication needs. Imagine having access to 30 different business-grade carriers, offering everything from basic phone lines to high-speed internet options like wireless and satellite.
Whether you need ISDN PRI lines for your office phone system, MPLS networks to connect multiple locations, or Gigabit Ethernet for high-bandwidth applications like video conferencing, you have options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Nails Down SIP Trunking Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 05:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</guid><description>Want to discover how your business could save upwards of $88,000 annually just by switching to SIP trunking service?
Hold on a minute! To achieve this level of savings, your business needs to have a certain volume of operations and spending. This figure comes from XO Communications, a leading voice and data carrier, and their new Enterprise SIP Savings Estimator.
So, what kind of business can expect these substantial savings? In this scenario, a company with 1,000 employees spread across 10 locations, where half of their phone calls are internal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-nails-down-sip-trunking-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is a DS3 Circuit Or T3 Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line often choose DS3. This article explores DS3, its relationship to T3 lines, and competition from Ethernet over Copper.
DS3, or Digital Signal level 3, follows standards set by Bell Labs for the telephone industry. The smallest unit, DS0, has a 64 Kbps bandwidth, enough for one digitized phone call using the original digital standard, PCM (Pulse Code Modulation). Combining 24 DS0s creates a DS1, which runs on a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Multiple Data Center Dilemma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</guid><description>The increasing number of mergers and acquisitions has left many companies with a surplus of data centers. Instead of choosing one data center to become the central hub, companies should consider the unique characteristics of each facility, such as equipment, applications, and staffing. Furthermore, consolidating data centers necessitates a reassessment of connectivity.
While internal network traffic often surpasses external traffic, the rising reliance on cloud services demands greater Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional DS3 Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</guid><description>The most popular high-reliability broadband option for businesses, T1 lines, are widely accessible, budget-friendly for most small and medium-sized businesses, and come with various options like PBX telephone lines, dedicated internet, point-to-point electronic data interchange, and Integrated T1 (voice and data combined). The main issue with T1 service is the possibility of outgrowing its capacity.
T1 connections offer 1.5 Mbps full-duplex bandwidth, also known as symmetrical, for internet service, providing 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Right to Competitive T1 Prices Protected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) recently upheld your right to benefit from competition among wireline telecommunication services. The FCC unanimously rejected a request from Verizon Telephone Companies to be released from regulations requiring them to provide competitive access to their lines in six Northeastern cities.
This regulation, part of the Telecommunications Act of 1996, aims to level the playing field between established phone companies and newer competitors. Historically, these incumbent companies, descendants of the Bell System monopoly, operated without competition for a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-right-to-competitive-t1-prices-protected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why You Want A GigE Port</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</guid><description>Is it difficult to predict your future bandwidth requirements? You might be aware of your current traffic levels, but what about tomorrow, next week, or during peak seasons like holidays? How can you plan for the unknown?
Inaccurate bandwidth estimations can lead to overspending on unused capacity or, even worse, business losses due to insufficient bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to optimize your bandwidth allocation.
Traditional telecom services often come with lengthy installation and upgrade processes, making them inflexible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is DS-3 Bandwidth An Endangered Species?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</guid><description>For a long time, businesses needing a moderate amount of bandwidth have relied on DS-3 telecom services for dedicated internet access, file transfers, and video transport. While the price of DS-3 has been steadily decreasing due to increased competition, it might be approaching obsolescence. But why?
The shift began when data packets replaced digitized voice as the dominant traffic on global networks, and now video demands a significant portion of available bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-ds-3-bandwidth-an-endangered-species/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Rising Rapidly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</guid><description>Enhanced business environments and productivity gains through automation are pushing businesses towards higher bandwidth network solutions. Instead of simply increasing their current T1 or other line services, smart managers are exploring new technology that delivers more bandwidth at a lower cost. Ethernet over Copper is emerging as a leading WAN network service.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a straightforward concept: it&amp;rsquo;s an Ethernet service delivered through existing twisted pair copper wiring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>If you need a significant bandwidth upgrade but find traditional options limited or excessively expensive, consider 20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper (EoC). This technology delivers a symmetrical 20 Mbps upload and download speed over readily available twisted pair copper cable.
This professional-grade service provides dedicated, full-duplex bandwidth, allowing simultaneous uploads and downloads at maximum speed. In contrast, T1 lines offer a base speed of 1.5 Mbps and require bonding multiple lines to achieve higher bandwidth, becoming cost-prohibitive beyond 10-12 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Expand Your Telecom Services Line Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 22:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/</guid><description>Instead of physical cards, a &amp;ldquo;line card&amp;rdquo; in telecommunications sales refers to the range of products and services your company provides. Expanding this range can attract new customers and increase sales but often involves higher inventory costs, franchise fees, or sales quotas. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to expand your offerings without these burdens, specifically within the professional telephone and enterprise network sectors.
This opportunity involves selling wireline telecom services. While you might already provide clients with handsets, PBX systems, network equipment, installation, and training, they might be purchasing telecom services elsewhere at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/</a></p></description></item><item><title>600 Mbps Ethernet vs OC12 SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</guid><description>Companies that need bandwidth in the fractional Gigabit range have often relied on OC12 SONET fiber optic service. While it remains a solid high-speed choice, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering 600 Mbps Ethernet as well. Comparing these two options might yield some surprising results.
OC-12 (622 Mbps) is the next tier up from OC-3 (155 Mbps) in the SONET optical carrier hierarchy. This service is widely available in Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and as a dedicated internet access connection for mid-sized internet service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Exchange For Miami, Dallas and Los Angeles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet is emerging as a strong contender to replace the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), as evidenced by the increasing number of Ethernet Exchanges that facilitate traffic sharing among carriers. Telx, a prominent interconnection and colocation provider, recently expanded its Ethernet Exchange services to Miami, Dallas, and Los Angeles. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the significance of Ethernet Exchange and its impact on the future of international wide-area networking.
The PSTN&amp;rsquo;s global reach and interoperability have contributed to its longstanding success, enabling communication between any two phones worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI Offers Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 15:39:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</guid><description>If your company relies heavily on phone communication, using numerous phone lines managed by an internal system, ISDN PRI might be the solution for you. It provides excellent voice quality, quick call transfers, and additional features like Caller ID, all while potentially saving you money.
ISDN PRI, or Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is an advanced form of the traditional T1 digital phone line. While it utilizes the same T1 line infrastructure, making it widely accessible, its channel organization sets it apart...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-offers-caller-id/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet From Coast To Coast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</guid><description>Imagine your current office Ethernet network expanding beyond the building, connecting your locations across the city and the country. This vision of a unified, nationwide network is now a reality with Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet is essentially the same Ethernet used in local networks, but enhanced and standardized for use in metropolitan and long-distance networks.
To get Carrier Ethernet, businesses need to partner with a network provider offering this service. These providers typically have built extensive, nationwide fiber optic networks with service points in major cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speeds Without DS3 Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</guid><description>Businesses needing substantial bandwidth for tasks like online commerce, video streaming, medical data transfer, or dedicated internet access have historically relied on DS3 connections. These provided speeds exceeding T1 lines. However, a new option delivers comparable speeds without the high price tag: Metro Ethernet and Carrier Ethernet.
These terms represent regional and long-distance high-bandwidth transport services using the Ethernet protocol. An Ethernet WAN connection connects your LAN to another business location, a network of multiple locations, or a dedicated high-speed internet connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over DS3 Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber are becoming increasingly popular choices for WAN connections. This popularity is driven by competitive pricing and the availability of services like layer 2 switching with direct Ethernet connections. So why would you consider Ethernet over DS3?
It may seem like an unusual combination. DS3, a widely available telecom service, provides 45 Mbps using TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) technology from the T-Carrier standard. Organizations typically use DS3 for dedicated point-to-point connections, high-bandwidth internet access, and high-volume phone lines in contact and call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find The Ethernet Internet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</guid><description>Looking for increased bandwidth for your business without the high price tag? An Ethernet Internet connection might be the solution you need.
Ethernet Internet connections are a newer offering. While we’ve utilized Ethernet in our local area networks for years and the internet itself aligns with LAN Ethernet, connecting the two has involved specialized telecom services.
You likely currently have T1 or DS3 service, which require specific equipment and software for protocol conversion and signal interfacing with standard network Ethernet ports...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Taming The Video Bandwidth Monster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</guid><description>Cisco forecasts that video will represent over half of all internet traffic by the close of next year, reaching 62% by 2015&amp;rsquo;s end. This surge in video consumption, driven by streaming and downloads, necessitates that both providers and consumers adapt to the escalating demand for bandwidth.
Netflix&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a cable and satellite TV competitor is accelerating the dominance of video data on the internet. Consumers are experiencing a transformation in how they consume &amp;ldquo;TV,&amp;rdquo; now utilizing computers, tablets, and smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DS1 DS3 Relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</guid><description>The terms DS1 and DS3 are frequently used in business telecommunications networking. DS, which stands for Digital Signal level, indicates the capacity of a digital line within the T-carrier system. Essentially, DS1 is associated with T1 service, while DS3 corresponds with T3.
The origins of the T-carrier system can be traced back to the 1950s when Bell Labs recognized the benefits of transitioning from an entirely analog telephone system to digital connections between telephone company offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrated T1 Gives You Phone and Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:42:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</guid><description>Small businesses need high-quality telecom services without the high price tag of large corporations. While you might not need the same capacity as a major company, you can still access reliable phone and internet services tailored to your needs.
Achieving this involves using a T1 line, a standard for voice and data transmission. While medium-sized companies might have multiple T1 lines, a single line can suffice for smaller businesses by combining phone and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>