<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SPRING on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spring/</link><description>Recent content in SPRING on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:10:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Hood Mounting Screw Springs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</guid><description>During my quest for the ideal Beogram 4000 turntable, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that none of the early models possess the hood mounting screw springs found on the later Beogram 4002 and 4004. These springs make removing and attaching the hood significantly easier. After consulting the service manuals, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the Beogram 4000 was not designed with these springs. It seems B&amp;amp;O employed a continuous improvement approach, refining their designs over time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Missing Leaf Spring on a Plate Lock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</guid><description>During the rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5513), I encountered an issue while adjusting the sub-chassis, platter, and tonearm. The large aluminum plate wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly against the plinth when it was pushed back, making it impossible to align the platter flush with the plate.
The problem originated from one of the locking mechanisms in the back left corner. These locks, equipped with leaf springs, are designed to secure the plate to the frame when the plinth is moved back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-missing-leaf-spring-on-a-plate-lock/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore fully supports the enhancement of quality and standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 08:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/</guid><description>SPRING Singapore has increased its grant budget by S$10 million to assist local businesses in enhancing quality and utilizing standards as key business strategies. Enterprises can leverage this funding to create and implement new standards.
Quality and standards can make businesses more efficient, minimize waste, produce safer and higher-quality environmentally friendly products, and create stronger product and service differentiation.
SPRING will also provide funding to establish new standards development organizations that will manage the creation and promotion of standards in emerging sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-fully-supports-the-enhancement-of-quality-and-standards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Government support for research and development in Singapore SMEs and startups has been increased</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</guid><description>The Singapore government is increasing its support for research, development, and commercialization (R&amp;amp;D&amp;amp;C) activities undertaken by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups. This support encompasses financial assistance through grants, participation in business incubator programs, and favorable tax structures, as highlighted by Lim Chuan Poh, Chairman of the Agency for Science, Technology and Research (A*STAR), during his guest speaker appearance at the Developer and Global Entrepreneur Day, part of IBM&amp;rsquo;s XCite event in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter and the Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</guid><description>Having completed the restoration of the Beogram 4000, I noticed the platter wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting correctly within its aluminum panel. It needed adjustments to align it properly. The service manual suggests adjusting the platter in relation to the chassis first, and then aligning the chassis within the enclosure. This ensures the platter sits flush and centered within the panel, achieving that desirable &amp;ldquo;Beoloving&amp;rdquo; aesthetic.
To illustrate the process, I created two videos...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-and-the-chassis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>