<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computer-network/</link><description>Recent content in Computer Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computer-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price.</description></item><item><title>The Gift of Bandwidth For Administrative Professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Administrative Professionals Week, a time to show appreciation for those essential staff members who keep everything running smoothly. While thoughtful gestures like cards and lunches are always appreciated, let&amp;rsquo;s not forget about the practical tools that can truly empower administrative professionals to excel in their roles.
Beyond personal recognition, what administrative professionals truly benefit from are improved tools that enhance their productivity. These individuals are often models of efficiency, making the most of available resources.</description></item><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities.</description></item></channel></rss>