<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Excellence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/excellence/</link><description>Recent content in Excellence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/excellence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Frost introduces the Thailand Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</guid><description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, a global business growth consulting firm, granted 28 Thailand Excellence Awards to companies that exhibited remarkable accomplishments and exceptional performance across various sectors.
Koh Eng Lok, Country Head of Thailand at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, highlighted the recipients&amp;rsquo; dedication to their clients. He explained that the award categories are carefully chosen each year to represent the prevailing market trends and encompass both established and emerging segments. The sectors range from ICT, automotive, energy &amp;amp; power, healthcare, building technologies to chemicals and palm oil...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CHKLC has announced the winners of the 2014 HK Corporate Governance Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</guid><description>The Chamber of Hong Kong Listed Companies (CHKLC) recently revealed the winners of the Hong Kong Corporate Governance Excellence Awards 2014. The CHKLC defines corporate governance as respecting shareholder rights and values, maintaining board and management integrity, and demonstrating transparency and accountability.
Dr. Eddy Fong, Judging Panel Chairman, highlighted that the awardees went beyond standard practices, tailoring their governance strategies to address industry-specific risks and challenges.
&amp;ldquo;Furthermore,&amp;rdquo; he stated, &amp;ldquo;winning companies view sustainability as inseparable from good corporate governance, crucial for long-term growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>