<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ordinary Legislative Procedure on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ordinary-legislative-procedure/</link><description>Recent content in Ordinary Legislative Procedure on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ordinary-legislative-procedure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it time for the EU to increase transparency in its legislative process, as condemned by the EU Court?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</guid><description>Massimo Frigo, Senior Legal Adviser of the International Commission of Jurist’s Europe Programme*
Occasionally, cases concerning seemingly insignificant administrative matters evolve into pivotal judgments, shaping the continuous development of our democratic legal frameworks. A prime example in the US is Marbury v. Madison, a case initially garnering limited public interest due to its focus on judicial appointment procedures. Nonetheless, it ultimately established the crucial precedent of constitutional review within the US legal system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>