<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EoF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eof/</link><description>Recent content in EoF on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eof/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>GigE and FastE Bandwidth Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 04:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-and-faste-bandwidth-services/</guid><description>Companies routinely upgrade their bandwidth from older technologies like T1 lines to faster Ethernet options, often without significant cost increases. However, for those requiring substantial bandwidth, choices beyond these basic levels are necessary.
Carrier Ethernet is becoming the preferred choice for medium to high bandwidth needs, replacing traditional DS3, T3, and SONET technologies. Ethernet offers cost advantages and greater flexibility in provisioning.
Lower bandwidth Ethernet services commonly utilize existing copper telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>Lock In Telecom Cost Savings For Next Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lock-in-telecom-cost-savings-for-next-year/</guid><description>As we wrap up the year and analyze our performance, it&amp;rsquo;s common to wonder if we&amp;rsquo;re overspending on business operations, especially networking and telecom. A thorough market analysis often reveals opportunities to secure better rates for the same services. By doing this now, you can lock in savings for the entire next year.
Why are such savings possible? Primarily, increased competition and technological advancements. Previously, businesses were limited to local telephone companies for their communication needs.</description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</guid><description>Metropolitan and Wide Area Networks can send your data anywhere you want. To access these networks, you need a connection known as &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connectivity. Ethernet offers advantages for this first mile link.
Several technologies, such as T1 lines, DSL, SONET fiber optic services, and even microwave or 3G/4G wireless, work well for first mile connections. These options connect your building to your service provider or a gateway to their network.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Fiber Needed By Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</guid><description>While many believe fiber optic bandwidth is the way of the future, it&amp;rsquo;s already a smart choice for businesses today.
Traditionally, businesses have depended on copper-based telecom services. The copper wiring integrated during a building&amp;rsquo;s construction becomes the backbone for multi-line phone systems, ISDN digital trunking for PBX systems, and T1 lines connecting offices and providing broadband internet. This infrastructure has been the standard for many small and medium-sized businesses for decades.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Business-grade Carrier Ethernet services are gaining popularity. If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about Ethernet and its potential benefits, read on.
Ethernet dominates as a LAN protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable how quickly it outpaced competitors. Switched Ethernet is nearly ubiquitous. A similar shift is happening with telecom services, moving from traditional circuit-switched technologies to packet-switched networks that align better with modern devices. Ethernet is poised to become the standard for both metropolitan and long-distance networks.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV.</description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Connection Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</guid><description>Businesses require internet access for both customer communication and internal operations. Unlike residential internet, business connections demand higher reliability because downtime directly translates to financial losses, especially for online businesses. Cost-effectiveness is also crucial.
Ethernet Internet is a relatively new technology that offers advantages in both cost and reliability. Additionally, it may provide bandwidth options previously unavailable in your area. A quick search with this Ethernet Internet Finder can reveal your options.</description></item><item><title>Copper First, Then Fiber Bandwidth Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</guid><description>When your business needs a fast internet connection but fiber optic installation isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a two-step solution that uses existing technology as a stopgap. This method combines the strengths of different connection types to get you online quickly and upgrade seamlessly later on.
Fiber optic connections, whether SONET or Ethernet, provide the highest bandwidth– starting from 50-100 Mbps and reaching up to 10 Gbps or even higher in some areas.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines.</description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Next Wire Should Be Glass</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 11:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-next-wire-should-be-glass/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The telecommunications and computer networking industries were built upon copper wire technology. While technologies like Cat5e and Cat6 cabling are sufficient for many networking needs, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering fiber optic solutions for your next connection.
LAN vs. WAN Copper-based Ethernet is effective for short distances, making it suitable for internal networks. Most users don&amp;rsquo;t require speeds exceeding 1000 Mbps. Therefore, installing fiber to individual desktops seems excessive.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors.</description></item></channel></rss>