<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireless Backup on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-backup/</link><description>Recent content in Wireless Backup on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 Line With Instant Wireless Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</guid><description>Losing business broadband during a crucial moment can be incredibly frustrating. This is why many companies choose dedicated T1 lines instead of standard DSL or cable internet, despite the higher reliability of T1, they can still experience outages. Issues like equipment malfunctions or accidents can unexpectedly cut your connection.
To prevent downtime, some companies opt for diverse T1 service, ordering two lines from separate providers. However, this solution isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof, as both lines often use the same physical infrastructure owned by the Incumbent Local Exchange Carrier (ILEC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>