<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workstation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workstation/</link><description>Recent content in Workstation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workstation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell creates business solutions to meet the needs of modern workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</guid><description>The new Latitude series blends elegant design with enterprise-grade security, manageability, and dependability.
The Vostro line offers a balance of performance and style for small businesses.
Redesigned Precision workstations provide sleek, new choices for creative professionals.
OptiPlex business PCs have become more compact, faster, and more energy-efficient.
New Dell printing solutions grant one-stop access to various cloud-based services.
Rakesh Mandal, Director and GM of Client Solutions for South Asia &amp;amp; Korea at Dell, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to providing state-of-the-art products developed using user insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-creates-business-solutions-to-meet-the-needs-of-modern-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces new Tiny all-in-one workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 18:49:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s new TiO features a compact desktop computer (shown on the left) that connects to the back of a 23-inch monitor (on the right). These components can function independently or as a combined unit.
Lenovo introduced workstations and a &amp;lsquo;Tiny-in-one&amp;rsquo; (TiO) as part of its final significant product launch in 2014.
Pictured on the left are Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s latest workstation models.
&amp;ldquo;We carefully considered extensive customer feedback after the recent debut of our P300 workstation,&amp;rdquo; stated Jessie Quek, Lenovo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Country General Manager...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces the ThinkStation P series of desktop workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo has introduced the ThinkStation P Series, a new line of desktop workstations. The P900, P700, and P500 models join the entry-level P300, which was launched in May 2014, to form Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s most potent professional-grade desktop workstations.
Rob Herman, Director of Worldwide Workstation Product and Vertical Marketing at Lenovo, stated that the company listened to customer feedback regarding the need for faster, more dependable, and user-friendly workstations, and the ThinkStation P Series is their response...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-the-thinkstation-p-series-of-desktop-workstations/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>