<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analytics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analytics/</link><description>Recent content in Analytics on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eliminating uncertainty in analytics with BeyondCore Apps for Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</guid><description>Source: BeyondCore website.
BeyondCore has introduced BeyondCore Apps for Office, a solution that provides automated analysis for the Microsoft Office suite with a single click. The company recognized the need for accessible and efficient analytics tools for business users who require data-driven insights to make informed decisions and improve their operations.
Arijit Sengupta, CEO and Founder of BeyondCore, highlighted the challenges of traditional analytics, describing it as a manual and time-consuming process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify has identified a total of 1,369 musical genres up to this point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</guid><description>Spotify uses a music intelligence platform that analyzes music in real time to pinpoint groups of similar sounds, which helps them discover and categorize emerging music genres.
Eliot Van Buskirk, Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Data Storyteller, highlighted in a blog post that this allows Spotify to stay ahead of the curve in identifying new genres as they emerge, ensuring users can discover them quickly.
The platform analyzes the listening habits of real music fans to understand how songs and artists are trending within specific genres...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free E-Books to Get More Sales Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market, businesses face constant pressure to attract and retain customers. Finding new customers is crucial for growth, as a lack of fresh leads can cause a business to stagnate and eventually fail. Companies that can&amp;rsquo;t adapt to changing market conditions risk being overtaken by more agile competitors or innovative startups.
To help your business thrive, we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of free ebooks offering valuable insights on enhancing sales and marketing strategies in the age of social media:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>