<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software Defined Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/software-defined-network/</link><description>Recent content in Software Defined Network on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/software-defined-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>