<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Saudi Arabia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/saudi-arabia/</link><description>Recent content in Saudi Arabia on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/saudi-arabia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft.</description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year.</description></item><item><title>Flynas has teamed up with Pegasus Airlines to provide flights from Saudi Arabia to Turkey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</guid><description>Source: flynas. Aerial view of Turkey.
The Saudi Arabian airline flynas has partnered with Turkish budget airline Pegasus Airlines to expand its flight offerings in Turkey. This collaboration will initially allow flynas passengers to travel to five new Turkish destinations: Antalya, Ankara, Adana, Hatay, and Trabzon. This will be achieved by utilizing Pegasus Airlines&amp;rsquo; extensive network of domestic flights operating from Istanbul&amp;rsquo;s Sabiha Gökçen International Airport.
Bander Al Mohanna, Group CEO of NAS Holding, stated that Pegasus Airlines is a leading Turkish airline with over two decades of experience in innovation within the country&amp;rsquo;s aviation industry.</description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base.</description></item><item><title>Lateefa AlWaalan has been awarded the title of Saudi Arabia's EY Entrepreneur Of The Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</guid><description>Lateefa AlWaalan, the driving force behind the Arabic coffee startup Yatooq, has been crowned Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s EY Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) for 2015.
A panel of independent judges selected AlWaalan from a pool of eleven finalists representing ten different companies. Her entrepreneurial spirit, robust financial performance, strategic thinking, and positive social impact distinguished her as a leader. Fahad Altoaimi, EY&amp;rsquo;s Office Managing Partner in Riyadh and the Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader, emphasized that this award recognizes AlWaalan&amp;rsquo;s significant business accomplishments, innovative spirit, and contributions to her community.</description></item></channel></rss>