<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU Judicial System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-judicial-system/</link><description>Recent content in EU Judicial System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:40:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-judicial-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do not bring up the additional judges!" The transformation of CJEU reform into a mockery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ongoing debate surrounding the reform of the Court of Justice (CJEU) is becoming increasingly chaotic, reminiscent of an episode of the British comedy &amp;ldquo;Fawlty Towers.&amp;rdquo; The show&amp;rsquo;s humor stems from Basil Fawlty&amp;rsquo;s futile attempts to manage unpredictable situations in his hotel, often venting his frustrations on his staff. While no one would endorse his management style, the current CJEU reform debate mirrors this comedic chaos.
To recap, following several unsuccessful attempts to reform the EU judicial structure, the CJEU proposed that the General Court, the lower EU court, should double its number of judges to two per Member State.</description></item><item><title>Reforming the EU's Court System: The path to progress lies in creating a more accountable court, not simply a larger one.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</guid><description>Alberto Alemanno, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law &amp;amp; Risk Regulation, HEC Paris
Laurent Pech, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Middlesex University London
1. Setting the Stage
Recent media attention on the EU Court of Justice highlights a departure from its previous low profile. Surprisingly, this attention is not focused on a specific court decision but rather on internal disputes regarding a proposal to address the court&amp;rsquo;s efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Politicians 1, Architects 0: Constructing the EU Judicial System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently suggested that the EU should double the number of judges on the General Court and eliminate the EU Civil Service Tribunal. This piece examines the reasons behind this significant proposition for restructuring the EU judicial system and evaluates its merits.
Background
The EU judicial system has consistently expanded to accommodate a growing caseload. The Single European Act of 1987 allowed for the establishment of the Court of First Instance (renamed the General Court by the Lisbon Treaty) to support the Court of Justice.</description></item></channel></rss>