<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ACCA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/acca/</link><description>Recent content in ACCA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/acca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession.</description></item><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally.</description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field.</description></item><item><title>ACCA predicts a growing market demand for professional business and advisory services in ASEAN and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-predicts-a-growing-market-demand-for-professional-business-and-advisory-services-in-asean-and-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-predicts-a-growing-market-demand-for-professional-business-and-advisory-services-in-asean-and-china/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), the world&amp;rsquo;s largest global professional accounting body, has published a new report, supported by the Singapore Accountancy Commission, that explores the future demand for professional business and advisory services.
Source: ACCA Global website. Cover for
the Market demand for Professional
Business and Advisory Services report.
The report highlights the increasing demand for professional services, particularly those related to data science, analytics, and artificial intelligence, by corporations, including small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs).</description></item></channel></rss>