<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Oman on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oman/</link><description>Recent content in Oman on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anantara's Al Baleed Resort Salalah introduces new wellness program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anantara-s-al-baleed-resort-salalah-introduces-new-wellness-program/</guid><description>Source: Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara. The Balance Wellness by Anantara program includes custom-designed vegan cuisine.
The luxurious, private pool villa resort Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara has introduced a new wellness program with an a la carte approach.
Situated between a private beach and a freshwater lagoon in Salalah, Oman, Al Baleed Resort Salalah by Anantara provides a serene setting for guests to focus on their wellness goals.</description></item><item><title>Terhal by Bank Muscat provides financing for travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:19:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/terhal-by-bank-muscat-provides-financing-for-travel/</guid><description>To celebrate the summer holidays (from Q2 to Q3) and the upcoming Eid al Fitr, Bank Muscat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Terhal,&amp;rdquo; a new set of travel services combined with banking features. This initiative reflects the bank&amp;rsquo;s motto, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s do more,&amp;rdquo; and aims to offer a unique banking experience for customers who enjoy traveling.
Terhal provides customers with access to financing up to RO10,000 at a 3.5% interest rate, repayable over a year.</description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal.</description></item><item><title>You can book Mwasalat taxis without using the mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-book-mwasalat-taxis-without-using-the-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Mwasalat. Taxi Butler devices will offer taxi booking
services.
Mwasalat has introduced &amp;ldquo;Taxi Butlers,&amp;rdquo; kiosks that streamline taxi bookings. This initiative is part of the public transportation company&amp;rsquo;s ongoing plan to modernize Oman&amp;rsquo;s taxi services.
Taxi Butlers eliminate the hassle of individual driver contact by allowing users to pre-book taxis. The kiosks offer the convenience of booking multiple taxis and provide passengers with real-time updates on arrival times, driver information, and vehicle arrival alerts.</description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank celebrates reaching 100,000 Facebook Likes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</guid><description>Alizz Islamic Bank has achieved a significant milestone by reaching 100,000 likes on Facebook. This achievement places them among the top two banks in Oman to attain this level of popularity on the platform.
Over the past year, Alizz Islamic Bank has significantly bolstered its social media presence, driven by a strong belief in its ability to enhance customer service. In addition to their Facebook success, they have also surpassed 30,000 followers on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank has enhanced its mobile application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</guid><description>Source: Alizz Islamic Bank. The app.
Alizz Islamic Bank has introduced a redesigned mobile banking app and online platform to solidify its position as a customer experience frontrunner in Oman.
The dual-language app, compatible with both Android and iOS devices, boasts high-level security features and a self-registration option. Users can conveniently manage web banking logins, money transfers, bill payments, and other transactions using QR codes. The app is compatible with 3D Touch technology and is the first of its kind in Oman to provide in-app alerts for new transactions and payment reminders.</description></item><item><title>Bank Sohar introduces a new relationship banking service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 04:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/</guid><description>Bank Sohar has introduced &amp;ldquo;Al Khaas,&amp;rdquo; a premium banking service designed to provide a personalized experience. This service includes dedicated relationship managers, wealth advisors, exclusive banking centers, a dedicated call center, and a range of benefits such as prize draws, rewards, and more.
Al Khaas aims to meet the needs of high-net-worth individuals (HNI) by providing a superior banking experience across all of its 31 branches in Oman. Dedicated Al Khaas service centers will also be available in select major branches.</description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer.</description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board.</description></item></channel></rss>