<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Akamai on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/akamai/</link><description>Recent content in Akamai on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/akamai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization.</description></item></channel></rss>