<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Camera on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/camera/</link><description>Recent content in Camera on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/camera/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>EZVIZ introduces new action cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 07:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ezviz-introduces-new-action-cameras/</guid><description>Source: EZVIZ. The FIVE action cam.
EZVIZ, a company specializing in Wi-Fi cloud cameras and video surveillance equipment, will introduce a new action camera series at CES 2016, designed for sports enthusiasts and content creators.
Priced at US$299.99, the EZVIZ FIVE action camera boasts an Ambarella A12 chipset, a built-in 2-inch IPS touchscreen with 320x240 resolution, a 900mAh battery, and the capability to record continuously at 4K resolution at 15 frames per second.</description></item><item><title>Sony has expanded its range of full-frame lenses and introduced a new OSS Super-Telephoto lens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-expanded-its-range-of-full-frame-lenses-and-introduced-a-new-oss-super-telephoto-lens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-expanded-its-range-of-full-frame-lenses-and-introduced-a-new-oss-super-telephoto-lens/</guid><description>Sony unveiled its latest addition to the full-frame E-mount lens lineup: the FE 24-105mm F4 G OSS Standard Zoom (model SEL24105G). This new lens covers the popular 24-105mm focal length range, offering exceptional G Lens image quality in a lightweight design. Its fast, precise, and quiet autofocus makes it suitable for both still photography and video recording with Sony E-mount cameras.
High-Quality Optics The Sony FE 24-105mm F4 G OSS lens provides excellent sharpness across the entire zoom range, along with aesthetically pleasing background blur (bokeh) at all focal lengths.</description></item><item><title>I Know Where You Took Your Pictures Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</guid><description>Eye-Fi, the WiFi-enabled memory card, has introduced a new feature: location tagging. Their latest product, Eye-Fi Explore, automatically adds geotags to photos as you take them.
You might be surprised to learn that they haven&amp;rsquo;t actually included a GPS receiver in the small SD card. Instead, it uses a system that determines location based on known WiFi hotspots. This method covers a significant portion of the U.S. population and major metropolitan areas in Europe.</description></item><item><title>OPPO empowers Singaporeans to discover the ultimate experience with #UncoverTheUltimate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</guid><description>Last week, OPPO, a global provider of smart devices, introduced its latest lineup of smartphones, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s first 5G offering, the Find X2 Pro 5G, and a new addition to its creative Reno series, the Reno3.
This unveiling follows the global online launch of the Find X2 series on March 6. The Find X2 Pro boasts a 120 Hz QHD AMOLED screen, 65 W SuperVOOC Flash Charge 2.0 technology, and the Qualcomm Snapdragon 865 processor, delivering an enhanced overall photography and video experience.</description></item><item><title>The Huawei nova 2i is a mid-range phone with four cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</guid><description>Source: Huawei website. The nova 2i boasts a 5.9&amp;quot; FullView display.
Huawei has released the nova 2i, a 4G LTE mid-range phone designed for users who love taking selfies. This device stands out with its four cameras - two in the front and two on the back.
Clement Wong, Director of Global Product Marketing for the Huawei Consumer Business Group, highlighted that four cameras are uncommon in mid-range phones. He explained that Huawei aims to make its cutting-edge technology accessible to a wider customer base.</description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently.</description></item><item><title>The EOS M6 Mark II from Canon offers exceptional video production capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Canon the EOS M6 Mark II.
Canon has expanded its EOS M series of mirrorless cameras with the new EOS M6 Mark II. This stylish and portable camera is significantly lighter and smaller than a typical mid-range DSLR.
Edwin Teoh, Head of Marketing for Canon Singapore, highlights the EOS M6 Mark II&amp;rsquo;s portability and enhanced features, emphasizing its ability to capture life&amp;rsquo;s important moments. He also points out the camera&amp;rsquo;s advanced video capabilities, catering to the increasing popularity of videography and vlogging.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new 4K HDR camcorders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</guid><description>Sony has introduced three new 4K HDR1 camcorders—the XDCAM PXW-Z90, the NXCAM HXR-NX80, and the Handycam FDR-AX700—all featuring Sony&amp;rsquo;s Fast Hybrid AF system.
Source: Sony. Sony launches new 4K HDR camcorders.
These compact camcorders all share the same fast and dependable autofocus system, designed specifically for their 1.0-type stacked Exmor RS CMOS image sensor. This allows them to capture high-quality footage with excellent clarity and offer a variety of shooting options.</description></item><item><title>Blackmagic Design presents 4K Pocket Cinema Camera and DaVinci Resolve 15 at Broadcast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackmagic-design-presents-4k-pocket-cinema-camera-and-davinci-resolve-15-at-broadcast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 07:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackmagic-design-presents-4k-pocket-cinema-camera-and-davinci-resolve-15-at-broadcast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Blackmagic Design. Camera, video editing software slated for an Asia Pacific launch at Broadcast Asia.
Blackmagic Design is introducing the Pocket Cinema Camera 4K and DaVinci Resolve 15 to the Asia Pacific market at Broadcast Asia. Though intended for professional filmmakers, the line between pro-grade gear and high-end solutions for business or personal use is becoming increasingly blurred.
“Blackmagic Design is committed to making top-tier video production accessible to everyone, fostering a truly creative post-production and television industry,” remarked Grant Petty, Blackmagic Design CEO.</description></item><item><title>The new α7R III camera from Sony offers a combination of high resolution and fast speed for interchangeable lenses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-7r-iii-camera-from-sony-offers-a-combination-of-high-resolution-and-fast-speed-for-interchangeable-lenses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-7r-iii-camera-from-sony-offers-a-combination-of-high-resolution-and-fast-speed-for-interchangeable-lenses/</guid><description>Sony has introduced the α7R III (model ILCE-7RM3), a new full-frame mirrorless camera. This camera boasts a high-resolution 42.4MP back-illuminated Exmor R CMOS image sensor and advanced image processing. It can shoot continuously at up to 10 fps with full AF/AE tracking and produces stunning image and 4K video quality. Other notable features include a 15-stop dynamic range, high sensitivity with reduced noise, and more.
Exceptional Image Quality The camera&amp;rsquo;s 42.</description></item><item><title>The V40ThinQ smartphone by LG has been revealed in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has launched the LG V40ThinQ, a new smartphone with five cameras. Designed for today&amp;rsquo;s multimedia storytellers, the device is marketed as a powerful tool for content creation.
Source: LG.
Staying true to the V series design, the LG V40ThinQ boasts an enhanced 6.4&amp;quot; FullVision OLED display with even slimmer bezels. It runs on the Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 Mobile Platform, coupled with 6 GB of RAM and 128 GB of internal storage, promising a superior smartphone camera experience.</description></item><item><title>Preorders for GoPro HERO5 cameras and Karma drones are now available at Shopee Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 14:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorders-for-gopro-hero5-cameras-and-karma-drones-are-now-available-at-shopee-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a popular online marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is now offering preorders for the new GoPro HERO5 cameras.
Source: GoPro. The HERO5 series.
GoPro&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO, Nicholas Woodman, introduced the HERO5 on September 19th, alongside a cloud-based software platform and the Karma drone.
Woodman emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to easy storytelling: &amp;ldquo;With these new products, we&amp;rsquo;re making it simpler to capture and share compelling stories. HERO5&amp;rsquo;s automatic photo and video uploads to GoPro Plus streamline the entire process of editing, sharing, and enjoying your experiences on the go.</description></item><item><title>Fujifilm has launched the X100T premium compact camera in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:44:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fujifilm-has-launched-the-x100t-premium-compact-camera-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Fujifilm has introduced the X100T, a high-end compact camera succeeding the successful X100S, to the Middle East market.
Source: Fujifilm. The X100T is available
in black and silver.
&amp;ldquo;The X100, launched in March 2011, established a new market for premium compact cameras. A year later, the second-generation X100S was released, featuring an updated sensor, processor, and an advanced Hybrid Viewfinder,&amp;rdquo; stated Yuta Kawamura, Marketing Manager for the electronic imaging division at Fujifilm Middle East &amp;amp; Africa.</description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI P30 completely sold out on its first day in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Huawei P30 Series launched in Singapore at VivoCity yesterday and quickly sold out, with the first people in line having arrived the night before to buy the newest model in Huawei&amp;rsquo;s photography-focused smartphone line.
The Huawei P30 Series has garnered attention since its global launch last week in France for its Leica Quad Camera, the first of its kind, which boasts cutting-edge zoom and low-light capabilities.
Yvelyn Tey, the first person in line, waited with her fiance to purchase the phone.</description></item><item><title>HTC revolutionizes photography with the RE camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</guid><description>HTC is launching a new camera called the RE, aiming to change how people take pictures. This waterproof handheld device can capture time-lapse photos and even act as a remote viewfinder for smartphones.
Source: HTC blog.
HTC CEO Peter Chou emphasizes their dedication to innovation, stating that the RE camera will allow people to experience photography in a new way. The RE&amp;rsquo;s grip sensor activates upon pickup, removing the need for a power button.</description></item><item><title>Canon has introduced a second camera to its mirrorless EOS R range and has also revealed its RF lens roadmap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-introduced-a-second-camera-to-its-mirrorless-eos-r-range-and-has-also-revealed-its-rf-lens-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-has-introduced-a-second-camera-to-its-mirrorless-eos-r-range-and-has-also-revealed-its-rf-lens-roadmap/</guid><description>Canon has introduced the EOS RP, the second camera in their EOS R series of full-frame mirrorless interchangeable-lens cameras.
The EOS RP is the lightest and most compact camera in Canon&amp;rsquo;s full-frame lineup, but it still packs impressive capabilities. It boasts the new RF lens mount and Canon&amp;rsquo;s proprietary technology, including a DIGIC 8 image processor and Dual Pixel CMOS AF for exceptional optical quality.
Significantly smaller than other EOS cameras, the EOS RP weighs only 485g, making it comfortable to use, especially for those new to full-frame cameras.</description></item><item><title>Huawei has launched the HUAWEI nova 3i</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 06:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</guid><description>Singapore is among the first countries globally to introduce the HUAWEI nova 3i, a midrange smartphone equipped with AI-powered front-facing dual cameras.
Huawei aims to make high-end technology and value accessible to budget-conscious consumers, according to Cheng Jiangfei, Managing Director of Huawei Singapore Consumer Business Group. He emphasized that the HUAWEI nova 3i combines stylish design with advanced AI features, offering exceptional quality and functionality at an affordable price.
Notable features of the HUAWEI nova 3i include:</description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:</description></item></channel></rss>