<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accenture on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accenture/</link><description>Recent content in Accenture on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accenture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>According to Accenture, gaining digital skills could help reduce the gender gap by up to 40 years faster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-accenture-gaining-digital-skills-could-help-reduce-the-gender-gap-by-up-to-40-years-faster/</guid><description>Source: Accenture. Closing the gender gap at work.
According to Accenture research, digital skills and technologies are empowering women in Singapore to secure and progress in their careers. However, a wage disparity persists, with men earning more. Ranked 5th out of 31 countries in Accenture&amp;rsquo;s research, Singaporean women demonstrate significant progress in digital fluency, reflecting their adoption and utilization of digital tools for knowledge acquisition, networking, and enhanced efficiency.</description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence.</description></item><item><title>Entrepreneurs may find synergy in collaborating with larger corporations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-may-find-synergy-in-collaborating-with-larger-corporations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entrepreneurs-may-find-synergy-in-collaborating-with-larger-corporations/</guid><description>Large corporations are missing out on a $1.5 trillion global growth opportunity by not collaborating with entrepreneurs on digital innovation, reveals a new study by Accenture. This missed opportunity, representing 2.2% of global GDP, exists despite the fact that businesses of all sizes recognize the need for digital transformation.
The report, &amp;ldquo;Harnessing the Power of Entrepreneurs to Open Innovation,&amp;rdquo; surveyed over 1,000 entrepreneurs and 1,000 large companies across G20 nations. Findings indicate that 82% of corporations acknowledge the learning potential startups offer in digital business transformation.</description></item><item><title>Investment in Fintech in the Asia Pacific region is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investment-in-fintech-in-the-asia-pacific-region-is-increasing/</guid><description>By July 31st of this year, financial technology (fintech) ventures in the Asia-Pacific region, especially in China, secured US$9.62 billion in investments. This represents more than double the US$4.26 billion invested across the entire region throughout 2015, as reported by Accenture.
Data from CB Insights reveals that Asia-Pacific leads in fintech investments, surpassing both North America and Europe. As of July 31st, North America attracted US$4.58 billion, while Europe received US$1.</description></item><item><title>Accenture states that just-in-time marketing leads to higher conversion rates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-states-that-just-in-time-marketing-leads-to-higher-conversion-rates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 06:19:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-states-that-just-in-time-marketing-leads-to-higher-conversion-rates/</guid><description>Source: Accenture infographic.
A recent report from Accenture, based on a survey of over 500 chief marketing officers (CMOs) globally, suggests that just-in-time marketing can lead to a greater return on investment and significantly boost revenue growth. Companies using this method are three times more likely to surpass their competitors in terms of revenue growth.
Just-in-time marketing focuses on crafting relevant marketing content precisely when needed and tailoring it to appeal to interested consumers at the exact moment they are ready to make a purchase.</description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future.</description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand.</description></item></channel></rss>