<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blue Card on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blue-card/</link><description>Recent content in Blue Card on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blue-card/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance.</description></item><item><title>Will the new Blue Card proposal entice a greater number of highly skilled workers to the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-blue-card-proposal-entice-a-greater-number-of-highly-skilled-workers-to-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-blue-card-proposal-entice-a-greater-number-of-highly-skilled-workers-to-the-eu/</guid><description>Jean-Baptiste Farcy, Research Assistant, Universite Catholique de Louvain
Introduction
After a 2001 attempt to create a comprehensive EU law regarding entry and residency for non-EU workers failed, the EU&amp;rsquo;s approach to labor migration has been fragmented and industry-specific. Due to the sensitivity surrounding immigration and the importance of national sovereignty, the EU has focused on creating laws for a select few economic migrant categories.
Highly skilled workers are one such category.</description></item><item><title>What are the reasons behind the ineffectiveness of the Blue Card Directive for highly-skilled workers, and what solutions can be implemented to improve its functionality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 2009, the EU introduced the ‘Blue Card’ Directive to attract highly qualified individuals from non-EU countries. As part of a broader strategy for legal immigration, this Directive is crucial. However, a recent Commission assessment suggests that the Directive has not effectively reached its goals. This raises the question of necessary revisions for improvement.
Implementing the Directive
While all EU Member States obligated to implement the Directive have done so, the actual impact has been underwhelming.</description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths.</description></item></channel></rss>