<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-network/</link><description>Recent content in IP Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency.</description></item><item><title>Future Proofing Your WAN With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Wide area networks (WANs) are changing. While once reliant on telephone technology, core networks are shifting towards packet-switched services to handle the increasing dominance of data and video traffic over voice. This shift raises questions for businesses about adapting their connections to stay current.
Many organizations face growing bandwidth demands. As their service contracts near renewal, they are reevaluating options, considering newer Ethernet services as alternatives to traditional T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Networks Interconnect in Arizona</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</guid><description>Ethernet is quickly gaining popularity as the preferred protocol for metropolitan and wide area networks. It&amp;rsquo;s predicted that IP networks using standard Ethernet services will eventually replace the outdated Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). The main obstacle to this is the fragmented nature of Ethernet service providers, comprising a mix of established and newer carriers with limited service areas. However, E-NNI technology is emerging as the solution to connect these disparate networks.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item></channel></rss>