<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rating on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rating/</link><description>Recent content in Rating on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Intelligence Information System for sharing insights on businesses in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced the Business Intelligence Information System (BIIS), a new digital platform designed to revolutionize how business information is accessed and utilized.
This initiative aligns with the UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum&amp;rsquo;s vision of transforming Dubai into a smart city. BIIS provides a centralized hub for users to obtain crucial information about local and international businesses, empowering companies to identify potential partners and make well-informed decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>