<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sullivan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sullivan/</link><description>Recent content in Sullivan on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sullivan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bioactive ingredients will drive growth in the personal care industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bioactive-ingredients-will-drive-growth-in-the-personal-care-industry/</guid><description>A global shift from synthetic to natural active ingredients in personal care products is driving significant investments in the market, according to research firm Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. This trend is fueled by a growing consumer belief that natural ingredients are safer for human health and the environment.
Source: Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan. Generic personal care dispensers.
Currently, natural active ingredients represent 25% to 30% of the total market share. However, this is predicted to double by 2023, leading to increased innovation in addressing the challenges of incorporating these often delicate ingredients.</description></item><item><title>Frost introduces the Thailand Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 12:15:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-introduces-the-thailand-excellence-awards/</guid><description>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, a global business growth consulting firm, granted 28 Thailand Excellence Awards to companies that exhibited remarkable accomplishments and exceptional performance across various sectors.
Koh Eng Lok, Country Head of Thailand at Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, highlighted the recipients&amp;rsquo; dedication to their clients. He explained that the award categories are carefully chosen each year to represent the prevailing market trends and encompass both established and emerging segments. The sectors range from ICT, automotive, energy &amp;amp; power, healthcare, building technologies to chemicals and palm oil.</description></item></channel></rss>