<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Integration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integration/</link><description>Recent content in Integration on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/integration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Integration requirements for family reunification: the CJEU restricts the autonomy of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In recent times, many EU member states have started requiring non-EU citizens to pass an integration test before they can be reunited with their families in the EU. The EU&amp;rsquo;s family reunification rules allow for this, stating that family members joining non-EU citizens &amp;ldquo;may be required to comply with integration measures.&amp;rdquo; However, for family members of refugees and highly skilled migrants with EU Blue Cards, these tests can only be applied after they arrive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrations for Dynamics GP in real time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrations-for-dynamics-gp-in-real-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 22:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrations-for-dynamics-gp-in-real-time/</guid><description>Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been getting a lot of questions about how to build real-time integrations between Dynamics GP and other systems. It seems like everyone wants their data synced as quickly as possible!
While I&amp;rsquo;ve successfully designed several of these integrations, I&amp;rsquo;ve also noticed some common misunderstandings about what &amp;ldquo;real-time&amp;rdquo; actually means. My goal here is to share some insights based on my experience. This isn&amp;rsquo;t about being &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; or dictating a specific approach, but rather offering a practical perspective...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrations-for-dynamics-gp-in-real-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrations-for-dynamics-gp-in-real-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Address Parsing: Bringing Unstructured Addresses into Dynamics GP - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/address-parsing-bringing-unstructured-addresses-into-dynamics-gp-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/address-parsing-bringing-unstructured-addresses-into-dynamics-gp-part-1/</guid><description>A few years back, I tackled a Dynamics GP implementation involving the migration of over 30,000 customer records from a legacy AS400 system. The client provided the customer data in text files, but the real challenge lay in the data structure.
The AS400 stored data in free-form text fields like ADDRESS1, ADDRESS2, without dedicated fields for city, state, or zip code. This lack of structure resulted in data inconsistencies, errors, and random notes, making a clean import challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/address-parsing-bringing-unstructured-addresses-into-dynamics-gp-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/address-parsing-bringing-unstructured-addresses-into-dynamics-gp-part-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resources for Dynamics GP and SharePoint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/</guid><description>Clients are frequently asking about SharePoint, often in conversations about Business Portal and how to share Dynamics GP data with a wider, non-Dynamics GP user group. To help with these discussions, I&amp;rsquo;m sharing some resources I often use. Please feel free to share yours, and I&amp;rsquo;ll update the blog accordingly.
To clarify the differences between Windows SharePoint Services (WSS) and Microsoft Office SharePoint Server (MOSS), and other editions, refer to the SharePoint Edition Comparison: http://office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resources-for-dynamics-gp-and-sharepoint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beo4 Enabled Commander Remote Control: Seamless Integration of Beogram 4002 or 4004 with More Recent B&amp;O Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</guid><description>Dirk, a Beolover from Berlin, recently reached out about controlling his Beogram 4004 turntable with a Beo4 remote. He wanted to seamlessly integrate the turntable with his existing Beosound 9000 system.
I found his idea intriguing and decided to modify the Beolover Commander remote to make it compatible. This involved adding a 455kHz IR receiver for Beo4 communication and deciphering the Beo4&amp;rsquo;s code system to rewrite the Commander&amp;rsquo;s firmware accordingly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>