<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adobe on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/adobe/</link><description>Recent content in Adobe on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/adobe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adobe and Microsoft software will now collaborate more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-and-microsoft-software-will-now-collaborate-more-effectively/</guid><description>Adobe has enhanced Adobe Document Cloud as part of their partnership with Microsoft. Both companies want to provide excellent digital document experiences to their many shared customers.
Adobe Sign is now more integrated with Microsoft Dynamics 365. This provides real-time access to customer information from LinkedIn Sales Navigator and allows for more automated sales processes. New PDF integrations will enable all Office 365 users who subscribe to Adobe Acrobat DC for teams or enterprises to create, edit, and view secure, high-quality PDFs.</description></item><item><title>Adobe provides a list of suggestions for creating email campaigns that are optimized for mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Adobe&amp;rsquo;s recent email survey suggests that email is not going away anytime soon, at least not in the United States. The survey, which focused on American white-collar workers, revealed that individuals frequently check both their personal and work email. Interestingly, smartphones have surpassed computers as the preferred device for email access. This trend is likely even more pronounced in Asia, a region with high mobile device adoption rates. A study by Experian highlighted that email remains a leading marketing channel in Singapore, especially for driving online traffic to physical stores.</description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales.</description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is a region where digital marketing is effective</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</guid><description>Source: Adobe website.
Recent research from Adobe highlights the growing importance of mobile devices for marketers in Southeast Asia, emphasizing its effectiveness in customer interaction and engagement. This shift toward mobile-first business strategies is particularly prominent in the Asia Pacific region.
Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Digital Index &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Benchmark&amp;rdquo; for 2015 analyzed website performance across eight regions, including Southeast Asia. By comparing the top 20% of websites (&amp;ldquo;best of the best&amp;rdquo;) with the overall average across six key performance indicators, the research provides valuable insights into the strategies of high-performing digital marketing organizations.</description></item><item><title>Adobe Sign simplifies the process of creating digital signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-sign-simplifies-the-process-of-creating-digital-signatures/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new cloud-based digital signature solutions, Adobe Document Cloud and Adobe Sign, built on an open standard developed with the Cloud Signature Consortium. This new technology, announced following the Consortium&amp;rsquo;s formation last June, allows digital signatures on any browser or mobile device.
Adobe Sign works with over 200 providers from the European Union Trust List (EUTL) and Adobe Approved Trust List (AATL), offering users a wide selection of trusted digital IDs.</description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%).</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>The Adobe Symposium 2016 will be sharing important digital marketing trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. Logo for Adobe Symposium 2016.
Over 1,000 professionals in digital marketing, publishing, advertising, content management, and marketing executives will come together at the Adobe Symposium in Singapore on July 28, 2016. This event will provide insights into how innovative global brands have successfully utilized digital trends to deeply understand their customers, create personalized campaigns, and effectively manage content and assets.
With over 50 sessions across four tracks, attendees will witness the latest innovations from Adobe Marketing Cloud.</description></item><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate.</description></item><item><title>Holiday spending in Singapore is expected to exceed S$4 billion by the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. A minimum of 10% of all online sales in Australia, mainland China, Singapore, Japan, New Zealand, Hong Kong, and Thailand occur during the year-end holiday season.
This holiday season, Singaporean shoppers are predicted to heavily utilize their mobile devices for online shopping, according to the latest Adobe Digital Index Holiday Shopping Prediction.
Tablets and smartphones are anticipated to be crucial to shoppers in Singapore, with purchases made on these devices projected to represent 17% of all online sales from now until Christmas.</description></item><item><title>In the corporate hierarchy, creative roles are gaining prominence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 20:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-corporate-hierarchy-creative-roles-are-gaining-prominence/</guid><description>The increasing prominence of design-led thinking in business and strategic problem-solving is benefiting creatives&amp;rsquo; careers globally.
A 2016 Adobe survey of over 1,700 creatives, including graphic and web designers and artists, revealed that these professionals feel they are making a bigger impact within their organizations. Over half of respondents in the Asia Pacific region (56%) reported a greater impact compared to two years prior, with 89% stating that their companies now place more emphasis on creativity and design thinking.</description></item><item><title>The strenuous effort put into improving customer satisfaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</guid><description>A recent survey by Adobe and Econsultancy, involving 14,000 marketers including participants from the Asia Pacific region, reveals that marketers see customer experience as the key differentiator for businesses in 2017.
While investing in technology is important, businesses also recognize the need for a customer-focused, adaptable, and collaborative company culture. The survey indicates that 22% of client-side respondents consider “optimizing the customer experience” as the most exciting opportunity for the coming year.</description></item><item><title>Adobe improves the functionality of the PDF format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-improves-the-functionality-of-the-pdf-format/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-improves-the-functionality-of-the-pdf-format/</guid><description>Adobe has introduced new features for Adobe Document Cloud, providing user-friendly mobile experiences. Document Cloud enables users to work seamlessly across integrated cloud services, mobile, and desktop applications. Leading this update are enhancements to Adobe Sign for increased usability and accessibility, and Adobe Scan, a new complimentary app that transforms mobile devices into smart scanning and text recognition tools.
&amp;ldquo;Documents are fundamental to society, conveying information from contracts and textbooks to financial statements and everything in between,&amp;rdquo; stated Abhay Parasnis, CTO of Adobe.</description></item><item><title>The top four visual trends for 2020 according to Adobe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</guid><description>Adobe has predicted the biggest visual trends for 2020, sharing four key themes brands should embrace in a recent blog post.
_Inclusivity for All Ages _
Marketing is moving away from solely youth-focused campaigns. Recognizing the influence and engagement of older demographics, brands are showcasing diverse, energetic individuals from various age groups.
_Authenticity in Expression _
Consumers are increasingly drawn to genuine representations of themselves and their experiences. This desire for authenticity extends to brands, public figures, and politicians, who are expected to reflect real life in their messaging.</description></item></channel></rss>