<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guangzhou on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guangzhou/</link><description>Recent content in Guangzhou on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/guangzhou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guangzhou businesses enter into Letters of Intent with Singapore organizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</guid><description>Source: Guangzhou Municipal Government. Cai.
The city of Guangzhou held a promotional event in Singapore to explore collaboration and innovation between the two business hubs. Two agreements were reached: one between the Sino-Singapore International Joint Research Institute and Chinese Academy of Sciences Holdings Company, and another between Guangzhou Gas Group, Guangzhou Port Group, and the industrial group Royal Golden Eagle.
Guangzhou&amp;rsquo;s Vice Mayor, Cai Chaolin, who also leads the Nansha District&amp;rsquo;s Communist Party and Development Zone, highlighted the shared attributes between Guangzhou and Singapore, such as their size, cultural similarities, and languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guangzhou-businesses-enter-into-letters-of-intent-with-singapore-organizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses looking to invest in China can gain a competitive advantage at the recently established Singapore Centre in Guangzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</guid><description>Source: Ascendas.
Companies from Singapore expanding their business into China now have access to a centralized service platform with the recent launch of the Singapore Centre at the Sino-Singapore Guangzhou Knowledge City (SSGKC). Known as Singapore Centre @SSGKC (Singapore Centre), this resource hub is situated within Ascendas OneHub GKC, an all-inclusive business park located within the SSGKC.
The Singapore Centre consolidates key agencies and resources from both China and Singapore to offer comprehensive assistance for Singaporean companies investing in China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-looking-to-invest-in-china-can-gain-a-competitive-advantage-at-the-recently-established-singapore-centre-in-guangzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Shunde Marriott Hotel has officially opened its doors in Foshan, China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 19:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its presence in China with the opening of the 258-room Shunde Marriott Hotel. Located in Shunde, a district of Foshan in Guangdong Province, the hotel is owned by Shunde Midea Group and managed by Marriott under a long-term agreement. This latest addition brings the Marriott Hotels brand&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in Greater China to 19 properties.
Source: Marriott. The Shunde Marriott offers guests views of either Shunfeng Mountain Park or the city skyline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shunde-marriott-hotel-has-officially-opened-its-doors-in-foshan-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>