<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Islamic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/islamic/</link><description>Recent content in Islamic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/islamic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Consumer Card achieves outstanding success, according to DIB's report</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</guid><description>Source: DIB website. Banner for the Consumer Card page.
The Consumer Card, a collaboration between the Department of Economic Development (DED) in Dubai and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the largest Islamic bank in the UAE, has surpassed expectations in a very competitive market by the close of 2016. This success highlights how much customers value the card&amp;rsquo;s transparency and customer-centric approach.
Customers appreciate the card&amp;rsquo;s straightforward rewards system, which focuses on everyday transactions rather than requiring increased spending...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-card-achieves-outstanding-success-according-to-dib-s-report/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DIB Mobile app has been enhanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 02:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</guid><description>Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has launched an upgraded version of its mobile banking app for iOS and Android devices. This enhanced app offers access to over 60 services, including features designed to help users manage their personal finances effectively.
With smartphone usage on the rise and Nielsen reporting that 78% of the UAE population owns at least one such device, DIB&amp;rsquo;s mobile app caters to this growing trend...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dib-mobile-app-has-been-enhanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank has enhanced its mobile application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</guid><description>Source: Alizz Islamic Bank. The app.
Alizz Islamic Bank has introduced a redesigned mobile banking app and online platform to solidify its position as a customer experience frontrunner in Oman.
The dual-language app, compatible with both Android and iOS devices, boasts high-level security features and a self-registration option. Users can conveniently manage web banking logins, money transfers, bill payments, and other transactions using QR codes. The app is compatible with 3D Touch technology and is the first of its kind in Oman to provide in-app alerts for new transactions and payment reminders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>