<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>222JHBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/222jhbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 222JHBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/222jhbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all switch terminals on a Beogram 4000 restoration project, the next step involved addressing the electronics. The restoration typically begins by replacing outdated reservoir and motor capacitors, as they are frequently out of specification and nearing failure. The image provided showcases these original components.
To ensure proper fitment of the (smaller) modern replacement capacitors, a custom 3D-printed fixture was designed and utilized. This fixture secures the capacitors in the correct position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Assembly - Gold Plated Switch Terminals and Light Bulbs Replaced with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the repair of the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking systems, the next step was to focus on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control center: the keypad assembly. This unit houses an early digital control system that manages inputs from the keypad&amp;rsquo;s keys. The mechanical switches connected to these keys are a common source of problems and should be gold-plated to ensure reliable, long-term operation after restoration.
The keypad cluster was removed from the Beogram and opened, revealing a missing light bulb in the position indicator scale.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New DIN 5 Plug and Installation of a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:48:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a severely corroded and improperly installed DIN 5 plug, clearly not the original. The attached photos illustrate its poor condition.
One of the pictures highlights a loose black wire, potentially a makeshift attempt to address humming issues (unsurprising given the plug&amp;rsquo;s installation). Adding to the problem, a poorly executed soldering job had left one of the signal leads disconnected.
I removed the old plug and prepared the wires for a new one, as shown in the photo.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Adjustment of AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>After restoring the electronics of a Beogram 4000 turntable, attention turned to the AC platter motor. This model features an older pulley design without built-in belt guards, relying instead on separate guards added to the motor mounting posts. These added guards are not essential, as the pulley&amp;rsquo;s shape effectively secures the belt. Motor tilt allows for adjustments to the belt&amp;rsquo;s vertical positioning.
Like the DC motors in later Beogram models, the AC motors can also suffer from dried-out bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>The initial phase of the Beogram 4000 restoration involved the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking mechanisms. The solenoid and damper, essential for the arm&amp;rsquo;s smooth and controlled descent onto the record, were revealed.
Each part was carefully removed, cleaned, and lubricated.
Attention then turned to the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm. Located on the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s side, it required the arm&amp;rsquo;s removal to access and lubricate the linkage&amp;rsquo;s pivot point.</description></item></channel></rss>