<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aircraft on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aircraft/</link><description>Recent content in Aircraft on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:11:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aircraft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ghost Routers In The Sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-routers-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Wireless internet access on airplanes is becoming a reality. Although it had a slow start, major airlines like American, Delta, Northwest, and Virgin are now embracing in-flight Wi-Fi.
This shift is inevitable in a society increasingly reliant on technology. We might be giving up old habits, but staying connected online is non-negotiable. Just like hotels and restaurants adapted to this need, airlines are following suit. Passengers are willing to endure cramped conditions and forgo traditional amenities, but internet access is a must-have.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas.</description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes.</description></item></channel></rss>