<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Longevity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/longevity/</link><description>Recent content in Longevity on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:34:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/longevity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vitamin D does not increase longevity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</guid><description>While some believe vitamin D is a miracle cure, new research from the University of Cambridge, which analyzed data from almost 100 studies, indicates that vitamin D supplementation alone doesn&amp;rsquo;t decrease mortality rates in older adults.
Past research connected low vitamin D levels with illnesses like multiple sclerosis, cancer, and cardiovascular disease. To clarify if vitamin D supplementation by itself (without calcium or other interventions) impacts death from various causes, researchers examined 73 observational cohort studies and 22 randomized trials on naturally occurring vitamin D and supplements (D2 or D3).</description></item><item><title>The difficulty of innovating quickly enough to ensure a comfortable life until the age of 100</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</guid><description>An on-site poll at The Longevity Summit – Is Asia ready for 100? in Singapore revealed that the majority (60%) of the 200 Asian business leaders, government officials, and healthcare professionals present didn&amp;rsquo;t believe the current pace of innovation could address the challenges of increasing longevity. Attendees convened to explore how to better integrate Asia&amp;rsquo;s senior population into the workforce and promote healthier, longer lives.
A Call for Total Change Kanwaljit Soin, Founding President of Women’s Initiative for Ageing Successfully, emphasized the need to overhaul the current linear life model.</description></item></channel></rss>