<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Feedback on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/feedback/</link><description>Recent content in Feedback on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/feedback/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering Mechanism, Replacement of Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a LED Assembly, and a New Aluminum Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 arrived damaged from shipping, so I began by fixing it. The carriage, which moves along a rod with bearings, had detached.
I took out the rod and bearings to put them back into the carriage correctly. Then, I used a wrench to secure them. This allowed me to reinstall the carriage.
Next, I started my usual restoration process, beginning with the arm lowering mechanism. I took apart the solenoid, damper, connecting parts, and springs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-replacement-of-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-led-assembly-and-a-new-aluminum-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523) began, as always, with the arm lowering mechanism. The lubricants in these mechanisms often harden with age, preventing the tonearm from lowering correctly. The mechanism is shown here in its original condition:
Each moving part was removed
for cleaning and re-lubrication before reassembly. Next, I lubricated the damper-to-arm linkage pivot point. This required removing the sensor arm, as pictured below from the back:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Upgrade of the Tracking System with a LED Based Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</guid><description>With the DC motor operating correctly, the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) continued with the arm lowering mechanism and tracking feedback system.
The arm lowering mechanism, consisting of a solenoid and damper, was disassembled, cleaned, and lubricated. This process involved removing the damper, linkages, retaining washer, and spring. Detailed videos illustrating the rebuilding process are available. After reassembly, the arms were meticulously aligned parallel to each other and the keypad edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-upgrade-of-the-tracking-system-with-a-led-based-light-source/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration and Yet Another Exciting Aspect of Achieving RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 22:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</guid><description>To restore the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor, several upgrades are necessary. These include installing modern multi-turn RPM trimmers, a new RPM relay, replacing the RPM trimmer backlights with LEDs, and refreshing the motor bearings with oil. Testing the RPM stability after each step reveals their individual impact on performance.
This particular Beogram 4002 had already undergone most of these improvements, with the exception of the motor restoration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 06:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</guid><description>My work began with the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, as is customary for me. My client had already addressed the cleaning and lubrication of the damper and solenoid linkages, so my task was to detach the linkage connecting the damper and tonearm. This required removing the sensor arm assembly, as shown here:
Extracting the sensor arm involved removing two screws at its base:
The linkage could then be detached:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and the Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 08:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I was working on had a completely frozen arm lowering mechanism. The old lubricant had become so hardened that I had to use a screwdriver to pry the linkages off their pivot pins. This is a common issue, easily resolved by cleaning and re-lubricating the mechanism. Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the solenoid, damper, and linkages before disassembly:
This image shows the disassembled parts laid out on my workbench:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-the-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5513) began with the arm lowering and tracking systems, as these are essential for any further testing or repair work.
To start, I took out the damper and linkages to clean and lubricate them. Thankfully, all the components were in good condition, so lubrication and reassembly were straightforward. Next, I lubricated the pivot point connecting the damper to the arm linkage. This required removing the sensor arm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A Stuck Tonearm and Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously repaired, returned with a tonearm tracking issue. The problem was a misaligned tracking sensor aperture obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. To fix this, I slightly repositioned the aperture after loosening its screw. I replaced the original screw with a more secure flat socket head screw to prevent future misalignment. I then recalibrated the tracking sensor feedback.
While the Beogram was with me, the customer decided to have the dust cover polished...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-stuck-tonearm-and-polishing-the-hood/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED and Improvement of the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 14:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>Replacing the sensor arm LED is typically the final step in converting a Beogram 4002 to use all LEDs. After restoring the DC motor, the next task was to install a recently designed flex-PCB-based LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb. The image below shows the sensor arm with the detector assembly removed:
Upon zooming in on the full-resolution image, a small black spot is visible on the glass bulb. This spot indicates significant tungsten evaporation from the filament, suggesting the bulb is nearing the end of its life and could soon fail, rendering the Beogram inoperable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-and-improvement-of-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering Mechanism and Linear Tracking System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 07:02:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</guid><description>My restoration project of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable started with the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. These mechanisms often require attention because of hardened lubricants and misadjusted tracking sensors.
After taking the mechanism apart for cleaning and lubrication, I addressed the linkage connecting the damper to the tonearm, which commonly experiences stiffness due to hardened lubricants.
The sensor arm was then removed for disassembly to further work on the linkage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-mechanism-and-linear-tracking-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with an SMD LED Light Source and Adjustment of the Feedback Sensisitivy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 turntable had a damaged part (the tracking sensor aperture) that was bent and obstructing the arm&amp;rsquo;s movement. This issue prevented the tracking system from working correctly. The initial setup used an incandescent light bulb:
Upon removing the bulb housing, it was evident that the aperture was bent and rubbing against the optical sensor housing:
The aperture was carefully straightened, and the bulb assembly was replaced with a new SMD LED light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-an-smd-led-light-source-and-adjustment-of-the-feedback-sensisitivy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 04:19:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>The initial phase of the Beogram 4000 restoration involved the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking mechanisms. The solenoid and damper, essential for the arm&amp;rsquo;s smooth and controlled descent onto the record, were revealed.
Each part was carefully removed, cleaned, and lubricated.
Attention then turned to the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm. Located on the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s side, it required the arm&amp;rsquo;s removal to access and lubricate the linkage&amp;rsquo;s pivot point...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>