<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IPO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipo/</link><description>Recent content in IPO on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ipo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IPO activity in Singapore is expected to exceed that of 2016 in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 09:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ipo-activity-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-that-of-2016-in-2017/</guid><description>During the first half of 2017, Singapore saw a surge in initial public offerings (IPOs), attracting US$329 million in investments, as reported by PwC Singapore. This momentum is projected to continue, potentially exceeding the total funds raised in 2016. Professional services are emerging as a leading sector, with HRnetGroup and Shopper360&amp;rsquo;s IPOs securing a combined US$134 million, a significant leap from the previous year.
While Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) and business trusts, a traditional strength for the Singapore Exchange (SGX), constituted 33% of IPO proceeds, the anticipated listing of NetLink Trust, estimated at US$1.</description></item><item><title>Frost &amp; Sullivan anticipates a need for independent analyses to support IPOs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 09:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/</guid><description>A research and consulting firm, Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, predicts significant growth for the Australian Stock Exchange (ASX) in 2017, with nearly 45 companies already lined up for initial public offerings (IPOs). This positive outlook comes after the ASX saw a stable number of IPOs in 2016, similar to the previous year. Notably, technology and fintech companies made up about 25% of these listings.
Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan played a key role in several 2016 ASX IPOs by providing independent market reports (IMRs).</description></item></channel></rss>