<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lab on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lab/</link><description>Recent content in Lab on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brief Lab introduces new online certification program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</guid><description>The Brief Lab, an organization that trains professionals to be concise communicators, is marking its one-year anniversary with a redesigned website and the introduction of its first online certification program, Brief Practitioner.
Source: The Brief Lab website.
The Brief Practitioner program is geared towards professionals who want to embrace conciseness and become certified in a structured approach to lean communication. The online course is designed for those who aim to champion these methodologies within their organizations.</description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods.</description></item></channel></rss>