<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Debt on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/debt/</link><description>Recent content in Debt on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:53:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/debt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DebtorsWatch compiles data on delinquent payments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</guid><description>DebtorsWatch is the first online platform in India designed for reporting trade defaults. The interactive website allows businesses to report overdue payments and defaults, conduct credit checks, and monitor customer creditworthiness. Registered members can also utilize the data for due diligence.
Deepanjan Periwal, Chartered Accountant and founder of DebtorsWatch, highlights the lack of transparency in India&amp;rsquo;s credit system compared to countries like the US, UK, and Australia, where credit tracking is standard practice.</description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures.</description></item></channel></rss>