<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Desire on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/desire/</link><description>Recent content in Desire on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/desire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>HTC has unveiled the Desire 620 and 620G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC Desire 620 dual sim, the successor to the HTC Desire 610.
Source: HTC. The 620G in Milkyway gray.
Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia, stated that the new HTC Desire model provides a balance of modern design, strong processing, and fast connectivity, making it a suitable option for budget-conscious entertainment enthusiasts.
The Desire 620 dual sim is equipped with a Snapdragon 410 Qualcomm processor, Android 4.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience.</description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices.</description></item></channel></rss>