<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Accor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accor/</link><description>Recent content in Accor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/accor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Accor Plus is the latest paid loyalty program offered by Accor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 10:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plus-is-the-latest-paid-loyalty-program-offered-by-accor/</guid><description>Source: Accor.
Accor Advantage Plus, the paid loyalty program from Accor with more than 350,000 members in 17 countries, has been renamed and enhanced. Now known as Accor Plus, this 21-year-old program allows members to enjoy enhanced experiences at over 600 Accor properties in the Asia Pacific region. The company stated that members can benefit from substantial discounts on accommodations, dining at over 800 restaurants, and access to various VIP events and partner offers.</description></item><item><title>Accor plans to introduce the ibis Styles brand to Singapore later this year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-plans-to-introduce-the-ibis-styles-brand-to-singapore-later-this-year/</guid><description>Source: Accor. The ibis Style in the Macpherson area, Singapore, will be launched this year.
Accor plans to open an ibis Styles hotel in Singapore by the last quarter of 2015, introducing a trendy, lifestyle-focused brand to the country. Situated within the same complex as the MacPherson shopping mall, the hotel is conveniently located at the intersection of MacPherson and Aljunied Roads, a short 20-minute drive from the airport.</description></item><item><title>Accor reveals the opening of its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 05:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-reveals-the-opening-of-its-600th-hotel-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has achieved a significant milestone with its 600th hotel in the Asia Pacific region, the iconic Park Lane hotel in Hong Kong, joining the group&amp;rsquo;s upscale Pullman brand. This rebranding is particularly noteworthy as it marks the 50th Pullman hotel in the region, highlighting the brand&amp;rsquo;s impressive growth since its introduction in late 2007. Coinciding with The Park Lane&amp;rsquo;s 40th anniversary, this transformation signifies a new chapter for the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar.</description></item><item><title>Accor hotels will be providing newspapers and magazines digitally starting in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 18:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-hotels-will-be-providing-newspapers-and-magazines-digitally-starting-in-2015/</guid><description>Accor, partnering with PressReader, is launching a complimentary information service across its hotel group by early 2015. This initiative aligns with Accor&amp;rsquo;s Leading Digital Hospitality strategy, focused on incorporating and enhancing digital aspects throughout the guest experience.
Through &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader,&amp;rdquo; hotel guests can access over 3,000 international and local publications on their smartphones, laptops, or tablets, using various operating systems (iOS, Android, Blackberry, Windows).
Guests can access &amp;ldquo;Accor Press by PressReader&amp;rdquo; through the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Wi-Fi, allowing them to download articles, newspapers, and magazines for offline reading.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-pullman-bangkok-grande-sukhumvit/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
The Pullman brand is expanding its presence in the Asia Pacific region with the addition of the Pullman Bangkok Grande Sukhumvit. This new hotel, formerly known as the Grand Millennium Sukhumvit Bangkok, will be the third Pullman in Bangkok, increasing the upscale brand&amp;rsquo;s room count by 325.
Michael Issenberg, Chairman and CEO of AccorHotels Asia Pacific, expressed excitement about the new addition, highlighting its stylish accommodations designed for modern travelers.</description></item><item><title>Accor has launched the Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp; Residences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</guid><description>Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences, the largest five-star hotel in Kolkata, is now open in the city’s New Town precinct.
Source: Accor Hotels. The Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences. The hotel has 347 guest rooms and suites. It is located near the airport and offers the city&amp;rsquo;s first serviced apartments. Guests can enjoy amenities such as a flat-screen LED TV, coffee and tea maker, in-room safe, refreshment center, and complimentary internet access.</description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices.</description></item><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney.</description></item><item><title>Sofitel Kunming provides convenient access to the city center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-kunming-provides-convenient-access-to-the-city-center/</guid><description>Sofitel, the luxury hotel brand under AccorHotels, has launched its newest property, Sofitel Kunming. Located in the city center, it&amp;rsquo;s the only international luxury hotel in Kunming.
Situated in Kunming&amp;rsquo;s central business district, the 400-room hotel spans the 27th to 52nd floors. It showcases a blend of French elegance and art de vivre with touches of Yunnan&amp;rsquo;s vibrant ethnic cultures and customs.
&amp;ldquo;The debut of Sofitel Kunming signifies a period of rapid growth for AccorHotels in China, as we continue to solidify our dedication to delivering world-renowned, refined French hospitality to discerning Chinese travelers,&amp;rdquo; shared Paul Richardson, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China.</description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts.</description></item><item><title>Travel insomnia tips from Accor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-insomnia-tips-from-accor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 06:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travel-insomnia-tips-from-accor/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. Raffles Dubai – calming amenities help to welcome a restful night’s sleep.
In honor of World Sleep Day on March 15th, Accor Hotels has put together advice for getting a good night&amp;rsquo;s sleep while traveling.
Warm mood lighting
For travelers, lighting plays a crucial role in achieving quality sleep. Swissôtel&amp;rsquo;s Vitality Rooms are equipped with circadian lighting technology. This technology adapts to individual preferences and habits, ultimately enhancing well-being and overall health.</description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media.</description></item></channel></rss>