<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Amplifier on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/amplifier/</link><description>Recent content in Amplifier on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 13:50:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/amplifier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Audiophile Triad HS-3 Audio Transformer Auction for Elephants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 13:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As many know, I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about protecting both captive and wild elephants globally. What people may not realize is that our generation might be the last to coexist with these magnificent creatures. In recent times, wild elephant populations have been decimated, their numbers plummeting from millions to mere thousands. This decline threatens their genetic diversity, jeopardizing the species&amp;rsquo; survival.
Each elephant is precious. One organization close to my heart is the Friends of the Asian Elephant hospital (FAE) in Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: First Prototype Installed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</guid><description>I was tasked with creating an internal RIAA preamplifier for a restored Beogram 4002 (5521). This addition makes sense since many modern receivers lack a dedicated phono input. Additionally, the pre-opamp RIAA preamps found in many vintage B&amp;amp;O receivers introduce more noise compared to modern low-noise audio op-amps.
Researching contemporary RIAA preamp designs led me to the LM833 operational amplifier, a specialized low-noise op-amp for audio applications. I adapted a high-precision RIAA preamp circuit from a Texas Instruments application note AN-346, as established RIAA preamplifier designs exist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-first-prototype-installed/</a></p></description></item><item><title> Beomaster 2000 Type 2801: Back to the Beomaster 2000 to repair the dial cord</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-2000-type-2801-back-to-the-beomaster-2000-to-repair-the-dial-cord/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-2000-type-2801-back-to-the-beomaster-2000-to-repair-the-dial-cord/</guid><description>The previous Beolover Blog post concluded with a functioning Beomaster 2000 (Type 2801) amplifier and verified key voltages. However, the display lamps needed replacement due to burnouts, and the tuning dial cord was significantly frayed. These parts had to be ordered.
With the arrival of the new parts, the restoration process resumed, starting with the dial cord replacement, considered the most challenging task based on the service manual&amp;rsquo;s instructions.
A high-quality black radio dial cord, measuring 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-2000-type-2801-back-to-the-beomaster-2000-to-repair-the-dial-cord/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-2000-type-2801-back-to-the-beomaster-2000-to-repair-the-dial-cord/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 RIAA Preamplifier: A New Power Supply Design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 03:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous one about the RIAA preamplifier I&amp;rsquo;m building for a Beogram 4002 turntable. This preamp will allow the Beogram to connect directly to a modern amplifier&amp;rsquo;s AUX or TAPE input. While initially pleased with my prototype, I redesigned it for a cleaner layout and had it manufactured.
The new boards arrived, and I assembled a preamplifier, thrilled with its appearance. After installing and testing it, however, I realized I hadn&amp;rsquo;t tested it thoroughly enough beforehand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-riaa-preamplifier-a-new-power-supply-design/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>