<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gen X on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gen-x/</link><description>Recent content in Gen X on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gen-x/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's Influential Brands are identified by Gen X</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Leading Brands Chosen by Generation X
A consumer-driven award program spearheaded by Brand Alliance has identified the top Influential Brands in Singapore, as determined by the upwardly mobile Generation X (Gen X) demographic.
Source: Brand Alliance. Brand Alliance presented the 2013 Influential Brands awards in November 2013. The 2014 Influential Brands conference is scheduled for November 10, 2014.
The survey highlighted over 100 prominent brands resonating with consumers in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>