<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CJEU Case Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cjeu-case-law/</link><description>Recent content in CJEU Case Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cjeu-case-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Overview and analysis of the relaunched negotiations for EU accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-and-analysis-of-the-relaunched-negotiations-for-eu-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The potential inclusion of the EU into the ECHR has been a long-awaited development. With the necessary Treaty modifications in the Lisbon Treaty and a negotiated accession treaty by 2013, it appeared that the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s December 2014 ruling would solidify this union. However, the Court&amp;rsquo;s judgment (Opinion 2/13), which was subject to criticism on this blog, unexpectedly disrupted the accession process.
However, the process was resurrected in 2019 and has advanced quickly since then.</description></item><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period.</description></item><item><title>Clarification on Dual Citizens and EU Citizenship by the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarification-on-dual-citizens-and-eu-citizenship-by-the-ecj/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
A fundamental principle within EU law concerning the freedom of movement posits that it primarily pertains to EU citizens residing in a Member State different from their home country. Consequently, EU citizens residing in their own Member State cannot generally invoke this law. However, ECJ case law sometimes permits them to assert rights based on their EU citizenship.
This begs the question: what happens to citizens of two Member States?</description></item><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in C-582/14 Breyer establishes IP addresses as personal data.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The opinions presented are solely those of the author and should not be interpreted as representing the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s official stance.
Background
The Breyer case saw the German Supreme Court (Bundesgerichtshof) request clarification from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on whether dynamic IP addresses constitute personal data under the EU Data Protection Directive and to what extent their storage and processing is permissible for maintaining website functionality.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's decision on the importance of parenthood in EU law slips away from us.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Most EU laws and court decisions on sex discrimination focus on improving women&amp;rsquo;s job opportunities and ensuring equal treatment in the workplace. A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Maistrellis case tackles these issues from a different perspective: a father&amp;rsquo;s access to parental leave when the mother isn&amp;rsquo;t employed or looking for work. This judgment brings up important questions about how EU employment and discrimination laws affect family life.</description></item><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ has upheld the EU law on relocating asylum-seekers, but some question if it is a Pyrrhic victory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</guid><description>The EU Court Rules on Refugee Relocation: A Pyrrhic Victory? Professor Steve Peers examines the European Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s (ECJ) decision regarding the mandatory relocation of asylum-seekers, highlighting the complex interplay between legal effectiveness and political realities.
In 2015, facing a significant influx of asylum-seekers, the EU implemented a measure requiring member states to relocate 160,000 individuals from overburdened Italy and Greece. This decision faced resistance, particularly a legal challenge from Slovakia and Hungary, questioning its legal basis and practicality.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal.</description></item><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice is deciding whether monks can be prohibited from practicing law, posing the question, "Can a man serve two masters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</guid><description>Rebecca Zahn, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Strathclyde
Lawyers in the European Union hold a distinctive position. They ensure access to justice, manage its administration, and uphold the rule of law within their Member States. Similar to other professions like medicine or architecture, national bodies strictly regulate entry. However, legal practice is inherently location-specific, unlike other professions. A lawyer&amp;rsquo;s knowledge base is tied to the jurisdiction where they were trained and qualified.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the special status of minority religious groups, stating "You are all individuals!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-special-status-of-minority-religious-groups-stating-you-are-all-individuals/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea, Professor of Constitutional and European Law, University College London
The Court of Justice recently issued five significant decisions regarding Directive 2000/78&amp;rsquo;s provisions on religious discrimination, a topic it hadn&amp;rsquo;t addressed in many years. This surge in rulings signifies the Court&amp;rsquo;s renewed focus on this area.
The latest case originated from Austria&amp;rsquo;s Supreme Court and concerned a law granting paid holidays on Good Friday to members of three minor Christian denominations, excluding others.</description></item><item><title>The EU consumer's status after Faber v Hazet: no longer "Faber" fortunae suae</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-consumer-s-status-after-faber-v-hazet-no-longer-faber-fortunae-suae/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 12:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-consumer-s-status-after-faber-v-hazet-no-longer-faber-fortunae-suae/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD candidate, King&amp;rsquo;s College London
Background
A recent Court of Justice ruling in the Faber case (C-497/13) determined that purchasers are considered &amp;ldquo;consumers&amp;rdquo; even if they don&amp;rsquo;t explicitly claim this status, as long as the purchase wasn&amp;rsquo;t for business or professional purposes. The Court decided that national courts must independently determine if a purchaser qualifies as a consumer, guaranteeing the application of EU consumer protection laws regardless of the purchaser&amp;rsquo;s awareness of their rights.</description></item><item><title>ClientEarth: a significant milestone in the Court of Justice of the European Union's environmental law rulings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-a-significant-milestone-in-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-s-environmental-law-rulings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-a-significant-milestone-in-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-s-environmental-law-rulings/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther, Trainee, Research Department of the CJEU
Background
Yesterday, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on a case referred by the UK Supreme Court. This case involved the UK&amp;rsquo;s failure to request an extension to meet nitrogen oxide limits as outlined in EU law. The environmental NGO, ClientEarth, brought the case forward in the UK, arguing that the UK was violating Article 13 of Directive 2008/50/EC (the ‘Air Quality Directive’).</description></item><item><title>Has the European Court of Justice shifted from being an offender to a protector of human rights in the context of the European Arrest Warrant?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 04:52:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-the-european-court-of-justice-shifted-from-being-an-offender-to-a-protector-of-human-rights-in-the-context-of-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Since its rushed creation after the 9/11 attacks, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) has become a cornerstone of EU criminal law. It replaces traditional extradition with a streamlined system lacking most of the usual limitations. This has worried critics concerned about potential miscarriages of justice but pleased supporters who appreciate the faster return of more fugitives to face justice.
Despite concerns from some EU countries&amp;rsquo; constitutional courts, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) has long dismissed human rights criticisms of the EAW.</description></item><item><title>Is it cheerleading or judging? The CJEU supports the EU's unified patent system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 06:33:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-cheerleading-or-judging-the-cjeu-supports-the-eu-s-unified-patent-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Two recent rulings by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirm the EU regulations for a unitary patent system are legal. This analysis examines the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning and evaluates its coherence.
Background
Establishing EU-wide patent regulations has been a long-standing challenge. The Lisbon Treaty introduced Article 118 TFEU, aiming to streamline intellectual property rules. While most rules fall under ordinary legislative procedures (requiring qualified majority voting), language regulations necessitate unanimous agreement.</description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens.</description></item><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions).</description></item><item><title>Finally free? Detention, the European Arrest Warrant, and Julian Assange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-free-detention-the-european-arrest-warrant-and-julian-assange/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Lanigan case, which deals with prolonged pre-trial detention and the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), is especially noteworthy given the UN&amp;rsquo;s recent statement regarding Julian Assange&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;arbitrary detention.&amp;rdquo; Assange, who is also facing an EAW, presents a unique situation. What can we learn from each of these cases about the intersection of detention length and the EAW?</description></item><item><title>Preserving the euro: Gauweiler's challenge to the legality of the OMT program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
On June 16th, the Court of Justice ruled in the Gauweiler case, declaring the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program legal under EU law. This decision has significant implications for the ECB&amp;rsquo;s authority, the EU Economic and Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s constitutional structure, and the relationship between the Court of Justice and the referring court, the German Federal Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states.</description></item><item><title>As the lawyers entered the bar, the Court of Justice made it easier for legal professionals to practice across borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-the-lawyers-entered-the-bar-the-court-of-justice-made-it-easier-for-legal-professionals-to-practice-across-borders/</guid><description>Dr Julian Lonbay, Senior Lecturer,
Postgraduate Research Admissions Tutor, Birmingham Law School, University
of Birmingham
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice judgment in the Joined Cases C-58/13 and C-59/13 Angelo Alberto Torresi and Pierfrancesco Torresi v Consiglio dell&amp;rsquo;Ordine degli Avvocati di Macerata considered whether EU law permits citizens to pursue the fastest route to professional qualification, even if it bypasses significant portions of training mandated by national law for entry into the corresponding national profession.</description></item><item><title>Is the Essent ruling a new milestone in the legal precedent for the free movement of goods?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</guid><description>A Reassessment of Proportionality and Discrimination in Light of the Essent Case Filippo Fontanelli, Lecturer in International Economic Law, University of Edinburgh
Introduction
The September 11, 2014, Essent case (Joined Cases C-204 to C-208/12) judgment by the Court of Justice of the EU presents a nuanced analysis of proportionality, weighing factors such as promoting free energy trade, safeguarding the environment and human health, adhering to international emission reduction agreements, bolstering local employment, and encouraging energy self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Court of Justice reconsidering the European equivalent of the 'fifth amendment'? The CJEU makes a decision on the right to remain silent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</guid><description>Inês Pereira de Sousa, Lecturer and PhD candidate at Porto Faculty of Law, Universidade Católica Portuguesa; Researcher at CEID – Católica Research Centre for the Future of Law; Member of ANESC – Academic Network on the European Social Charter and Social Rights; Member of EUCRIM –European Criminal Law Associations’ Forum - isousa@porto.ucp.pt
On February 2, 2021, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) had the chance to reexamine the right to remain silent and the right against self-incrimination in a case originating from the Italian Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice's initial decision on detaining asylum-seekers within the Dublin system and its implications for the rule of law in immigration detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</guid><description>Tommaso Poli, LL.M. candidate in Human Rights and Humanitarian Law at the University of Essex, School of Law.
The detention of those seeking asylum is a contentious issue within immigration law. While not initially covered by the European Common Asylum System (CEAS), it is now addressed in several of the second-phase CEAS measures. These measures include the Asylum Procedures Directive, the Reception Conditions Directive, the Qualification Directive, the Dublin Regulation, and the EURODAC Regulation.</description></item><item><title>Determining the Impact of the Advocate General on the European Union Court of Justice: Is it Correlation or Causation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 08:10:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/determining-the-impact-of-the-advocate-general-on-the-european-union-court-of-justice-is-it-correlation-or-causation/</guid><description>Carlos Arrebola and Ana Julia Mauricio (PhD students at the University of Cambridge)
It is widely claimed, especially in publications like The Guardian, that Advocate Generals significantly influence the European Court of Justice (ECJ)&amp;rsquo;s decisions. This belief is also prevalent among legal professionals specializing in EU law. However, there is limited empirical evidence to support this assumption. Our research investigates whether this perceived influence is accurate or merely a misconception.</description></item><item><title>Could Data Protection be Returning Home? The CJEU's Ruling on Data Protection Law in Relation to Jehovah's Witnesses and Political Canvassing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re showering when the doorbell unexpectedly interrupts. Hoping it&amp;rsquo;s the anticipated Amazon delivery with a birthday gift for your daughter, you rush downstairs, only to find a pair of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witnesses.
After dismissing their pleas, you close the door, putting the encounter out of your mind. However, they haven&amp;rsquo;t forgotten you. To maintain their focus on potential converts, they keep records of visited homes, categorizing residents as &amp;ldquo;Believer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Unbeliever,&amp;rdquo; or perhaps even &amp;ldquo;Satanist,&amp;rdquo; depending on your towel situation.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for prosecutors from Belgium, France, and Sweden to issue European Arrest Warrants? The CJEU provides clarification on the necessity of independent public prosecutors.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:27:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</guid><description>Laure Baudrihaye-Gérard, Fair Trials The European Court of Justice (CJEU) has again clarified who can issue a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). This decision is significant for this key EU judicial cooperation tool, used countless times daily to extradite individuals between member states for investigations or to serve sentences.
Courts in Luxembourg and the Netherlands recently paused EAWs from prosecutors in Belgium, France, and Sweden to seek clarification from the CJEU.</description></item><item><title>The Council needs to quickly establish a legal framework similar to the CEOS for employees working in CSDP missions: Analysis of the Jenkinson case (Case C-46/22 P)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</guid><description>Antje Kunst*
Photo credit: Jan-Tore Egge, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
In a January 18, 2024, ruling, the European Union Court of Justice dismissed an appeal by Irish citizen Mr. Jenkinson. This decision impacts thousands of individuals working in EU international missions governed by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). While the Court sided with the defendants (the Council, Commission, European External Action Service, and Eulex Kosovo), their victory is questionable.</description></item><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that students from third countries have the right to enter school.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the new academic year begins, students across the EU are met with a mix of anticipation and anxiety. Juggling academics, finances, personal life, and social activities is a universal experience for students, and those from outside the EU face the added pressure of meeting immigration requirements.
These requirements are standardized by the EU&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Students’ Directive. However, the degree of uniformity across member states remains unclear. Do individual countries retain the right to impose additional entry prerequisites?</description></item><item><title>Council v H: Another Court victory in the Common Foreign and Security Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</guid><description>Graham Butler, PhD Fellow at the Centre for Comparative and European Constitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen, Denmark
Introduction
This summer, the Court of Justice (the Court) issued two significant decisions influencing the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) legal landscape. Despite the Treaty of Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s integration of this largely intergovernmental area (previously the Second Pillar) into the unified ‘EU’, its legacy persists. Enduring evidence of CFSP as a distinct yet incorporated legal domain allows it to be termed ‘CFSP law’.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Mixed messages are being sent by the CJEU regarding LGBTI asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mixed-messages-are-being-sent-by-the-cjeu-regarding-lgbti-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many nations have severe punishments for individuals identifying as LGBTI, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recognizes persecution based on sexual orientation as grounds for asylum in the EU. This protection falls under the &amp;lsquo;particular social group&amp;rsquo; category within the EU&amp;rsquo;s qualification Directive.
The CJEU has previously clarified that individuals seeking asylum on the basis of sexual orientation are not required to conceal their sexual orientation in their home country.</description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems.</description></item><item><title>A missed chance to enhance access to justice in environmental issues: the CJEU's ruling on the applicability of the Aarhus Convention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</guid><description>**
**
Dr. Apolline J. C. Roger, Senior Teaching Fellow in EU environmental law, University of Edinburgh Law School.
The right to access justice is a crucial safeguard for environmental NGOs and citizens, allowing them to contest public authorities&amp;rsquo; decisions that impact the environment and public health. By joining the Aarhus Convention in 2005, the EU acknowledged this right as a pillar of good governance and a key element of the human right to a healthy environment.</description></item><item><title>AGET Iraklis Case: Balancing Economic Freedoms and Labour Rights - Can Governments Regulate Mass Layoffs by Employers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis
DPhil Candidate, University of Oxford; Researcher, Erasmus University of Rotterdam.
The AGET Iraklis case, despite its legal and political importance, has not received adequate attention from scholars or the public. Overshadowed by events like the UK referendum on EU membership and significant court rulings on data retention and trade agreements, the Grand Chamber judgment in this case, delivered on December 21, 2016, highlights the complex interplay between fundamental economic freedoms and collective labor rights.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU missed an opportunity to address mass hacking and fundamental rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Hugo Partouche, a Paris Bar Attorney-at-law (avocat), and Chloé Berthélémy, a Senior Policy Advisor at EDRi, collaborated on this piece.
Photo credit: hacker-silhoutte, via Wikimedia commons
*This article initially appeared in French in Actualité Juridique (AJ) Pénal, Dalloz Revues. You can find it here.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on the ‘EncroChat’ case on April 30, 2024.
This case arose from large-scale European police operations targeting organized crime.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU clarifies CILFIT regarding the final courts' obligations to refer questions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 19:34:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-clarifies-cilfit-regarding-the-final-courts-obligations-to-refer-questions/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
In a previous post, I argued that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) held national supreme courts to a higher standard than the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) regarding preliminary references to the CJEU. I suggested this was due to the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s ruling in the CILFIT case. However, the CJEU has recently proven me wrong.</description></item><item><title>The Dublin system: Balancing Mutual Trust and Human Rights Protection in the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated to the Centre of Interdisciplinary Research in Constitutional Law of Saint-Louis University (USL-B) and the Centre of European Law of the Free University Brussels (ULB). The author wishes to thank the Professors E. Bribosia and S. Van Drooghenbroeck for their valuable advice.
Introduction
On February 16th, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) issued a significant judgment in the case of C.</description></item><item><title>Claimants of benefits who are not part of the European Union and the impact on the European Union's relationship with Switzerland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely to grab sensationalist headlines, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling on social security rules for Swiss citizens raises important questions about extending such rules to non-EU countries and the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Switzerland.
Background
This ruling marks the second instance where the UK has challenged the legal basis of Council Decisions concerning the extension of revised EU social security coordination rules to specific non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>The Utilization of Prisons for Detaining Migrants in Europe and the EU Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 23:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-utilization-of-prisons-for-detaining-migrants-in-europe-and-the-eu-returns-directive/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, a researcher at the Global Detention Project and the Global Migration Centre, and a PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies in Geneva, examines a legal question: can immigration detainees be held in prisons alongside ordinary prisoners?
On July 17, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this question in its decisions regarding the combined cases of Bero and Bouzalmate and the separate case of Pham.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK's limitation on EU workers' eligibility for benefits lawful - and if not, should it be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK government recently established a new income requirement for EU citizens from other Member States to be classified as &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and access certain benefits. This raises the question of whether these rules align with EU law regarding the free movement of workers and if modifications are necessary.
Under these regulations, EU citizens must earn a minimum of £150 weekly for at least three months to be considered &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and qualify for benefits such as child benefit, child tax credit, job-seekers&amp;rsquo; allowance, and housing benefit.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families.</description></item><item><title>Prisoner voting is now a legal issue under EU legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 05:28:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Jo Shaw, Salvesen Chair of European Institutions
Article 39(2) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights states:
‘European Parliament members shall be chosen through direct, universal suffrage in a free and secret ballot.’
The Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice, in a concise and understated judgment in Delvigne (Case C-650/13; ECLI:EU:C:2015:648) delivered on October 6, 2015, provided further definition to this provision. It found that national policies determining voter eligibility in European Parliament elections fall under EU law&amp;rsquo;s purview, as they implement EU law according to Article 51(1) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU issues its first ruling on interim measures regarding the rule of law in Poland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-issues-its-first-ruling-on-interim-measures-regarding-the-rule-of-law-in-poland/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The October 19th decision by the Vice-President of the Court of Justice concerning Poland&amp;rsquo;s Judiciary Reform Act is groundbreaking. This decision, which orders Poland to halt the implementation of the Act and prevents the removal of judges due to the new retirement age, represents uncharted territory. It places the Court of Justice in the unprecedented position of compelling a sovereign member state to decide between adhering to European integration principles or embracing illiberalism.</description></item><item><title>UK Motor Insurance Law in the EU: Road Accidents and Off-Road Responsibilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-motor-insurance-law-in-the-eu-road-accidents-and-off-road-responsibilities/</guid><description>James Marson (Reader in Law, Sheffield Hallam University), Katy Ferris (Assistant Professor in Business Law, Nottingham University Business School) and Neil Fletcher (Senior Lecturer, Sheffield Hallam University)
Introduction
While the UK has seen notable legal victories concerning member state liability for breaches of EU law, the ability to hold the state accountable for individual losses remains limited. Establishing a breach significant enough to warrant damages is often a hurdle, except in motor vehicle insurance law.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union rejects benefit tourism by EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant ruling in the case of Dano, which dealt with the ability of EU citizens to access social welfare benefits when they relocate to another Member State. The Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the laws in this case (and other rulings earlier this year involving EU citizens with criminal histories) suggests a stricter approach, possibly reflecting the ongoing political discussions regarding the free movement of EU citizens.</description></item><item><title>Brexit: You have the option to change your mind. The CJEU ruling in Wightman allows for a U-turn.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 09:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-you-have-the-option-to-change-your-mind-the-cjeu-ruling-in-wightman-allows-for-a-u-turn/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The recent definitive ruling by the Full Court concerning the Wightman case reaffirms the UK&amp;rsquo;s ability to independently revoke its withdrawal notification from the EU under the most flexible terms. This judgment aligns with the non-binding opinion given the previous week by an Advocate-General.
The judgment
The Court dismissed the UK government&amp;rsquo;s claim of the case being hypothetical, emphasizing the imminent involvement of some litigants (who are MPs) in voting on the proposed withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU).</description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law.</description></item><item><title>Child abduction: an additional expansion of the EU's exclusive external authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Parental child abduction is a serious issue, often arising from custody disputes during family law proceedings. While abduction by a stranger presents a clear danger, abduction by a non-custodial parent violates court decisions and can hinder the custodial parent&amp;rsquo;s rights, especially when the child is taken to another country.
The Hague Convention, established in 1980, seeks to address this problem. This international treaty, with 93 signatory countries including all EU members, provides a framework for resolving international parental child abduction cases.</description></item><item><title>Access to documents: The Council may choose not to enforce a significant CJEU ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU is frequently criticized for its lack of transparency, particularly concerning its legislative processes. Ideally, these processes should be as open as those in national legislatures, allowing public access to draft legislation.
However, despite a 2001 regulation on public access to documents, EU transparency in this area remains an issue. Within the Council, some Member States prefer to keep their positions confidential during negotiations. This secrecy undermines the idea that citizens, through their national parliaments, can hold their governments accountable for actions taken within the Council.</description></item><item><title>Beware of the Accountability Gap in the EU's Financial Supervisory Authorities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City Law School
The year 2010 saw the creation of three European Supervisory Authorities: the European Banking Authority, the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority, and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA). These authorities were established by the European Union in response to the then-unprecedented financial crisis. On January 22, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant judgment (Case C-270/12, United Kingdom v Council &amp;amp; Parliament) concerning recent legislation granting ESMA the authority to impose legally binding measures on financial institutions in Member States when the proper functioning of financial markets or the stability of the EU financial system is threatened.</description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations.</description></item><item><title>Is the non-refoulement principle in the EU's qualification Directive considered invalid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</guid><description>By Pieter Boeles, visiting professor migration law, VU University Amsterdam, emeritus professor University Leiden
Introduction
The principle of non-refoulement, which forbids returning individuals to unsafe nations, is generally considered absolute. However, ambiguity persists concerning its application within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, which governs the determination of refugee or subsidiary protection status. The Czech Nejvyšší správní soud inquired with the Court of Justice of the European Union on July 14, 2016, about the potential conflict between Article 14(4) of the Qualification Directive and the principle of non-refoulement (Case C-391/16).</description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?</description></item><item><title>Brexit has not resulted in any legal changes yet, as the Court of Justice of the European Union continues to rule on the execution of European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK before Brexit Day.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While there are many legal discussions surrounding the impact of Brexit, the ultimate authority on these matters, at least for the EU, is the EU Court of Justice. The Court&amp;rsquo;s first ruling on Brexit, released today, clarifies the legal standing until Brexit Day and potentially influences the approach after that.
The judgment in the case of RO addressed whether Ireland remained obligated to enforce a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) issued by the UK considering its impending withdrawal from the EU after triggering Article 50 TEU.</description></item><item><title>Love triumphs in the CJEU: Equal Marriage and EU Freedom of Movement Legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/love-triumphs-in-the-cjeu-equal-marriage-and-eu-freedom-of-movement-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling on same-sex marriage within the framework of EU free movement law in the case of Coman. This case involved a Romanian citizen, Mr. Coman, who married his American husband in Belgium while residing there. When they attempted to return to Romania, the Romanian government, which does not legally acknowledge same-sex marriage, refused residency to Mr.</description></item><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim.</description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence.</description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice (CJEU) provides clarification on the patentability of stem cells in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther; all views are the author&amp;rsquo;s own
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently clarified its stance on biotechnology patents in the International Stem Cell Corporation case, modifying its earlier decision in Brüstle. The court now emphasizes the &amp;ldquo;inherent capacity&amp;rdquo; of a non-fertilized human egg stimulated by parthenogenesis to become a human being as the defining factor for it to be considered a &amp;ldquo;human embryo&amp;rdquo; and thus ineligible for patenting under the Biotechnology Directive.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ ruling in Joined Cases C-203/15 and C-698/15 Tele2 and Watson (Grand Chamber) on data retention and national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent court decision examined the legality of national data retention laws from a human rights standpoint. These laws remained in effect even after the Data Retention Directive was struck down in the Digital Rights Ireland case due to its disproportionate impact on Articles 7 and 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (EUCFR). This judgment clarifies the interpretation of Articles 7 and 8 within EU law, particularly in the context of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive, and may impact the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU post-Brexit.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on police powers in relation to mobile phone theft and EU eprivacy law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ministerio Fiscal contributes to the understanding of the ePrivacy Directive, specifically Article 15, which allows Member States to make exceptions to the confidentiality of communications for certain purposes. This article played a role in the legal framework surrounding the mass retention of communications data from the Digital Rights Ireland case, where the CJEU established that data retention is justified only in cases of &amp;ldquo;serious crime,&amp;rdquo; as per the Tele2/Watson case.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling in Case C-632/20 P Spain v Commission (Kosovo) on Third Parties, Nations, and Other Entities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
Photo credit: Aljabakphoto, via Wikimedia commons - Šar Mountains National Park in Dragaš, Kosovo
On January 17th, 2023, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in Case C-632/20 P, Spain v Commission (Kosovo), deciding that Kosovo can participate in the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications (BEREC). This decision, reached despite the EU&amp;rsquo;s non-recognition of Kosovo as a state, clarifies that &amp;ldquo;third country&amp;rdquo; status, as defined by the EU, can include territories not recognized as sovereign states and that these entities are eligible for participation in EU agencies.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU upholds the right of asylum seekers to family housing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:41:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This piece examines the housing obligations of EU Member States toward asylum-seeking families. The European Court of Justice (CJEU) recently clarified the minimum standards required of Member States in its ruling on the Saciri case. The judgment is a positive development, confirming that regardless of the challenges Member States face in providing reception services for asylum-seekers, families cannot be left homeless or in extremely poor living conditions by denying them financial aid for housing.</description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice in Bank Refah Kargaran making a groundbreaking decision by allowing action for damages in relation to CFSP decisions regarding restrictive measures?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</guid><description>Professor Dr. Peter Van Elsuwege and Joyce De Coninck (PhD Researcher), Ghent European Law Institute
The recent Grand Chamber judgment in the case of Bank Refah Kargaran v Council, issued on October 6, 2020, sheds further light on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) jurisdiction concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Drawing on previous judgments such as Elitaliana, H v. Council, Rosneft, and SatCen vs.</description></item><item><title>The rights of pregnant workers and the free movement rights of EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Jessy Saint Prix, a young woman from France, relocated to Britain in 2006 to pursue a teaching career. Her experience led her to learn much more about EU law and the English legal system than she expected.
After working in the UK as a teaching assistant for a year, she began a teacher training program (PGCE). During the program, she became pregnant and decided to pause her studies to register with a teaching agency.</description></item><item><title>Is there a role for the Court of Justice of the European Union in ensuring the accountability and independence of the Governors of National Banks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-role-for-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-ensuring-the-accountability-and-independence-of-the-governors-of-national-banks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 10:12:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-role-for-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-ensuring-the-accountability-and-independence-of-the-governors-of-national-banks/</guid><description>Dr. Marios Costa, Senior Lecturer, City, University of London
The European Union (EU) has faced criticism for administrative and structural shortcomings, with reports and discussions pointing to political irregularities within its system. Similarly, concerns about alleged corruption, maladministration, and money laundering at the national governance level raise anxieties for both citizens and the Union.
On February 26, 2019, the Court of Justice (Grand Chamber) issued a significant judgment on two combined cases.</description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood.</description></item><item><title>The Achmea ruling by the CJEU: A Fatal Blow to Independent Investment Protection Tribunals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-achmea-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-fatal-blow-to-independent-investment-protection-tribunals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-achmea-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-fatal-blow-to-independent-investment-protection-tribunals/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz*
*For the original German version of this article, see Verfassungsblog
Public interest in current events tends to be fleeting. Take, for example, the excitement generated in the international media by the regional parliament of Wallonia&amp;rsquo;s threat to block the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) with Canada. Currently, free trade is enjoying a surge in popularity thanks to Donald Trump’s opposition to it, as few Europeans are eager to be seen aligning with the US President on this issue.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice clarifies the vertical direct effect of Directives in cases where Daddy is responsible for paying for your crashed car.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-clarifies-the-vertical-direct-effect-of-directives-in-cases-where-daddy-is-responsible-for-paying-for-your-crashed-car/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-clarifies-the-vertical-direct-effect-of-directives-in-cases-where-daddy-is-responsible-for-paying-for-your-crashed-car/</guid><description>Albert Sánchez Graells, Reader in Economic Law, University of Bristol*
EU law can be complicated, especially when it comes to Directives. Unlike Regulations, Directives are not automatically binding between private parties. However, individuals can use Directives against the State, creating a need to define what &amp;ldquo;State&amp;rdquo; means in this context, given the variety of public-private relationships across the EU.
EU law addresses this through the concept of &amp;ldquo;emanation of the State,&amp;rdquo; which clarifies which bodies are subject to Directives.</description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's stance on the minimum age requirement for spouses in a family reunification application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently ruled in the Noorzia case concerning the age requirement for family reunification. The case revolved around whether a national law, requiring both the sponsor and their spouse to be 21 years old when applying for family reunification, aligns with European Union (EU) law. The CJEU determined that the national law was indeed consistent with EU Directive 2003/86/EC.</description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues.</description></item><item><title>Continuing the saga of EU/Armenia relations with Case C-180/20 Commission v Council (CEPA) and the 'centre of gravity' test in the CFSP.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</guid><description>Narine Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in EU and International Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Jesper Ahlin Marceta via Wikicommons
Introduction
The recent ruling in Case C-180/20 (the CEPA case) marks a new chapter in the ongoing debate about the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) and its boundaries. This case saw the Commission challenge the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to deviate from a proposed Council Decision concerning the EU-Armenian Comprehensive and Enhanced Partnership Agreement (CEPA).</description></item><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference.</description></item><item><title>Opinion of Advocate General Szpunar on the compatibility of the Energy Charter Treaty with the Treaties and the jurisdiction of the CJEU in Case C-741/19.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, an Assistant Professor in Law at Aarhus University, examines a September 24, 2019 request by the French Cour d’appel de Paris. The court asked the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) to interpret &amp;ldquo;investment&amp;rdquo; as used in Article 1.6 of the Energy Charter Treaty (ECT). The intersection of the ECT and EU law, especially following the Achmea judgment against investor-state dispute settlement (ISDS) provisions in bilateral investment treaties (BITs) between EU Member States, has drawn scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>The impact of Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein v. Wirtschaftsakademie Schleswig-Holstein GmbH on Facebook fan pages and EU data protection regulations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
Case Summary
The Wirtschaftsakademie, a business using a Facebook fanpage, was ordered by the Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein (ULD), a German data protection authority, to deactivate their page. The ULD argued that the page failed to warn visitors about potential data collection by Facebook through cookies.
This case highlights the benefits and data implications associated with Facebook fanpages. Page administrators benefit from free, anonymous user statistics through &amp;ldquo;Facebook Insights,&amp;rdquo; while Facebook gathers data for targeted advertising.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals.</description></item><item><title>The potential threat to human rights protection posed by the CJEU and the EU's accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The CJEU’s Opinion on EU Accession to the ECHR: Taking the Football Home Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) finally issued its ruling on the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed accession to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). This intricate judgment brings up numerous legal points. This post will present a concise summary of the ruling, examine its implications, and offer an initial critique of the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning.</description></item><item><title>Restrictions on extradition to countries outside the EU due to EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/restrictions-on-extradition-to-countries-outside-the-eu-due-to-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) is a well-known EU law that streamlined extradition between member states, EU law generally doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern extradition to non-EU nations. Exceptions exist in cases of pre-existing treaties, like those with the USA and Norway/Iceland, or regarding asylum seekers. The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum laws restrict extraditing asylum-seekers before determining if the requesting country intends to persecute them.
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Petruhhin case has changed this.</description></item><item><title>Can a third state legally challenge EU restrictive measures? The Court of Justice says 'yes'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 07:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-third-state-legally-challenge-eu-restrictive-measures-the-court-of-justice-says-yes/</guid><description>Francesca Finelli, PhD student, University of Luxembourg
In the legal case Venezuela v Council (C-872/19 P), the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) reversed a prior General Court decision. It determined that Venezuela has the right to legally challenge EU sanctions imposed against it. This judgment is groundbreaking as it allows any third-party country facing EU economic sanctions to challenge them in EU courts, a precedent not previously established.</description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean.</description></item><item><title>Following the Dano ruling, under what circumstances can unemployed EU citizens be deported?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/following-the-dano-ruling-under-what-circumstances-can-unemployed-eu-citizens-be-deported/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Dano case focused on benefit applications, not deportation. Therefore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t directly affect deportation. However, due to the Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the EU citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive, it might indirectly impact deportation.
Earlier this year, I published a blog post about when unemployment could justify deporting or banning EU citizens. This post expands on that analysis, considering the Dano judgment.</description></item><item><title>Preserving the Formal Rule of Law in the EU's Asylum Policy: The CJEU's Ruling on the Asylum Relocation Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, Ph.D. Researcher in European Union Law at the School of Law and Government of Dublin City University*
*Reblogged from the Bridge Network blog
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling found Poland, Hungary, and the Czech Republic to be in violation of European Union (EU) law. The violation stems from their failure to implement two Council Decisions outlining the relocation of asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>Judicial review of monetary policy and banking supervision by the European Central Bank.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</guid><description>Introduction
The European Union has experienced widespread political and economic consequences due to the financial crisis. These effects extend to the legal realm, leading to the European Central Bank (ECB) not only creating debatable new methods for involvement in monetary policy but also acquiring new authority in banking supervision. Additionally, the ECB, alongside the European Commission and the International Monetary Fund (forming the &amp;lsquo;Troika&amp;rsquo;), has become engaged in austerity measures within Member States requiring financial support.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU bolsters criminal law protection of the EU's finances in The Italian Job.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Contrary to popular belief, fraud against the EU budget is not typically committed by corrupt EU officials. As per EU reports, the usual culprits are individuals or companies exploiting EU funds managed by Member States. These violations also extend beyond spending to include EU income reduction, such as evading customs duties on imports.
Establishing and upholding EU-wide regulations for such misconduct has been challenging. However, the Court of Justice (CJEU) significantly strengthened the law in this area with its recent Taricco judgment.</description></item><item><title>Poor drivers and European Union legislation: The Court of Justice of the European Union takes the wrong approach.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poor-drivers-and-european-union-legislation-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-takes-the-wrong-approach/</guid><description>Steve Peers
There&amp;rsquo;s a humorous anecdote about national stereotypes, where an American, a Canadian, a Brit, and a Frenchman are asked to write about elephants. The punchline highlights their different perspectives: the Frenchman focuses on the elephant&amp;rsquo;s mating habits, the Brit on its colonial significance, the American on its military uses, and the Canadian on whether the elephant falls under federal or provincial jurisdiction. This humorous scenario underscores how jurisdictional issues are central to Canadian identity.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State.</description></item><item><title>Are potential asylum-seekers entitled to a Schengen visa?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
In a recent decision concerning the Koushkaki case, the Court of Justice provided clarity on applying for a Schengen visa. The court effectively ruled that individuals have a right to a visa if they fulfill the established requirements. However, this decision also implicitly raises questions about denying visa applications from potential asylum-seekers.
The judgment
Mr. Koushkaki, an Iranian citizen residing in Iran, applied for a Schengen visa to visit Germany but was denied due to insufficient proof of financial support for his stay and return.</description></item><item><title>Maxima Latvija: Non-compete clauses in commercial lease agreements are considered competition restrictions by their nature.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxima-latvija-non-compete-clauses-in-commercial-lease-agreements-are-considered-competition-restrictions-by-their-nature/</guid><description>Michele Giannino (Italian qualified lawyer: LL.M. Leicester, Ph.D London)
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) concerning the Maxima Latvija case determined that commercial lease agreements containing clauses granting tenants the right to approve leases with third parties are not inherently anti-competitive. This means a full analysis of the agreements&amp;rsquo; economic effects is required to ascertain if they violate competition laws. The CJEU outlined the criteria for evaluating the agreements&amp;rsquo; competition impact.</description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit.</description></item><item><title>Is Poland violating the principle of effective judicial protection? Recent developments in the CJEU suggest so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:17:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-poland-violating-the-principle-of-effective-judicial-protection-recent-developments-in-the-cjeu-suggest-so/</guid><description>Femke Gremmelprez, PhD Researcher and Academic Assistant, Department of European, Public and International Law, Research group Ghent European Law Institute
While the Court of Justice plays a significant role in enforcing EU law through infringement and preliminary ruling procedures (Articles 258 and 267 TFEU, respectively), it has largely been excluded from enforcing EU values, particularly the rule of law. The EU Treaties lack explicit provisions granting the Court of Justice the power to address rule of law breaches by Member States.</description></item><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership.</description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states.</description></item><item><title>Salesman's Vacation: CJEU provides clarification on holiday pay calculation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salesman-s-vacation-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-holiday-pay-calculation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 07:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salesman-s-vacation-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-holiday-pay-calculation/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Working Time Directive is frequently a source of contention in the UK. However, certain workers, especially those who might not otherwise receive it, appreciate the four weeks of paid annual leave it guarantees. A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Lock case addressed a crucial question concerning holiday pay calculation for commissioned employees.
Commission often constitutes a significant portion of a worker&amp;rsquo;s earnings, highlighted by Mr.</description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data.</description></item><item><title>AG Kokott dismisses challenges to the legality of the Tobacco Products Directive - what does this mean for standardized packaging laws in Member States?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</guid><description>Jonathan Griffiths, Reader in Intellectual Property Law, Queen Mary University of London
The Tobacco Products Directive (Directive 2014/40/EU, revising Directive 2001/37/EC) implements strict rules for selling tobacco products. This includes requiring larger image and text health warnings on cigarettes and rolling tobacco, tighter marketing regulations for tobacco products (including e-cigarettes), and a ban on marketing tobacco products with &amp;ldquo;characterizing flavors,&amp;rdquo; such as menthol cigarettes.
On December 23rd, Advocate General Kokott presented her Opinions on three cases regarding the validity of specific parts of the Directive.</description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the voluntary departure of irregular migrants: Act before you are forced to leave.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 18:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-voluntary-departure-of-irregular-migrants-act-before-you-are-forced-to-leave/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued its first ruling on &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; provisions within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, which governs the deportation of undocumented non-EU migrants. While technically still an obligation to leave under threat of force, &amp;ldquo;voluntary departure&amp;rdquo; offers a more humane alternative to forced removal.
Typically, migrants are given 7 to 30 days for voluntary departure, extendable in specific cases. However, this period can be denied or shortened to less than seven days if the migrant is deemed a flight risk, if their application for legal stay was rejected as unfounded or fraudulent, or if they pose a risk to public safety, security, or national interests.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence).</description></item><item><title>The relationship between the EU and Morocco and the issue of the Western Sahara: the European Court of Justice and the principles of international law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</guid><description>Markus W. Gehring: University Lecturer, University of Cambridge; J.S.D. (Yale), LL.M. (Yale), Dr jur. (Hamburg), MA (Cantab); Deputy Director, Economic Law at CIGI
On December 21, 2016, the Court of Justice issued its appeals decision in the case of Council v. Front Polisario. This Grand Chamber judgment, reached under an expedited procedure, overturned the prior decision made by the EU General Court in Front Polisario v Council roughly a year before.</description></item><item><title>Is the notice to withdraw from the EU being revoked? Wightman's opinion suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-notice-to-withdraw-from-the-eu-being-revoked-wightman-s-opinion-suggests-so/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
Is initiating the Article 50 withdrawal process from the EU irreversible, like jumping off a cliff? Or is it more like going shopping, where you can change your mind along the way, in the parking lot, or even inside the store? Perhaps this change of heart might be due to discovering the promised sale doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, the management is under investigation, and the supposed extensive international food section is just a couple of dusty packages.</description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/13 on EU accession to the ECHR: Searching for the Positive Aspect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 16:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-13-on-eu-accession-to-the-echr-searching-for-the-positive-aspect/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge
Introduction Opinion 2/13 is a legal judgment with significant political consequences. It provides a thorough examination of the Draft Accession Agreement (DAA) clauses and fundamental EU law principles. While some have offered helpful explanations of the Opinion, others have criticized it intensely. This piece aims to explore a more favorable interpretation of the Opinion, focusing on three key points: the potential oversight of the bigger picture during negotiations, whether Opinion 2/13 was an act of judicial self-importance, and its impact on the relationship between the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR).</description></item><item><title>Balancing Health and Trade: The Scotch Whisky Association ruling on finding the right equilibrium.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-health-and-trade-the-scotch-whisky-association-ruling-on-finding-the-right-equilibrium/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School The Court of Justice has issued its judgment regarding the legality of Scotland&amp;rsquo;s minimum alcohol pricing (MUP) measure in Case C-333/14. Both the Scottish Government and the Scotch Whisky Association (SWA), which initiated the legal challenge, have expressed satisfaction with the ruling, although the SWA might be more content as the case now returns to Scotland&amp;rsquo;s Inner House of the Court of Session, which had referred it to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates.</description></item><item><title>Explaining the European Court of Justice's decisions on headscarf bans in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued rulings on whether employers can prohibit employees from wearing headscarves at work. These rulings have garnered significant attention, although some of it stems from misunderstandings. This post aims to provide a clear explanation of the rulings.
Background
The EU has established laws against discrimination based on sex, nationality, race, disability, age, sexual orientation, and religion. While the ECJ has frequently addressed cases related to the first three grounds, the recent judgments in G4S v Achbita and Bougnaoui mark the first instance where the court has been asked to interpret workplace discrimination based on religious grounds.</description></item><item><title>EU Animal Welfare Rules' Extraterritorial Reach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</guid><description>By Jessica Lawrence, PhD student, VU University Amsterdam
In the Zuchtvieh-Transport case, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that Regulation 1/2005, concerning the protection of animals during transport, applies beyond EU borders. This means that even when transport starts within the EU and ends outside its borders, the regulation still governs the journey. This decision is significant as it promotes animal welfare but also reflects the CJEU’s expanding interpretation of EU jurisdiction, stretching conventional international law principles on &amp;rsquo;territorial jurisdiction'.</description></item><item><title>People from another place? EU citizenship and the renunciation of national citizenship in Member States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-from-another-place-eu-citizenship-and-the-renunciation-of-national-citizenship-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-from-another-place-eu-citizenship-and-the-renunciation-of-national-citizenship-in-member-states/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*This blog post draws from the upcoming second edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Typically, the rules governing the acquisition and loss of nationality are decided by individual Member States. However, this issue is central to EU law because, as stated in Article 20(1) TFEU, EU citizenship is reliant on possessing the nationality of a Member State:</description></item><item><title>We have the freedom to laugh at anything, but not everyone can appreciate it!" Examining the boundaries of freedom of expression through parody: the ruling of the CJEU in the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 04:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception
at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
The Advocate-General recently issued an opinion on parody, sparking significant interest in the topic. This opinion, while not yet available in English, has been the subject of discussion in legal circles. Further amplifying this attention, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has now released its own judgment on the matter.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on data retention: Mass surveillance is prohibited.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</guid><description>Steve Peers
On July 7, 2005, a relative of mine was on her way to work on a London tube train when terrorists detonated bombs on her train and three others across the city. While my relative was unharmed, dozens of people tragically lost their lives.
This event, along with the prior attacks on 9/11 and in Madrid, understandably fueled public anxiety around terrorism and spurred the EU to introduce additional anti-terrorism measures.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice resolves the issue of posting third-country workers within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Amedeo Arena, Assistant Professor of European Law - University of Naples &amp;ldquo;Federico II&amp;rdquo; School of Law
Judgment of the court (Second Chamber) of 11 September 2014, Essent Energie Productie BV v. Minister van SocialeZaken en Werkgelegenheid, Case C-91/13.
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) has consistently maintained that, in contrast to workers from EU Member States, Turkish nationals do not possess the right to freedom of movement within the European Union.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state.</description></item><item><title>National legal challenges to the Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
This article delves into the numerous legal obstacles faced by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, both at national and EU levels. This is the third installment in a series examining this controversial legislation, which has recently been overturned by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The information presented is a result of research conducted by Statewatch as part of the SECILE project, which focuses on the impact, legitimacy, and effectiveness of counter-terrorism measures in securing Europe.</description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role.</description></item><item><title>Guardianship, freedom of movement, and child rights: the SM ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 21:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardianship-freedom-of-movement-and-child-rights-the-sm-ruling/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
*This blog post expands on research that informed the upcoming revised edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Defining a &amp;ldquo;family member&amp;rdquo; legally can be complex, especially when it comes to immigration law and child welfare. The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment in the SM case highlights these complexities, particularly where EU free movement law intersects with the family law of non-EU nations.</description></item><item><title>In search of the Babel-fish: Addressing language discrimination in EU law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-search-of-the-babel-fish-addressing-language-discrimination-in-eu-law/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano
Introduction: Language Differentiation in the EU
The EU already faces a considerable language challenge with 24 official languages recognized by Regulation n. 1/1958. While the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights allows citizens to communicate with EU institutions in their chosen language, the primary working languages are English, French, and German. However, all official EU documents necessitate translation into all 24 recognized languages.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling on the Legality of the Revised European Firearms Directive: Gun Control in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 22:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-legality-of-the-revised-european-firearms-directive-gun-control-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, PhD candidate, Dublin City University
Introduction
On December 3rd, 2019, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) delivered its final ruling on a case concerning Czech firearm regulations. This judgment, providing guidance on EU lawmaking, addressed key EU law principles and refined their interpretations. Following terrorist attacks in Paris and Copenhagen, the EU legislature utilized its single market powers (Article 114 TFEU) to pass Directive (EU) 2017/853, amending existing firearms Directives 91/477 and 2008/51/EC.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item><item><title>What authority should the Court of Justice have in EU Foreign Policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD student, King’s College London
Article 24(1) of the Treaty on the European Union states that the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) operates under distinct rules and procedures, explicitly stating that the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) holds no jurisdiction over these provisions.
Legal experts are debating whether &amp;ldquo;the CJEU shall not have jurisdiction&amp;rdquo; implies a degree of jurisdiction. AG Wahl articulated this question: Does the exclusion of CJEU jurisdiction encompass all CFSP actions or only specific categories?</description></item><item><title>Are agency workers adequately protected under EU legislation?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 06:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-agency-workers-adequately-protected-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Workers with non-traditional employment arrangements, such as those lacking full-time permanent contracts, frequently face precarious positions in the labor market, making them susceptible to exploitation. Additionally, the utilization of such employment models may negatively impact other workers. Conversely, there are instances where such employment benefits both workers and employers, acting as a significant source of job creation. In balancing these concerns, the EU has implemented measures regulating three specific non-traditional employment categories: agency workers, part-time workers, and fixed-term workers.</description></item><item><title>Ensuring the right to a nationality for children of same-sex couples in the EU - A crucial matter in the case of V.M.A. v Stolichna Obsthina (C-490/20) before the CJEU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-right-to-a-nationality-for-children-of-same-sex-couples-in-the-eu-a-crucial-matter-in-the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obsthina-c-490-20-before-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ensuring-the-right-to-a-nationality-for-children-of-same-sex-couples-in-the-eu-a-crucial-matter-in-the-case-of-v-m-a-v-stolichna-obsthina-c-490-20-before-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Patrícia Cabral, Legal Policy Officer, European Network on Statelessness*
The recognition of LGBTQ* rights, including same-sex partnerships or marriages and legal parentage for same-sex couples, varies significantly across Europe. This inconsistent landscape presents challenges for rainbow families (families with at least one LGBTQ* parent), particularly regarding the legal recognition of their civil status, birth registration processes, and access to birth certificates. Consequently, some children in these families face statelessness or a heightened risk of it.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy.</description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends.</description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR.</description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice of the European Union mindful of the boundaries of EU authority?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Vilija Vėlyvytė, British Academy Post-Doctoral Fellow, Somerville College, University of Oxford
Photo credit: civarmy, by wikipedia
My recently published book, ‘Judicial Authority in EU Internal Market Law: Implications for the Balance of Competences and Powers’ (Hart Publishing 2022), investigates how the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) broadens the EU’s authority through its interpretation of EU internal market law.
The expansion of EU power, often referred to as ‘competence creep’, into areas where the EU lacks explicit authority, such as public health and social security, has been extensively discussed.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's confusion on biometric data and data protection law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Growing concerns about the protection of biometric data have led the EU to propose a data protection regulation classifying such data as sensitive, thus providing it with a higher level of protection. However, until this proposal is enacted, existing EU regulations address this issue, although not always effectively, as demonstrated by the recent CJEU ruling in the Willems case, which falls short in its application of existing regulations to biometric data.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War.</description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles.</description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the downfall of Poland's controversial "judicial reforms"? Reflections on the recent ECJ decision in Commission v Poland regarding the Independence of the Supreme Court.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 02:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-downfall-of-poland-s-controversial-judicial-reforms-reflections-on-the-recent-ecj-decision-in-commission-v-poland-regarding-the-independence-of-the-supreme-court/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, a Professor of European Law at Middlesex University London, and Sébastien Platon, a Professor of Public Law at the University of Bordeaux, have written about a situation unfolding in a country within the EU where the government and parliament, both controlled by the same political party, have made changes to their judicial system.
These changes include lowering the retirement age for judges on the country&amp;rsquo;s highest court. This move has been presented by the government as a necessary reform to hold accountable judges who were supposedly involved in the country&amp;rsquo;s previous communist regime, even though that regime ended three decades ago.</description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts.</description></item><item><title>Is the recent ruling by the CJEU indicative of an irrational fear of genetic mutations in EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-ruling-by-the-cjeu-indicative-of-an-irrational-fear-of-genetic-mutations-in-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:57:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-ruling-by-the-cjeu-indicative-of-an-irrational-fear-of-genetic-mutations-in-eu-law/</guid><description>A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has increased the difficulty of developing plants modified through mutagenic breeding. This blog post presents two perspectives on the judgment, one from Kathleen Garnett and another from Felix Beck.
Confédération Paysanne &amp;amp; Others, Case C-528/16: GMO cabbage or plain old cabbage?
Kathleen Garnett, Consultant and writer on EU government and law
In 2016, Stefan Jansson, a plant biology professor at Umeå University in Sweden, consumed a meal of cabbage he had cultivated in his garden using seeds modified with CRISPR Cas-9 technology.</description></item><item><title>How do the Court's rulings on December 21, 2023 impact UEFA's position as a 'gatekeeper' in the Football Revolution?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 02:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-do-the-court-s-rulings-on-december-21-2023-impact-uefa-s-position-as-a-gatekeeper-in-the-football-revolution/</guid><description>Steve Weatherill, Somerville College and Faculty of Law, University of Oxford
Photo credit: Werner100359, via Wikimedia Commons
Summary
Recent Court of Justice rulings on December 21, 2023, determined that practices requiring prior approval for new sporting competitions created by external entities clash with EU law. This decision primarily stemmed from the lack of clear, unbiased, and transparent criteria and procedures. While governing bodies, particularly in football, are obligated to adjust their practices, the extent of their authority as gatekeepers remains unclear.</description></item><item><title>Disappointing CJEU ruling upholds ban on blood donation by gay and bisexual men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-cjeu-ruling-upholds-ban-on-blood-donation-by-gay-and-bisexual-men/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice in Case C-528/13 Léger determined that permanent bans on blood donation by gay and bisexual men solely based on their sexual history with other men might be justified in certain situations to ensure high health protection standards. This piece argues that this ruling is disappointing and could lead to accusations of inadequate LGB rights protection or even ingrained homophobia.</description></item><item><title>Is the judicial oversight of detention a misleading disruption?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-judicial-oversight-of-detention-a-misleading-disruption/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III
Member of the Institut Universitaire de France
On June 5, 2014, the European Court of Justice (CJEU) issued a decision in the Mahdi case, providing further interpretation of the Return Directive. This directive, formally known as Directive 2008/115/EC, establishes common standards for EU Member States regarding the return of illegally staying third-country nationals. The CJEU&amp;rsquo;s judgment builds upon its prior rulings concerning this directive.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the ECJ to intervene in Brexit?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 06:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-ecj-to-intervene-in-brexit/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent High Court decision mandates that the UK government must secure parliamentary approval before initiating Article 50, the process for exiting the European Union. While this post won&amp;rsquo;t delve into the national constitutional law aspects, it will examine the potential involvement of EU courts in Brexit disputes.
Following the government&amp;rsquo;s announced appeal to the Supreme Court, some have suggested a further &amp;ldquo;appeal&amp;rdquo; to the European Court of Justice (ECJ).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU interprets the e-commerce Directive regarding Facebook's responsibility for defamatory posts.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, several legal decisions have addressed how individuals can control their information online. Two cases, GC et al and Google v CNIL, focused on how search engines should interpret their obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This post will focus on a third case, Glawischnig-Piesczek v Facebook, which examined how the e-Commerce Directive&amp;rsquo;s prohibition on general monitoring applies to &amp;ldquo;stay down&amp;rdquo; notices. The case raises a broader question about the consistency of different internet regulations, including those related to intellectual property, child exploitation, and terrorism.</description></item><item><title>Constitutional Conflict in the European Union: A Jurisprudential Analysis (OUP 2022)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/constitutional-conflict-in-the-european-union-a-jurisprudential-analysis-oup-2022/</guid><description>Ana Bobić, Law Clerk at the Court of Justice of the European Union
Photo credit: Antoine Montulé, via Wikicommons
It has been almost 60 years since the Court of Justice established that EU law takes precedence. However, this principle still sparks discussions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s constitutional system. Initially, the integration of EU law into national legal frameworks caused tension between the Court of Justice and national constitutional courts. The Court of Justice believes strongly in the importance of EU law&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness and expects all national courts to share this view.</description></item><item><title>Protection for fixed-term workers against unfair dismissal and mistreatment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union (EU) has increasingly addressed the rise of non-standard employment through measures like agreements on part-time and fixed-term work, and a Directive on agency work. The fixed-term work rules, in particular, have spurred many legal cases in the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). However, until recently, the court had not fully considered the connection between these rules and national laws on unfair dismissal, particularly for university researchers.</description></item><item><title>EU law and its impact on minority languages in court proceedings: exploring the potential and constraints.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 23:18:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-its-impact-on-minority-languages-in-court-proceedings-exploring-the-potential-and-constraints/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), through its judgment in the Ruffer case, reinforced and broadened its stance on using minority languages in legal processes.
The case involved Mrs. Ruffer, a German citizen residing in Germany, who was injured in a skiing incident in Bolzano, Italy, a region where German is commonly spoken. She held Ms. Pokoma, a Czech citizen living in the Czech Republic, responsible for the accident and filed a lawsuit against her in the Italian courts.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening and weakening the legal standing of individuals granted subsidiary protection under European Union law – the ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union in the case of Alo and Osso.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 23:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strengthening-and-weakening-the-legal-standing-of-individuals-granted-subsidiary-protection-under-european-union-law-the-ruling-by-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-in-the-case-of-alo-and-osso/</guid><description>Dr. Louise Halleskov Storgaard, Assistant Professor, Aarhus University
Can a country that offers subsidiary protection (a form of protection similar to refugee status) restrict the movement of those beneficiaries within its borders if they receive social security benefits? This is the central question addressed by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Alo and Osso case on March 1, 2015. The CJEU’s answer is notable, innovative, and potentially contentious as it reinforces the influence of the Geneva Convention on subsidiary protection standards but also raises questions about the applicable non-discrimination standard.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU affirms that data protection authorities are independent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent judgment on data protection, while not as impactful as a prior ruling, is still significant. In Commission v Hungary, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) expanded on earlier decisions in Commission v Germany and Commission v Austria concerning the independent operation of data protection authorities. The judgment&amp;rsquo;s implications, however, reach beyond this specific area.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive mandates that data protection authorities be established to uphold the Directive&amp;rsquo;s regulations, in addition to individual legal action.</description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws.</description></item><item><title>It's finally here - the CJEU has confirmed that UK citizens have officially lost their EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has affirmed that UK citizens lost EU citizenship due to Brexit, as per a recent judgment. This aligns with the earlier Advocate-General’s opinion. While other similar cases exist, the CJEU is unlikely to deviate from this decision.
This judgment is notable for its dismissal of arguments advocating for the retention of EU citizenship for British citizens, marking a significant shift.</description></item><item><title>Comments on the Polish ruling party's "fake judges" in Case C-824/18 AB and Case C-132/20 Getin Noble Bank before the European Court of Justice.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-polish-ruling-party-s-fake-judges-in-case-c-824-18-ab-and-case-c-132-20-getin-noble-bank-before-the-european-court-of-justice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 14:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-polish-ruling-party-s-fake-judges-in-case-c-824-18-ab-and-case-c-132-20-getin-noble-bank-before-the-european-court-of-justice/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, University of Middlesex On March 2, 2021, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) delivered its third judgment in a preliminary ruling case from a Polish court. This case pertained to the deterioration of the rule of law in Poland, an ongoing issue for over five years. Notably, there have been 35 requests for preliminary rulings from Polish courts compared to only three infringement actions brought by the Commission.</description></item><item><title>The Imbalance in the Right to Free Movement for European Union Citizens: A Focus on Students</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia*, Connor Brown**
*Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
** LLB Law European and International, University of Sheffield
This post reflects the preliminary results of a research project conducted as part of the Sheffield Undergraduate Research Experience programme (SURE). It also builds on a presentation at the International Society of Public Law (ICON-S) annual conference in New York on 2nd July 2015
INTRODUCTION
Growing concerns about limited public funds, diminished international cooperation, and declining support for a more unified Europe have cast a shadow on a key principle: the free movement of people.</description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>Is it reasonable to expect consumers to be fluent in foreign languages? This was the question addressed by the CJEU in the Golden Balls case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 02:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther, Trainee, Research Department of the CJEU (All views author’s own)
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a judgment on November 20th in the case of Intra-Presse SAS v OHIM (the &amp;lsquo;Golden Balls&amp;rsquo; case), which did not resolve the seven-year trademark dispute between the UK company Golden Balls Ltd. and Intra-Presse, the French organizers of FIFA’s Ballon d’Or award. The case revolves around the registration of the word mark ‘Golden Balls&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides additional clarification on how the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement applies to Western Sahara.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</guid><description>By Markus W. Gehring, Lecturer in Law, University of Cambridge
On February 27, 2018, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in a case referred by the High Court of England and Wales. The case, Western Sahara Campaign UK v. HM Revenue and Customs, Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, C-266/16, concerned the legality of EU fishing activities in waters adjacent to Western Sahara.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU judgment in NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford has erased the blurry line between employment discrimination and the right to freedom of expression.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Ph.D. Researcher in International Studies at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case C‑507/18, NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford, centers around the balance between freedom of expression and the harmful impact of discriminatory language. Advocate General Eleanor Sharpston aptly used bird metaphors in her opinion, likening discriminatory statements to volatile birds that can quickly spread their harmful effects.</description></item><item><title>No one will know his name...: An analysis of the CJEU ruling on the use of names acknowledged by other Member States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/no-one-will-know-his-name-an-analysis-of-the-cjeu-ruling-on-the-use-of-names-acknowledged-by-other-member-states/</guid><description>Jacques BELLEZIT, Université de Strasbourg
A primary criticism of the European Union is its tendency to involve itself in matters that initially appear outside its defined powers, as outlined in Articles 3 to 6 of the TFEU.
The principle of attributed powers is embedded in EU law and acknowledged as legally binding to ensure the EU operates as a &amp;ldquo;rule of law&amp;rdquo; entity (Les Verts judgment). However, this has not prevented the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) from broadly interpreting its jurisdictional authority concerning EU law.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union and Spanish mortgage legislation: safeguarding consumers, addressing floor clauses, and expediting repayment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-and-spanish-mortgage-legislation-safeguarding-consumers-addressing-floor-clauses-and-expediting-repayment/</guid><description>Juan Carlos Benito Sánchez, PhD Fellow at the University of Louvain (Belgium).
Twitter: @jcbensan
Over recent years, the European Court of Justice has issued several judgments invalidating parts of Spanish mortgage law, both in terms of its content and procedures, and how it’s interpreted by the courts. These rulings were based on the fact that these laws went against EU consumer protection regulations. In particular, the Court based its decisions on Council Directive 93/13/EEC of 5 April 1993 on unfair terms in consumer contracts.</description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Disappointing ruling by the CJEU on reverse discrimination against rape victims</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</guid><description>Steve Peers
National criminal justice systems are frequently criticized for overlooking the needs of crime victims. In contrast, the EU has been attentive to this matter since the initial stages of EU criminal law development. Early on, one of the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Framework Decisions&amp;rsquo; addressed victims&amp;rsquo; rights. This measure has since been superseded by a comprehensive Directive on this subject, which Member States are required to implement by October 2015.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions on cases involving obesity and discrimination laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 03:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-on-cases-involving-obesity-and-discrimination-laws/</guid><description>Katharina O Cathaoir
The European Court of Justice, in its decision on Kaltoft, determined that obesity itself is not a protected characteristic under EU employment law, nor is it automatically a disability. However, the Court acknowledged that the EU Directive prohibiting workplace discrimination based on disability might apply in certain situations. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this ruling specifically pertains to employment disputes, as EU law does not address disability discrimination outside of the workplace.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has upheld the temporary free movement rights of third-country family members of EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the McCarthy case addresses a crucial question about EU free movement law in the UK: can the UK restrict the ability of family members (who are third-country nationals) of UK (and other EU) citizens to visit the UK?
The case involved a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual British and Irish citizen).</description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter.</description></item></channel></rss>