<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UCaaS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ucaas/</link><description>Recent content in UCaaS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ucaas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item></channel></rss>