<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business and Human Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-and-human-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Business and Human Rights on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-and-human-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Evaluation of the updated EU Council Guidelines on Freedom of Expression in both digital and physical spaces.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods from the University of Essex, and co-author of Steiner and Woods, EU Law, discusses new EU guidelines on freedom of expression.
The European Union Council recently established guidelines for freedom of expression. These guidelines, falling under the Foreign Affairs Council, are designed for application within the framework of the Union’s Common Foreign and Security Policy, similar to previous guidelines addressing issues like torture, capital punishment, and human rights advocates.</description></item><item><title>Litigation in England involving business and human rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Anil Yilmaz Vastardis, Lecturer in Law, Human Rights Centre, University of Essex
Following the UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union, there is widespread uncertainty about the future. While political questions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit dominate the discussion, the consequences extend far beyond, impacting individuals worldwide, including victims of human rights abuses perpetrated by British corporations. A key concern revolves around the fate of EU laws implemented in the UK, either through legislation or direct application.</description></item><item><title>Companies will now have to comply with new EU human rights reporting requirements, which go beyond the current rules in the UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/</guid><description>Authored by Anil Yilmaz, Lecturer in Law at the University of Brighton, and Rachel Chambers, PhD candidate at the University of Essex.
Background The European Union, as stated in Article 3(3) of the Treaty on the European Union, aims to establish a unified internal market and foster sustainable growth. This growth should be characterized by balanced economic advancement, price stability, and a highly competitive social market economy. This economic model strives for full employment, social progress, and robust environmental protection and improvement.</description></item></channel></rss>