<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Centre on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-centre/</link><description>Recent content in Business Centre on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-centre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Compass Offices has launched a new business center at Oberoi Centre in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/compass-offices-has-launched-a-new-business-center-at-oberoi-centre-in-dubai/</guid><description>Compass Offices, a leading provider of serviced offices in the Asia Pacific region, is expanding its presence to the United Arab Emirates with the inauguration of its first business center in Dubai in July 2014. This strategic move comes on the heels of the company&amp;rsquo;s recent expansion into Australia and Kazakhstan, as well as the establishment of new business centers in Hong Kong.
Alexander Passler, Vice President of Business Development at Compass Offices, highlighted Dubai&amp;rsquo;s growing appeal for businesses, stating, &amp;ldquo;Dubai&amp;rsquo;s reputation for economic stability and its thriving financial hub status are attracting a growing number of companies.</description></item><item><title>Avanta India inaugurates a new office space in Gurgaon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</guid><description>Avanta Business Centre has established a new premium office space in Gurgaon, India, spanning 25,000 square feet. Conveniently situated near the HUDA City Centre Metro station, the Park Centra facility offers easy accessibility.
This marks Avanta&amp;rsquo;s second business center in Gurgaon. The Park Centra location provides a variety of office sizes, ranging from 77 square feet to approximately 20,000 square feet, to accommodate a diverse clientele. The space is ready for occupancy and features around 300 workstations, a communal area, a pantry, and four meeting rooms.</description></item></channel></rss>