<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article 8 ECHR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-8-echr/</link><description>Recent content in Article 8 ECHR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-8-echr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Sumption's perspective on human rights is not coherent when considering the historical context of gay rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jonathan-sumption-s-perspective-on-human-rights-is-not-coherent-when-considering-the-historical-context-of-gay-rights/</guid><description>In his Reith Lecture, “Human Rights and Wrongs,” Jonathan Sumption argues that the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) has overstepped its boundaries. He believes the court continuously expands its interpretation of the European Convention on Human Rights, creating new rights and encroaching on areas that should be determined by elected officials.
Sumption has raised similar concerns previously, stating in 2016 that the ECtHR is at the forefront of creating fundamental law that goes beyond the original text of the Convention.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Role of the European Court of Human Rights in Addressing Harassment of Human Rights Defenders: Evaluating Democracy, Malicious Intent, and Covert Motives.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:41:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</guid><description>Protecting Critics: The European Court of Human Rights Strengthens its Stance Against Azerbaijan in Aliyev v. Azerbaijan By Dr Marco Antonio Simonelli, PhD, University of Siena, and Alast Najafi, LLM candidate, University of Leiden
Introduction The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) used Article 18 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), a rarely utilized provision, to condemn Azerbaijan for human rights violations in the case of Aliyev v. Azerbaijan.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions.</description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US.</description></item></channel></rss>