<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Over Copper on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-over-copper/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Over Copper on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-over-copper/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks.</description></item><item><title>Are Your T1 Lines Saturated?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-t1-lines-saturated/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The perfect network connection is invisible. Whether it uses copper wires, coaxial cable, fiber optics, or wireless technology, if it impacts your network traffic, it&amp;rsquo;s not truly transparent. The more noticeable these limitations become, the more they hinder productivity, demanding your attention.
Artificial Limitations
Shared broadband services like Cable, DSL, 4G Cellular, or satellite internet, despite promising &amp;ldquo;best effort,&amp;rdquo; are inherently limited by technology and company policies. Each type has a maximum capacity, typically accessible round-the-clock, except for rare outages.</description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper vs Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</guid><description>T1 lines have long been considered a reliable connection option for small to medium businesses, gaining traction as prices dropped in recent years. However, a new technology called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers even greater bandwidth at a lower cost and with simpler connectivity.
EoC, like T1, uses existing twisted-pair telephone wiring commonly found in business locations. Traditional T1 lines use two twisted pairs within this wiring, allowing for simultaneous two-way data transfer at 1.</description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet.</description></item><item><title>Cyber Monday is For Business Buyers Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-monday-is-for-business-buyers-too/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cyber Monday is known for online shopping deals that shoppers couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in crowded stores during Black Friday sales. While there are many consumer deals, businesses need to consider their savings opportunities as well. Business spending is a significant part of the economy, and their savings can lead to lower prices for consumers. Taking advantage of Cyber Monday bargains is a win-win situation for everyone.
Businesses should explore potential savings on services they might not typically consider.</description></item><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>Increasing Bandwidth By Pair Bonding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</guid><description>When your T1 line starts reaching its bandwidth limit, upgrading to a DS3 line might seem like the next step, but it comes with challenges. DS3 often requires fiber optic cable instead of the copper used for T1, and the cost difference is significant.
A simpler solution for a moderate bandwidth boost is adding another T1 line and using &amp;ldquo;pair bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines two lines into one, effectively doubling your bandwidth to 3 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company.</description></item><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Bandwidth vs Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</guid><description>Businesses choose dedicated internet services, like T1 lines and Ethernet over Copper, when they prioritize consistent performance and service guarantees, or when shared options aren&amp;rsquo;t available. Cable broadband, on the other hand, attracts businesses with its high bandwidth for a lower cost. Although cable lacks service guarantees, its proven track record and widespread availability, especially during business hours, make it appealing.
The term &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; in this context signifies that a specific bandwidth amount is exclusively allocated to the user.</description></item><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Access Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 08:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-access-companies/</guid><description>Consumers access the internet in various ways, and businesses have similar options, along with some exclusive ones. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the choices available for companies at their business locations.
Popular consumer broadband choices include DSL and cable for stationary setups, and 3G for mobile use. 4G wireless is emerging, with providers like CLEAR offering it for both fixed and mobile applications. In remote areas, satellite broadband delivers connectivity where wires can&amp;rsquo;t reach.</description></item><item><title>POTS Panned</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pots-panned/</guid><description>The era of traditional phone service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), seems to be nearing its end. The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) is seeking input on how service providers are transitioning to internet-based networks, prompting AT&amp;amp;T to propose a complete shutdown of the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network) – the century-old infrastructure behind POTS.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the 21st century, and modern networks rely on packet switching instead of circuit switching.</description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines.</description></item><item><title>Business Broadband Options in Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 03:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-options-in-rural-areas/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses located in bustling city centers have a wide array of broadband Internet options, unlike their rural counterparts. While the lack of service providers in less populated areas might make it seem like broadband is a luxury they can&amp;rsquo;t afford, there are actually several options available, depending on the location.
Rural businesses might feel limited in their connectivity choices. Unlike their city counterparts, they don&amp;rsquo;t have numerous service providers vying for their business.</description></item><item><title>Qwest Embraces Ethernet over Copper to Reach Rural Business Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</guid><description>Qwest Communications, a leading telecom provider in the US, boasts a nationwide fiber optic network capable of transmitting data at 40 Gbps, with plans to upgrade to 100 Gbps. While this caters to large enterprises requiring substantial bandwidth, what options are available for remotely located businesses?
Remote offices, even those belonging to large corporations, often face challenges justifying the cost of installing fiber optic cables due to their distance from carrier Points of Presence (POPs).</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Reviving The Local Loop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</guid><description>Local loop usage has decreased as people switch from traditional phone lines to wireless or internet-based phone services. This has prompted some to suggest that these copper lines be completely removed. However, just as this idea emerges, new technology is giving these old lines a new purpose.
Fiber optic connections may be the future, but they’re not widely available yet. Only a small percentage of businesses currently have fiber, due to lack of demand, high installation costs, or limited infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate.</description></item><item><title>Is There a Broadband Stimulus Job For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</guid><description>The U.S. government is investing an additional $795 million in broadband stimulus funding to address the country&amp;rsquo;s lag behind nations like Japan and Korea in providing affordable, high-speed internet. This investment presents a potential win-win situation, offering both short-term job creation and long-term economic benefits.
One study projects the creation of approximately 5,000 immediate jobs from these high-speed internet projects. While seemingly small compared to the number of job seekers, it&amp;rsquo;s a step in the right direction.</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions.</description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle.</description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity For Multi-Business Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</guid><description>Instead of constructing their own offices, many businesses rent space in large buildings like office complexes, shopping centers, or strip malls. This shared situation offers a unique opportunity to secure better bandwidth at lower costs by joining forces with other tenants in the building.
There are a few approaches to leverage the collective bandwidth requirements of multiple businesses. One method is for the building owner to become an ISP, providing bandwidth to all tenants.</description></item><item><title>What Is a DS3 Circuit Or T3 Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line often choose DS3. This article explores DS3, its relationship to T3 lines, and competition from Ethernet over Copper.
DS3, or Digital Signal level 3, follows standards set by Bell Labs for the telephone industry. The smallest unit, DS0, has a 64 Kbps bandwidth, enough for one digitized phone call using the original digital standard, PCM (Pulse Code Modulation). Combining 24 DS0s creates a DS1, which runs on a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths.</description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>EoC and EoTDM Complement Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a significant disparity in bandwidth offered by traditional telecom services, particularly between smaller businesses and large corporations. Smaller businesses often rely on slower T1 lines (1.5 Mbps), while larger corporations enjoy significantly faster speeds (100-1000 times faster) through fiber optic connections.
However, technologies like Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and Ethernet over TDM (EoTDM) are bridging this gap by enabling a broader range of bandwidths on existing copper infrastructure. This allows for a smoother transition between T1 speeds and gigabit or even higher speeds.</description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment.</description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Distance Sensitivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</guid><description>The arrival of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers businesses a range of bandwidth options previously unavailable without fiber optic connections. EoC surpasses the speed limits of traditional T1 lines, provides easy scalability, and often comes at a lower price point, making it an attractive option for businesses seeking robust internet solutions.
However, a few limitations hinder the widespread use of EoC. Firstly, it requires compatible equipment at the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office (CO), where your copper lines terminate.</description></item><item><title>Combine T1 Lines For Higher Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a popular choice for small and medium-sized businesses for many years due to their reliability, security, dedicated bandwidth, and accessibility. While their affordability has increased in recent years, their speed has remained a limitation. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution to overcome this without sacrificing the benefits of T1 technology: bonding.
Bonding is a standard industry technique that allows you to combine the bandwidth of multiple T1 lines. This effectively merges them into a single, faster connection.</description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery.</description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service.</description></item><item><title>Many Flavors of Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 17:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-flavors-of-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting your business to the internet is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world. It&amp;rsquo;s practically impossible to operate without a broadband connection. Customers, cloud services, backups, suppliers, and even connections to home offices or remote locations rely on it. The question is, how can you establish the best connection for your business?
Businesses have numerous options for internet service, but the variety can be overwhelming. Choosing the cheapest option might leave you frustrated if it can&amp;rsquo;t handle your needs.</description></item><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true.</description></item><item><title>Integrated Access Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 03:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-access-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>T1 lines can be used for broadband data or digital phone lines. However, needing separate lines for voice and data was expensive for smaller businesses. Integrated T1 offered a solution by combining voice and data on a single line, proving cost-effective for a while. But now, Integrated Access using Ethernet over Copper is an even better option.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a strong competitor to T1 lines. Both use existing copper telephone wiring, offering reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables.</description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Rising Rapidly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</guid><description>Enhanced business environments and productivity gains through automation are pushing businesses towards higher bandwidth network solutions. Instead of simply increasing their current T1 or other line services, smart managers are exploring new technology that delivers more bandwidth at a lower cost. Ethernet over Copper is emerging as a leading WAN network service.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a straightforward concept: it&amp;rsquo;s an Ethernet service delivered through existing twisted pair copper wiring.</description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Plus Copper Equals High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 03:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Our appetite for bandwidth is insatiable, growing daily. Businesses and consumers alike are hampered by insufficient bandwidth, preventing them from fully utilizing the latest technologies. Content providers and productivity vendors face similar hurdles, unable to deliver their full potential due to inadequate transport and last-mile bandwidth.
This scenario mirrors the early days of personal computers. For decades, limitations in processor speed, RAM, and hard disk capacity were constant challenges. While advancements in these areas have significantly minimized these bottlenecks, they haven&amp;rsquo;t entirely vanished.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections.</description></item><item><title>20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>If you need a significant bandwidth upgrade but find traditional options limited or excessively expensive, consider 20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper (EoC). This technology delivers a symmetrical 20 Mbps upload and download speed over readily available twisted pair copper cable.
This professional-grade service provides dedicated, full-duplex bandwidth, allowing simultaneous uploads and downloads at maximum speed. In contrast, T1 lines offer a base speed of 1.5 Mbps and require bonding multiple lines to achieve higher bandwidth, becoming cost-prohibitive beyond 10-12 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area.</description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased.</description></item><item><title>Copper First, Then Fiber Bandwidth Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</guid><description>When your business needs a fast internet connection but fiber optic installation isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a two-step solution that uses existing technology as a stopgap. This method combines the strengths of different connection types to get you online quickly and upgrade seamlessly later on.
Fiber optic connections, whether SONET or Ethernet, provide the highest bandwidth– starting from 50-100 Mbps and reaching up to 10 Gbps or even higher in some areas.</description></item><item><title>Cable, T1 and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have three primary broadband options today: Cable, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper (EoC). While their costs are relatively similar, each offers distinct advantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options further.
T1 lines, a long-standing choice for SMBs, utilize half-century-old telephone industry technology. This technology transmits digital signals across standard copper telephone wiring. A T1 line consists of two copper pairs, one for uploads and the other for downloads, achieving a consistent speed of 1.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Growing By Leaps and Bounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</guid><description>The hottest new access network service is Ethernet over Copper (EoC), with competitive carriers rushing to expand coverage.
What makes EoC so popular? It stems from evolving network needs. Wide Area Networks (WANs) have been dominated by the telephone industry, adapting phone technology for data and video transmission.
T1 lines, using two pairs of copper telephone wires, have been the standard for businesses needing dedicated Ethernet connections. They offer 1.5 Mbps upload and download speeds.</description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires.</description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations.</description></item><item><title>Should You Buy VoIP as a Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-buy-voip-as-a-service/</guid><description>Cloud-based services, including Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP), have been around for a while. What&amp;rsquo;s becoming more popular now is the trend of large businesses connecting their different locations using SIP Trunks and all sizes of businesses choosing to outsource their PBX functionality. This can be considered VoIP as a Service.
Many home and small business users adopted cloud-based VoIP early on to cut costs. They did this by replacing their traditional phone lines and using their broadband internet connection for both high-speed internet and phone service.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3.</description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Looking For A Lit Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</guid><description>When seeking high-speed internet for your business, you need more than just a building with lights on at night. You need a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; – one connected to a fiber optic network.
Fiber optic connectivity is crucial for high bandwidth. While most buildings have copper wiring for traditional phone lines and T1 connections, these offer limited bandwidth (1.5 Mbps per line). Fiber optics, on the other hand, provide significantly faster speeds (10 Gbps or more per fiber) using light to transmit data.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Steal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</guid><description>Everyone appreciates a bargain, especially for telecommunications services. The current prices for Ethernet might even make you wonder if they&amp;rsquo;re legitimate. To see just how competitive these prices are, take a moment to compare Ethernet costs for your business locations.
The reason Ethernet services are so affordable now is due to rapid technological advancements. Until recently, traditional telephone company services were the only option. Today, competition has introduced alternatives that have completely changed the landscape.</description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices.</description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems.</description></item><item><title>Double Bonded T1 Cost and Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 23:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/double-bonded-t1-cost-and-alternatives/</guid><description>Many businesses appreciate their reliable T1 service, but eventually, the 1.5 Mbps bandwidth becomes insufficient. Instead of abandoning T1, companies can opt for double bonded T1 service, which combines two lines to provide 3 Mbps. This bonding is implemented within customer premises equipment, usually a router with two T1 inputs.
The bandwidth can be further increased by triple bonding (4.5 Mbps) or quadruple bonding (6 Mbps), up to a practical limit of eight bonded lines for 12 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speed Using Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speed-using-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Fiber optic communication lines are expected to be the future of connectivity, with major companies already utilizing their fiber infrastructure. While smaller companies with high bandwidth requirements have transitioned to fiber, the lack of availability in certain areas poses a challenge.
Traditionally, T1 lines, offering 1.5 Mbps speed, were the go-to solution due to their widespread availability and affordability. However, with the increasing bandwidth demands of modern businesses, the limitations of T1 lines have become apparent.</description></item><item><title>Where Competition Is Cutting Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</guid><description>In this day and age, everyone is trying to save money. Your monthly telecom costs are a great place to start. Telecom expenses are often high and confusing, so it’s a good idea to take a close look at your bills and see if you can find ways to reduce costs or find a better deal. Keep in mind that pricing can vary significantly depending on your location.
We often assume that the cost of goods and services is relatively consistent regardless of location.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker.</description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively.</description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations.</description></item><item><title>5x5 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</guid><description>Businesses often want greater internet bandwidth, lower telecommunication costs, or both. A relatively new service called 5x5 Ethernet might be the solution.
Ethernet services are a recent development. Before their rise in popularity, the best bandwidth options were T1 lines and fractional DS3 bandwidth. Fixed location wireless service has sometimes been available, but only for locations with a direct line of sight to their provider.
How do Ethernet services improve upon previous options?</description></item><item><title>T1 Bonding Buys Breathing Room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</guid><description>Businesses often face the challenge of needing more resources, like network bandwidth, without the budget to acquire them. This is particularly true for WAN bandwidth. Companies often start with a modest plan, assuming they can upgrade when demand (and revenue) increase. However, in times of economic uncertainty, business activity might grow while revenue lags. So how can businesses meet their needs without overspending?
One solution is incrementalism, specifically &amp;ldquo;just in time&amp;rdquo; incrementalism.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses.</description></item><item><title>Can You Believe 200 Mbps EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a widely used technology that delivers mid-band Ethernet connections without the delays and costs of fiber optic installation. Although initially considered a temporary solution, EoC has become a strong competitor to fiber services.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/)Businesses currently using T1 lines or considering them are a key market for EoC. T1 is a well-established, dependable, and cost-effective telecom service that offers 1.5 Mbps using one or two pairs of twisted copper telephone wiring.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations.</description></item><item><title>T1 or Better Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 01:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-or-better-internet-service/</guid><description>Are you frustrated with your business-grade DSL or Cable broadband despite opting for a supposedly higher-tier plan? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why that might be happening and delve into alternative business broadband solutions for superior performance.
DSL and Cable Internet services are not inherently flawed. Millions of users are content with their performance, especially considering the affordability factor. However, this is where the issue arises. Businesses are enticed by the cost-effectiveness of these options but are often let down by the lack of robust, telecom-grade performance.</description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</guid><description>Traditional business bandwidth solutions, typically offering low to moderate speeds, have long relied on T1 lines and their bonded counterparts. However, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) solutions are rapidly replacing these older technologies, delivering enhanced bandwidth at a lower cost.
We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on services ranging from 1 to 20 Mbps, encompassing both dedicated point-to-point private lines and dedicated internet connections. Ethernet standards also enable private LAN services, facilitating connections between multiple business locations.</description></item></channel></rss>