<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metropolitan Area Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metropolitan-area-network/</link><description>Recent content in Metropolitan Area Network on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metropolitan-area-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>600 Mbps Ethernet vs OC12 SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</guid><description>Companies that need bandwidth in the fractional Gigabit range have often relied on OC12 SONET fiber optic service. While it remains a solid high-speed choice, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering 600 Mbps Ethernet as well. Comparing these two options might yield some surprising results.
OC-12 (622 Mbps) is the next tier up from OC-3 (155 Mbps) in the SONET optical carrier hierarchy. This service is widely available in Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and as a dedicated internet access connection for mid-sized internet service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>