<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Service Providers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service-providers/</link><description>Recent content in Internet Service Providers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-service-providers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Exchange Email Service Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</guid><description>POP3 email, while widely used by both businesses and individuals, has limitations that might make you reconsider your email service. While convenient, its client-server model, where emails are downloaded to your device, poses risks such as data loss and limited accessibility.
What exactly is POP3? It stands for Post Office Protocol, an internet standard for retrieving emails from a server to a client, like Microsoft Outlook or Mac Mail, installed on your computer.</description></item><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2.</description></item><item><title>Are We Finally Out of IPv4 Addresses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-we-finally-out-of-ipv4-addresses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-we-finally-out-of-ipv4-addresses/</guid><description>For years, experts have predicted a looming internet crisis that has been largely dismissed. The internet, exceeding its initial scope, is pushing against its technological limits, threatening a system crash if not addressed. This crisis point now appears to be 2010.
ARIN, the organization responsible for distributing internet addresses, has issued a warning to Internet Service Providers: we&amp;rsquo;re running out of IPv4 addresses. These addresses, the foundation of the internet, are 32-bit identifiers for every device connected online.</description></item><item><title>Biggest Cisco Router Yet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biggest-cisco-router-yet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biggest-cisco-router-yet/</guid><description>The launch of Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest and most powerful routing platform, the CRS-3 Carrier Routing System, confirms that the information age is in full swing. This system is a significant improvement over its predecessor, the CRS-1, which is widely used as a core router for internet traffic and data centers.
The CRS-3&amp;rsquo;s impressive 322 Terabits per second throughput is noteworthy, but equally important is Cisco&amp;rsquo;s acknowledgment of the changing nature of internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options.</description></item><item><title>Apartment Manager's Little Money Maker</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apartment-managers-little-money-maker/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apartment-managers-little-money-maker/</guid><description>Even though real estate prices are declining, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance to make more money from your current tenants and even bring in new ones. It&amp;rsquo;s something they need and are already paying for, but would be happy to get from you at a lower price. This opportunity is providing broadband internet service.
You might wonder how apartment managers can become internet providers. The reality is that, regardless of the size of your building, your tenants are spending a significant amount on internet services.</description></item></channel></rss>