<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virus/</link><description>Recent content in Virus on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft.</description></item><item><title>WHO dismisses the likelihood of a worldwide Ebola outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</guid><description>On August 11th, the World Health Organization (WHO) released a statement regarding the Ebola virus disease (EVD) outbreak in West Africa. They emphasized that nations with strong health systems are unlikely to experience an epidemic. This is due to the way the virus spreads and past experiences with outbreaks.
The WHO also noted that while fear has led to increased global vigilance and suspicion of the virus, this heightened awareness makes it more likely that cases will be detected and managed quickly, thus limiting further transmission.</description></item></channel></rss>