<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wavelengths on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelengths/</link><description>Recent content in Wavelengths on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wavelengths/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Choosing Dark Fiber vs Lit Fiber Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</guid><description>When applications require the bandwidth of fiber optic transmission, businesses face a choice: use existing &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; fiber services or establish their own transport services using purchased or leased &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; fiber.
Deciding between these options involves weighing performance, cost, and installation time. Focusing solely on cost can lead to extended installation delays, potentially impacting operational needs. While a cost-effective solution might be suitable with ample planning time, immediate bandwidth demands may necessitate prioritizing availability over cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-dark-fiber-vs-lit-fiber-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting in Clouds and Colos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</guid><description>There are many hosting choices available. Shared hosting is popular among individuals and small businesses due to its affordability and acceptable performance. However, as your needs grow, you face a decision: self-hosting or a managed solution.
While setting up a website previously required technical expertise in server management, Linux and Windows hosting have become increasingly user-friendly and widely accessible. Even large enterprises accustomed to managing their servers in-house are reconsidering colocation and cloud solutions, driven by cost and resource optimization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>