<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Competitiveness on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competitiveness/</link><description>Recent content in Competitiveness on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competitiveness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranks second in global competitiveness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</guid><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) recently published its Global Competitiveness Report for 2016.
The report determined that a global trend of decreasing openness in countries is negatively impacting growth and prosperity. Financial stimuli like quantitative easing are insufficient for sustained growth and must be paired with reforms that bolster competitiveness. For emerging markets, modernizing business practices and investing in innovation are now just as crucial as infrastructure, skilled workforces, and efficient markets.</description></item></channel></rss>