<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SilkAir on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/silkair/</link><description>Recent content in SilkAir on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/silkair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SilkAir will begin flying between Okinawa and Japan in January 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will launch its inaugural charter flights between Singapore and Okinawa, Japan.
Operated in partnership with Okinawa Tourist Service (OTS) and Jumbo Tours Okinawa, these monthly charters will run from September 9, 2014, to January 3, 2015. Utilizing Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both business and economy class seating, these direct flights aim to provide travelers with a convenient option to visit Okinawa.
From September to October 2014, flights will depart Singapore Changi Airport Terminal 2 at 10:00 am and arrive at Okinawa Naha Airport at 4:15 pm.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will enhance Singapore Airlines' offerings to Male</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</guid><description>Source: SilkAir. Male.
Starting October 25, 2015, SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will introduce four weekly flights to Male, Maldives. Previously, Singapore Airlines operated between 10 and 14 flights per week to Male. With the addition of SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s new flights, the two airlines will jointly offer two daily round trips, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, highlighted the benefits of this collaboration: “By coordinating the networks of both carriers, we can provide our customers with more choices and flexibility when planning their travel.</description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir introduces a new daily flight from Singapore to Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</guid><description>Starting December 12, 2014, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines, will introduce a daily flight service to Denpasar, Indonesia, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, stated, “The increase in flights demonstrates the Singapore Airlines Group&amp;rsquo;s dedication to expanding our service offerings and providing our customers with more choices and convenience. By connecting the networks of both airlines, we can improve connectivity options for our customers through our combined network, reaching 99 cities across 35 countries.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir have reduced their fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir, its regional subsidiary, have reduced their fuel surcharges due to decreasing fuel prices.
These new surcharge amounts apply to flights from both airlines and range from US$5 to US$83 lower per one-way trip, depending on the flight distance and class of travel.
Route Surcharge in US$* First Class, Suites Between Singapore and South East Asian gateways[1] 50 Between Singapore and Europe/South Africa[2] 175 Between Singapore and Americas 235 Between Europe and Australia/New Zealand[3] 265 All other flights[4] 131 * Figures in US Dollars, converted into currency of sale at time of ticketing</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will provide direct charter flights to Okinawa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-provide-direct-charter-flights-to-okinawa/</guid><description>To encourage travel between Singapore and Okinawa, SilkAir, the Okinawa Prefecture government, Japan, and Changi Airport Group are collaborating on seven direct SilkAir charter flights. These flights will operate between June 1st and 25th, 2016, connecting Singapore and Okinawa, Japan&amp;rsquo;s southernmost prefecture.
Travelers can book these full-service flights through Singapore travel agents. SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s Boeing 737-800 aircraft, featuring Business and Economy class cabins, will service the route. Passengers will enjoy a comprehensive range of full-service offerings, including a baggage allowance of 30kg for Economy and 40kg for Business class, inflight meals, and complimentary inflight entertainment through SilkAir Studio.</description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin.</description></item></channel></rss>