<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real/</link><description>Recent content in Real on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:25:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JLL reports that tech startups are a significant driver of real estate demand in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>New types of office users are emerging in the form of startups, with more tech companies exploring unconventional spaces such as coworking facilities and industrial properties, according to JLL, a real estate and investment management firm.
The technology sector in the Asia Pacific region has experienced significant growth, driven by mobile technology, e-commerce, and the rise of fintech. This growth has fueled demand for both traditional office spaces and business parks.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place.</description></item></channel></rss>