<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu/</link><description>Recent content in EU on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B.</description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable.</description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings.</description></item><item><title>Is Juncker capable of being a reformist Commission President, like Nixon was in going to China?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A common saying in American politics, &amp;ldquo;only Nixon could go to China,&amp;rdquo; suggests that only a politician with a well-established reputation can persuade their base to accept a major policy shift. Nixon, a staunch anti-Communist, was able to convince American conservatives that engaging with Communist China was in their best interest. This principle might apply to the European Union as well. The recent European Parliament (EP) elections saw a rise in support for anti-EU parties in several Member States.</description></item><item><title>Better Network Connectivity Into France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</guid><description>Globalization is increasingly common, and even companies without a multinational presence often conduct business internationally. The European Union, with its vast pool of consumers and producers, is a significant market, and France stands out as a key destination within the EU.
Level 3 Communications, a major telecommunications provider, recently enhanced its resources, infrastructure, and services for French enterprise customers. The company expanded its network reach with additional Points of Presence (POPs) in Paris and its surrounding areas, along with core network extensions in Lille, Lyon, and Toulouse.</description></item></channel></rss>