<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Usage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usage/</link><description>Recent content in Usage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/usage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase.</description></item><item><title>The guidelines for using YouTube have been published by the UAE's Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-guidelines-for-using-youtube-have-been-published-by-the-uae-s-telecommunications-regulatory-authority-tra/</guid><description>The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) of the UAE has introduced guidelines for using YouTube as part of its UAE Social Media White Papers series.
The TRA highlights the immense popularity of YouTube, with over a billion unique monthly users and over 100 hours of video uploaded every minute. They emphasize that UAE law forbids publishing content that violates public morals, Islamic principles, and the social and moral well-being of the UAE.</description></item></channel></rss>