<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OC3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc3/</link><description>Recent content in OC3 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Offers Synchronous Service Transport For Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>Need to move massive amounts of data quickly and reliably? Within a building or campus, fiber optic cables provide sufficient speed and capacity. However, for longer distances, you need robust carrier services. Quest&amp;rsquo;s Synchronous Service Transport (SST) offers a solution.
SST utilizes fiber optics and SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) to provide high-speed, point-to-point data transfer. SONET, a dependable carrier service based on Time Division Multiplexing (TDM), was initially designed for telephone companies and later adopted by large organizations requiring extensive bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Diverse Connections For Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</guid><description>The reliability of data connections is crucial for data centers and colocation facilities to ensure service availability. Having multiple separate network connections is not enough; you need multiple diverse data connections from different providers that take different routes to your facility.
Simply having multiple connections from a single provider offers limited protection because a catastrophic failure could take down the entire connection. This risk is amplified in your own facility, where a single connection runs for miles and is vulnerable to disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>When your business or applications need more bandwidth than T1 lines can offer, even multiple bonded ones, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider fiber optic solutions. But with various options available, how do you choose?
Traditionally, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was the primary fiber optic bandwidth option, pioneered by phone companies. SONET surpasses T-Carrier technology (T1 and T3 lines). While T1 provides 1.5 Mbps over copper and T3 offers 45 Mbps over coaxial cable, SONET scales up to OC-1, OC-3, OC-12, OC-24, OC-48, OC-192, OC-256, and OC-768...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over DS3 Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber are becoming increasingly popular choices for WAN connections. This popularity is driven by competitive pricing and the availability of services like layer 2 switching with direct Ethernet connections. So why would you consider Ethernet over DS3?
It may seem like an unusual combination. DS3, a widely available telecom service, provides 45 Mbps using TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) technology from the T-Carrier standard. Organizations typically use DS3 for dedicated point-to-point connections, high-bandwidth internet access, and high-volume phone lines in contact and call centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DS1 DS3 Relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</guid><description>The terms DS1 and DS3 are frequently used in business telecommunications networking. DS, which stands for Digital Signal level, indicates the capacity of a digital line within the T-carrier system. Essentially, DS1 is associated with T1 service, while DS3 corresponds with T3.
The origins of the T-carrier system can be traced back to the 1950s when Bell Labs recognized the benefits of transitioning from an entirely analog telephone system to digital connections between telephone company offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>