<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Animal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/animal/</link><description>Recent content in Animal on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:36:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/animal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals video predictions for each Chinese zodiac animal for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 08:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-video-predictions-for-each-chinese-zodiac-animal-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Joey Yap, founder and CEO of the Mastery Academy of Chinese Metaphysics and Chief Consultant of the Joey Yap Consulting Group, created 12 videos outlining the year ahead for the 12 Chinese zodiac animal signs in areas such as career, relationships, business, and health.
The videos are in English and include traditional Chinese subtitles.
The year of the fire rooster starts on January 28, 2017. Yap considers the rooster one of the luckiest animals in 2017.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals, a brand that is committed to being cruelty-free, has launched a new range of eyeshadows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</guid><description>Everyday Minerals (EM) prioritizes using the purest natural ingredients to create all-natural, vegan, and cruelty-free makeup. Their products are handmade in Texas and packaged in eco-friendly, recyclable materials.
Source: Everyday Minerals blog.
Vegan makeup is characterized by its exclusion of animal-derived ingredients and its non-reliance on animal testing. Ingredients like lanolin and collagen are examples of animal-derived components. A growing number of cosmetics companies are introducing vegan product lines or, like EM, adopting a fully vegan approach.</description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces new Stan Smith designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</guid><description>This summer, the Stan Smith shoe gets a bold update with the Wrapped Animal Pack. Available in three color combinations, the pack keeps the Stan Smith&amp;rsquo;s famous shape while incorporating textured snake, alligator, and crocodile leather around the outsole.
Source: adidas.
Complementary heel tab accents in green, red, and black add a fashionable touch to this classic preppy sneaker. The Adidas Originals Stan Smith, originally a tennis shoe, has become a timeless classic thanks to its all-leather design and simple aesthetic.</description></item></channel></rss>