<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Freemium on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freemium/</link><description>Recent content in Freemium on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freemium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions.</description></item><item><title>CA Technologies reports that CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has been successful in its first 100 days</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</guid><description>CA Technologies, a provider of IT management solutions for securing and managing complex IT environments, has released a new version of its freemium product, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap. This solution helps businesses support agile business services.
Since its release 100 days ago, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has seen 5,000 downloads from SMBs, Fortune 1000 companies, and IT service providers across 147 countries. The full-featured version of CA Nimsoft Monitor shares the same codebase and proactively monitors servers, networks, storage, databases, and applications.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item><item><title>The free WooCommerce WordPress plugin has reached 4 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</guid><description>WooThemes, a developer of WordPress themes, plugins, and shopping cart features, announced that its WooCommerce WordPress plugin has been downloaded over 4 million times. WooCommerce is WooThemes&amp;rsquo; free flagship product, officially partnered with companies like Amazon, Mastercard, and PayPal.
Source: WooThemes website.
WooCommerce enables businesses to operate e-commerce sites using WordPress as their content management system.
WooThemes uses a freemium model. The basic plugin and some add-ons are free, while more advanced extensions and themes require payment.</description></item></channel></rss>