<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Business Broadband on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components.</description></item><item><title>Telnes Broadband for T1 Dedicated Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 23:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telnes-broadband-for-t1-dedicated-internet/</guid><description>Reliable, always-on internet connectivity has transitioned from a convenient business tool to a necessity. Companies of all types rely on consistent bandwidth for communication with customers, suppliers, and even phone services. Dedicated connections, like T1 data lines, offer the highest reliability with guaranteed uptime.
Telnes Broadband is an Internet Service Provider (ISP) catering specifically to businesses and government entities, constituting over 99% of their clientele. Their reputation for dependable WAN connections, especially for businesses with multiple locations, has made them a popular choice.</description></item><item><title>Covad Offers A Nationwide MPLS VPN Network For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</guid><description>Companies with numerous offices across the country have access to a new secure networking solution. Covad&amp;rsquo;s recently launched Intelligent Network Platform offers expanded WAN networking capabilities at a lower cost than traditional options.
Covad&amp;rsquo;s MPLS VPNs are designed for small to medium-sized businesses and larger dispersed companies needing to connect multiple locations, such as franchises, remote offices, warehouses, retail stores, factories, and hotels. Multi-location networking presents two key challenges: establishing secure and reliable connections between all sites and doing so cost-effectively.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:</description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3.</description></item><item><title>A Myriad of Business Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-myriad-of-business-broadband-options/</guid><description>There are many choices for business broadband internet, even beyond options like DSL, 3G and 4G Wireless, Cable, Satellite, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper. These choices depend on if your business is small, medium, or large. However, no matter what they are physically made of (wireless, copper, coaxial cable, or fiber optic), they all boil down to two types: dedicated or shared broadband connections.
Shared bandwidth options, like DSL, Cable, 3G &amp;amp; 4G Wireless and Satellite, are typically the cheapest.</description></item><item><title>HughesNet Special Deals on Satellite Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 19:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hughesnet-special-deals-on-satellite-broadband/</guid><description>Living remotely doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to be disconnected. Just like you get your TV via satellite, you can get internet access the same way. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a specialized dish that transmits and receives data, connect it to your power source and computer, and you&amp;rsquo;re online!
HughesNet is one provider catering to both homes and businesses. Plans start at $59.99 per month, with download speeds up to 700 Kbps and upload speeds up to 128 Kbps, similar to many DSL or cellular broadband services.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Obsolete?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-obsolete/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you been relying on a T1 line for a long time? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable, given their long history. When the Internet was new, a T1 line provided businesses with a dependable, high-bandwidth connection that made dial-up modems seem incredibly slow. These days, similar bandwidth options are available at comparable prices, making those old T1 lines appear slow in comparison. So, are T1 lines still a viable business solution, or are they outdated?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 19:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-for-your-business/</guid><description>Businesses can now benefit from a new, cost-effective broadband connection service: Ethernet Internet. To learn more about this exciting development, watch my concise YouTube presentation here: Ethernet Internet business presentation.
As the presentation highlights, Ethernet Internet offers a rare combination of affordability and superior performance. This cutting-edge technology is rapidly evolving and expanding beyond metropolitan areas. Soon, it will be accessible across the country, delivered wirelessly in rural regions and through copper or fiber optic connections in urban centers, with speeds reaching up to 10 Mbps or higher.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity For Multi-Business Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</guid><description>Instead of constructing their own offices, many businesses rent space in large buildings like office complexes, shopping centers, or strip malls. This shared situation offers a unique opportunity to secure better bandwidth at lower costs by joining forces with other tenants in the building.
There are a few approaches to leverage the collective bandwidth requirements of multiple businesses. One method is for the building owner to become an ISP, providing bandwidth to all tenants.</description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time.</description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs.</description></item><item><title>Improve Cloud Performance With Direct Network Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many companies are experiencing buyer&amp;rsquo;s remorse after transitioning to the cloud. They expected cost savings, increased performance, and limitless resources, but instead, they&amp;rsquo;re facing performance issues. The problem likely isn&amp;rsquo;t the cloud service itself, but the connection used to access it.
While your current internet connection might be sufficient for tasks like file transfers and email, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for real-time applications like VoIP, video conferencing, or cloud-based software.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Curb and Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Copper is quickly disappearing from telecommunications networks, being replaced by fiber optic cabling. While this new cabling might be installed in the same spaces as the old copper, the outdated copper lines are often left behind.
You might be thinking, &amp;ldquo;But I still use copper connections!&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s true that many devices use copper wiring. So where exactly is all this fiber?
Mostly Fiber Outside, Mostly Copper Inside</description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line With Instant Wireless Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</guid><description>Losing business broadband during a crucial moment can be incredibly frustrating. This is why many companies choose dedicated T1 lines instead of standard DSL or cable internet, despite the higher reliability of T1, they can still experience outages. Issues like equipment malfunctions or accidents can unexpectedly cut your connection.
To prevent downtime, some companies opt for diverse T1 service, ordering two lines from separate providers. However, this solution isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof, as both lines often use the same physical infrastructure owned by the Incumbent Local Exchange Carrier (ILEC).</description></item><item><title>Why You Need Dedicated Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume all high-speed internet connections are equal, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t true. Unfortunately, businesses may only discover this reality after missing out on sales and losing valuable customers.
While the core of the internet is quite reliable, with issues like packet loss, latency, and bandwidth rarely impacting crucial applications, the most significant difference between internet services lies in the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection – the link between your router and the provider.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls.</description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?</description></item><item><title>Types of Bandwidth for Wide Area Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) connect your business to the outside world, encompassing private networks across various locations. These connections, often called &amp;ldquo;long haul circuits&amp;rdquo;, form the foundation of wide area networking.
Connecting your local area network (LAN) to a WAN usually involves a router and a specialized interface corresponding to the WAN circuit type.
A common WAN connection is a T1 line, terminating at a &amp;ldquo;smart jack&amp;rdquo; in your telecom closet.</description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>The Importance Of Buying Ernest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 07:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-importance-of-buying-ernest/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous locations often struggle to manage their telecommunications across the board. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t a single, national provider that understands local needs be ideal? While that might seem contradictory, Ernest Communications offers precisely that solution.
Ernest specializes in serving businesses with widespread locations, such as chain stores, hotels, and restaurants, by providing phone lines, data connections, and wireless services. Essentially, any company with franchises, branches, or service centers across various regions fits their model.</description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough.</description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV.</description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Copper First, Then Fiber Bandwidth Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-first-then-fiber-bandwidth-solution/</guid><description>When your business needs a fast internet connection but fiber optic installation isn&amp;rsquo;t feasible yet, there&amp;rsquo;s a two-step solution that uses existing technology as a stopgap. This method combines the strengths of different connection types to get you online quickly and upgrade seamlessly later on.
Fiber optic connections, whether SONET or Ethernet, provide the highest bandwidth– starting from 50-100 Mbps and reaching up to 10 Gbps or even higher in some areas.</description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Fiber Optic WAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</guid><description>As your company grows, you might find that your internet connection, cloud services, and connections between offices are slowing down. It might be time to upgrade your bandwidth before things get sluggish. But what should you get? More of what you already have or something new?
Outdated Connections Are Holding You Back When your business was starting out, networking was mostly about connecting computers and printers in the same office, with a basic connection to the outside world.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs T1 in Under 3 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-t1-in-under-3-minutes/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Ethernet bandwidth services are generating a lot of interest, but are they truly superior to traditional T1 lines? Is switching from copper to fiber a wise decision financially? This brief comparison of Ethernet and T1 services will provide clarity.
Interested in determining which connectivity and hosted services best meet your business needs? Get instant pricing and availability for Ethernet, T1, and other connectivity options.</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Metro and Long Haul Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies with multiple locations and many employees may find that standard internet and private lines are insufficient for their needs. At a certain point, having complete control over your network becomes desirable, allowing you to establish performance benchmarks and implement upgrades as needed.
This sounds great, but how can you maintain the same level of control over a network that extends beyond your physical premises? Should you become your own network provider and install fiber optic cable to all your locations?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost.</description></item><item><title>Tips To Reduce Your Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses are facing a challenging time as they grapple with the fluctuating economic landscape brought on by the Covid-19 crisis. While growth was once the primary focus, survival has now taken center stage, making cost control paramount. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some immediate steps you can take to reduce expenses without jeopardizing operations.
Are You Paying For Unused Services?
It might seem improbable, but both individuals and businesses frequently pay for services they don&amp;rsquo;t utilize.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over DS3 Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-ds3-advantage/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper and Ethernet over Fiber are becoming increasingly popular choices for WAN connections. This popularity is driven by competitive pricing and the availability of services like layer 2 switching with direct Ethernet connections. So why would you consider Ethernet over DS3?
It may seem like an unusual combination. DS3, a widely available telecom service, provides 45 Mbps using TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) technology from the T-Carrier standard. Organizations typically use DS3 for dedicated point-to-point connections, high-bandwidth internet access, and high-volume phone lines in contact and call centers.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard about Metro Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity for business WAN connections, particularly in major cities with concentrated business areas. These areas have been the primary focus of competitive bandwidth providers offering lower per-Mbps pricing. However, you might assume that Ethernet WAN services are only accessible in downtown areas or large suburbs.
This is about to change. Hatteras Networks has introduced a line of repeater and line power modules that extend Mid-Band Ethernet service up to 25 miles over standard telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>SDN Performance Takes a Leaf of Faith</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cloud computing has highlighted the importance of reliable internet connections, known as WANs (Wide Area Networks). In the past, slow file transfers or unreliable internet were acceptable because crucial tasks were handled within the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network. However, now that businesses rely on cloud services, the performance of the WAN is just as crucial as the internal network (LAN).
WAN Challenges
The main challenge with WANs is that businesses don&amp;rsquo;t control them like they do their internal networks.</description></item><item><title>Competitive Fiber Optic Service Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</guid><description>Does your company use a lot of bandwidth? We&amp;rsquo;re talking 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps or more of reliable, commercial-grade bandwidth. If so, bonded T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. You need fiber optic service. But is competitive fiber optic bandwidth an option in your area? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out&amp;hellip;
The reality is that buildings equipped for fiber optic service are appearing faster than ever. Why? Because today&amp;rsquo;s data-heavy applications need increasingly faster network speeds.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Copper 50 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 06:35:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-copper-50-mbps/</guid><description>Businesses that need to connect numerous employees to the internet or move large files, particularly high-resolution images, require more bandwidth than a standard connection provides. Traditionally, they&amp;rsquo;ve upgraded their T1 lines to DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. Now, there are more choices for around 50 Mbps using both copper and fiber optic connections.
DS3 is often considered a copper wireline service because it connects with coaxial cables and uses BNC connectors.</description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service.</description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area.</description></item></channel></rss>