<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Monitoring on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Network Monitoring on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>