<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Greece on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greece/</link><description>Recent content in Greece on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greece/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to suspend Schengen due to Greece? Is it necessary to do so?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 18:22:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</guid><description>A recent leak of a Council document proposes a potential suspension of the Schengen system for a duration of up to two years. This proposal stems from what are being termed &amp;ldquo;systemic deficiencies&amp;rdquo; in Greece&amp;rsquo;s management of its external borders, particularly concerning the influx of refugees and migrants. Such a suspension would provide any Schengen country the option to reinstate or implement border controls along their shared internal borders. While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely that every Schengen country would exercise this option, it&amp;rsquo;s anticipated that several would choose to do so, especially given that a number already have active border controls in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-suspend-schengen-due-to-greece-is-it-necessary-to-do-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice is deciding whether monks can be prohibited from practicing law, posing the question, "Can a man serve two masters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:08:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</guid><description>Rebecca Zahn, Senior Lecturer in Law, University of Strathclyde
Lawyers in the European Union hold a distinctive position. They ensure access to justice, manage its administration, and uphold the rule of law within their Member States. Similar to other professions like medicine or architecture, national bodies strictly regulate entry. However, legal practice is inherently location-specific, unlike other professions. A lawyer&amp;rsquo;s knowledge base is tied to the jurisdiction where they were trained and qualified...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-is-deciding-whether-monks-can-be-prohibited-from-practicing-law-posing-the-question-can-a-man-serve-two-masters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Citizens' Initiative and Greek debt: A surprising pairing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</guid><description>Anastasia Karatzia, Law Lecturer, University of Essex
Introduction
Decisions from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on the European and Monetary Union (EMU) are infrequent. Recent cases on this topic, including landmark judgments like Pringle and Gauweiler, have addressed measures enacted during the Eurozone crisis. Among these decisions is Anagnostakis v Commission, a case challenging the Commission&amp;rsquo;s refusal to register a proposed European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI) titled &amp;ldquo;One million signatures for solidarity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-greek-debt-a-surprising-pairing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AGET Iraklis Case: Balancing Economic Freedoms and Labour Rights - Can Governments Regulate Mass Layoffs by Employers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis
DPhil Candidate, University of Oxford; Researcher, Erasmus University of Rotterdam.
The AGET Iraklis case, despite its legal and political importance, has not received adequate attention from scholars or the public. Overshadowed by events like the UK referendum on EU membership and significant court rulings on data retention and trade agreements, the Grand Chamber judgment in this case, delivered on December 21, 2016, highlights the complex interplay between fundamental economic freedoms and collective labor rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aget-iraklis-case-balancing-economic-freedoms-and-labour-rights-can-governments-regulate-mass-layoffs-by-employers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What are the legal implications of leaving the economic and monetary union according to EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 08:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Greece&amp;rsquo;s upcoming referendum on accepting its creditors&amp;rsquo; offer brings uncertainty. It&amp;rsquo;s unclear if rejecting the offer means Greece automatically leaves the EU or EMU, or defaults on its debt. Accepting the offer doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide clarity either, as negotiations were ongoing during the referendum announcement, potentially making the offer outdated.
Given the range of possibilities, examining the legal framework for departing economic and monetary union (EMU) is crucial. A key question is whether Greece must leave the EU if it exits the single currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-legal-implications-of-leaving-the-economic-and-monetary-union-according-to-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What lies ahead for Greece and the Eurozone: catharsis or catastrophe?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent victory of the anti-austerity party Syriza in the Greek elections raises questions about its potential effects on the EU&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union. Syriza&amp;rsquo;s objective is not to withdraw from the EU or the single currency but to renegotiate Greece&amp;rsquo;s debt and austerity measures. Their goal is to secure debt forgiveness and renegotiate terms, including the removal of austerity demands associated with previous bailouts.
However, this program might encounter legal obstacles due to limitations on debt forgiveness and ending austerity outlined in EU Treaties and Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Greece to be expelled from the eurozone? How will the ECB's actions in limiting funding options for Greece impact Target2?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</guid><description>Ioannis Glinavos (@iGlinavos), Senior Lecturer, University of Westminster https://iglinavos.wordpress.com/
The European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) actions regarding Greece, particularly since Syriza&amp;rsquo;s political victory, have drawn considerable criticism. This piece examines the gradual tightening of Greece&amp;rsquo;s financial situation within the framework of ECB regulations and considers potential outcomes if a resolution for Greece&amp;rsquo;s urgent funding requirements isn&amp;rsquo;t reached by June 2015.
ECB Halts Greek Government Bonds as Collateral
Since accepting its initial bailout in 2010, Greece has largely been unable to secure funding from markets except through domestic T-Bill issuances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-greece-to-be-expelled-from-the-eurozone-how-will-the-ecb-s-actions-in-limiting-funding-options-for-greece-impact-target2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is this the start of the Euro's downfall? EU regulations on exiting EMU or defaulting on debts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The stability of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) is once again in question after a period of relative calm. This follows the announcement of early elections in Greece. Should the anti-austerity party, Syriza, gain control of the government, the consequences could be significant.
It is crucial to note that such an outcome is not guaranteed. Syriza holds a small lead in the polls, and even if they become the leading party, they might not secure enough seats to hold a majority...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-start-of-the-euro-s-downfall-eu-regulations-on-exiting-emu-or-defaulting-on-debts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The program in the European Union that allows Syrian refugees in Turkey to seek humanitarian admission.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</guid><description>Laura Robbins-Wright
PhD Candidate in Government, London School of Economics and Political Science
On December 15, 2015, the European Commission put forward a suggestion for a program to offer humanitarian entry to Syrian refugees residing in Turkey. This proposal follows earlier EU initiatives, including a plan to relocate refugees within the EU and a program for resettling refugees from other countries. It also builds upon an action plan from October 2015 and a more recent decision to give €3 billion to a Refugee Facility designed to better coordinate aid for Syrian refugees in Turkey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Urgent Information Needed on 'Hotspots' for Asylum Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 14:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</guid><description>Frances Webber, a lawyer, journalist, and lecturer, holds significant roles as the vice chair of the Institute of Race Relations and as co-editor for prominent legal publications. She is also the author of &amp;ldquo;Borderline Justice: the fight for refugee and migrant rights&amp;rdquo;.
The European Union (EU) aims to control refugee flows through its new system for relocating refugees from Italy and Greece. This system includes a strict screening process at entry points, seemingly designed to separate a small number of &amp;ldquo;deserving&amp;rdquo; refugees from those deemed &amp;ldquo;undeserving&amp;rdquo; economic migrants, who the EU seeks to deport quickly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/urgent-information-needed-on-hotspots-for-asylum-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can a temporary Grexit be legally feasible? EMU like the Hotel California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 19:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/</guid><description>Steve Peers
News sources report that during the recent Eurogroup meeting about a potential new bailout plan for Greece, the German government was privately proposing a plan for a temporary Greek exit from the eurozone (&amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo;). Putting aside any political or economic arguments, the most pressing question is whether this is even legally feasible. The short answer: It&amp;rsquo;s not.
A temporary Grexit isn&amp;rsquo;t possible because a permanent one isn&amp;rsquo;t allowed under the current treaties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-temporary-grexit-be-legally-feasible-emu-like-the-hotel-california/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Assessing the Legal Implications of the EU/Turkey Refugee Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</guid><description>Steve Peers analyzes the legal and political implications of the recent EU-Turkey agreement on refugees. The agreement, while legally controversial, aims to address the refugee crisis and restore order.
A key point of contention is the return of migrants arriving in Greece to Turkey. While the agreement states this will be done in accordance with international law, returning all migrants without considering individual circumstances raises concerns about collective expulsion, a violation of EU and international law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging the legality of ECB restrictions on Greek bank accounts – and ways you can support the cause</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many citizens across the EU have observed the plight of Greeks limited to €60 withdrawals per day with sympathy and apprehension. This situation stems from the European Central Bank (ECB) restricting emergency funds for Greek banks.
Beyond the human cost, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s actions raise serious legal, political, and economic concerns. A core function of any central bank is acting as a last-resort lender for banks, a role the ECB is demonstrably failing to fulfill in this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>