<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SG50 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sg50/</link><description>Recent content in SG50 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:02:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sg50/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beads Actually is introducing a special merlion bead in celebration of SG50, available for a limited time only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 11:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beads-actually-is-introducing-a-special-merlion-bead-in-celebration-of-sg50-available-for-a-limited-time-only/</guid><description>The Singaporean store Beads Actually is offering pre-orders for a merlion bead from OHM Beads. The merlion, a creature with a lion&amp;rsquo;s head and a fish&amp;rsquo;s body and tail, is a well-known symbol of Singapore.
Only two hundred of these beads are available, exclusively through Beads Actually from July 2nd to July 31st. Following this period, it will be available for individual purchase globally.
The bead, priced at S$110, is included in a starter kit featuring either a plain bangle or a snap-clasp bracelet.</description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued.</description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts.</description></item></channel></rss>