<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Light on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/light/</link><description>Recent content in Light on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/light/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Experience personalized lighting effects with Philips Hue Play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 03:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-personalized-lighting-effects-with-philips-hue-play/</guid><description>Source: Signify. Philips Hue Play light effects now available in Singapore.
Signify, a company specializing in lighting solutions, has introduced the Philips Hue Play to the Singapore market. This compact light bar is designed to create an immersive atmosphere with its adaptable placement options.
The Philips Hue Play can function independently as an indirect light source, serving as backlighting or accent lighting.
Using Philips Hue Sync, a software available for both PC and Mac computers, users can synchronize the Hue Play with on-screen content, such as movies, video games, or music.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Repair of an Intermittent Sensor Arm Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously restored in May 2022, recently came back to my workshop due to a malfunctioning sensor arm LED. This was concerning because I had implemented a redesigned LED assembly for this particular unit.
To my relief, the LED functioned correctly when I powered up the turntable in my workshop. This suggested an intermittent problem that resolved itself during transport.
I tried manipulating the plugs and cables, but the LED remained illuminated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a small, portable printer for mobile use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 19:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-small-portable-printer-for-mobile-use/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WF-100 is designed for professionals on-the-go.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has introduced the Epson WorkForce WF-100. This printer is one of the smallest and lightest mobile printers globally. Its compact design caters to professionals who are frequently on the move. It features a built-in battery that can be recharged via USB and integrated wireless capabilities for easy printing while traveling.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Speed Indictor Light Bulbs with RGB LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</guid><description>During the wait for a 3D-printed part for a Beogram 4002 turntable restoration, the author decided to upgrade its speed indicator lights. Using a method from a previous video, they replaced the incandescent bulbs with RGB LEDs for a more authentic look.
The original setup with incandescent bulbs was documented before the upgrade.
The new setup utilizes both the red and green diodes of an RGB LED for a natural appearance, addressing the issue of amber LEDs failing to illuminate red scale markers properly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustment of the Tonearm Height and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 11:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustment-of-the-tonearm-height-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and with the major tasks complete, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the finer points. One detail that caught my eye was the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s resting position, which was noticeably higher than the sensor arm when lifted.
[Image]
Although this doesn&amp;rsquo;t impact sound quality, it was aesthetically displeasing. After consulting the manual, which recommended aligning the tonearm height with the sensor arm, I made the adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Arrival from Italy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 20:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-arrival-from-italy/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be working on another Beogram 4000 restoration. The unit arrived from overseas in just three days and was packaged very well, ensuring its safe arrival.
The exterior looks good overall. The wood veneer is undamaged and the dust cover can be polished back to its original shine.
The aluminum trim on the back of the dust cover needs to be reattached, which should be a simple fix. Inside, the aluminum plates need a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Test Drive with Herbie Hancock (Secrets)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 07:21:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-test-drive-with-herbie-hancock-secrets-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to share that I just got my hands on a nearly perfect copy of Herbie Hancock&amp;rsquo;s 1976 album &amp;ldquo;Secrets.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s in such great condition, it practically looks untouched! This album holds a special place in my heart, especially the track &amp;ldquo;People Music&amp;rdquo; with its captivating atmospheric interludes and those classic 70s analog synthesizer sounds, likely created on a &amp;ldquo;Maestro Universal Synthesizer System.&amp;rdquo;
To celebrate, I decided to listen to the record on my newly restored Beogram 4002(5513) turntable, which is temporarily hooked up to my Beomaster 6000 4-Channel receiver for testing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulb of the Tracking Sensor with a Drop-In LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 11:06:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulb-of-the-tracking-sensor-with-a-drop-in-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 400x turntable, it&amp;rsquo;s common to replace the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s incandescent bulb with a more durable LED assembly. A drop-in replacement for the Beogram 4002 and 4004 models has been created and documented, while the Beogram 4000 version incorporates a Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen-specified intensity trimmer for fine-tuning the tracking feedback system&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity.
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to recalibrate the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s position after any light source replacement to maintain accurate tracking sensitivity.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering.</description></item></channel></rss>