<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Credit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/credit/</link><description>Recent content in Credit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/credit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>DebtorsWatch compiles data on delinquent payments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</guid><description>DebtorsWatch is the first online platform in India designed for reporting trade defaults. The interactive website allows businesses to report overdue payments and defaults, conduct credit checks, and monitor customer creditworthiness. Registered members can also utilize the data for due diligence.
Deepanjan Periwal, Chartered Accountant and founder of DebtorsWatch, highlights the lack of transparency in India&amp;rsquo;s credit system compared to countries like the US, UK, and Australia, where credit tracking is standard practice.</description></item><item><title>Al Rajhi's initiative to promote card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</guid><description>Al Rajhi Bank has introduced its &amp;ldquo;House, Car and Salary&amp;rdquo; campaign, offering over SR4 million in prizes to encourage the use of its Mada and credit cards within Saudi Arabia and internationally.
The grand prize, exclusively for Saudi citizens, includes a house, a BMW 7 Series car, and a year of monthly SR20,000 payments. Four additional winners will receive a BMW 7 Series car each, while seven others will get a year of monthly SR20,000 payments.</description></item><item><title>Credit card applications can now be approved instantly by DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 11:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-card-applications-can-now-be-approved-instantly-by-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank in Singapore has introduced a new online application service using the national platform, MyInfo. This service allows new and existing customers to apply for credit cards and open DBS Cashline accounts with instant approval and access to funds, making it a first in Singapore.
Available to 3.3 million SingPass holders, this service, accessible through DBS/POSB Internet banking and websites, simplifies the application process. Typically, new customers wait up to a week for credit card or DBS Cashline access, but using MyInfo eliminates the need for traditional applications and physical documents, providing real-time approval.</description></item><item><title>Business Intelligence Information System for sharing insights on businesses in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-intelligence-information-system-for-sharing-insights-on-businesses-in-dubai/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced the Business Intelligence Information System (BIIS), a new digital platform designed to revolutionize how business information is accessed and utilized.
This initiative aligns with the UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, HH Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum&amp;rsquo;s vision of transforming Dubai into a smart city. BIIS provides a centralized hub for users to obtain crucial information about local and international businesses, empowering companies to identify potential partners and make well-informed decisions.</description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year.</description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave.</description></item><item><title>UOB creates profiles of the contemporary Singaporean woman and customizes card privileges to suit her needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-creates-profiles-of-the-contemporary-singaporean-woman-and-customizes-card-privileges-to-suit-her-needs/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) has introduced Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first profiles of the modern Singaporean woman, categorized by their behaviors and spending habits. The UOB Leading Ladies report identifies these women as digital natives, young professionals, and cosmopolitan leaders.
Jacquelyn Tan, UOB&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director and Regional Head of Cards and Payments, highlighted the report&amp;rsquo;s focus on the entrepreneurial spirit and spending trends of contemporary Singaporean women. She emphasized the significant contribution of women to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s GDP, exceeding 40%, and their dedication to both work and family.</description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions.</description></item><item><title>UOB introduces its inaugural credit card tailored for millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uob-introduces-its-inaugural-credit-card-tailored-for-millennials/</guid><description>A recent study by United Overseas Bank (UOB), the UOB Young Professionals Survey, has revealed that the spending habits of millennials are influenced by their desire for travel and sharing food experiences with loved ones. UOB aims to secure half of all millennials as customers within the next three years, recognizing their imminent rise as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s dominant consumer group.
UOB categorizes millennials as individuals between the ages of 26 and 35.</description></item><item><title>DED and DIB introduce a credit card with safeguards for consumer rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 12:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ded-and-dib-introduce-a-credit-card-with-safeguards-for-consumer-rights/</guid><description>Source: DED.
The Dubai Department of Economic Development (DED) and Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the UAE&amp;rsquo;s leading Islamic bank, have introduced the Consumer Card in the UAE. DIB currently serves a vast retail customer base exceeding 1.5 million people through its 90 branches nationwide.
This collaborative credit card prioritizes consumer protection and offers savings on everyday transactions. It reflects the DED&amp;rsquo;s commitment to partnering with the private sector and enhancing the shopping experience in Dubai and the wider UAE.</description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills.</description></item></channel></rss>