<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Safety on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/safety/</link><description>Recent content in Safety on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/safety/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bosch is advocating for an increase in the number of vehicles in Southeast Asia to be equipped with safety features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</guid><description> Road traffic deaths in ASEAN countries are estimated at 117,000 annually, with over half involving motorcycles.
 An increasing number of countries and territories, including Japan, Taiwan, and India, are making motorcycle antilock braking systems (ABS) mandatory for new motorcycles.
 Malaysia is the first and only ASEAN nation to require all new cars to have electronic stability control (ESC) as of 2018.
Bosch believes Southeast Asia can do more to enhance road safety.</description></item><item><title>ValueChampion warns that driving in Singapore is more perilous than you might realize</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</guid><description>While Singapore boasts one of the world&amp;rsquo;s lowest road fatality rates per person, ValueChampion suggests that driving in Singapore might be riskier than in other developed nations. Anastassia Evlanova, a Senior Research Analyst at ValueChampion Singapore, highlights in a recent blog post (which builds on research from 2017) that Singapore recorded 12.13 deaths per 100,000 vehicles in 2019, surpassing rates in Japan and Australia.
She explains, &amp;ldquo;Looking at road safety solely based on deaths per capita creates a deceptive view of driving safety in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time).</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization recommends restricting the use of personal audio devices to less than one hour per day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</guid><description>Source: WHO.
The World Health Organization (WHO) cautions that over a billion adolescents and young adults risk noise-induced hearing loss. This danger stems from unsafe listening practices with personal audio devices like smartphones and exposure to high sound levels at entertainment venues, including sporting events.
WHO analysis of data from developed and developing nations reveals that nearly half of teenagers and young adults aged 12-35 experience unsafe sound levels from personal audio devices.</description></item></channel></rss>