<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chatbot on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chatbot/</link><description>Recent content in Chatbot on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:05:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chatbot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tokio Marine Life Insurance Singapore enhances chatbot with recruitment features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 08:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/</guid><description>Source: TMLS website.
The TOMI avatar.
Tokio Marine Life Insurance Singapore (TMLS), the only Japanese life insurer in Singapore, has introduced a recruitment feature to its chatbot, TOMI (Tokio Marine Insurance).
This addition makes TOMI the first chatbot in Singapore to assist an insurer&amp;rsquo;s recruitment process, further enhancing its role as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first self-learning AI chatbot designed to increase public access to life insurance.
With the goal of engaging today&amp;rsquo;s tech-savvy generation in the recruitment process, TOMI is now equipped to answer over 300 questions about becoming a financial advisor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tokio-marine-life-insurance-singapore-enhances-chatbot-with-recruitment-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the surrounding areas of Hotel Indigo in the new Neighbourhood 15 campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</guid><description>Hotel Indigo&amp;rsquo;s new brand campaign, &amp;ldquo;Neighbourhood 15,&amp;rdquo; highlights the unique character of each hotel&amp;rsquo;s surrounding area, specifically within a 15-minute radius. The campaign showcases local businesses and individuals who contribute to the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s vibrant atmosphere.
A two-minute video featuring the Hotel Indigo Bali Seminyak Beach, the brand&amp;rsquo;s first resort location, introduces viewers to nearby attractions like Surf School Bali, Divine Earth restaurant, and Bali Barber. Starting in October, a series of videos will delve deeper into these local businesses, offering insights and personal stories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The desired features in chatbots according to Amdocs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-desired-features-in-chatbots-according-to-amdocs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 03:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-desired-features-in-chatbots-according-to-amdocs/</guid><description>A recent study focusing on artificial intelligence (AI) spending in major communications and media companies across the Americas, Europe, and Asia reveals that the anticipated increase in AI-powered customer service might be hindered by misguided investments and a shortage of skilled personnel. This research, commissioned by Amdocs and conducted by Forrester Consulting, surveyed over 2,500 individuals, including CEOs, senior decision-makers, and consumers.
The study found that in Asia, nearly one-third of consumers interact with virtual agents weekly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-desired-features-in-chatbots-according-to-amdocs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-desired-features-in-chatbots-according-to-amdocs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>