<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Singapore Airlines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singapore-airlines/</link><description>Recent content in Singapore Airlines on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/singapore-airlines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SilkAir will enhance Singapore Airlines' offerings to Male</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</guid><description>Source: SilkAir. Male.
Starting October 25, 2015, SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will introduce four weekly flights to Male, Maldives. Previously, Singapore Airlines operated between 10 and 14 flights per week to Male. With the addition of SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s new flights, the two airlines will jointly offer two daily round trips, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, highlighted the benefits of this collaboration: “By coordinating the networks of both carriers, we can provide our customers with more choices and flexibility when planning their travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir introduces a new daily flight from Singapore to Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</guid><description>Starting December 12, 2014, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines, will introduce a daily flight service to Denpasar, Indonesia, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, stated, “The increase in flights demonstrates the Singapore Airlines Group&amp;rsquo;s dedication to expanding our service offerings and providing our customers with more choices and convenience. By connecting the networks of both airlines, we can improve connectivity options for our customers through our combined network, reaching 99 cities across 35 countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir have reduced their fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir, its regional subsidiary, have reduced their fuel surcharges due to decreasing fuel prices.
These new surcharge amounts apply to flights from both airlines and range from US$5 to US$83 lower per one-way trip, depending on the flight distance and class of travel.
Route Surcharge in US$* First Class, Suites Between Singapore and South East Asian gateways[1] 50 Between Singapore and Europe/South Africa[2] 175 Between Singapore and Americas 235 Between Europe and Australia/New Zealand[3] 265 All other flights[4] 131 * Figures in US Dollars, converted into currency of sale at time of ticketing..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vistara, a new airline, launches in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</guid><description>Tata SIA Airlines Limited (TSAL) revealed &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; as the name for its new airline on August 11th. This announcement follows a September 2013 agreement between Tata Sons and Singapore Airlines to create a new Indian airline, aiming to further boost air travel demand.
Source: Twitter. The Vistara logo was unveiled on Twitter and Facebook.
The name &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; originates from the Sanskrit word &amp;ldquo;vistaar,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;limitless expanse,&amp;rdquo; symbolizing the boundless sky, the airline&amp;rsquo;s domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines expands its presence in the United States with a new codeshare agreement with Asiana Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines has broadened its codeshare partnership with Asiana Airlines, expanding its network beyond Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon International Airport to include Honolulu, Seattle, and Los Angeles.
These Star Alliance members have been codesharing on flights between Singapore and Seoul-Incheon since September 2005. Singapore Airlines currently offers four daily flights on this route, with one continuing to San Francisco, while Asiana operates daily flights.
Asiana also places its code on Singapore Airlines-operated flights extending beyond Singapore to Jakarta, Indonesia; Perth, Australia; Auckland, New Zealand; and Cape Town, South Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>