<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Music on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/music/</link><description>Recent content in Music on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAKE UP CALL is coming to Bali in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</guid><description>Source: WAKE UP CALL website. W Hotels is putting on a unique music festival at three locations in 2018, with a Dubai edition planned for 2019.
W Hotels presents WAKE UP CALL, a distinctive music festival hosted at three W Hotels, including the W Bali, alongside venues in the US and Europe.
Merging their love for music with their signature Whatever/Whenever approach, WAKE UP CALL brings the festival experience directly to the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals its list of 25 talented individuals under the age of 25 in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 23:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</guid><description>Spotify has unveiled the top 25 most influential artists under 25 who are currently dominating the music scene in Singapore.
Shawn Mendes, an 18-year-old singer-songwriter from Canada, takes the top spot. He boasts 25 million monthly listeners on Spotify and over 500 million streams for his hit song, &amp;ldquo;Stitches.&amp;rdquo; Following closely behind Mendes are Ariana Grande, Martin Garrix, Justin Bieber, and Alessia Cara. Popular artists Gentle Bones and Fifth Harmony are also included in the list...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-its-list-of-25-talented-individuals-under-the-age-of-25-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces music services that do not use data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 22:58:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</guid><description>Singtel debuted its Singtel Music service, a first-of-its-kind offering in Singapore. For a fixed monthly price, subscribers gain access to music from Spotify, KKBOX, AMPed, and MeRadio without incurring data charges.
Representatives from Singtel Music at the launch event.
Singtel Music provides premium accounts from Spotify, KKBOX, or AMPed, enabling users to stream an extensive library of songs without data usage concerns. Additionally, they can enjoy 13 MeRadio stations without impacting their data allowance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-music-services-that-do-not-use-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Halo Smart is designed to enhance both your calling and music experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</guid><description>Jabra Halo Smart headphones are designed for users who prioritize call quality but also enjoy listening to music. Research indicates that 79% of consumers desire headphones suitable for both calls and music, yet find most music headphones lacking in call performance.
These headphones prioritize calls with features like high-quality microphones, wind-noise reduction, and a dedicated button for Google Now or Siri. At the same time, they offer great audio quality for music with 10mm speakers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton guests will enjoy Live Nation experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and Live Nation, a live entertainment company, have launched a new five-year marketing partnership. This collaboration will provide unique experiences, including artist connections and concerts, to Hilton HHonors members, guests, and employees across Hilton&amp;rsquo;s global network of over 4,250 hotels.
Source: Hilton Worldwide. Hilton
aims to motivate a new,
healthier way of thinking - urging
individuals to embrace the unfamiliar,
gain perspective, and learn from daily
life and travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Nathan Hartono concert is brought to you by Singtel Music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel Music presents Hartono concert.
At the beginning of 2017, music enthusiasts will have the opportunity to connect with Singaporean singing star Nathan Hartono. Singtel Music is showcasing its support for local musical talent by holding an exclusive event, Up-Close with Nathan Hartono, on January 21, 2017.
Singtel states that fans can experience Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance and interact with him during the event. Hartono, backed by a full band, will perform a selection of songs in both English and Chinese, including new original pieces from his EP scheduled for release in early 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KKBOX has initiated a Cpop campaign on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</guid><description>Source: Twitter. Screenshot of Tia Ray&amp;rsquo;s tweet.
Twitter and KKBOX, a popular music streaming service in Asia, are collaborating to increase global recognition and appreciation of Chinese pop music, known as Cpop (#Cpop).
To achieve this, KKBOX is developing exclusive Cpop content (#OnlyOnTwitter) for their main Twitter account (@KKBOX). This includes weekly live question and answer sessions with Cpop artists, personalized video messages from Cpop musicians and producers using Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Challenger app, frequent #KKvote contests to encourage international fan participation, and live streams of Cpop concerts and the yearly KKBOX music awards through Periscope (@KKBOXTW)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 18th edition of All That Matters will take place from September 11th to 13th, 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</guid><description>All That Matters, a key event for professionals in Asia&amp;rsquo;s music, sports, gaming, digital, marketing, Web3, and entertainment sectors, is back for its 18th year. It will be held from September 11th to 13th at the Hilton Singapore Orchard.
Source: All That Matters organisers. Event poster.
The event combines a daytime conference with a nightly music festival. It offers attendees, including representatives from major labels, sports organizations, distributors, and publishers, a chance to connect with global brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Throwback Thursday Spotify style with Your Time Capsule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/throwback-thursday-spotify-style-with-your-time-capsule/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/throwback-thursday-spotify-style-with-your-time-capsule/</guid><description>Spotify has introduced &amp;ldquo;Your Time Capsule,&amp;rdquo; a new personalized playlist that follows the success of their summer playlist, &amp;ldquo;Your Summer Rewind.&amp;rdquo;
This playlist, available now to Spotify users in 60 markets, curates 30 nostalgic tracks from a user&amp;rsquo;s teenage and young adult years, offering a musical trip down memory lane.
Source: Spotify. Spotify launches Your Time Capsule playlist.
To find Your Time Capsule, check the top of the Home section or the Decades section in the Browse area on Spotify&amp;rsquo;s iOS and Android mobile apps, or visit the playlist online...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/throwback-thursday-spotify-style-with-your-time-capsule/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/throwback-thursday-spotify-style-with-your-time-capsule/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify has identified a total of 1,369 musical genres up to this point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</guid><description>Spotify uses a music intelligence platform that analyzes music in real time to pinpoint groups of similar sounds, which helps them discover and categorize emerging music genres.
Eliot Van Buskirk, Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Data Storyteller, highlighted in a blog post that this allows Spotify to stay ahead of the curve in identifying new genres as they emerge, ensuring users can discover them quickly.
The platform analyzes the listening habits of real music fans to understand how songs and artists are trending within specific genres...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-has-identified-a-total-of-1-369-musical-genres-up-to-this-point/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify celebrates the year of the rooster with a fresh playlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Welcoming the lunar new year.
To celebrate the Lunar New Year on January 28th, Spotify has launched a special playlist. This playlist features popular songs by artists born in the Year of the Rooster.
Interested?
Check out Spotify&amp;rsquo;s 恭賀新年 (welcoming the new year) playlist..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-celebrates-the-year-of-the-rooster-with-a-fresh-playlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Twitter has revealed its inaugural collaboration with Singaporean musician @Sezairi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</guid><description>● #SezairiQA and live songs on Twitter and Periscope @ 6:30pm on August 31, 2016 ● #SezairiLive debut show at Twitter APAC HQ in Singapore @ 7:30pm on September 2, 2016 ● Winners of @Sezairi photo caption contest get free tickets to #SezairiLive event
Singaporean singer Sezairi (@Sezairi) will be performing live (#SezairiLive) on Twitter, Periscope, and at Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters. The performances follow a pre-listening party (#SezairiPreLP) on Twitter held the previous week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel Music is excited to announce the addition of TIDAL to its portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</guid><description>Singtel Music now offers its customers access to the global music and entertainment platform, TIDAL.
TIDAL differentiates itself as the sole music app providing high-fidelity, lossless audio quality and exclusive content from top global artists. Singtel Music users can enjoy both TIDAL Premium and TIDAL HIFI without impacting their data plans.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its music streaming options. Following the addition of Saavn in October, TIDAL further solidifies Singtel Music&amp;rsquo;s goal of providing the best music streaming experience with diverse content, attractive pricing, and no data charges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify users in Singapore have collectively spent 11.4 billion minutes on the platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/</guid><description>Forty percent of Singaporeans with Internet access use Spotify for their streaming needs.
The music streaming service is celebrating its third successful year in Singapore. Since its launch, Spotify has become a favorite way for Singaporeans to enjoy music, according to Sunita Kaur, Spotify Asia&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director. She believes that Spotify is the ideal music streaming service for Singapore, offering the best local and international music and features.
Since Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Singapore launch, users have spent 11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization recommends restricting the use of personal audio devices to less than one hour per day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</guid><description>Source: WHO.
The World Health Organization (WHO) cautions that over a billion adolescents and young adults risk noise-induced hearing loss. This danger stems from unsafe listening practices with personal audio devices like smartphones and exposure to high sound levels at entertainment venues, including sporting events.
WHO analysis of data from developed and developing nations reveals that nearly half of teenagers and young adults aged 12-35 experience unsafe sound levels from personal audio devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Come join us on a journey back to a time when things were simpler</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-join-us-on-a-journey-back-to-a-time-when-things-were-simpler/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 09:10:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-join-us-on-a-journey-back-to-a-time-when-things-were-simpler/</guid><description>Source: Ben Barbic/Ajax. Way Back is a call to revisit simpler, more carefree times.
Reggae/hip-hop artist Ben Barbic released Way Back, a tribute to his long friendship with producer Ajax and their first posthumous collaboration.
Barbic and Ajax have been friends since they were two years old. Although geographically separated as adults, with Barbic residing in the Bay area and Ajax in Manhattan, their shared passion for music remained strong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-join-us-on-a-journey-back-to-a-time-when-things-were-simpler/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-join-us-on-a-journey-back-to-a-time-when-things-were-simpler/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JJ Lin has composed a song that was inspired by Jewel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 15:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Lin&amp;rsquo;s The Right Time.
Changi Airport Group (CAG) collaborated with Singaporean singer-songwriter JJ Lin on his new song, &amp;ldquo;The Right Time.&amp;rdquo;
Inspired by the April opening of Jewel Changi Airport, Lin shared that the Rain Vortex, Jewel&amp;rsquo;s impressive waterfall centerpiece, sparked his creativity for this piece.
Lin composed the music for &amp;ldquo;The Right Time&amp;rdquo; with lyrics by Xiaohan. Filmed in July, the music video showcases Jewel&amp;rsquo;s waterfall and lush surroundings, featuring Lin alongside popular regional actor Christopher Lee...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jj-lin-has-composed-a-song-that-was-inspired-by-jewel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify creates playlists for foggy weather</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has curated a playlist specifically for the hazy conditions currently affecting Singapore and Malaysia. You can listen to the playlist below.
Interested in learning more?
Stay informed about the hourly air quality readings in Singapore.
Read this WorkSmart Asia blog article about Spotify&amp;rsquo;s mobile-first approach.
Hashtag: #SGHaze..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive Global Jay Chou content available on Spotify from December 16th to 18th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 09:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/</guid><description>Source: Spotify website.
Music streaming platform, Spotify, released Asian pop star Jay Chou&amp;rsquo;s latest single, &amp;ldquo;What Kind of Man are You?&amp;rdquo; today.
Spotify is offering fans an early preview of one of the year&amp;rsquo;s most anticipated albums, with the release of Jay Chou&amp;rsquo;s latest album, &amp;ldquo;Aiyo, Not Bad,&amp;rdquo; planned for December 26th, days before its official release.
Recently ranked the most streamed Asian artist on Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Year in Music charts, Jay Chou is celebrating his return to the pop charts with this new album after a two-year hiatus...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most popular videos on YouTube in Hong Kong for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</guid><description>Content related to local news, tutorials, and parodies were the most popular on YouTube in Hong Kong this year.
A wider variety of music genres are gaining traction.
YouTube Hong Kong Rewind 2019 highlights this year&amp;rsquo;s trending videos, showcasing categories like the Top 10 Trending Videos, Top 10 Trending Local Music Videos, Top 10 Trending International Music Videos, and Top 10 Emerging Channels.
Music, in various forms like music videos, live shows, remixes, and covers, remains a favorite among Hong Kong viewers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore International Festival of Music is ready for its October shows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 13:56:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</guid><description>The Singapore International Festival of Music (SIFOM), Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first classical music festival, returns for its second year. Centered around the theme &amp;ldquo;Myths and Legends,&amp;rdquo; the festival showcases classical music inspired by folklore and fairy tales. From October 13th to 30th, the festival offers free public programs, masterclasses, and ticketed events including orchestral performances, musical theater, and vocal concerts.
The 2016 SIFOM lineup features the festival&amp;rsquo;s own SIFOM Orchestra and Ensemble, Ding Yi Music Company (showcasing Singapore&amp;rsquo;s finest young musicians), and internationally-renowned guests from the Chamber Orchestra of Europe (COE), a distinguished chamber orchestra...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>