<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireline on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireline/</link><description>Recent content in Wireline on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Triple Play Helps Wireline Fight Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-helps-wireline-fight-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-helps-wireline-fight-satellite/</guid><description>The market for television services is completely saturated. While getting TV used to be simple, viewers now have a wide range of options, including over-the-air, cable, satellite, telco (AT&amp;amp;T), and fiber optic (Verizon).
The recent discontinuation of analog television transmissions was met with indifference by most, except for a small number of consumers who didn&amp;rsquo;t buy a converter or new digital TV. Now, these individuals are rushing to find converter boxes or signing up with cable or satellite providers like DirecTV or Dish Network.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Wireline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 23:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-wireline/</guid><description>In the world of telecommunications, &amp;ldquo;wireline&amp;rdquo; traditionally refers to connections made through copper wires, while &amp;ldquo;wireless&amp;rdquo; implies no physical connections. However, &amp;ldquo;fiber optic&amp;rdquo; technology exists as a distinct category, utilizing physical cables but transmitting data through light rather than electricity. This distinction makes fiber optics a promising successor to the traditional copper wire infrastructure.
Several factors contribute to fiber optic cable&amp;rsquo;s potential to replace copper wire. Interestingly, their structures share similarities.</description></item></channel></rss>