<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtual on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual/</link><description>Recent content in Virtual on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>Bank Simpanan Nasional has launched virtual teller machines in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Bank Simpanan Nasional (BSN) is the first bank in Malaysia to introduce virtual teller machines (VTMs). These machines allow bank tellers to assist customers in different locations throughout Malaysia remotely, through a live virtual banking system.
BSN&amp;rsquo;s adoption of VTMs was inspired by kiosk banking already in place in other countries, including those in Europe, China, Canada, and the US. The project is a collaboration between BSN and Vastcomp to develop a specialized system.</description></item><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession.</description></item><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it.</description></item><item><title>Keppel Land enhances marketing strategy with virtual show suites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</guid><description>Keppel Land is the first developer in Singapore to utilize Oculus Rift technology to create 360-degree immersive virtual reality (VR) show suites for its Highline Residences property. These two digitally rendered suites complement the three existing physical show suites at the Highline Residences showroom in Singapore.
The new VR platform, a collaboration between Keppel Land and visualisation firm VMW Group, features virtual tours of these new unit layouts. It also allows for a virtual exploration of key landmarks in the trendy Tiong Bahru neighborhood where Highline Residences is located.</description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality.</description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app.</description></item></channel></rss>