<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bouquet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bouquet/</link><description>Recent content in Bouquet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bouquet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves.</description></item><item><title>Add some festive flowers to the office to celebrate Chinese New Year and bring some brightness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</guid><description>Starting January 19, 2015, Viva La Fleur will debut a new collection of long-lasting bouquets and table arrangements. The color palette for this collection features predominantly red, orange, and yellow tones, symbolizing love, luck, and fortune, perfectly aligning with the festive season.
This arrangement, part of Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s new collection, showcases deep red roses, hydrangeas, and caspia accented with brown twigs. You can find this arrangement in Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s online shop here.</description></item></channel></rss>