<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Etihad on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etihad/</link><description>Recent content in Etihad on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etihad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi First Class Lounge &amp; Spa has been opened by Etihad Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has opened a new flagship First Class Lounge &amp;amp; Spa in Terminal 3 of Abu Dhabi International Airport. This space highlights the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to offering exceptional and desirable hospitality.
Inspired by top-tier hotels, private clubs, and fine dining establishments, the lounge provides an exclusive environment. It features unmatched design, style, comfort, world-class dining, and personalized beauty and relaxation services.
The lounge offers 16 distinct zones for guests to unwind, recharge, and enjoy entertainment in complete luxury before their flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now offers Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner on flights from Abu Dhabi to Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has upgraded its Abu Dhabi to Shanghai route, now offering flights on the Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner. This change increases capacity by 14%, offering 28 business class and 271 economy seats.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Peter Baumgartner, highlighted the significance of the Chinese market, particularly the rising demand from business and leisure travelers. The decision to utilize the Dreamliner reflects Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s status as a major global hub and its importance in Etihad&amp;rsquo;s network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways introduces more flights on the Abu Dhabi to Doha route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is commemorating a decade of service to Qatar this year by adding nine weekly flights to its Abu Dhabi-Doha route, strengthening its dedication to this important Gulf market.
Starting August 1, 2016, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s national airline will boost its weekly service to Qatar&amp;rsquo;s capital to 37 flights. These new daily morning and early evening departures on Thursdays and Saturdays offer more flexibility and convenience, catering to business travelers in both Abu Dhabi and Doha...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces the Dreamliner to Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has started using Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners for flights to Perth, Australia. These planes provide passengers with larger windows, improved air quality, spacious storage, and advanced technology for a more comfortable journey.
Flight EY486, the first Dreamliner flight, arrived in Perth on June 2nd and was greeted with a water cannon salute. This daily service replaces the Airbus A330-200, increasing capacity by 14%, with Business Class seating up by 27%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, Etihad will assume control of Virgin's Sydney-Abu Dhabi slots</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</guid><description>Etihad Airways will increase flights between Abu Dhabi and Sydney to twice daily starting February 6, 2017. Flights EY450 departing Abu Dhabi in the morning and EY451 departing Sydney in the afternoon will now operate seven days a week.
This schedule change coincides with strategic partner Virgin Australia&amp;rsquo;s move to shift its Abu Dhabi operations from Sydney to Perth, effective June 9, 2017. Etihad Airways will expand its current codeshare agreement with Virgin Australia to include their new tri-weekly Perth-Abu Dhabi flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad updates baggage policy and fare structure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
The national airline of the United Arab Emirates, Etihad Airways, is rolling out a new, clearer fare system starting September 14, 2015. This system aims to offer travelers more choices when booking their flights.
Eight new &amp;ldquo;Fare Choices&amp;rdquo; will be introduced, allowing travelers to customize their bookings to fit their needs. These transparent Fare Choices come with different baggage allowances, levels of flexibility, and included benefits that previously needed to be purchased separately...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Complimentary stopovers offered to Etihad Economy Class passengers traveling from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is offering a complimentary one-night stay at the Radisson Blu hotel on Abu Dhabi’s Yas Island. This offer is open to Economy Class passengers flying from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan who have a layover in Abu Dhabi.
Mohammad Al Bulooki, Etihad Airways Executive VP Commercial, expressed the airline&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for showcasing Abu Dhabi to its guests. He highlighted the diverse attractions of the UAE capital, ranging from cultural landmarks and beaches to sports and adventure activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport Terminal 1 has been reopened by Etihad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has officially reopened its First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport’s Terminal 1 after a complete renovation.
The improved lounge, open around the clock, spans over 1,044 square meters and can accommodate 134 guests. This updated space in Terminal 1 provides a variety of amenities to meet the needs of modern business and leisure travelers. Mirroring the lounge in Terminal 3, the refurbished facility features comfortable seating, a designated dining area, modern business facilities, complimentary Wi-Fi, USB charging ports, restrooms with shower facilities, and a children&amp;rsquo;s play area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad provides a wider range of choices for Mediterranean travel destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is increasing the number and capacity of flights to Athens, Greece, and Larnaca, Cyprus.
Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, stated that the new flights to Athens will offer travelers two different departure times to and from Abu Dhabi. The additional flights to Larnaca will provide more options and flexibility, as well as enhanced connectivity through Abu Dhabi.
He added that these additions will support business and leisure travel growth through Abu Dhabi and offer travelers a wider choice of destinations in the Gulf region, Indian Subcontinent, Asia, and Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad and Fiji Airways establish codeshare partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</guid><description>Fiji Airways and Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, have established an interline agreement. This partnership enables both airlines to sell tickets to and from a wider range of destinations. Passengers can now travel between 17 cities in the Middle East, 29 cities in Asia, and three cities in Australia to and from Fiji, along with other destinations.
James Hogan, President and CEO of Etihad Airways, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, stating that Fiji is an excellent vacation destination and enhances Etihad&amp;rsquo;s global network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways releases statement regarding military coup in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has recommended that passengers on flight EY407 from Bangkok to Abu Dhabi be prepared to show their passports and tickets if asked by military personnel. This applies when traveling to Suvarnabhumi Airport during the curfew, which is in effect from 10:00 PM to 5:00 AM local time. The airline advises, &amp;ldquo;Guests are advised to allow extra time to reach the airport.&amp;rdquo;
Due to the suspension of public transportation starting at 9:00 PM local time and possible limited taxi services, Etihad suggests that hotel guests consider booking airport limousine services through their hotels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad improves chauffeur services in the United Arab Emirates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has launched new features to improve its chauffeur services in the UAE.
Passengers can now book and manage Etihad&amp;rsquo;s chauffeur services directly through the airline&amp;rsquo;s updated mobile-friendly website, eliminating the need to contact the Etihad call center or a travel agent. This feature is effective immediately.
Travelers can book and confirm their chauffeur service up to 12 hours before their flight&amp;rsquo;s departure. Developed with Vxceed Technologies, the new system also allows passengers to modify or cancel their chauffeur booking, giving them more control over their travel plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad plans to increase the number of flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, will begin offering daily A380 flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne starting June 1, 2016. This will affect flight numbers EY460/461, one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily trips between the cities. This change replaces one of the three-class Boeing 777-300ER aircraft currently used. Passengers can now enjoy The Residence by Etihad, a luxurious private three-room suite, and other cutting-edge products and services across all cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways has implemented improvements to its baggage policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Starting September 14, 2015, Etihad Airways will launch its new Fare Choices tariff program, which includes changes to its baggage policy. The airline claims these updates will benefit travelers, particularly those enrolled in the Etihad Guest loyalty program.
This new policy aims to provide more flexibility and align Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; baggage policies with partner airlines by catering to individual customer needs. Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, states: “This is about offering a fair and transparent baggage concept that is an industry best practice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>