<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Instagram on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/instagram/</link><description>Recent content in Instagram on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/instagram/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instagram outperformed Facebook during the Rio 2016 Olympics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</guid><description>Source: ComScore. Social network interactions between Facebook and Instagram for July 2016 around the Olympic games, which ran from 5 to 21 August.
ComScore, a media measurement company, found that Instagram was the top platform for engagement during the 2016 Rio Olympics, even though Facebook, its parent company, was primarily used for pre-event official content sharing.
In June, the UK ranked third globally in unique visitors to the official Rio Olympics website (RIO2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>