<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Culinary on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/culinary/</link><description>Recent content in Culinary on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/culinary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CULINARYON has opened a cooking studio in Singapore for classes and parties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</guid><description>A workstation equipped with eggs and two varieties of flour, ready for preparing homemade tagliatelle.
CULINARYON, the largest culinary edutainment studio in Europe, established in Moscow in 2012, has expanded to Singapore. Their 7,000 square foot studio at One Raffles Place, inaugurated in October 2015, is their second location and holds the title of the biggest cooking studio in Asia.
The CULINARYON studio has a capacity of 200 people and can be reconfigured into a conference room and four distinct event spaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-has-opened-a-cooking-studio-in-singapore-for-classes-and-parties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore emerges victorious at the Culinary Olympics 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</guid><description>Source: the Singapore National Culinary Team. The Singapore National Culinary Team outperformed over 30 countries to become the champions of the Culinary Olympics 2016. The team achieved gold medals in both the Cold Display and Hot Cooking categories, proving the country&amp;rsquo;s chefs are world-class. From left: Teo Yeow Siang, team captain, from Lavish Catering; Triston Fang, team member, from Ocean Restaurant by Cat Cora, Resorts World Sentosa; Alan Wong, team member, from Lavish Catering; team manager Louis Tay from Swissotel Merchant Court; Roy Lim, team member, from Unilever FoodSolutions; and Alex Chong, team member, from The Regent Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing a new food tour by Isan Explorer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</guid><description>Source: Isan Explorer website.
Isan Explorer, a tour operator specializing in Northeast Thailand, has launched a culinary tour showcasing the cuisine of the lesser-known Isan region.
The day-long tour starts with a visit to a bustling fresh market to gather ingredients for lunch and dinner. Afterward, the tour proceeds to a nearby village.
Participants will enjoy a tasting menu featuring 20 main dishes, such as bamboo shoot curry, sour fish, grilled chicken, steamed mushrooms, green bean salad, and eggplant dipping sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>