<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Website on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/website/</link><description>Recent content in Website on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people.</description></item><item><title>Dude, Where's My Site?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 04:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</guid><description>Ever feel like the internet is taking a break, but you&amp;rsquo;re not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s just you? Sometimes, websites refuse to load, leaving you wondering if the problem is on your end. A new tool called DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com provides a simple solution. Just enter the website address, and it will tell you if the site is truly down or if it&amp;rsquo;s just your connection.
Created by a Twitter engineer, DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com addresses the common question of whether a website is offline or if it&amp;rsquo;s a personal issue.</description></item><item><title>Today is the day for the landrush of .global, .website, and .press domain names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</guid><description>Starting August 27th, Singapore time, several top-level domain names will be up for grabs in a &amp;ldquo;landrush&amp;rdquo; phase, according to online brand specialist IP Mirror.
The &amp;ldquo;sunrise&amp;rdquo; phase, reserved for trademark holders to register their brands, precedes this period. During the landrush phase, anyone can secure remaining domain names at a premium price.
IP Mirror highlights &amp;ldquo;.global&amp;rdquo; as a particularly appealing option, signifying a broad international reach. This domain&amp;rsquo;s landrush phase lasts from August 27th to September 4th.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan.</description></item><item><title>Journeyful has revamped its website, incorporating additional listings and enhancing rewards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/journeyful-has-revamped-its-website-incorporating-additional-listings-and-enhancing-rewards/</guid><description>Source: Journeyful. The Journeyful 2.0 website.
Journeyful, a company located in Singapore, has relaunched an updated website for its rewards-based online travel agency, Journeyful.com. The new and improved &amp;ldquo;Journeyful 2.0&amp;rdquo; website features a selection of over 200,000 hotels globally, a price-match guarantee, and Facebook integration.
The redesigned website includes Journeyful MICE, which offers comprehensive solutions for business conferences, corporate events, and incentive trips. A Journeyful representative explained that once an online inquiry is submitted, MICE consultants collaborate offline with the organization to personalize solutions.</description></item><item><title>Google prefers websites that are optimized for mobile devices. Have you taken any steps to ensure your site is mobile-friendly?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:04:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-prefers-websites-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices-have-you-taken-any-steps-to-ensure-your-site-is-mobile-friendly/</guid><description>World Markets Korea, a Seoul-based online marketing firm, has outlined some of the factors Google now considers when evaluating websites for mobile friendliness. These include text size, spacing between links, and whether the content fits comfortably on a mobile screen. Google uses these criteria to determine if a website is &amp;ldquo;Mobile Friendly.&amp;rdquo;
The company recommends that businesses engage their web designers to update their sites accordingly. World Markets Korea also provides services to optimize websites for mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Adobe aims to achieve the highest level of performance in order to increase repeat visits and online sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 12:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-aims-to-achieve-the-highest-level-of-performance-in-order-to-increase-repeat-visits-and-online-sales/</guid><description>Source: Adobe.
Recent Adobe research indicates that marketers in the Asia Pacific region who use best practices are significantly outperforming their competitors.
The Adobe Digital Index Best of the Best Benchmark for Asia Pacific analyzed websites across six regions: Australia and New Zealand, Southeast Asia, India, South Korea, Hong Kong, and China, comparing the average website performance with the top 20% based on six key performance indicators: mobile and tablet traffic, stick rate, visits per visitor, time spent, and conversion rate.</description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector.</description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base.</description></item><item><title>Kluje.com is enhancing its property management bidding e-platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 07:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kluje-com-is-enhancing-its-property-management-bidding-e-platform/</guid><description>Kluje.com, pronounced &amp;ldquo;clue-jay&amp;rdquo;, has expanded its online contractor platform to include over 30,000 property agents and facility managers. The platform allows users to easily find qualified contractors for various tasks, such as electrical work, plumbing, and flooring.
Jamey Merkel, CEO of Kluje.com, explains that the platform addresses the time constraints faced by real estate and facilities professionals responsible for property upkeep. By streamlining the process of finding and hiring contractors, Kluje.</description></item><item><title>GoDaddy has expanded its presence to 11 Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a global technology provider for small businesses, has expanded its reach into 11 Asian markets. This expansion brings GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based products and customer support services to millions of small and medium enterprises (SMEs) within the region.
With these 11 new markets, GoDaddy now operates in 14 markets across Asia, encompassing 10 languages. These markets include Hong Kong (English and Traditional Chinese), Indonesia, Japan, Malaysia (English and Malay), Philippines (English and Filipino), Singapore (English and Simplified Chinese), South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, and Vietnam.</description></item><item><title>Save Elephants By Transferring Your Domain Names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-elephants-by-transferring-your-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 01:13:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-elephants-by-transferring-your-domain-names/</guid><description>This is a limited-time chance to save money on domain names and support a good cause.
Namecheap, a reputable domain and hosting provider, has a special offer today (August 15, 2014). Transfer your .com, .net, or .org domain to Namecheap for just $7.88 for the first year using the code SAVEDUMBO. This is a significantly lower price than most hosting companies.
Renewal prices are also competitive. For example, a .com domain renewal costs $10.</description></item></channel></rss>