<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Carriers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-carriers/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Carriers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-carriers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom Providers Build Their Own Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</guid><description>As cloud computing companies start to establish themselves, internet service providers and similar carriers are developing their own cloud services. This creates a challenge for IT professionals and business owners who need to choose the best option.
It’s important to recognize that cloud computing is still in its early stages. Like any new technology, it will take time for it to fully develop. As the technology progresses, we will see a lot of activity from many different companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Community Builds Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a narrative circulating that our infrastructure is failing. While this might be true in some areas, a massive construction project is currently underway to create a robust fiber optic network across the nation. This &amp;ldquo;nervous system&amp;rdquo; for information technology promises practically limitless, low-lag bandwidth for the foreseeable future.
This surge in fiber optic infrastructure isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by failing systems, but rather by existing infrastructure reaching full capacity. The late 20th century witnessed a fiber optic boom, which initially seemed excessive when the tech bubble burst...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic DWDM Up to 100 Gbps Per Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 09:44:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth keeps increasing, even during economic slowdowns. The main reason is the huge popularity of video, especially high-definition video, which needs a lot of bandwidth on all types of networks. Now, fiber optic systems using DWDM (Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing) can handle 100 Gbps per wavelength.
It seems like just yesterday we were excited about moving from 10 Gbps to 40 Gbps channels. Now, Alcatel-Lucent offers an upgrade that handles both 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps on a single optical carrier for their 1830 Photonic Service Switch (PSS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-dwdm-up-to-100-gbps-per-wavelength/</a></p></description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Getting Network Connections Into Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</guid><description>Although many businesses only require domestic WAN connections, a growing number are seeking global connectivity, particularly with European markets for financial trading, sales, and support. This raises the question of how US-based companies can establish cost-effective connections with Europe.
Fortunately, several carriers offer transatlantic connectivity to major European cities. Some US carriers have partnerships for traffic handover to European data centers, as illustrated by AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement with ancotel GmbH in Frankfurt, Germany...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-network-connections-into-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TW Telecom's Extensive Service Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</guid><description>tw telecom is a full-service communications provider with a privately owned, nationwide fiber optic network. They provide service in 75 major markets and over 8,800 commercial buildings. Their network spans more than 26,000 route miles and features a 10 Gbps IP backbone. They offer a wide array of services, from affordable T1 lines to high-speed Carrier Ethernet services ranging from 2 Mbps to 10 Gbps.
You might recognize the name tw telecom from its previous iterations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tw-telecoms-extensive-service-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet MPLS Has Cost and Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 17:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet, also called Metro Ethernet, and MPLS networks are two popular technologies for voice, video, and data networking. These technologies can be used together to increase bandwidth while reducing costs.
Traditionally, there&amp;rsquo;s a significant difference in speed and compatibility between customer networks and telecom networks. These differences stem from their distinct developmental paths. While connecting these networks is now possible through clever interfacing, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal. We can now transmit data packets between LANs over telephone-based telecom networks, but a better solution exists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-mpls-has-cost-and-bandwidth-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>