<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>APEC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apec/</link><description>Recent content in APEC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region.</description></item><item><title>BCM Institute offers Business Continuity Management courses specifically designed for small and medium-sized enterprises in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bcm-institute-offers-business-continuity-management-courses-specifically-designed-for-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-singapore/</guid><description>The BCM Institute, in collaboration with the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC), is offering a free two-day Business Continuity Management (BCM) course designed to enhance the resilience of small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) against disruptions.
Taking place on October 28-29, 2014, at the Singapore Productivity Centre, this course is presented with support from the Singapore Business Federation and SPRING Singapore. Participants will engage with the following topics:
APEC-endorsed step-by-step BCM implementation guidelines Complimentary, ready-to-use BCM templates Guidance on utilizing BCM templates Insights into BCM trends affecting SMEs, shared by an APEC ASEAN BCM Working Group Committee member SMEs meeting the criteria of an annual sales turnover not exceeding S$100 million or employing 200 or fewer staff are eligible to participate.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is the third best city in APEC for living and conducting business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</guid><description>A new study presented at the APEC 2015 CEO Summit has positioned Singapore as the third most desirable city for living and conducting business within the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) region.
Conducted by PwC, the &amp;ldquo;Building Better Cities&amp;rdquo; study aims to provide city leaders with insights into their current standings and to encourage collaboration and knowledge sharing among APEC cities to tackle persistent challenges.
The study examines the role urban centers play in APEC&amp;rsquo;s economic and social progress, emphasizing their growing global influence.</description></item><item><title>The Brunei boot camp is designed to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in transitioning to digital platforms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 01:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-brunei-boot-camp-is-designed-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-transitioning-to-digital-platforms/</guid><description>DHgate, the APEC Business Advisory Council (ABAC) China, and ABAC Brunei have initiated the Asia Pacific Economic Cooperation Cross-Border E-commerce Training (APEC CBET) boot camp in Brunei. This program aims to develop more skilled professionals within the cross-border e-commerce sector and elevate industry training standards.
E-commerce exporters see a greater first-year survival rate (60-80%) than traditional businesses (30-50%), according to the APEC CBET website. E-commerce also allows exporters to reach around 40 different economies compared to just three to four for traditional exporters.</description></item></channel></rss>