<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metro E on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-e/</link><description>Recent content in Metro E on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-e/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How To Find Better Metro E Service Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) services are widely available and offer a practical solution for businesses operating within a metropolitan area to connect their various locations. However, securing the most cost-effective Metro E services requires careful consideration.
Metro Ethernet is a type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) designed to meet the local connectivity needs of businesses. Unlike traditional wide-area networks, MANs focus on providing high-speed connections within a specific city or region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>