<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Broken on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broken/</link><description>Recent content in Broken on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Incandescent Bulb in the Sensor Arm with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 15:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-incandescent-bulb-in-the-sensor-arm-with-an-led/</guid><description>To ensure stability after restoring Beograms, I like to test them thoroughly. While playing records on a recently revived Beogram 4000, the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s light bulb burned out. This presented a chance to modify my LED assembly design, previously used for the Beogram 4002, to fit the Beogram 4000.
The redesigned Kapton flex board can be folded to fit the sensor arm bulb cavity:
A 3D-printed wedge, attached to the back, positions the LED for optimal light reflection into the arm&amp;rsquo;s sensor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Unit Switches Immediately to 45 RPM After Pressing Start</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-unit-switches-immediately-to-45-rpm-after-pressing-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable being restored exhibited a peculiar issue during initial testing. Upon starting, the tonearm moved as expected but the speed immediately switched to 45 RPM. Pressing the 33 RPM button temporarily resolved the issue, but the speed reverted back upon release.
This unusual behavior pointed to a potential problem with transistors TR3 or TR2. Examining the circuit diagram, we can see how speed selection operates:
The speed control mechanism utilizes a flip-flop circuit with transistors TR3 and TR4.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>The last remaining bulb to be replaced with an LED in this Beogram 4000 was the one in the sensor arm. A new flexPCB assembly with a warm-white LED was designed to fit within the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s bulb compartment. This particular Beogram 4000 model has a sensor arm with a socket connection for the bulb/sensor compartment. This convenient design allowed for simple removal of the entire assembly, making the LED conversion a benchtop task.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 3000 (5228): Restoration of the Plexiglass Hood - Repair of a Cracked Hinge and Installation of 3D Printed Mounting Brackets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-3000-5228-restoration-of-the-plexiglass-hood-repair-of-a-cracked-hinge-and-installation-of-3d-printed-mounting-brackets/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 3000 turntable with a damaged plexiglass dust cover. The plastic mounting brackets that held the cover were broken, and one of the plexiglass hinges was also broken.
and one of the plexiglass hinges was broken off:
To address these issues, I created a repair kit. This kit includes 3D-printed replacement mounting brackets, a specialized tool for reinstalling the spring tensioning block, and laser-cut plexiglass pieces for fixing the broken hinge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak.</description></item></channel></rss>