<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>External Competence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-competence/</link><description>Recent content in External Competence on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-competence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinion of the Legal Service of the Council on the Brexit agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</guid><description>This document presents the EU Council legal service&amp;rsquo;s analysis of whether the Brexit deal requires approval from both the EU and its Member States (a &amp;lsquo;mixed agreement&amp;rsquo;), or solely from the EU. It concludes that the EU can act alone due to the deal encompassing a blend of exclusive EU competences and competences shared between the EU and its member states. This aligns with Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law, which allows the EU to enact a treaty encompassing shared competences either independently or jointly with its Member States.</description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics.</description></item><item><title>Is the agreement between the EU and Turkey on refugees and migration considered a treaty?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</guid><description>Maarten den Heijer*, Thomas Spijkerboer**
*Assistant professor of international law at the Universiteit van Amsterdam
**Professor of migration law at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.
The European Parliament recently inquired about the legal standing of the EU-Turkey Statement of March 18th, which initiated the return of asylum seekers from Greece to Turkey. Concerns arose because the agreement bypassed the standard EU treaty procedure outlined in Article 218 TFEU. The Parliament seeks clarification on whether the Council views this statement as a binding treaty and, if not, whether Turkey is aware of its non-binding status.</description></item><item><title>Child abduction: an additional expansion of the EU's exclusive external authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/child-abduction-an-additional-expansion-of-the-eu-s-exclusive-external-authority/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Parental child abduction is a serious issue, often arising from custody disputes during family law proceedings. While abduction by a stranger presents a clear danger, abduction by a non-custodial parent violates court decisions and can hinder the custodial parent&amp;rsquo;s rights, especially when the child is taken to another country.
The Hague Convention, established in 1980, seeks to address this problem. This international treaty, with 93 signatory countries including all EU members, provides a framework for resolving international parental child abduction cases.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics.</description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence).</description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?</description></item><item><title>The ECJ clarifies EU's authority over copyright law in the Marrakesh Treaty ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</guid><description>Gesa Kübek, PhD candidate at the law faculty of the University of Passau.
In its February 14, 2017 Opinion 3/15, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) determined that the European Union (EU) possesses exclusive competence to enter into the Marrakesh Treaty to Facilitate Access to Published Works for Persons Who Are Blind, Visually Impaired, or Otherwise Print Disabled (hereafter: Marrakesh Treaty). This decision aligns with Advocate General (AG) Wahl’s prior Opinion, which similarly argued for exclusive EU competence in this domain.</description></item></channel></rss>