<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Big Data on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/big-data/</link><description>Recent content in Big Data on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/big-data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Graphical Introduction to Big Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</guid><description>Confused about the hype surrounding Big Data? This infographic might help clear things up&amp;hellip;
Feeling limited by your current internet connection when dealing with large amounts of data, cloud services, backups, or file transfers? Upgrading might be more affordable than you expect. Get immediate pricing on cost-effective copper and fiber internet options for your business.
Credit to Wikibon Infographics for this infographic on Big Data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Can You Cope With Big Data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 22:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</guid><description>The sheer size of &amp;ldquo;Big Data&amp;rdquo; is a popular topic, but what does it really mean?
Does the thought of managing massive amounts of data feel overwhelming, or do you see it as an opportunity? Ensuring you have the right infrastructure and connectivity is essential. Discover the cloud and connection services tailored for your business&amp;rsquo;s location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-you-cope-with-big-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transforming the WAN Into The Smart WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</guid><description>People tend to think of WAN connections as basic channels for data, similar to how Senator Ted Stevens once described the internet. However, with the shift from on-site data centers to cloud-based systems, VoIP, and video streaming, our needs have outgrown this simple model. This is where the concept of a Smart WAN comes into play.
Instead of treating all data equally, a Smart WAN prioritizes different types of data through a system called Class of Service (CoS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>