<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jobs on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jobs/</link><description>Recent content in Jobs on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:21:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is There a Broadband Stimulus Job For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</guid><description>The U.S. government is investing an additional $795 million in broadband stimulus funding to address the country&amp;rsquo;s lag behind nations like Japan and Korea in providing affordable, high-speed internet. This investment presents a potential win-win situation, offering both short-term job creation and long-term economic benefits.
One study projects the creation of approximately 5,000 immediate jobs from these high-speed internet projects. While seemingly small compared to the number of job seekers, it&amp;rsquo;s a step in the right direction.</description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily.</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing In Lieu of Outsourcing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</guid><description>Over recent years, outsourcing has become increasingly popular as a way to meet business needs. However, since the Great Recession, crowdsourcing has emerged as a new and growing trend. This approach leverages the collective talent of a group to find solutions for specific tasks.
Crowdsourcing provides a decentralized approach to problem-solving, unlike traditional methods of assigning tasks to employees or contractors. Imagine needing a building sold – you&amp;rsquo;d hire a real estate agent.</description></item></channel></rss>