<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes a Great MAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</guid><description>Access to Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs), previously limited to large corporations, is now feasible for small and medium-sized businesses. If your company requires communication between multiple locations within a city, a metro network might be beneficial.
Metro Ethernet is the modern solution for data connections in major cities and surrounding areas. There are two main types: E-Line and E-LAN. E-Line provides a direct Ethernet connection between two points, such as a business and its data center, warehouse, factory, or branch office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Build Wide Area Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Imagine offering your clients network installations that stretch across the city or even the entire country! You might think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible, but it&amp;rsquo;s more achievable than you think.
You won&amp;rsquo;t need massive spools of wire or heavy equipment. Everything is taken care of, allowing you to focus on expanding your business and profits.
This is possible due to two key advancements: the rise of Metro and Carrier Ethernet services from competitive carriers and a business model that lets you integrate these Ethernet WAN services into your network designs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-build-wide-area-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Windfall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</guid><description>When budgets are strained, expanding into new markets and generating much-needed revenue often depends on increasing Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. However, more bandwidth usually means higher expenses, creating a difficult situation.
It&amp;rsquo;s generally accepted that increasing bandwidth leads to increased costs. For instance, 10 Mbps will likely cost more than 1 Mbps, although there might be a volume discount. But is it possible to get more bandwidth while paying less overall?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity for Telemedicine and Remote Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The rapid emergence of the Coronavirus pandemic is speeding up existing trends, particularly telemedicine and remote work. Both heavily rely on broadband internet bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available connection options.
Connecting the User
Most remote workers and telemedicine patients connect from home using devices like desktops, smartphones, laptops, or tablets. Home users often prefer cable broadband with speeds of 30 to 100 Mbps, while remote users rely on public WiFi or 4G/5G cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency WAN Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly demanding low latency in their WAN connections. But why is latency suddenly so important, and how can you achieve it?
Latency is the time it takes for data packets to travel between two points. While insignificant on local networks, latency can pose major problems on long-distance WAN connections, especially for applications where speed is critical.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that latency and bandwidth are not directly related. You can have slow connections with minimal latency and blazing-fast connections with terrible latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Services Proliferate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</guid><description>The increasing need for bandwidth in the business world has driven the rapid expansion of high-speed voice and data services. While T1 lines were once considered high-end, businesses now have a variety of options, including various DSx copper and fiber optic connections, wireless broadband, and even point-to-point laser technology.
DS3 is gaining popularity as companies find their T1 connections inadequate. Upgrading from a DS1&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 Mbps to DS3&amp;rsquo;s 45 Mbps accommodates more users and allows for dedicated internet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-services-proliferate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses currently using T1 lines for dedicated internet or point-to-point connections might be seeking ways to increase bandwidth without the high costs of upgrading to DS3 fiber optic cable. Metro Ethernet offers a solution. But how can you find it?
Locating Metro Ethernet service is straightforward with the right approach. Similar to finding anything else, the key is knowing where to look. A specialized tool designed to locate and map available Ethernet bandwidth in your vicinity is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I Want Fiber But Not Construction Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has become the top choice for business private lines and internet connections. It offers a practically unlimited capacity with minimal latency, packet loss, and jitter. Prices are now more competitive than before, provided you don&amp;rsquo;t encounter high construction costs.
Why Fiber Can Involve Construction Expenses
Businesses accustomed to T1 lines, Ethernet over Copper, or business cable might be surprised by quotes that include substantial construction costs for installing a fiber line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-want-fiber-but-not-construction-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Even Lower Latency Connections To Chicago</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</guid><description>The significance of network latency is evident in AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s efforts to establish faster fiber optic connections, even within a metropolitan area like Chicago, set to launch by the middle of next year. This begs the question: will other cities follow suit?
Latency is the new frontier, surpassing even bandwidth in importance. It represents the critical factor when exceptional computing performance is non-negotiable. This need is especially acute in the financial sector, where companies engaged in stock and commodity trading demand minimal delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/even-lower-latency-connections-to-chicago/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Brings 100 Gbps to Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</guid><description>Qwest is increasing its long haul network bandwidth from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. The implementation of this upgrade is underway and will continue throughout the following year.
What implications does this have for your company? Qwest provided examples of the speed of 100 Gbps point-to-point network traffic. Imagine downloading 138 DVDs (4.7 Gigabytes each) in just 60 seconds. A 2-hour HD movie or presentation could be transferred in a mere 9 seconds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Telecom Consulting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, many companies are hesitant to hire consultants due to budget constraints. While consultants can potentially save money in the long run, the initial expense can be difficult to justify. So, how can businesses access consulting services without breaking the bank? The answer is free consulting.
One company offers free technical consulting specializing in business telecommunications. By submitting an online inquiry or calling their toll-free number, businesses can connect with a consultant for immediate assistance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-telecom-consulting-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Caps: What They Are and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent internet user, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably encountered data caps. This article explains these usage limits and how to navigate them.
OK, What IS a Data Cap? A data cap restricts the amount of data transferred over a connection within a specific timeframe. Usually set monthly, these limits, measured in MB or GB, reset every 30 days. Activities like browsing, file transfers, and cloud backups consume this data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco's Virtual Teleportation Replaces Airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 21:36:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/</guid><description>Star Trek fans have always dreamed of instantly teleporting to any destination. While true teleportation is still science fiction, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovative technology, TelePresence, offers a virtual solution.
TelePresence allows users to participate in meetings around the world as if they were physically present. High-definition video, superior audio, and a unique virtual table setup create an incredibly realistic experience, making participants feel like they&amp;rsquo;re in the same room, even when separated by vast distances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-virtual-teleportation-replaces-airports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Leverages Your IT Staff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, most companies, including large and well-known ones, are hesitant to increase their staff. This poses a challenge for IT departments, which are often unable to grow to meet rising demands and may face hiring freezes or even staff reductions. How can this situation be managed effectively to prevent a decline in morale and productivity?
One solution is to find a way to increase the output of each team member without negatively impacting their well-being or overloading them with work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Filling Coverage Gaps With High Quality Business Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses in big cities have it easy when it comes to internet and phone service. There are so many options! But what if your business isn&amp;rsquo;t in a big city? What if you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with slow internet and outdated phone lines? You&amp;rsquo;re not out of luck!
Look Up for Better Options
Stop looking for internet and phone service on the ground. Look up! Satellite service is a great option for businesses that need fast, reliable service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Offers Synchronous Service Transport For Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>Need to move massive amounts of data quickly and reliably? Within a building or campus, fiber optic cables provide sufficient speed and capacity. However, for longer distances, you need robust carrier services. Quest&amp;rsquo;s Synchronous Service Transport (SST) offers a solution.
SST utilizes fiber optics and SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) to provide high-speed, point-to-point data transfer. SONET, a dependable carrier service based on Time Division Multiplexing (TDM), was initially designed for telephone companies and later adopted by large organizations requiring extensive bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Wavelengths to Serve You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</guid><description>When your network reaches its maximum capacity, you typically need to upgrade to a faster network with faster components. Upgrading your entire network infrastructure can be extremely expensive. However, with fiber optic networks, you can significantly increase bandwidth within the same cables using a technique called Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM).
WDM allows multiple light beams to transmit data simultaneously over a single fiber optic cable. Each beam operates on a different wavelength, increasing capacity proportionally to the number of beams...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-wavelengths-to-serve-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Escape the High Cost of Bonded T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:17:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The T1 line, a pioneering technology in digital communication, remains relevant for private lines, telephone trunking, and internet access even after fifty years. However, the cost of achieving higher bandwidth by combining multiple lines can be expensive, prompting a search for alternatives.
The Good and the Bad of T1 Lines T1 lines were once the only option, and their 1.5 Mbps symmetrical, full-duplex, and dedicated bandwidth was impressive in its time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-the-high-cost-of-bonded-t1-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheapest T1 On The Block</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/</guid><description>You might think T1 lines are too expensive for your business, but that&amp;rsquo;s not always true. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Originally, T1 lines weren&amp;rsquo;t meant for businesses. Telephone companies developed this &amp;ldquo;T-carrier&amp;rdquo; technology for themselves. However, as the internet grew, so did the need for robust digital communication, which T-carrier services like T1 and DS3 could provide.
Initially, only large corporations used T1 lines because they could easily afford the high cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Curb and Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 21:21:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Copper is quickly disappearing from telecommunications networks, being replaced by fiber optic cabling. While this new cabling might be installed in the same spaces as the old copper, the outdated copper lines are often left behind.
You might be thinking, &amp;ldquo;But I still use copper connections!&amp;rdquo; And it&amp;rsquo;s true that many devices use copper wiring. So where exactly is all this fiber?
Mostly Fiber Outside, Mostly Copper Inside..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-curb-and-premises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Capital Starved Companies Upgrade Technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</guid><description>Even with the economy recovering, securing funds for new technology can be challenging for businesses. Instead of traditional financing, consider &amp;ldquo;hosted solutions&amp;rdquo; or renting technology. This approach avoids large capital investments, allowing businesses to upgrade their systems affordably.
Website hosting is a prime example. Initially, hosting your website on your servers made sense. However, with increased competition, affordable hosting services have become widely available, making it more practical to outsource this function...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Line as an On Ramp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</guid><description>You might know about T1 lines as dedicated connections for digital data or PBX phone lines, but they also serve as excellent access points for various other services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Most businesses maintain a Local Area Network (LAN) and a Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect with the wider world. Your WAN connection often acts as an entry point to larger public or private networks.
A prime example is &amp;ldquo;T1 dedicated Internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Got a Bandwidth Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no limit to how much bandwidth we need, similar to how we always desire more money, health, or chocolate. As we gain more bandwidth, we discover new ways to utilize it. The most sought-after types are wireless, offering flexibility, and fiber optic, providing high capacity. Property owners who provide both to their business tenants might find their properties more appealing than those offering health, wealth, or even delicious chocolate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Need for Low Latency Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</guid><description>When discussing network performance, bandwidth is often the primary focus. Higher bandwidth is equated with faster speeds, allowing for quicker file transfers and increased productivity. However, another crucial aspect of network performance, latency, has gained significant attention recently.
Latency refers to the time delay within a network, specifically the time it takes for data packets to travel between nodes. While it might seem related to bandwidth, latency is a distinct characteristic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet as a DS3 Upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:47:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line provides have historically opted for DS3 service, which offers 45 Mbps. This high-speed digital connection typically runs on a SONET fiber optic circuit, with the final connection to the customer&amp;rsquo;s location installed and maintained by the local phone company. DS3 is fast, very reliable, and more affordable than ever before. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new contender – Fast Ethernet.
Fast Ethernet is a standard Ethernet LAN speed that delivers 100 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-as-a-ds3-upgrade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Router Included With Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</guid><description>Considering upgrading your voice or data bandwidth? DS3 service offers 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads, suitable for demanding tasks like video transfer, medical imaging, or call centers. But finding the right DS3 router for your network can feel like an added burden.
Rest assured, DS3 is a well-established technology with readily available equipment and decreasing prices. As more companies switch from T1 lines to DS3 bandwidth, implementation is becoming increasingly straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Juniper Has Routers For The 100 Gbps WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</guid><description>Verizon and Juniper are partnering on a large-scale project to implement 100 Gbps fiber optic connections to meet the increasing demand for faster internet speeds.
While carriers have experimented with 100 Gbps transmission, which is significantly faster than the typical 10 Gbps long-haul networks, it seems that widespread adoption is on the horizon. Juniper has developed an interface capable of handling this bandwidth directly, eliminating the need for carriers to combine multiple links...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP VPN vs MPLS VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Data security within a cloud network is crucial. Constructing a Wide Area Network (WAN) with dedicated private lines offers robust security against observation and tampering. Alternatively, a Virtual Private Network (VPN) utilizes shared resources, providing a more cost-effective solution.
Dedicated private lines provide complete control over access and resource allocation, eliminating concerns about competition for bandwidth. Encryption during transmission adds an extra layer of security, albeit at a higher cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-vpn-vs-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Networks Need Denser Wavelength Multiplexing To Meet Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</guid><description>Despite the economic downturn, fiber optic network providers are experiencing a surge in demand. However, instead of widespread digging, they are leveraging technology to boost capacity on existing infrastructure.
XO Communications, a leading fiber optic network provider, recently revealed plans to double its capacity per fiber strand using Infinera&amp;rsquo;s optical line equipment. The Infinera Line System 2 increases the channel count for C-band fiber optic systems from 80 to 160, resulting in an extra 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-networks-need-denser-wavelength-multiplexing-to-meet-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maxed Out On Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 23:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your business pushing the limits of its WAN bandwidth? Are you facing network congestion during peak hours? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are solutions to improve your situation.
Start by evaluating your network efficiency. Are you using quality of service management, or are you simply hoping for the best? Prioritizing voice packets can resolve issues with VoIP calls without impacting other processes.
Consider the timing of bandwidth-heavy tasks. Running backups to remote sites during peak hours can hinder employee productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maxed-out-on-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Bandwidth Can Affect Productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 12:39:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</guid><description>Businesses are grappling with decisions about bandwidth allocation, often facing costs calculated per Megabit per second (Mbps). While strategies exist to maximize Mbps per dollar, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to first understand the correlation between network bandwidth and employee productivity.
If your bandwidth is primarily used for non-work activities, reducing it might seem like a productivity booster. However, most businesses rely heavily on internal and external network connectivity for operations. So, how do you determine the appropriate bandwidth level?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-can-affect-productivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Lines For MPLS Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</guid><description>Companies needing to link numerous locations are increasingly choosing MPLS networks, often finding T1 lines to be the optimal solution for network access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Consider an MPLS (Multi Protocol Label Switching) network as a private internet. This private ownership allows the MPLS operator to guarantee the bandwidth and service quality needed for your applications&amp;rsquo; reliable operation. Security is also strengthened as access is exclusive to subscribing businesses.
An MPLS network functions as a customized cloud, connecting only your specified locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lines-for-mpls-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There Will Be Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</guid><description>The 19th and 20th centuries were defined by the gold rush and oil boom, respectively. Similarly, the 21st century is witnessing a fiber optic revolution. Fiber optic communication has become essential for modern businesses. This era presents lucrative opportunities for entrepreneurs to capitalize on the insatiable demand for high-bandwidth communication. A new technology has emerged, promising to reshape the competitive landscape.
Consider a scenario where two telecommunications providers are discussing the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LMDS Fills the Fiber Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</guid><description>Although fiber optic bandwidth is widely available across the country, connecting businesses to this network over the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; is a different story. It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to realize that less than 20% of commercial buildings are equipped for fiber optic telecommunications services.
This is primarily due to the high cost of installing fiber optic cables, a process that&amp;rsquo;s difficult to justify when businesses already have access to telephone and data services through existing copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1's for Business Parks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</guid><description>Most businesses require reliable communication services, but options can be limited outside of major city centers. While downtown areas boast a variety of high-speed internet providers, businesses in industrial parks often face fewer choices.
Similar to essential utilities, reliable internet access is crucial for modern businesses. However, many older industrial parks were developed before the internet&amp;rsquo;s prominence, lacking the infrastructure for high-speed connections.
Despite this, businesses in these areas still have reliable options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1s-for-business-parks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bonded T1 Solution Increases Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</guid><description>A 1.5 Mbps T1 bandwidth has long been a standard for small businesses, often proving sufficient for their needs. Some businesses even utilize an Integrated T1 solution for combined internet and telephone services. However, as bandwidth demands increase, many find T1 bandwidth limiting their productivity.
A simple solution to increase bandwidth is adding a second T1 line, doubling it to 3 Mbps. However, for these lines to function as a single, larger line, they should be ordered from the same provider with a &amp;ldquo;bonded T1 solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who Needs A T1 Line at Home?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 12:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</guid><description>T1 lines are famous for their reliability and accessibility wherever there&amp;rsquo;s telephone service, but they might not be suitable for everyone&amp;rsquo;s home broadband needs. The cost alone is a major deterrent for most people. However, in some situations, a T1 line might be the only practical option.
Residential broadband prioritizes affordability to reach a broad market. That&amp;rsquo;s why DSL services can cost under $20 monthly, and Cable broadband with 3 to 6 Mbps typically costs $30 to $40...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SD-WAN vs MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 06:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The landscape of information technology and businesses has undergone significant changes recently, primarily due to the shift towards cloud-based computing and as-a-service models. Network infrastructure, however, has been slow to adapt, but is now changing due to cost and cloud architecture influences.
Traditional WANs: Connecting with Individual Lines
Before MPLS, businesses relied on dedicated point-to-point lines like T1, DS3, and fiber optic circuits for connectivity. While straightforward for connecting two locations, this method became complex and expensive as more offices and facilities were added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sd-wan-vs-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be Part of Your SD-WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networks (SDN) and Software Defined Wide Area Networks (SD-WAN) are seeing increased implementation due to their ability to offer cost-effective, high-quality bandwidth for businesses. SD-WAN is sometimes the sole option for acceptable bandwidth in remote or rural locations. These software-defined networks act as a blend of various connection technologies, intelligently maximizing the use of each available connection, including satellite.
The Need For SD Networks
Traditionally, connecting to the internet or a cloud service provider involved ordering a &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection from a business location or a dedicated point-to-point line between two points, like an office and a cloud provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-part-of-your-sd-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cure The Bulging T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</guid><description>Not too long ago, you got your first T1 line. It was impressive with its 1.5 Mbps speed for both uploading and downloading. The connection was reliable, and there was a guarantee for quick assistance if any issues arose. Though a bit pricey, it was worth it, and you believed it would last forever. However, lately, that once-speedy connection has slowed to a crawl. So, what now?
Many businesses are facing the issue of overloaded T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why GHz is So Last Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 09:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</guid><description>GigaHertz, representing a billion cycles per second, has become the standard, making MegaHertz seem outdated. However, as technology advances, even GigaHertz might be surpassed by TeraHertz speeds, potentially rendering current benchmarks obsolete.
In the early days of personal computers, 640 KB of RAM seemed excessive. However, as software evolved, demanding more resources with graphics, images, and the rise of the internet, hardware struggled to keep up. It took decades for platforms to mature and offer sufficient RAM, hard drive space, and processor speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tired of Flaky Internet Connections?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</guid><description>Running a business is challenging when your tools are unreliable. You would think technology would make things easier, but it often has the opposite effect. As processes become more complex and interconnected, they seem to become less dependable. A simple cash transaction can turn into an e-commerce nightmare. Why can&amp;rsquo;t things just work flawlessly all the time?
While expecting perfection might be unrealistic, your business systems should function seamlessly most of the time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Can GigE Bandwidth Do For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly common in local area networks, with network cards and backbones now supporting these higher speeds. Companies that rely heavily on digital processes and high bandwidth data transfers are likely already using Gigabit Ethernet. However, they need a way to extend these high-speed transfers beyond their local networks.
Companies with large numbers of employees, extensive customer bases, or applications that generate significant amounts of data can benefit from Gigabit Ethernet WAN connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Broadband and Phone Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 17:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses require both internet and phone service. While ordering these services separately remains an option, businesses now have more choices.
Bundled services, offering both phone and internet, often make the most sense for smaller businesses with limited needs and budgets. Two primary bundled options provide cost savings compared to separate services.
The first option, known as Integrated T1 or SIP Trunking, utilizes line sharing but differs in connection methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-broadband-and-phone-comparison/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Need a Fiber Optic WAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</guid><description>As your company grows, you might find that your internet connection, cloud services, and connections between offices are slowing down. It might be time to upgrade your bandwidth before things get sluggish. But what should you get? More of what you already have or something new?
Outdated Connections Are Holding You Back When your business was starting out, networking was mostly about connecting computers and printers in the same office, with a basic connection to the outside world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-fiber-optic-wan-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying Out of the Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</guid><description>While the use of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is widespread in information technology, understanding its complexities is crucial. The cloud often represents large, intricate networks that users may not fully comprehend.
Although many users are content with the cloud&amp;rsquo;s seemingly magical abilities, David G. Rusin, CEO of American Fiber Systems, argues against perceiving internet clouds as uniform entities. He emphasizes the differences in integrity, reliability, and delivery among cloud providers, highlighting the importance of scrutinizing these aspects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Audio Interview With Adam Edwards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</guid><description>Telarus, Inc. is considered a leading innovator in telecommunications marketing since the major telecom expansion of the 1990s. The company has transformed how businesses purchase services like T1, Ethernet, and other high-speed internet options.
I recently spoke with Adam Edwards, Telarus&amp;rsquo;s president, to understand the company&amp;rsquo;s success as a top master agency. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share an MP3 recording of our conversation so you can hear directly from Adam instead of reading a transcript...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speeds Without DS3 Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</guid><description>Businesses needing substantial bandwidth for tasks like online commerce, video streaming, medical data transfer, or dedicated internet access have historically relied on DS3 connections. These provided speeds exceeding T1 lines. However, a new option delivers comparable speeds without the high price tag: Metro Ethernet and Carrier Ethernet.
These terms represent regional and long-distance high-bandwidth transport services using the Ethernet protocol. An Ethernet WAN connection connects your LAN to another business location, a network of multiple locations, or a dedicated high-speed internet connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Metro and Long Haul Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 16:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies with multiple locations and many employees may find that standard internet and private lines are insufficient for their needs. At a certain point, having complete control over your network becomes desirable, allowing you to establish performance benchmarks and implement upgrades as needed.
This sounds great, but how can you maintain the same level of control over a network that extends beyond your physical premises? Should you become your own network provider and install fiber optic cable to all your locations?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/metro-and-long-haul-dark-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Will Light Your Building</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</guid><description>Ethernet has become the preferred option for WAN (Wide Area Networking), moving beyond its established role in LAN networks. It makes sense to extend your LAN using the same standards both internally and for connecting to remote locations or the internet.
A key advantage is cost-effectiveness as bandwidth needs grow. While a 1.54 Mbps T1 line might cost around $450 per month ($292.20 per Mbps), a 45 Mbps DS3 connection could cost $5,000 per month ($111...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unlimited Internet's Days are Numbered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</guid><description>Remember the golden age of air travel? You could stroll into an airport right before your flight, effortlessly purchase a ticket, and enjoy luxurious treatment onboard. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a different story. We endure long lines and cramped seats, a far cry from the preferential treatment of the past. Sadly, this shift from luxury to cattle car is coming soon to the internet.
You might be skeptical. After all, the internet has felt limitless for over a decade...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips To Reduce Your Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses are facing a challenging time as they grapple with the fluctuating economic landscape brought on by the Covid-19 crisis. While growth was once the primary focus, survival has now taken center stage, making cost control paramount. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some immediate steps you can take to reduce expenses without jeopardizing operations.
Are You Paying For Unused Services?
It might seem improbable, but both individuals and businesses frequently pay for services they don&amp;rsquo;t utilize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Speed Challenged By EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 01:59:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</guid><description>When a company needs more bandwidth than its T1 lines can provide, the typical upgrade has been to DS3. However, DS3 is usually delivered through fiber optic SONET connections, which can be costly to install unless a building is already equipped for fiber optic services. A new service called EoC offers a potential solution by providing DS3 speeds over existing copper telephone wiring.
EoC stands for Ethernet over Copper. It delivers high bandwidth services, up to DS3 levels of 45 Mbps, without needing fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speed-challenged-by-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Network Cameras for Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-network-cameras-for-security/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-network-cameras-for-security/</guid><description>Most businesses need security cameras. While older models typically provide video output to monitors and recorders, advancements in camera technology now allow for network connectivity.
IP or network cameras have a built-in processor and network interface card, enabling access from any location on the network. This means you can use a web browser to view your security camera footage from anywhere globally, providing peace of mind and the ability to respond promptly to incidents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-network-cameras-for-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-network-cameras-for-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber WAN is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 17:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that your business needs the speed of fiber optic WAN service to ensure cloud-based applications are responsive and your team stays productive. However, you may have struggled to find this service in the past. It&amp;rsquo;s time to try again.
Why Is Fiber More Accessible Now?
Fiber optic used to be a rare and costly option limited to large corporations. You had to rely on the telephone company and hope they serviced your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-wan-is-closer-than-you-think/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>