<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Image on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/image/</link><description>Recent content in Image on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/image/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instaviz 2.0, a tool for conceptualizing iOS, makes its debut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 19:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</guid><description>Pixelglow Software, a company known for creating user-friendly business software, has released Instaviz 2.0. Initially launched in December 2008, Instaviz is a leading diagramming app for iOS that enables users to visualize, refine, and share their ideas.
[Image of Instaviz diagram]
Source: Pixelglow Software. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Instaviz consistently ranks among the top 100 business apps on the App Store, boasting over 17,700 downloads and an average user rating of three and a half stars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instaviz-2-0-a-tool-for-conceptualizing-ios-makes-its-debut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi has teamed up with Telenor to provide its subscribers with a complimentary image storage service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 04:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</guid><description>Telenor, through Digi, has launched Capture, a free mobile app and cloud storage service for backing up images and videos.
Capture allows users to automatically save and back up photos and videos from their devices, safeguarding memories if their phone is lost or needs to be replaced. It also provides additional storage, especially useful for entry-level devices with limited capacity.
Non-Digi customers can download and utilize Capture with 2GB of free storage space...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-has-teamed-up-with-telenor-to-provide-its-subscribers-with-a-complimentary-image-storage-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ImageCrowd has identified a market opportunity for an Asian stock photography marketplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/</guid><description>ImageCrowd, a new multilingual platform, wants to make it easier to find Asian photography. They connect international buyers with Asian photographers in their native languages. Buyers can make specific image requests, and ImageCrowd will crowdsource photographers to find the perfect match. Both professional and amateur photographers can submit photos. Any photos not purchased are added to a stock photography database.
&amp;ldquo;These days, visual campaigns need to be highly targeted,&amp;rdquo; says Gijs Waverijn, CEO of ImageCrowd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imagecrowd-has-identified-a-market-opportunity-for-an-asian-stock-photography-marketplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to a global survey by YouGov, body confidence increases with age</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 19:45:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</guid><description>A recent global survey by YouGov revealed that most adults feel content with their weight and body image, and this satisfaction generally increases with age. However, the survey also highlighted a widespread concern that celebrity culture negatively impacts young people&amp;rsquo;s body image across almost all countries surveyed.
The survey, spanning the US, Australia, and most of Europe and the Asia Pacific region, found that older individuals are considerably more likely to feel satisfied with their bodies compared to those in their twenties and thirties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-a-global-survey-by-yougov-body-confidence-increases-with-age/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AC Works introduces Korean versions of free stock image websites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 15:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</guid><description>Source: AC works. Screen capture of illustAC.
AC works, a company with over 2.3 million users in Japan, is expanding globally. They recently introduced Korean versions of their popular stock image platforms: photoAC, illustAC, and silhouetteAC.
The stock image industry has historically been restrictive, often imposing fees for various uses of a single image. Costs are common for both the stock images themselves and their vector files. Purchased images typically come with limited usage rights, like a single use within a specific advertising campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-works-introduces-korean-versions-of-free-stock-image-websites/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>