<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ATA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ata/</link><description>Recent content in ATA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ata/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted VoIP Solutions Include New Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</guid><description>Cloud services are changing how we think about technology. Just like server racks are moving to the cloud, so are office phone systems. Traditional PBX systems are being replaced by cloud-hosted solutions. But this transition begs the question: what happens to the physical phone lines?
Similar to connecting data servers off-site, a connection called a SIP Trunk links your on-premise network to the hosted PBX. While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to use existing analog phones with adapters, this approach misses out on the advanced features of Voice over IP (VoIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Super Cheap Business Phone Service for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 05:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the economy slowly recovers, controlling business expenses, including phone bills, remains crucial. Many businesses find themselves overspending on phone services.
Businesses often begin with a single traditional phone line. As they expand, they might add cordless phones sharing that line or install a second line. While sufficient for small offices, this setup lacks the features and cost savings of PBX or enterprise VoIP systems.
Fortunately, small businesses can utilize network voice solutions, also known as VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), to reduce phone costs significantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/super-cheap-business-phone-service-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need A Special Phone For VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:19:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</guid><description>Many people ask if a special phone is required for VoIP service. The answer depends on the situation.
Regular phones can&amp;rsquo;t plug directly into internet equipment because they use incompatible connectors. To bridge this gap, you need a special phone or an adapter.
Many residential and small business VoIP services, like PhonePower, offer adapters. These adapters allow you to connect your existing phone to your internet modem or router. Inside the adapter, circuitry converts the analog signals of your phone into digital packets for the internet, and vice versa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Residential and Small Business VoIP Rates Crushed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</guid><description>In recent years, VoIP telephony, also known as broadband phone service, has transformed from a niche computer application into a major competitor to traditional telephone services. This shift is largely due to the widespread adoption of broadband internet and its increased availability to small businesses. As a result of increased broadband access, there&amp;rsquo;s been a surge in VoIP providers, with Phone Power emerging as a major player. Phone Power is disrupting the industry by offering unlimited residential and small home-based business service plans for less than $15 per month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Try VoIP Phone Service For Under $10 a Month</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/</guid><description>Ever considered trying out those new VoIP phone services to see if they&amp;rsquo;re better than your old landline? The ads are tempting, offering combined local and long-distance billing, tons of features without extra charges, and cheap international rates. It all sounds great and much cheaper than your current plan.
Hesitations are understandable. Will you like the service? Will it work well with your internet? Maybe long-term contracts, especially at $40-$50 a month, aren&amp;rsquo;t appealing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SOHO VoIP Phone Service With Two Lines at $8.33/mo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</guid><description>Looking for affordable business or home phone service with great features? Imagine paying just $8.33 a month for a two-line system! This incredible price is possible through VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol) technology, which uses your existing broadband connection for phone calls.
Competitive providers like Phone Power offer this technology at unbeatable rates. You don&amp;rsquo;t need special equipment—simply plug your existing phones into an adapter that allows two simultaneous calls. This means no more waiting for someone to hang up!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soho-voip-phone-service-with-two-lines-at-833mo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Analog Telephone Adaptor Enables VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</guid><description>Analog Telephone Adapters (ATAs) bridge the gap between traditional analog phones and Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) technology. They essentially trick both the phone and the internet connection into thinking they&amp;rsquo;re interacting with familiar systems.
On one side, the ATA connects to a regular phone using a standard RJ-11 jack, providing the necessary power and signals like dial tone and caller ID. It also translates the phone&amp;rsquo;s touch-tone signals into a digital format for VoIP communication using the Session Initiation Protocol (SIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-analog-telephone-adaptor-enables-voip/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>