<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UK Constitutional Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-constitutional-law/</link><description>Recent content in UK Constitutional Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/uk-constitutional-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is this the beginning of the end for citizens' rights in the Brexit 'Sufficient Progress' deal?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-this-the-beginning-of-the-end-for-citizens-rights-in-the-brexit-sufficient-progress-deal/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The recent joint report on Brexit negotiations, along with accompanying documents, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of discussions. This phase will center around a transition period and the framework for the future relationship between the UK and the EU.
Although a political rather than legal document, this report holds significant practical relevance for the withdrawal agreement. It outlines agreed-upon details concerning citizens&amp;rsquo; rights, the Irish border, the financial settlement, and concluding rules.</description></item><item><title>Divergent rulings on Parliament's suspension in England and Scotland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergent-rulings-on-parliament-s-suspension-in-england-and-scotland/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk.
The A-Z of Scots Law: From Avizandum to the Zany Antics of Boris Johnson
Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s recent actions are under scrutiny by the Scottish legal system. In the Cherry case, the Scottish court deemed the decision to suspend Parliament unlawful. Further legal action is anticipated regarding the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s reported refusal to adhere to the European Union (Withdrawal) (No.</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item><item><title>Reading between the lines of the High Court's Brexit ruling: Protecting EU transnational rights and their safeguards.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 08:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reading-between-the-lines-of-the-high-court-s-brexit-ruling-protecting-eu-transnational-rights-and-their-safeguards/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia, Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
This piece revisits the recent High Court ruling on the UK government&amp;rsquo;s authority to initiate the process of leaving the EU. It delves deeper into the judgment&amp;rsquo;s EU law implications, going beyond the political turmoil it has caused and potentially extending beyond the immediate consequences of Brexit. The article argues that the judgment, though focused on UK constitutional law, also touches upon the issue of safeguarding transnational rights, such as those of British citizens in other EU countries, during a Member State&amp;rsquo;s withdrawal.</description></item></channel></rss>