<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ad on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ad/</link><description>Recent content in Ad on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions.</description></item></channel></rss>