<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Certificate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/certificate/</link><description>Recent content in Certificate on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/certificate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>