<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Maldives on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/maldives/</link><description>Recent content in Maldives on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/maldives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AccorHotels establishes a high-end presence in the Maldives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>AccorHotels is entering the Maldives market with its first luxury resort there, the Dhevanafushi Maldives Luxury Resort. Located on the private island of Meradhoo, the resort will undergo improvements in late 2018 and subsequently become part of the prestigious Raffles brand.
Currently, the resort offers 21 island villas and 16 ocean villas, all with private pools. Guests can enjoy three restaurants and a variety of amenities and activities for relaxation and rejuvenation, such as a luxurious spa, an overwater fitness center, yoga classes, watersports, and private dining options.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir will enhance Singapore Airlines' offerings to Male</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</guid><description>Source: SilkAir. Male.
Starting October 25, 2015, SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will introduce four weekly flights to Male, Maldives. Previously, Singapore Airlines operated between 10 and 14 flights per week to Male. With the addition of SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s new flights, the two airlines will jointly offer two daily round trips, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, highlighted the benefits of this collaboration: “By coordinating the networks of both carriers, we can provide our customers with more choices and flexibility when planning their travel.</description></item><item><title>New sculptures have been added to the Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi Coralarium</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 03:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-sculptures-have-been-added-to-the-fairmont-maldives-sirru-fen-fushi-coralarium/</guid><description>The Fairmont Maldives Sirru Fen Fushi resort has added new sculptures to its Coralarium, an underwater art installation that doubles as the Maldives&amp;rsquo; first and only coral regeneration project. This structure, now teeming with marine life, serves as an artificial reef.
The abstract sculptures, conceived by environmentalist and eco-artist Jason deCaires Taylor, draw inspiration from the natural beauty of coral reefs and are designed to resemble coral colonies. These ten partially submerged plinths, reaching heights of up to 5 meters, aim to raise awareness about endangered ecosystems, educate visitors about marine life, and help rehabilitate the reef.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Guests are invited by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi to discover the house reef</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 17:15:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-are-invited-by-jumeirah-dhevanafushi-to-discover-the-house-reef/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. Underwater view of a reef.
Jumeirah Dhevanafushi, a secluded resort at the southernmost point of the Maldives, has launched a new &amp;ldquo;Underwater Snorkeling Adventure&amp;rdquo; experience, allowing guests to explore the resort&amp;rsquo;s own reef.
This package provides a guided opportunity to discover some of the planet&amp;rsquo;s most impressive coral reefs. Led by Jumeirah Dhevanafushi&amp;rsquo;s resident marine biologist, guests can explore the reefs surrounding the heart-shaped Meradhoo island, situated on the Gaafu Alifu Atoll.</description></item></channel></rss>