<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Transport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-transport/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Transport on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Juniper Has Routers For The 100 Gbps WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</guid><description>Verizon and Juniper are partnering on a large-scale project to implement 100 Gbps fiber optic connections to meet the increasing demand for faster internet speeds.
While carriers have experimented with 100 Gbps transmission, which is significantly faster than the typical 10 Gbps long-haul networks, it seems that widespread adoption is on the horizon. Juniper has developed an interface capable of handling this bandwidth directly, eliminating the need for carriers to combine multiple links...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/juniper-has-routers-for-the-100-gbps-wan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet From Coast To Coast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</guid><description>Imagine your current office Ethernet network expanding beyond the building, connecting your locations across the city and the country. This vision of a unified, nationwide network is now a reality with Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet is essentially the same Ethernet used in local networks, but enhanced and standardized for use in metropolitan and long-distance networks.
To get Carrier Ethernet, businesses need to partner with a network provider offering this service. These providers typically have built extensive, nationwide fiber optic networks with service points in major cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>