<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>112TTBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/112ttbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 112TTBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/112ttbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>Following the repair of the MMC cartridge mount on the Beogram 4000, attention shifted to the malfunctioning arm lowering and tracking mechanisms.
The arm lowering system, comprising a solenoid and damper, was examined. The damper and its associated linkages were removed for cleaning and lubrication.
Inspection revealed the absence of a vital rubber washer in the damper unit, substituted with a makeshift transparency foil piece. This modification hindered proper damper function.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Floating Chassis, Arm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-floating-chassis-arm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>The next steps were to make adjustments to the platter, sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking weight. Additional information on this process is available on my Beogram 4000 page, which includes posts and videos. Before starting, I needed to replace the cabinet guiding washers because they were either damaged or replaced with unsuitable substitutes.
[Image of a missing cabinet guidance washer]
A video demonstrating this process is available in my Beogram 4002 playlist on my YouTube channel.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: RPM Performance Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</guid><description>I recently measured the RPM performance of my restored Beogram 4000 turntable. I was curious to see how the AC motor compared to the DC motors found in other models, like the Beogram 8000/8002 with their computer-controlled linear motors. After running the 4000 for 12 hours using my BeoloverRPM device, the results were interesting.
The AC motor demonstrated excellent stability, as evidenced by the graph. However, there was an initial period of drift as both the oscillator and motor warmed up.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured.</description></item></channel></rss>