<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ac/</link><description>Recent content in AC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:34:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000 AC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 AC platter motor from Massachusetts that had a knocking sound. Adjusting the voltage and tilt did not fix the problem. To address this, I typically disassemble the motor and submerge the housing parts in motor oil. Using a vacuum, I ensure the oil fills the material pores. Below is a picture of the motor upon arrival:
I drilled out the rivets and disassembled the motor:</description></item><item><title>Asians struggle with their comfort levels when it comes to using air conditioning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</guid><description>A Hong Kong-based startup, Ambi Labs, has initiated a crowdsourcing campaign for their latest product, Ambi Climate. This innovative device is designed to optimize air conditioning systems based on two years of user feedback gathered from ten Asian markets.
Source: Ambi Labs.
Ambi Labs conducted extensive online surveys across ten major Asian markets, engaging with over 4,000 participants. The findings revealed that the most significant challenge with air conditioners lies in maintaining a comfortable room temperature.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Chassis Springs and the Platter Height</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-chassis-springs-and-the-platter-height/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 03:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-chassis-springs-and-the-platter-height/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing into the final cosmetic stage. With the turntable functioning correctly, the focus is now on refining the exterior and replacing minor parts like the plug. Currently, I am fine-tuning the platter height, tilt, and the leaf springs supporting the turntable&amp;rsquo;s floating chassis. This is a delicate process with many interconnected factors. The sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s alignment, platter angle, transport lock travel, and belt tension all need to be perfect for the platter to be level, centered, and parallel to the arms, all while ensuring the chassis clears the open locks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 23:23:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-ac-motor/</guid><description>I noticed a knocking sound coming from my Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s AC motor, which meant the Oilite brass bearing needed lubrication. These bearings are designed to release oil onto the motor shaft over time. Eventually, they need to be replaced or re-lubricated. Using a food vacuum sealer and a mason jar, you can replenish the oil. Here&amp;rsquo;s how I did it:
First, I removed the motor.
Next, I removed the two rivets holding the motor together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of 'Knocking' AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</guid><description>I prefer to thoroughly test restored Beograms to ensure they&amp;rsquo;re free of intermittent issues. It&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for new problems to appear with regular use. This was the case with a recently restored AC motor Beogram 4002 (5501). After playing a few records, I detected a faint knocking sound coming from inside the turntable. Upon removing the aluminum plates, I discovered the knocking synchronized with the AC motor&amp;rsquo;s rotation. Adjusting the motor tilt provided temporary noise reduction, but the knocking always returned, intensifying with each record played until it was noticeable during quieter tracks—an unacceptable issue for a turntable!</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Adjustment of AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-adjustment-of-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>After restoring the electronics of a Beogram 4000 turntable, attention turned to the AC platter motor. This model features an older pulley design without built-in belt guards, relying instead on separate guards added to the motor mounting posts. These added guards are not essential, as the pulley&amp;rsquo;s shape effectively secures the belt. Motor tilt allows for adjustments to the belt&amp;rsquo;s vertical positioning.
Like the DC motors in later Beogram models, the AC motors can also suffer from dried-out bearings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 AC Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-ac-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-ac-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained an AC platter motor from a Beogram 4002 turntable to refurbish. Here&amp;rsquo;s what the motor looked like initially:
After taking off the pulley, I drilled out the rivets to disassemble the motor and take out the rotor and coil carriers:
Next, I submerged the motor housing parts in motor oil and created a vacuum:
This caused bubbling as air escaped from the assembly. The bubbling stopped after 24 hours, at which point I cleaned the parts and reassembled the motor.</description></item></channel></rss>