<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Over Fiber on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-over-fiber/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Over Fiber on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-over-fiber/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lit Buildings Have Near Infinite Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-have-near-infinite-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing a business location, consider &amp;ldquo;lit buildings&amp;rdquo; for their exceptional connectivity. These buildings are already equipped with fiber optic internet infrastructure, offering a solution to bandwidth concerns.
What Does &amp;ldquo;Lit Building&amp;rdquo; Mean?
&amp;ldquo;Lit building&amp;rdquo; signifies a building pre-wired for fiber optic internet and potentially point-to-point bandwidth services. The term &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; references the laser beams used to transmit digital signals at high speeds through fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider.</description></item><item><title>Is 5G Bandwidth Slicing The New Private Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet is great for connecting, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always reliable. While it provides widespread access, low costs, and supports most applications, it can fall short when high performance and reliability are crucial. Issues like latency, packet loss, and congestion can hinder or even prevent interactive applications from working correctly. The solution? Private networks.
What is a Private Network?
The internet is a public network, accessible to almost anyone.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 02:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Metropolitan and wide area networks are getting faster. Undersea cables are moving from 10 to 40 and even 100 Gbps, and land-based fiber lines are already at 100 Gbps. This means large companies, healthcare organizations, and video producers are starting to find their networks inadequate. The good news is that there are more affordable options than ever before.
There are several practical ways to boost your MAN or WAN bandwidth beyond one Gigabit per second, up to 10 Gbps.</description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth is Closer Than You Think</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 15:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-is-closer-than-you-think/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
There are many more options for internet connectivity than there were just a few years ago. Don&amp;rsquo;t assume that T1 lines are the be-all and end-all without exploring your options. You might be surprised!
Increased Bandwidth is Necessary Fiber optic bandwidth has been discussed as a future necessity for years. When you examine the applications that are most used by consumers and businesses, it is obvious that only fiber can accommodate their bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Fiber Needed By Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</guid><description>While many believe fiber optic bandwidth is the way of the future, it&amp;rsquo;s already a smart choice for businesses today.
Traditionally, businesses have depended on copper-based telecom services. The copper wiring integrated during a building&amp;rsquo;s construction becomes the backbone for multi-line phone systems, ISDN digital trunking for PBX systems, and T1 lines connecting offices and providing broadband internet. This infrastructure has been the standard for many small and medium-sized businesses for decades.</description></item><item><title>Data Caps: What They Are and How to Avoid Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 11:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-caps-what-they-are-and-how-to-avoid-them/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re a frequent internet user, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably encountered data caps. This article explains these usage limits and how to navigate them.
OK, What IS a Data Cap? A data cap restricts the amount of data transferred over a connection within a specific timeframe. Usually set monthly, these limits, measured in MB or GB, reset every 30 days. Activities like browsing, file transfers, and cloud backups consume this data.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (EoDWDM)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-dense-wavelength-division-multiplexing-eodwdm-/</guid><description>Large organizations with high bandwidth needs, such as financial institutions and research labs, often require more capacity than standard telecom services offer. Building a custom fiber network by installing owned or leased dark fiber is one solution. Another is leasing wavelengths on existing fiber infrastructure.
Your Own Fiber Installing fiber optic cable on your own property provides control over both the physical space and network assets. However, construction costs increase significantly beyond your premises, especially when obtaining right-of-way permissions.</description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service.</description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Fiber Replaces Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 02:23:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-fiber-replaces-bonded-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T1 lines have been a popular connectivity solution for businesses for many years due to their reliability and flexibility in private lines, dedicated internet access, and telephone trunking. However, with the increasing demands of cloud applications and HD video, the fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps has become a significant limitation.
Solution #1: Bonded T1 Lines
One way to increase bandwidth is to combine multiple T1 lines. This can be achieved using a WAN aggregation device or by ordering bonded T1 lines from a provider.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment.</description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Cost Saving Shared Fiber, Wireless and Coax</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 06:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-saving-shared-fiber-wireless-and-coax/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You need to get your business online but are worried about the cost. Rest assured, there are affordable ways to get connected without breaking the bank. Shared bandwidth options like wireless, cable, and fiber optic connections offer budget-friendly solutions. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options.
What is Shared Bandwidth?
Think of shared bandwidth like splitting the cost of living with roommates. Just as you share expenses to afford something expensive, internet connections can be shared to reduce costs.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices.</description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price.</description></item></channel></rss>