<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lambda on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lambda/</link><description>Recent content in Lambda on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lambda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Private Networking With Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-networking-with-wavelength-services/</guid><description>As companies expand, they often reach a point where traditional telecom services fall short. This leads IT departments to consider purchasing or leasing dark fiber for enhanced bandwidth, latency, and control. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option worth exploring: managed wavelength services.
In simple terms, a wavelength is a distinct color or lambda on a fiber optic strand. Fiber optic lines transmit multiple light beams simultaneously, with each color representing a unique wavelength or frequency of laser light.</description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward.</description></item></channel></rss>