<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marketing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marketing/</link><description>Recent content in Marketing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delta is launching Delta Innovation Classes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines has devised a novel method for premium customers to distinguish themselves and share contact information, using a compelling offer.
As stated on the Delta Innovation Class website, the airline is offering a &amp;ldquo;mentoring program – that just so happens to take place at 35,000 feet.&amp;rdquo;
This program, Delta Innovation Class, a play on flight classes, gives one fortunate customer a complimentary seat next to a notable figure or celebrity on a designated flight.</description></item><item><title>Singapore gets a sneak peek at the HUAWEI Mate 20 icon before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. The square icon at various malls in
Singapore.
People in Singapore were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through an unexpected display of an illuminated square icon projected onto buildings throughout the city over the weekend.
This symbolic imagery appeared on structures in various locations such as Raffles City, Bugis Junction, Bugis+, and Plaza Singapura.
This readily identifiable square represents the phone&amp;rsquo;s camera setup, which includes a Leica Triple Camera and flash seamlessly integrated into the back of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series smartphones.</description></item><item><title>Add a Toll Free Number For Next to Nothing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 11:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-a-toll-free-number-for-next-to-nothing/</guid><description>Upgrading your business phone system can be pricey, but there&amp;rsquo;s a budget-friendly way to add a toll-free number to any phone, even your cell phone, for a minimal monthly cost.
Toll-free numbers are beneficial for businesses with a public phone number. Local customers can call without long-distance charges, but even calls from nearby areas can become expensive. Out-of-state prospects might hesitate to call due to high long-distance rates.
Offering a toll-free number encourages calls from anywhere, as the business covers the cost.</description></item><item><title>Global marketing summit for Malaysian entrepreneurs hosted by INSKEN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-marketing-summit-for-malaysian-entrepreneurs-hosted-by-insken/</guid><description>Source: INSKEN. Firdaus delivered
welcome remarks at GMS 2018.
Now in its second year, the Institut Keusahawanan Negara&amp;rsquo;s (INSKEN) annual Global Marketing Summit (GMS) seeks to cultivate innovative leaders within the Malaysian entrepreneurial landscape.
Malaysian Minister Datuk Seri Mohd Redzuan Yusof highlighted the ongoing emphasis on fostering the expansion of entrepreneurs and small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), particularly those in the B40 and M40 income brackets. He stated that the Ministry of Entrepreneur Development (MED) will leverage allocated funds to execute a targeted and comprehensive entrepreneur development strategy in 2019.</description></item><item><title>HubSpot reveals the secrets of inbound marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot presentation. A higher volume of content leads to increased lead generation.
Ryan Bonnici, HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan, argues that traditional methods of customer acquisition are no longer effective. During the launch of HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Singapore office, which also serves as the company&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters, Bonnici explained the effectiveness of inbound marketing compared to outbound marketing.
Traditionally, marketing involved bombarding consumers with advertisements and flyers.</description></item><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation.</description></item><item><title>Tell Me You're Not PAYING For Equipment Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</guid><description>Stop wasting money on expensive equipment leads that often lead nowhere.
There&amp;rsquo;s a smarter way to generate sales and marketing leads for your telephone systems and IT networking equipment: commission-based leads. This means you receive qualified leads from serious businesses in your area as they emerge, completely free of charge. You then select the leads you want to pursue and focus your efforts on closing the deal. Only after a successful sale and payment from the customer do you share a small percentage with the agency that provided the lead.</description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans.</description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats.</description></item><item><title>Adobe provides a list of suggestions for creating email campaigns that are optimized for mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-provides-a-list-of-suggestions-for-creating-email-campaigns-that-are-optimized-for-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Adobe&amp;rsquo;s recent email survey suggests that email is not going away anytime soon, at least not in the United States. The survey, which focused on American white-collar workers, revealed that individuals frequently check both their personal and work email. Interestingly, smartphones have surpassed computers as the preferred device for email access. This trend is likely even more pronounced in Asia, a region with high mobile device adoption rates. A study by Experian highlighted that email remains a leading marketing channel in Singapore, especially for driving online traffic to physical stores.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users.</description></item><item><title>Sony Electronics Singapore is marking the first anniversary of the Sony Store with a celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-electronics-singapore-is-marking-the-first-anniversary-of-the-sony-store-with-a-celebration/</guid><description>Source: Sony Electronics Singapore. Sony Singapore’s Lifestyle Concept Store at Isetan Wisma Atria.
Sony Electronics is commemorating the first anniversary of its Sony Store located within Isetan Wisma Atria in Singapore. The celebration includes a store revamp and a variety of workshops and special deals offered throughout October.
Designed with the female shopper in mind, the Sony Store presents themed displays to demonstrate how the various products can complement their lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor categorizes audiences into seven different consumer types</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-categorizes-audiences-into-seven-different-consumer-types/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 17:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-categorizes-audiences-into-seven-different-consumer-types/</guid><description>Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Survey team has identified seven distinct global consumer types based on their Global Consumer Trends survey: the Undaunted Striver, Impulsive Spender, Balanced Optimist, Aspiring Struggler, Conservative Homebody, Independent Skeptic and Secure Traditionalist.
Source: Euromonitor
website.
Each consumer type exhibits unique preferences and habits, even when sharing similar demographics. For instance, the relatively young Impulsive Spender views life as busy but exciting, characterized by a social, indulgent, and friend-oriented nature. Conversely, Independent Skeptics, also categorized as young consumers, define themselves by living life on their own terms, embracing unconventionality, skepticism, and indifference.</description></item><item><title>KKBOX has initiated a Cpop campaign on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</guid><description>Source: Twitter. Screenshot of Tia Ray&amp;rsquo;s tweet.
Twitter and KKBOX, a popular music streaming service in Asia, are collaborating to increase global recognition and appreciation of Chinese pop music, known as Cpop (#Cpop).
To achieve this, KKBOX is developing exclusive Cpop content (#OnlyOnTwitter) for their main Twitter account (@KKBOX). This includes weekly live question and answer sessions with Cpop artists, personalized video messages from Cpop musicians and producers using Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Challenger app, frequent #KKvote contests to encourage international fan participation, and live streams of Cpop concerts and the yearly KKBOX music awards through Periscope (@KKBOXTW).</description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is a region where digital marketing is effective</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</guid><description>Source: Adobe website.
Recent research from Adobe highlights the growing importance of mobile devices for marketers in Southeast Asia, emphasizing its effectiveness in customer interaction and engagement. This shift toward mobile-first business strategies is particularly prominent in the Asia Pacific region.
Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Digital Index &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Benchmark&amp;rdquo; for 2015 analyzed website performance across eight regions, including Southeast Asia. By comparing the top 20% of websites (&amp;ldquo;best of the best&amp;rdquo;) with the overall average across six key performance indicators, the research provides valuable insights into the strategies of high-performing digital marketing organizations.</description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%).</description></item><item><title>Try Leh's Tryvertising receives a virtual enhancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-leh-s-tryvertising-receives-a-virtual-enhancement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 17:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-leh-s-tryvertising-receives-a-virtual-enhancement/</guid><description>Source: Try Leh. One of Try Leh&amp;rsquo;s kiosks.
Try Leh has expanded its &amp;ldquo;tryvertising&amp;rdquo; business model by introducing new virtual kiosks.
The company has placed physical kiosks across Singapore, enabling consumers to easily redeem and test product samples. These user-friendly vending machine-style kiosks allow brands to display up to 12 products at a time. Try Leh&amp;rsquo;s marketing packages offer campaigns ranging from four to eight weeks, with prices starting at S$700.</description></item><item><title>A new worldwide network of mobile social influencers has been introduced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</guid><description>VOLTU, a new performance-based social influencer network focused on mobile acquisition, has been officially launched by mobile advertising technology pioneer Glispa Global Group. Building on Glispa&amp;rsquo;s successful history of creating custom influencer campaigns for clients like Square Enix and Youzu, VOLTU connects advertisers with global content creators to increase app installs, brand awareness, and user engagement.
Influencer marketing is a proven method for engaging consumers because it utilizes genuine and relatable content made by consumers for consumers.</description></item><item><title>HubSpot for Startups simplifies the onboarding process for new businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</guid><description>HubSpot, a company that provides marketing and sales technology, has launched a new program called HubSpot for Startups. This program is specifically designed to support startups that are working with accelerators, incubators, and entrepreneurial organizations.
The program aims to help these small businesses gain momentum in their marketing and sales efforts by offering a substantial 90% discount on HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s products. These products include tools for customer relationship management (CRM), sales, and marketing.</description></item><item><title>Have you ever witnessed the power of a Leica Triple Camera and a single flash?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</guid><description>On the evenings of October 19th and 20th, Singaporeans were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through a series of unannounced projections.
This recognizable design, featuring a square arrangement of three Leica cameras and a flash, was displayed on buildings throughout Singapore, including Tampines Mall, Bugis+, and Star Vista. This camera setup, found on the back of HUAWEI Mate 20 smartphones, uses a 12 MP main RGB lens, an 8 MP telephoto lens, and a 16 MP ultra-wide-angle lens, all from Leica, along with a flash.</description></item><item><title>Discover Emirates aircraft in 3D</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates pioneers VR experience on its website.
Emirates has become the first airline to use web-based virtual reality (VR) technology. They&amp;rsquo;ve added 3D seat models to emirates.com.
This 3D model shows a 360-degree view of the inside of their A380 and Boeing 777 aircraft. It allows customers to view the Economy, Business, and First Class cabins, as well as the onboard lounge and shower spa on the A380.</description></item><item><title>The Adobe Symposium 2016 will be sharing important digital marketing trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. Logo for Adobe Symposium 2016.
Over 1,000 professionals in digital marketing, publishing, advertising, content management, and marketing executives will come together at the Adobe Symposium in Singapore on July 28, 2016. This event will provide insights into how innovative global brands have successfully utilized digital trends to deeply understand their customers, create personalized campaigns, and effectively manage content and assets.
With over 50 sessions across four tracks, attendees will witness the latest innovations from Adobe Marketing Cloud.</description></item><item><title>Fishbat provides commentary on the latest developments in iOS8 and the introduction of Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fishbat-provides-commentary-on-the-latest-developments-in-ios8-and-the-introduction-of-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple, the tech giant, recently launched the first beta version of iOS 8.1. This upgrade comes shortly after the release of iOS 8.0.2, which was itself a fix for a bug found in the recently launched iOS 8.0.1.
This new beta version offers several new features:
A redesigned icon for iBooks. An option to enable dictation within the keyboard settings. Updated application permission settings. Larger application icons specifically designed for the new widgets in the notification center.</description></item><item><title>Where to Get a 1-800 Number Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 20:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</guid><description>Want a 1-800 number without the high price tag? You can get one for just $5! Maintaining the number costs a mere $5 monthly, with incoming calls at 6.9 cents per minute—a small price for most businesses, and one with significant potential benefits.
Why? Because anyone dialing your 1-800 number found it through an advertisement, business card, flyer, newspaper, television, billboard, or radio. They have a reason for calling, usually translating to a motivated customer.</description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details.</description></item><item><title>The latest digital tools that lead to business success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</guid><description>Ebenezer Heng, Principal Consultant at Top Advertising, emphasizes that businesses must understand and leverage the connection between online and offline marketing to thrive. Speaking at the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld Conference, he argued that traditional success factors like &amp;ldquo;gut feel&amp;rdquo; are no longer enough in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
He illustrated this with the example of choosing a business location. Simply observing foot traffic isn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient; online sentiment analysis, which gauges public opinion about a location, can reveal a different picture of popularity.</description></item><item><title>Optimize marketing tactics with native mobile strategies tailored for the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 15:56:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/optimize-marketing-tactics-with-native-mobile-strategies-tailored-for-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Sinead Woodley, Managing Director UK at April Six, a digital marketing agency, emphasizes that the right marketing approach can significantly enhance early buyer engagement for tech companies. Speaking at the Asia Pacific launch of April Six in Singapore, she highlighted how technology can be leveraged to achieve this.
Woodley cited EMEA-wide campaigns for VMware as a prime example, where April Six successfully reached IT professionals who are typically averse to marketing.</description></item><item><title>Accenture states that just-in-time marketing leads to higher conversion rates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-states-that-just-in-time-marketing-leads-to-higher-conversion-rates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 06:19:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-states-that-just-in-time-marketing-leads-to-higher-conversion-rates/</guid><description>Source: Accenture infographic.
A recent report from Accenture, based on a survey of over 500 chief marketing officers (CMOs) globally, suggests that just-in-time marketing can lead to a greater return on investment and significantly boost revenue growth. Companies using this method are three times more likely to surpass their competitors in terms of revenue growth.
Just-in-time marketing focuses on crafting relevant marketing content precisely when needed and tailoring it to appeal to interested consumers at the exact moment they are ready to make a purchase.</description></item><item><title>Utilize online brand ambassadors to add a personal touch to your online presence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</guid><description>Source: Oomph! Lee.
Oomph!, a Singapore-based staffing agency, has introduced ENGAGE, a new online platform and service for brand ambassadors. This platform aims to replicate the personalized customer service of physical stores in the digital world.
ENGAGE connects businesses with trained online brand ambassadors who can interact with customers through a chat box, including video chat options. These ambassadors can help customers find suitable products, answer their questions, and even book in-person store visits for a more traditional shopping experience.</description></item><item><title>GetResponse introduces its email marketing platform in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getresponse-introduces-its-email-marketing-platform-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>GetResponse, an email marketing platform, has officially launched in the ASEAN region. The company enhanced its cloud-based platform earlier this year to include support for Chinese, Malay, and Thai languages. This move has contributed to a significant 41.6% surge in new account registrations. GetResponse has observed a 35.8% year-over-year growth in email marketing activities within ASEAN.
Source: GetResponse website.
Simon Grabowski, CEO of GetResponse, emphasized the significance of email marketing, especially for small and medium-sized businesses working with limited budgets.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singtel's Chinese New Year short film is on building connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Stills from the festive video emphasizing the importance of positive connections.
Singtel released its yearly short film for the Lunar New Year season. This year&amp;rsquo;s film uses humor to highlight the importance of connecting with others and nurturing relationships. The lighthearted short, His Grandfather’s Road, portrays a heated encounter between two families during the holiday rush. However, their road rage takes an unexpected turn when they discover shared ground and end their confrontation amicably.</description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations.</description></item><item><title>The APAC region is strongly featured in Warc's list of the top 100 marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Warc, a provider of marketing intelligence, has introduced the Warc 100, a new ranking of the top marketing campaigns globally based on their effectiveness and strategic impact.
The Asia Pacific region contributed over 30 entries, including one from the UAE, with Australia having the second-highest representation after the US with 11 entries.
Among the top 10 campaigns from the Asia Pacific are: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s More Fun in the Philippines&amp;rdquo; by the Philippines Department of Tourism and BBDO Guerrero (ranked 3rd), &amp;ldquo;Overstay Checkout&amp;rdquo; by Art Series Hotels and Naked Communications (5th), &amp;ldquo;Smoking Kid&amp;rdquo; by Thai Health Promotion Foundation and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (7th), &amp;ldquo;Old Parts for New&amp;rdquo; by ORBIS International and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (8th), and &amp;ldquo;Car Creation&amp;rdquo; by NRMA Insurance and Whybin\TBWA (10th).</description></item><item><title>The strenuous effort put into improving customer satisfaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 05:29:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-strenuous-effort-put-into-improving-customer-satisfaction/</guid><description>A recent survey by Adobe and Econsultancy, involving 14,000 marketers including participants from the Asia Pacific region, reveals that marketers see customer experience as the key differentiator for businesses in 2017.
While investing in technology is important, businesses also recognize the need for a customer-focused, adaptable, and collaborative company culture. The survey indicates that 22% of client-side respondents consider “optimizing the customer experience” as the most exciting opportunity for the coming year.</description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue.</description></item><item><title>The top four visual trends for 2020 according to Adobe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 05:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-four-visual-trends-for-2020-according-to-adobe/</guid><description>Adobe has predicted the biggest visual trends for 2020, sharing four key themes brands should embrace in a recent blog post.
_Inclusivity for All Ages _
Marketing is moving away from solely youth-focused campaigns. Recognizing the influence and engagement of older demographics, brands are showcasing diverse, energetic individuals from various age groups.
_Authenticity in Expression _
Consumers are increasingly drawn to genuine representations of themselves and their experiences. This desire for authenticity extends to brands, public figures, and politicians, who are expected to reflect real life in their messaging.</description></item></channel></rss>