<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3x3 Mbps Ethernet Doubles Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, who couldn&amp;rsquo;t benefit from additional internet speed? Websites, software, and files continue to grow larger, but unfortunately, technology budgets haven&amp;rsquo;t kept pace. Imagine doubling your internet speed without increasing your current expenses – an appealing proposition, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t you agree?
It might sound illogical to suggest that doubling your internet speed wouldn&amp;rsquo;t cost more, especially since internet providers aren&amp;rsquo;t known for giving things away for free. The secret lies in adopting newer, more cost-effective technology instead of simply replacing your existing service with an identical one from another provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3x3-mbps-ethernet-doubles-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2x2 Ethernet Takes on T-1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</guid><description>For the past decade, small and medium businesses have relied on T1 lines as their primary commercial telecom solution. However, a new competitor called 2x2 Ethernet, recently introduced by major nationwide carrier MegaPath, is emerging to challenge the long-standing T1. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what 2x2 Ethernet offers.
It might seem surprising that T1 lines would face competition, considering their 50-year history and widespread adoption. As the first widely available broadband digital connection for businesses, T1 emerged from telephone company research...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2x2-ethernet-takes-on-t-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1MORE will be introducing their new noise cancelling headphones at the PC Show</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1more-will-be-introducing-their-new-noise-cancelling-headphones-at-the-pc-show/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 05:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1more-will-be-introducing-their-new-noise-cancelling-headphones-at-the-pc-show/</guid><description>Intelligent noise reduction
Includes an airplane adapter and a USB Type-C to 3.5 mm connector
A quick 10-minute charge provides 3 hours of playback
Bluetooth 4.2 connectivity with Hi-Res Transmission Technology
Making their debut at the PC Show 2019 in Singapore are 1MORE&amp;rsquo;s inaugural noise-canceling headphones, known as the Dual Driver Bluetooth (BT) Active Noise Cancelling (ANC) In-Ear Headphones.
The headphones have garnered significant attention due to the involvement of renowned Chinese celebrity Jay Chou, who has invested in the company, and the expertise of Grammy-winning sound engineer Luca Bignardi, responsible for fine-tuning their audio...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1more-will-be-introducing-their-new-noise-cancelling-headphones-at-the-pc-show/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1more-will-be-introducing-their-new-noise-cancelling-headphones-at-the-pc-show/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1G, 2G, 3G, 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1g-2g-3g-4g/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:58:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1g-2g-3g-4g/</guid><description>Wireless phone technologies have evolved significantly, progressing through different &amp;ldquo;generations&amp;rdquo; like members of a family. From the early days of pre-cellular mobile phones, the industry has witnessed the rise of analog cellular (1G), digital cellular (2G), and the emergence of 3G, with 4G on the horizon.
Like any family, the wireless phone sector has its share of triumphs, conflicts, and aspirations. While wireless internet technologies like WiFi operate under different standards, there&amp;rsquo;s potential for convergence, such as phones supporting both cellular and WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1g-2g-3g-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1g-2g-3g-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>6 Tips for Maximizing Your Use of SQL Server Management Studio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/6-tips-for-maximizing-your-use-of-sql-server-management-studio/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 02:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/6-tips-for-maximizing-your-use-of-sql-server-management-studio/</guid><description>By Steve Endow
This article presents several helpful tips for using SQL Server Management Studio (SSMS) more efficiently.
A video demonstrating these tips is available.
Utilize the Object Explorer Details Window: Many users are unaware of the time-saving benefits offered by the Object Explorer Details window. Instead of solely relying on the Object Explorer pane for finding tables or stored procedures, pressing F7 to open the Details window significantly speeds up navigation and search...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/6-tips-for-maximizing-your-use-of-sql-server-management-studio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/6-tips-for-maximizing-your-use-of-sql-server-management-studio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G WiMAX Wireless Broadband Available Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 05:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</guid><description>Are you unhappy with your current internet options at home and on the go? Imagine a wireless internet service that works at your desk and travels with your laptop. What if this service was also cheaper than DSL, cable, and 3G wireless? What if it was incredibly fast? You should see if 4G WiMAX broadband is available in your area.
What is WiMAX and why is it superior to other broadband options?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wimax-wireless-broadband-available-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5x5 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 18:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</guid><description>Businesses often want greater internet bandwidth, lower telecommunication costs, or both. A relatively new service called 5x5 Ethernet might be the solution.
Ethernet services are a recent development. Before their rise in popularity, the best bandwidth options were T1 lines and fractional DS3 bandwidth. Fixed location wireless service has sometimes been available, but only for locations with a direct line of sight to their provider.
How do Ethernet services improve upon previous options?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5x5-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-saves-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>$2 Toll Free Numbers Help Professionals Go Independent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s challenging economy, many skilled professionals are thinking about becoming independent and leaving traditional employment. While it&amp;rsquo;s a significant decision, resources are available to help with this transition. One such resource is an affordable toll-free service that provides the flexibility of working independently.
Individuals starting their own businesses often work from home offices and are frequently on the move, particularly those in service industries or consulting roles. This raises the question of how to maintain communication with clients and prospects regardless of location, using only a cell phone and laptop...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2-toll-free-numbers-help-professionals-go-independent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>