<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analog Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analog-telephony/</link><description>Recent content in Analog Telephony on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analog-telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>