<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Computing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-computing/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Computing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-computing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers.</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business.</description></item><item><title>Tech Upheavals in 2009</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</guid><description>The world of technology is about to undergo another major shift, particularly in telecommunications and computing. While these changes have been in motion throughout 2008, 2009 looks to be the year they truly make their mark. Here are a few potential game-changers:
Wireless Broadband Takes the Lead: Traditional DSL and cable internet services are facing stiff competition from wireless providers. Cell towers, now equipped with broadband capabilities, offer comparable speeds to wired connections, often at slightly higher prices.</description></item><item><title>From CAPEX to OPEX In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The cost model for Information Technology is shifting from capital expenditure (CAPEX) to operational expenditure (OPEX) due to economic uncertainty and the rise of cloud computing.
Traditionally, businesses invested heavily in on-site data centers with servers, storage, and network equipment. This approach, while effective, requires substantial upfront capital and incurs ongoing operational costs like electricity, bandwidth, staffing, and software maintenance.
While this capital-intensive model was the norm, the economic downturn made businesses more cost-conscious.</description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability.</description></item><item><title>A Graphical Introduction to Big Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</guid><description>Confused about the hype surrounding Big Data? This infographic might help clear things up&amp;hellip;
Feeling limited by your current internet connection when dealing with large amounts of data, cloud services, backups, or file transfers? Upgrading might be more affordable than you expect. Get immediate pricing on cost-effective copper and fiber internet options for your business.
Credit to Wikibon Infographics for this infographic on Big Data.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company.</description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1.</description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps.</description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers.</description></item><item><title>Can You Get To The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing and storage are becoming increasingly popular, and many believe they will soon be the standard for computer use. There are many benefits to using the cloud, such as not needing to buy or maintain software, having data automatically backed up, accessing tools and data from anywhere on any device, and being able to use smaller, more portable computers, like netbooks, cellphones, and tablets. However, one concern remains: reliable access to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Services Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</guid><description>Companies are increasingly interested in cloud services because they can save money and access capabilities that they might not otherwise be able to afford. Cloud services offer a wide range of IP services and can be accessed in-house, privately, or purchased from a provider. While providers offer different services, they all deliver their services over IP networks, leading to the term &amp;ldquo;managed IP services.&amp;rdquo;
Managed services allow carriers or service providers to take responsibility for operations, a task typically handled by on-site IT staff.</description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly.</description></item><item><title>Disaster Recovery Is Now a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disaster-recovery-is-now-a-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 22:06:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disaster-recovery-is-now-a-service/</guid><description>Imagine a sweltering day with an unsettling stillness in the air, the kind that foreshadows trouble. Suddenly, the sky darkens, wind howls, and a deafening roar consumes everything. You seek shelter as the storm unleashes its fury, leaving a trail of destruction in its wake. Emerging from safety, you&amp;rsquo;re met with a scene of utter devastation—your business reduced to rubble.
The image of your business, once full of life, now a wasteland of debris stretching endlessly, is a stark reminder of the destructive power of unforeseen events.</description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in.</description></item><item><title>Amazon's CloudFront Moves In for Content Delivery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</guid><description>Amazon has expanded far beyond bookselling; it&amp;rsquo;s now a major player in network computing. Recognizing the value of their massive infrastructure, Amazon created Amazon Web Services (AWS) to offer cloud computing resources to businesses of all sizes.
AWS includes a range of services, such as Amazon EC2 for computing power, Amazon S3 for storage, and Amazon CloudFront for content delivery. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s global network, with numerous edge locations, makes it well-suited for content delivery.</description></item><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges.</description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers.</description></item><item><title>How Capital Starved Companies Upgrade Technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 15:56:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-capital-starved-companies-upgrade-technology/</guid><description>Even with the economy recovering, securing funds for new technology can be challenging for businesses. Instead of traditional financing, consider &amp;ldquo;hosted solutions&amp;rdquo; or renting technology. This approach avoids large capital investments, allowing businesses to upgrade their systems affordably.
Website hosting is a prime example. Initially, hosting your website on your servers made sense. However, with increased competition, affordable hosting services have become widely available, making it more practical to outsource this function.</description></item><item><title>Business Booming For Telx Interconnection and Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</guid><description>Despite the current economic downturn, data center provider Telx is experiencing a surge in construction at their main Chicago facility. This might seem counterintuitive during a recession, but it makes sense considering the ongoing technological transformation in business and finance.
Companies have shifted from manual processes to computer-based systems, leading to a client-server model that boosted efficiency and productivity. Now, forward-thinking companies are seeking new strategies for a competitive edge.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Telexplainer Expectations For 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 16:29:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telexplainer-expectations-for-2011/</guid><description>As we begin a promising new year for business and technology, let&amp;rsquo;s explore some key trends for 2011 and how to leverage them.
Bandwidth demands will continue to escalate this year, as they do annually. The economic recovery will likely generate increased internet traffic as more individuals return to work. Expect bandwidth demand to surge proportionally with employment, if not more. During the recession, businesses learned to enhance individual productivity by investing in technology.</description></item><item><title>Concentric Cloud Solutions Virtualizes Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentric-cloud-solutions-virtualizes-your-business/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been bombarded with information about virtualization, unsure if it can help control unpredictable business expenses. You might feel overwhelmed about the process of deploying virtualization. There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry, Concentric can guide you through it.
Initially confined to local data centers, virtualization has migrated to the cloud. The fundamental concept is maximizing hardware performance. This is achieved by making a single server function as multiple servers, or transforming a cluster of smaller servers into a powerful computing unit.</description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber for Bandwidth and Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 15:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-for-bandwidth-and-security/</guid><description>Upgrading from copper to fiber optics is a significant step for many businesses, but for some, it&amp;rsquo;s simply not enough. When even the highest capacity fiber optic services lack the necessary bandwidth or security features, dark fiber emerges as the solution.
One might wonder how lit fiber services could be insufficient, considering they offer speeds up to 10,000 Mbps (10 Gigabit SONET or Ethernet) and, in some cases, even up to 40 Gbps (OC-768).</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Network Monitoring Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</guid><description>The increasing reliance on electronic transactions, online services, and cloud technologies has made networks essential for businesses. This dependence requires IT departments to prioritize network monitoring, either through in-house solutions or external providers.
While companies have traditionally monitored their internal networks, extending this practice to telecom connections is crucial. This includes dedicated lines, public internet connections, and VPNs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to enhance network monitoring processes.
Smaller businesses often face challenges with network monitoring outside of business hours.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>Benefit From The Great CAPEX to OPEX Migration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 07:19:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefit-from-the-great-capex-to-opex-migration/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world, moving away from traditional capital expenditures (CAPEX) towards operational expenses (OPEX). This change, although seemingly subtle, represents a fundamental shift with far-reaching implications for businesses of all sizes.
Businesses incur both capital and operational expenses. Operational expenses are the costs of daily operations, like utilities, supplies, and salaries. Capital expenses, however, are long-term investments, such as purchasing buildings or major equipment. An example of this is an in-house PBX telephone system, which might soon be replaced by an operational expense alternative.</description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings.</description></item><item><title>Your Desk Just Moved To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 10:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The 20th century saw a significant shift in employment, moving from farm work to factory jobs and finally to office positions. Now, the 21st century is experiencing another major change as workplaces transition from offices to the cloud.
The Cloud is Here and Now
Contrary to the idea of the cloud being a distant concept, it has become an integral part of our present reality. Nearly everything we do has or will soon have a cloud connection.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Up and Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-up-and-down/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been said that 10 Mbps is the new standard for business bandwidth, similar to how the T1 line (1.5 Mbps) was once considered the benchmark. This shift towards higher bandwidth is driven by the increasing demands of modern business applications.
T1 lines gained popularity as the internet became a vital business tool in the 1990s. They offered sufficient speed and were readily available. However, the internet has evolved significantly since then.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle.</description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Manufacturing Driving Faster WANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</guid><description>The recent &amp;ldquo;Great Recession&amp;rdquo; stands out not just for its severity, but also for the uneven recovery that followed. While businesses have bounced back, job growth has lagged. This unusual trend has been attributed to unexpected gains in productivity, where output increases without a proportional rise in employment. But is this sustainable or merely a blip in the current economic climate?
The saying &amp;ldquo;everything old is new again&amp;rdquo; rings true. While new applications and technologies emerge, they often echo past advancements driven by innovation.</description></item><item><title>Computing In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 15:08:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computing-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud computing&amp;rdquo; has become ubiquitous, but what does it entail and what are its advantages over traditional data centers?
Initially, cloud computing provided access to a network of computers for tasks that exceeded the capabilities of individual resources. A prime example is the SETI@Home program, which harnesses the idle processing power of countless personal computers connected through the internet to analyze radio telescope data in search of extraterrestrial life.</description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery.</description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user.</description></item><item><title>Google's Plan To Chew Up Microsoft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</guid><description>A recent Wall Street Journal article hints at Google&amp;rsquo;s next target: Microsoft.
Google&amp;rsquo;s goals might extend beyond replacing Microsoft as the dominant force in PC operating systems. Their ambition could be complete control over all devices with embedded computers, essentially every electronic device.
This theory stems from reports that PC manufacturers like Hewlett-Packard are experimenting with Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system in netbooks. Android, primarily a mobile phone operating system, might seem harmless to established PC operating systems, but that might be a miscalculation.</description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption.</description></item><item><title>Hosted SharePoint For Content and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-sharepoint-for-content-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Large businesses use Microsoft SharePoint for managing content, documents, and collaborative work. Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) could also reap the benefits of SharePoint&amp;rsquo;s advanced automation, but often lack the resources for significant IT infrastructure expansion.
Fortunately, Integra Telecom now offers Microsoft SharePoint 2010 as a hosted solution. This makes cloud computing practical for SMBs. Using Integra as your SharePoint provider offers two advantages: access to their robust data center and computing platform, along with dedicated high-performance connectivity through their fiber optic network.</description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>What is Cloud Computing For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is gaining popularity, but what does it mean for businesses beyond giants like Amazon and Google? Essentially, the cloud isn&amp;rsquo;t a new invention. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of structuring technology, similar to the public telephone system, where a central provider manages the complex infrastructure (&amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo;), and users access services through simple devices (&amp;ldquo;thin clients&amp;rdquo;).
This centralized system, known as multi-tenancy, allows numerous users to access resources seemingly simultaneously while remaining isolated.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item><item><title>Why Have Reseller Hosting When You Don’t Resell Anything?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 00:16:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-have-reseller-hosting-when-you-don-t-resell-anything/</guid><description>Web hosting companies offer various plans, from shared hosting to dedicated servers and cloud services. One option is &amp;ldquo;reseller hosting,&amp;rdquo; which many website owners use without actually reselling hosting.
Many website owners use reseller hosting to manage multiple websites easily. Basic web hosting, like HostGator&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hatchling&amp;rdquo; plan, is affordable for individuals and small businesses with simple websites. These plans offer shared resources like disk space and bandwidth at a low cost.</description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds.</description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Is Making Obsolescence Obsolete</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</guid><description>Keeping up with technology is a constant struggle, similar to swimming against a strong current. Any pause or delay can cause you to fall behind competitors who are advancing rapidly.
Technology is constantly evolving, becoming outdated quickly. The longer you rely on existing technology, the more outdated it gets, eventually lacking support or functionality. While the physical hardware may remain functional, it struggles to utilize the latest resources and software.</description></item><item><title>Will 2013 Be Your Year of the Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-2013-be-your-year-of-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing was a major trend in 2012, with numerous vendors offering a wide range of solutions. Cloud services are no longer limited to powerful supercomputers; they&amp;rsquo;ve become accessible and practical for everyday resources, often surpassing the benefits of in-house solutions. This raises the question: will 2013 be the year you transition to the cloud?
For many businesses, the answer is a clear &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Cost-effectiveness, support, and accessibility are key drivers.</description></item></channel></rss>