<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rural Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rural-broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Rural Broadband on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rural-broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternative Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>For those living and working in rural areas, limited internet options can be a major problem. While major providers often only service cities, there are ways to stay connected without spending a fortune or waiting years for expanded infrastructure.
Forget DSL or cable – those are rare finds outside city limits. While universal telephone service guarantees basic phone lines (and thus, very slow dial-up internet), there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for fast, affordable internet: the existing cell phone network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking For Spectrum In All The White Spaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:51:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</guid><description>With the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction concluded, the wireless industry is feeling a sense of scarcity. All the valuable over-the-air spectrum, much like desirable beachfront property, has seemingly been claimed.
However, instead of viewing the spectrum as fully allocated, consider it as a landscape inhabited by powerful entities, like T-Rexes in the Cretaceous period. These dominant players, representing major TV stations, control their portions of the spectrum, leaving little room for newcomers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Satellite Be The Answer to Your Business Broadband Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you feeling stuck because your business needs internet, even if it&amp;rsquo;s just local? Have you considered cable and DSL but found them unavailable in your area? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution for getting high-speed internet, even in remote locations.
The answer is satellite internet! Forget about expensive cable or fiber optic lines; this video explains why looking up is the way to go:
Here are 10 important things to know about satellite internet for your business:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-satellite-be-the-answer-to-your-business-broadband-needs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is There a Broadband Stimulus Job For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 17:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</guid><description>The U.S. government is investing an additional $795 million in broadband stimulus funding to address the country&amp;rsquo;s lag behind nations like Japan and Korea in providing affordable, high-speed internet. This investment presents a potential win-win situation, offering both short-term job creation and long-term economic benefits.
One study projects the creation of approximately 5,000 immediate jobs from these high-speed internet projects. While seemingly small compared to the number of job seekers, it&amp;rsquo;s a step in the right direction...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-broadband-stimulus-job-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Dial-Up Internet Doomed?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-dial-up-internet-doomed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 08:41:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-dial-up-internet-doomed/</guid><description>Dial-up internet, once the king of online connectivity, is facing an uncertain future in a world dominated by broadband. With various technologies like WiFi, DSL, satellite, cable, fiber, and cellular competing for users, the relevance of the once-groundbreaking 56K dial-up is questionable.
It might be surprising to learn that millions of people in the U.S. still use dial-up. These users fall into two groups: those who would switch to broadband if it were affordable and those who use the internet so infrequently that they prefer a free option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-dial-up-internet-doomed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-dial-up-internet-doomed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Broadband Stimulus Hopes To One-Up Dial-up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 12:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</guid><description>Right before the 4th of July holiday, the much-awaited government funding plan for expanding rural broadband access was officially announced through a &amp;ldquo;Notice of Funds Availability (NOFA)&amp;rdquo; and a call for applications.
The application window is short, running from July 14th to August 14th, 2009, so interested parties need to act fast.
Don&amp;rsquo;t expect to see immediate changes if you&amp;rsquo;re hoping to use these new broadband services rather than provide them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-broadband-stimulus-hopes-to-one-up-dial-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Stimulus For The Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</guid><description>Rural America is on the verge of a major internet transformation thanks to a new broadband stimulus program. This program aims to bridge the digital divide by providing $7.2 billion in funding to states, enabling them to improve internet access significantly.
While South Korea is making strides in providing gigabit internet speeds to its citizens, many Americans struggle with significantly slower connections. This disparity stems from two main issues. Firstly, rural areas often lack the infrastructure and competition found in metropolitan areas, resulting in limited internet options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Economic Woes Drive Rural Telegraphy Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</guid><description>The recent economic downturn has forced a reevaluation of strategies for providing digital communication to rural communities. Access to the internet and even cell phone service is notoriously limited in these areas. While the Rural Broadband Initiative, part of the economic stimulus plan, aimed to address this issue by funding fiber optic cable installation, those funds have unfortunately been redirected.
Robb M. Blihnd, a hedge fund manager, explained that the funds were considered more essential for urban and suburban areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</guid><description>For a long time, the idea of &amp;ldquo;rural broadband&amp;rdquo; seemed contradictory. While cities enjoyed a variety of high-speed internet options, from DSL and cable to fiber optic connections, rural areas remained stuck with slow dial-up or satellite internet. Although high-speed business lines have become more affordable, fiber optic cables in rural areas were deemed too expensive. However, an organization in Vermont is challenging this assumption.
ValleyFiber, led by Dr. Timothy Nulty, is bringing fiber optic broadband to rural homes and businesses in Vermont&amp;rsquo;s Upper Valley...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, There IS Rural Broadband For Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</guid><description>Many people are excited about the economic stimulus plan&amp;rsquo;s promise of expanded rural broadband access. However, you might already be able to get the internet speeds your rural business needs.
Most major internet providers have overlooked rural areas, not because rural businesses are less important, but because the cost of installing infrastructure like coaxial cables or fiber optic cables is difficult to recoup when there are fewer customers. This is why cable and DSL internet services are less common in the countryside...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Lit Towers Improving Rural Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 16:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</guid><description>Living outside the city limits often means limited internet options. While options like 3G and satellite exist, they come with slow speeds and download caps. Businesses might have access to slightly better choices like T1 lines, but high-speed options are generally nonexistent.
Rural areas face a digital disadvantage compared to cities where gigabit and even 10 gigabit ethernet connections are readily available. Fixed wireless and cable options also offer much faster speeds in these areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>