<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bose on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bose/</link><description>Recent content in Bose on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bose/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bose's Bluetooth speakers and headphones simplify the process of making connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</guid><description>Bose has expanded its SoundLink mobile audio lineup with two new products: the SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker, their most budget-friendly SoundLink speaker yet, and the SoundLink Bluetooth on-ear headphones, Bose&amp;rsquo;s first foray into on-ear Bluetooth headphones.
The SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker features a brand new design. Weighing in at 1.25 pounds (567g), it measures 5 inches wide, 2.1 inches deep, and 5.3 inches high. Bose has engineered the speaker with dual-opposing passive radiators and two high-efficiency transducers to deliver powerful, full-range sound, including impressive bass performance.</description></item><item><title>Bose's sleepbuds are specifically created to improve our sleep quality by masking noise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-sleepbuds-are-specifically-created-to-improve-our-sleep-quality-by-masking-noise/</guid><description>Bose has introduced noise-masking sleepbuds — wireless earbuds designed to combat common sleep-disrupting noises with a blend of comfortable design and soothing sounds.
Source: Bose. Bose sleepbuds offer noise
masking, not noise cancellation.
These sleepbuds, the most compact product Bose has developed, come equipped with 10 preloaded &amp;ldquo;sleeptracks.&amp;rdquo; These tracks are designed to mimic the frequencies of common noises like snoring, neighbors, dogs, and traffic, effectively masking them with calming audio.</description></item></channel></rss>