<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Restoration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/restoration/</link><description>Recent content in Restoration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/restoration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some Cabinet Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I made progress reassembling the Beogram 4002, focusing on the cabinet trim and deck cover. To prevent damage, I had previously removed the rosewood trim.
The trim is attached to a metal frame that slides in and out to lock and unlock the cabinet. This frame relies on five guide washers, which are commonly broken in Beogram 4002 units. This one was no different. These washers have a unique design, as detailed in a past Beolover blog post.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Alternate "Circuit Diagram 2" with 24V Scale Illumination Lamps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 14:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-alternate-circuit-diagram-2-with-24v-scale-illumination-lamps/</guid><description>I recently acquired a well-preserved Beogram 4000 service manual containing a unique supplementary diagram. This diagram, Circuit Diagram 2, outlines the control system and features a notable difference in the position scale illumination. Instead of the typical two 12V bulbs wired in series, it depicts two 24V bulbs connected in parallel to the 24V power source.
This discovery complicated a recent interaction with Sonavor, who is currently restoring his own Beogram 4000.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Lubrication of Platter Motor Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-lubrication-of-platter-motor-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the DC motor was lubricated. This particular motor uses brushes and has simple sleeve bearings.
To access the bearings for lubrication, the pulley and outer housing were removed. The pulley is attached to the shaft with glue, allowing for easy removal. After taking out two small screws, the housing can be opened and the motor taken out.
Next, the black rubber vibration insulation boot was removed, revealing the circuit board connected to the brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cosmetic Items, Final Adjustments, and a Test Drive with George Duke on MPS!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cosmetic-items-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-george-duke-on-mps-/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration project, originating from Germany, is nearing completion. After adjusting the sub-chassis and arm height, I set the arm lowering limit, a crucial measure to protect the stylus from potential damage if the record detection fails.
Next, I calibrated the tracking weight, opting to enhance stability by replacing the original locking washer setup with an M3 nut and washer to secure the counterweight position.
Following that, I calibrated the arm weight using a digital scale and fine-tuned the feedback by adjusting the tracking sensor LED with a blue potentiometer.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Massachusetts - First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from a Massachusetts customer for a complete restoration. Thankfully, it was properly packaged and arrived without damage.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s dust cover shows typical signs of use, but it will be replaced with a new one. The aluminum surfaces are in good shape overall.
However, there are some minor flaws. The keypad has a corner ding, suggesting it might have come loose during past transportation. Additionally, there are small scratches on the aluminum, possibly from the keypad moving around.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Service Manual Adjustments &amp; Preparing for Use</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-service-manual-adjustments-preparing-for-use/</guid><description>In the previous post, I finished cleaning and deoxidizing the keypad and RPM panel. The keypad is now responsive, but the cueing up and down button is overly sensitive and needs further attention.
The RPM panel re-installation was put on hold because the plastic mounting fixtures were cracked, a common issue with Beogram 4002 turntables. I was fortunate that the cracks weren&amp;rsquo;t severe and the fixtures were still usable. To repair them, I used acrylic repair fluid while pressing the pieces together.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Final 3D Printed Part Added</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</guid><description>I have completed the final 3D printed component for my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control system. This piece fits into a 10mm opening on the remote control receiver board, allowing it to be secured using one of the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s screws. The image below shows the part with the screw in place:
Once the remote control board is in place, the original screw can be used to fasten it. The cylindrical portion is designed to prevent the remote board from pressing against the component pins on the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main PCB while ensuring a secure fit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Initial Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-initial-assessment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 11:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-initial-assessment/</guid><description>This Beogram 8002 turntable, sent from California, is the next restoration project. I prefer working on the same type of audio equipment consecutively because it minimizes workbench setup time.
The owner followed our packing advice and packaged the turntable very well, using double boxes and protective foam. The turntable arrived without damage.
Upon opening, I noticed the metal tonearm lid wouldn&amp;rsquo;t stay up. The part that connects to the hinge with damping grease was detached, a problem I haven&amp;rsquo;t encountered before.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>Slow response times from the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control panel buttons pointed to potential oxidation on the keypad contacts. This was confirmed upon opening the keypad assembly, revealing dull key contacts.
The contact pads were unsoldered and removed for a closer look. While they seemed okay, the leaf contacts engaged by the actuators showed signs of oxidation.
To address the oxidation, a fiberglass brush and Deoxit were used, restoring the contacts to a shiny and clean condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of Bearings, and Repair of a Broken Off Brush and a Disconnected Sensing Coil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 02:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-repair-of-a-broken-off-brush-and-a-disconnected-sensing-coil/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor from the Netherlands. The motor was dead on arrival, so I opened it up and discovered a broken commutator spring that had been taped on with electrical tape.
Unsurprisingly, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t turn. I also found a broken lead on one of the sensing coils, which should have a resistance of 22 Ohms between the contact terminals.
This break disabled the motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: New power supply capacitors and belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-new-power-supply-capacitors-and-belts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-new-power-supply-capacitors-and-belts/</guid><description>In the last update on this Beocord 5000 (Type 4923), I was about to install new belts and replace the power supply&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors.
This post covers the completion of those tasks.
The original power supply capacitors are shown below.
&amp;hellip;and the replacement capacitors are here.
Next up are the belts.
First is the tape counter belt.
Now for the clutch wheel and flywheel belts. Replacing these requires disassembling some brackets.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: From Oil Cleanup to First Operational Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-from-oil-cleanup-to-first-operational-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 23:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-from-oil-cleanup-to-first-operational-test/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration hit a snag. Although the main board was restored, the presence of rust and corrosion discovered earlier took priority. Addressing rust requires applying neutralizer and paint, which involves drying time between coats, thus delaying the planned reservoir capacitor and output board work.
Images highlighting the most severe rust spots are included.
Despite the significant rust, the turntable&amp;rsquo;s overall condition is good. To combat the rust, three coats of rust neutralizer were applied.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and have reached the stage of addressing cosmetic details. A common issue with this model, as with approximately 90% of them, is a worn keypad. The original coating deteriorates over time due to exposure to skin oils and acids. This results in unsightly smudges, especially on units that have seen regular use. I recently acquired some refurbished keypads from a contact in Denmark to have on hand for my restoration projects.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoring the DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoring-the-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the motor. The motor was noticeably loud, a common issue in DC 4002 models often caused by dried lubricant in the sleeve bearings. Addressing this requires disassembling the motor, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubricant.
The first image highlights the upper sleeve bearing after the rotor was removed.
The next image provides a view of the lower bearing, feedback coils, and brushes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Recapping the Tone Control &amp; FM Tuning Board (Unit #1)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-recapping-the-tone-control-fm-tuning-board-unit-1-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-recapping-the-tone-control-fm-tuning-board-unit-1-/</guid><description>The final major task in the Beomaster 1900 restoration, detailed in the previous post, has been completed. This post covers the last board requiring capacitor replacements: the Tone Control &amp;amp; FM Tuning Board. Replacing the ten capacitors on this board is straightforward due to their accessibility. The true challenge lies in cleaning and fixing the three slider controls: Bass, Treble, and Balance.
Before images of the Tone Control &amp;amp; FM Tuning Board are shown below.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Slow Rewinding, Inconsistent Pause Function and Auto Stop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-slow-rewinding-inconsistent-pause-function-and-auto-stop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-slow-rewinding-inconsistent-pause-function-and-auto-stop/</guid><description>After reinstalling the drive unit into the Beocord 5000 (4715), I began testing. Initial impressions were positive, with fast forward, rewind, play, and stop functions all working. However, the Auto Stop function would cease working after a few minutes. The tape would reach the end, but the drive mechanism would continue running, potentially harming the motor. The only solution was to turn off the deck for an hour to reset the function.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Final Tasks, Adjustments &amp; Playing Records</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-final-tasks-adjustments-playing-records/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-final-tasks-adjustments-playing-records/</guid><description>The final steps of a Beogram 4002 Type 5513 restoration project involved addressing corrosion damage and replacing the 5-pin DIN phono plug. Using a helpful audio path diagram, continuity checks were performed from the cartridge connector to ensure proper signal flow.
The replacement phono plug, a REAN model with gold contact pins, was installed, though the tight fit of the rubber boot on the cable posed a minor challenge. As an improvement, a grounding switch was added to the output board, eliminating the need for an external grounding wire.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Infusing Oilite Brass Bearings of DC Motor with Oil Under Vacuum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-infusing-oilite-brass-bearings-of-dc-motor-with-oil-under-vacuum/</guid><description>Restoring the DC motors found in Beogram 4002/4 turntables (models 551x and 552x) presents a significant challenge. Many of these motors exhibit loud operation and inconsistent rotational speed due to their age. While lubricating the motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings with grease might seem like a solution, this often only yields temporary improvement.
The root of the issue lies in the use of &amp;lsquo;oilite&amp;rsquo; bearings, which are designed to operate without external lubrication.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated DIN Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</guid><description>During the ongoing refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a corroded DIN5 plug was replaced after a new output relay had been installed. The original plug showed significant signs of wear.
A high-quality Rean DIN5 plug with gold-plated terminals was chosen as a replacement. Photos document the preparation of the cable and the installation process. The author notes the limited space inside the DIN5 plug, making it difficult to separate the signal and ground connections.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor: Spark Snubber Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-spark-snubber-replacement/</guid><description>I recently had a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor on my workbench that I had previously worked on in November 2016 due to a broken brush and a severed pickup coil lead.
The motor recently began experiencing RPM fluctuations again.
This pointed to a problem with the spark snubbers. To access the rotor, I opened the motor:
The spark snubbers, marked with red dots, are located around the commutator. The replacements are on the black pad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and RPM Stability Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-rpm-stability-test/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC motor from France was received for restoration.
As is typical, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite brass bearings needed fresh oil. This requires disassembling the motor and extracting the bearings for a vacuum oiling process.
The bearings were submerged in motor oil under vacuum, forcing air out of the porous material and drawing oil in. This process generally takes about 24 hours.
This shows the bearings after the oil infusion.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Germany En Route to California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4000 turntable from Germany, intended for a customer in California. My task is to refurbish the unit and deliver it to its new owner.
The turntable was poorly packaged for shipment, resulting in the keypad plates becoming detached during transit. This led to minor damage to the plates themselves and some cosmetic imperfections on other internal surfaces.
The aluminum surfaces are in surprisingly good shape considering the loose keypad plates.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A new Arrival from Nebraska</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-nebraska/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-nebraska/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from Nebraska arrived for a complete restoration. It was securely shipped in a Beolover container. This is my first look at the unit.
Upon unboxing and bench inspection:
The turntable is in relatively good cosmetic condition. The dust cover is in good shape, though it would benefit from polishing.
The aluminum surfaces show only minor imperfections:
The base has one slightly worn corner on the right side:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration and Test Drive with Cal Tjader and Claus Ogerman</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-and-test-drive-with-cal-tjader-and-claus-ogerman/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable for an Australian customer who purchased it on eBay. The turntable arrived in poor condition.
My initial evaluation is documented here.
This post details the unit&amp;rsquo;s restoration, excluding the dust cover, which will be covered separately.
I began with the DC platter motor, as is customary, since the bearing lubrication process requires a few days. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Final Adjustments, Repair of a Damaged Pinth Corner and Test Drive with Bobby Hutcherson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-final-adjustments-repair-of-a-damaged-pinth-corner-and-test-drive-with-bobby-hutcherson/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration is nearing completion. Following the installation of new gold-plated RCA plugs, I made adjustments to the sub-chassis, platter height, and meticulously cleaned the aluminum surfaces. To prevent the needle from contacting the platter ribs if the record detection mechanism fails, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering limit.
Subsequently, I calibrated the tracking weight scale and enhanced the counterweight adjustment mechanism. The original flimsy circlip was replaced with a more durable M3 nut and washer setup, enhancing its resistance to transport-related stress.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of DC Motor and a Dead TR2 Transistor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-a-dead-tr2-transistor/</guid><description>After refreshing the PCBs and the RPM trimmer scale backlighting on a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, I turned my attention to its DC motor. Most DC motors in these models need their Oilite brass bearings replenished with oil, as the oil tends to seep out over time, leading to RPM instability. To do this, the motor needs to be disassembled.
The bearings sit on a black pad within the motor. I noticed the motor had been previously repaired, evident in the bent brushes, which would have hindered its performance.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Test Drive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-test-drive/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 04:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-test-drive/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great day! My second Beocord 5000 (specifically models 4715/4716) is functional again and playing in sync with the rest of my setup: the Beomaster 6000 4-Channel and the Beogram 4002. To mark this occasion, I chose Sonny Rollins&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Alfie&amp;rdquo; for the first recording.
The movie &amp;ldquo;Alfie,&amp;rdquo; starring Michael Caine, is a personal favorite, and its soundtrack is incredible. Here are some snapshots from the listening session:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sensor Arm Light Bulb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sensor-arm-light-bulb/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 11:54:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sensor-arm-light-bulb/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I inspected the sensor arm light bulb and was surprised to find it in perfect condition. Unlike other bulbs I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered, which typically display a dark film on the glass due to filament evaporation, this one was spotless:
This suggests that this particular Beogram was either lightly used or had its bulb replaced previously. As a result, I will not change it. However, the bulb&amp;rsquo;s placement within its compartment is worth noting.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 01:49:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This document details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable. Initial assessment of the unit can be found on a separate blog post.
The restoration began with the platter motor, as its bearings require a lengthy oil treatment. The motor was extracted, disassembled, and its bearings were submerged in oil under a vacuum to allow for optimal oil diffusion.
Concurrently, the carriage assembly was cleaned. All &amp;ldquo;motion critical&amp;rdquo; parts, including the arm and its associated mechanisms, were removed, ultrasonically cleaned, and reassembled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Oil Infusion of DC Platter Motor Bearings and RPM Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</guid><description>To fully rebuild the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 DC motor, you must relubricate the motor bearings. Many DC motor Beograms have fluctuating RPMs because the oil in their porous brass bearings (called &amp;ldquo;Oilite&amp;rdquo;) depletes over time. These bearings can be &amp;lsquo;refilled&amp;rsquo; by using a vacuum to remove air and allow oil to replenish the pores. The challenge lies in extracting the bearings without causing damage. I documented this process in a recent video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Beogram 4002 Bonanza!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:24:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</guid><description>We seem to be inundated with Beogram 400x turntable restorations.
Beolover is occupied with multiple projects, and I have two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 projects that I began examining back in February of 2020. In those previous posts, I had sent four Beogram 400x platter motors to Beolover for his restoration expertise. He has since completed those motors, and they are now back in my possession, ready to be used.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments, a New Solenoid, and Test Drive with Christoph Spendel &amp; Wolfgang Schlüter Group on MPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-a-new-solenoid-and-test-drive-with-christoph-spendel-wolfgang-schl-ter-group-on-mps/</guid><description>The final steps of restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) involved replacing the sensor arm light bulb with an LED assembly and performing standard adjustments. These included calibrating the tracking feedback, platter height, level, sub-chassis height, and arm lowering limit, which prevents stylus damage.
To ensure accurate tracking weight calibration, the C-clip securing the counterweight adjustment screw was replaced with an M3 nut and washer for permanent fixation. This guarantees that the calibration remains consistent during shipping.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Complete Restoration Including a Refurbished Keypad and Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-complete-restoration-including-a-refurbished-keypad-and-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This unit is currently for sale. Please, see here.
This post details the complete restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) from Arizona, which I first inspected as shown here. The unit&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is pictured below:
My first step, as always, was to initiate oil infusion for the platter motor bearings. Here&amp;rsquo;s the motor after removal:
I took it apart to extract the bearings (two small rings on the black pad):</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: Initial assessment of another Beosystem 5000 companion component.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-initial-assessment-of-another-beosystem-5000-companion-component/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 23:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-initial-assessment-of-another-beosystem-5000-companion-component/</guid><description>This Beocord 5000 is the second cassette deck from Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen to bear this name. The original Beocord 5000, a Type 47xx model, was manufactured in the late 1970s. While distinct, both are high-quality cassette decks.
[Image]
[Image]
The Beocord 5000 Type 4923 aligns with the Beomaster 5000 Type 2323 and the CD50 Beosystem 5000 components in terms of size and design. Control and display access are provided both on the front panel and through a master remote control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Tangential Arm Assembly Oil Cleanup and Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-tangential-arm-assembly-oil-cleanup-and-restoration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-tangential-arm-assembly-oil-cleanup-and-restoration/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project continued with a thorough cleaning of the cabinet&amp;rsquo;s interior, focusing on removing oil residue. The tangential arm assembly was detached to access and clean the oil contamination found throughout the unit.
The oil had spread extensively, affecting various components from the arm&amp;rsquo;s mechanics to the switch contacts. The tangential arm position sensor assembly was entirely disassembled for cleaning.
With the old oil removed, the arm assembly restoration and adjustments could begin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Second Unit From Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:07:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-second-unit-from-houston/</guid><description>A few weeks back, I completed the first of two Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable restorations for a client in Houston. I&amp;rsquo;m now starting work on the second one. Both turntable platters had their motors removed before being sent to Beolover for refurbishment. He has since finished these and documented the process on his blog.
I believe that refurbishing the platter motor is an essential step in any Beogram 400x restoration project.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Completing the Restoration and a Test Spin with Weather Report!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:42:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-completing-the-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-weather-report-/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000 restoration project is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to review the work. Two previous posts covered specific repairs: addressing a missing transistor insulator and a faulty motor driver transistor, and creating a 3D printed replacement for the fragile MMC cartridge mounts.
This post summarizes the remaining restoration work.
Typically, the process begins with a complete overhaul of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s carriage. This involves disassembling and cleaning all moving parts, such as the arm lowering mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Cabinet Work Completion to First Record Play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</guid><description>I finally set up the Beogram 8002 turntable in a listening room to test its functionality.
While reassembly took a bit longer than expected due to a slight detour to repair chipped rosewood trim on the front panel.
Although fixing the trim wasn&amp;rsquo;t part of the initial restoration plan, I decided against leaving the front panel chipped.
Repairs involving glue, like this one, often take longer than expected due to the curing time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjustment of Sub-Chassis, Platter Height, Tonearm Lowering Limits and Tracking Weight</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 04:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjustment-of-sub-chassis-platter-height-tonearm-lowering-limits-and-tracking-weight/</guid><description>After successfully positioning the top aluminum plates, I could adjust the sub-chassis and platter. This step is crucial as it sets the foundation for adjusting the arm lowering limits and, ultimately, the tracking force. This Beogram will be ready for an initial test run once this is completed. I&amp;rsquo;ve previously provided detailed explanations of the chassis and platter adjustment process on my blog and YouTube channel. Two videos demonstrate the platter bearing adjustment and the subchassis adjustment (using a Beogram 4000 as an example, although the procedure is almost identical for the 4002).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Exciting DC Motor Failure Mode Due to a Shorted Spark Snubber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 05:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-exciting-dc-motor-failure-mode-due-to-a-shorted-spark-snubber/</guid><description>Another Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor in need of repair recently came to my workbench. During my standard pre-restoration test using a Beogram 4002, this motor was unusually sluggish, only operating with assistance. This contrasted with the typical DC motors I encounter, which generally run powerfully but exhibit RPM fluctuations and often produce high-pitched sounds due to dried-out bearings. This particular motor was noticeably underpowered.
I disassembled the motor and performed my usual bearing oil infusion to ensure the mechanical components were within specifications before addressing the sluggishness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513 - DC Motor, Main PCB and RPM Panel Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-dc-motor-main-pcb-and-rpm-panel-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from Arizona was received for restoration, exhibiting the common issue of RPM fluctuations. To address this, the motor was prioritized, as revitalizing dry bearings with oil is a time-consuming process.
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings. These were then submerged in motor oil within a vacuum environment. This process, characterized by vigorous bubbling, facilitates the oil&amp;rsquo;s penetration into the bearings&amp;rsquo; porous material by drawing out trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the RPM Indicator Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) and have been systematically replacing its lightbulbs. Today&amp;rsquo;s focus was the RPM indicator, which allowed me to refine my LED replacement method.
Previously, I detailed a process using red and green LEDs from an RGB through-hole 5mm LED to replace the incandescent bulbs. While somewhat successful, the backlighting of the RPM trimmer scales lacked uniformity. Standard through-hole LEDs emit light directionally, requiring me to sand their bulbs for a matte finish and paint the tops black to minimize uneven brightness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Chico Hamilton on Auto-Repeat!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 02:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-chico-hamilton-on-auto-repeat-/</guid><description>It was time for the final adjustments on the Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration project. Adjusting the platter and sub-chassis, arm lowering limits, and tracking force is always a satisfying part of the process. It means the turntable is ready for its initial post-restoration playback. Observing the intricate mechanics in motion, bringing out the best in vintage vinyl, is always captivating.
This Beogram presented a unique sub-chassis and platter adjustment challenge. The platter was positioned too close to the front right edge of the aluminum plate cutout.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Floating Suspension, Reservoir Capacitor &amp; Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 20:33:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-floating-suspension-reservoir-capacitor-platter-motor/</guid><description>This project is nearing completion. This post details the remounting of the floating chassis within the cabinet, replacing the reservoir capacitor, and installing the refurbished platter motor.
Here are the parts needed for mounting the floating suspension system back into the cabinet.
The threaded pin&amp;rsquo;s longer section is positioned at the bottom. When attaching the wing-nut, ensure it sits at the very beginning of the thread. I personally position it to allow enough thread for securing the nut while keeping the nut&amp;rsquo;s outer edge aligned with the topmost thread.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:16:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This blog post details the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a client in Florida. A previous post documented the initial assessment of the unit.
Upon beginning the restoration, the turntable was in relatively original condition. However, the platter motor showed signs of prior work, evidenced by an incorrectly installed pulley.
To address this, the motor was removed and disassembled to extract and lubricate the bearings. This involved immersing them in motor oil under vacuum until air bubbles ceased to appear, indicating the bearings were properly saturated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Fit and Finish Rework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</guid><description>Restoring Beogram 4002 turntables is a fulfilling endeavor, though it often necessitates revisiting steps multiple times. Despite getting this particular Beogram functioning properly, I was dissatisfied with the fit of some components.
The tonearm cover wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting flush, as evidenced by its crooked appearance in the photo, with the center divider visibly off-center between the fixed arm and tonearm.
A head-on perspective further highlights this issue, along with the misaligned deck trim, showing an undesirably wide gap between the panels.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Deteriorated Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:10:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-deteriorated-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002, deteriorated transport lock bushings, evidenced by small orange plastic pieces within the unit, were discovered. To address this, 3D-printed replacement bushings were designed for convenient installation without major disassembly. These bushings are comprised of two halves, insertable from above and below the sub-chassis.
The replacement bushings are available for purchase, with each bushing requiring two of the 3D-printed parts. A video detailing the installation process is accessible online.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: A couple of service manual retests and wrapping up the project</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-a-couple-of-service-manual-retests-and-wrapping-up-the-project/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 09:06:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-a-couple-of-service-manual-retests-and-wrapping-up-the-project/</guid><description>The Beocord 5000 (Type 4923) is performing very well in recording and playback testing. This stage of restoration always highlights the quality of the component. While it lacks auto-reverse and a monitoring tape head, the Beocord 5000 is a high-quality cassette deck with features some users prefer.
The previous post detailed the electrical adjustments outlined in the service manual. These procedures, while not overly complex, necessitate specialized calibration tapes and testing equipment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Floating Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 18:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-floating-chassis/</guid><description>This short post will illustrate an intriguing difference in the suspension systems of two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntables.
The first Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1312615, used a stack of concave washers to secure the floating suspension to the top plate. These washers were also present on the bottom lock.
The second Beogram 4002 Type 5513, serial number 1311076, features a slightly different suspension mechanism. This earlier production model employs a single, concave metal piece between the suspension lock and the top plate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Adjusting Platter and Chassis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 23:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-adjusting-platter-and-chassis/</guid><description>The visual appeal of a Beogram 400x relies heavily on the platter&amp;rsquo;s alignment with its surrounding aluminum panels. A correctly aligned platter sits flush with these panels, allowing the black &amp;lsquo;ribs&amp;rsquo; to stand out against a flat aluminum surface. Achieving this alignment is intricate, requiring several parameters to be perfectly adjusted. I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that a sensor arm that isn&amp;rsquo;t entirely parallel to the floating chassis often complicates this process. Both the service manual and my videos detail an adjustment procedure assuming the sensor arm&amp;rsquo;s parallelism.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Platter Motor: Replacement of Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-platter-motor-replacement-of-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) DC platter motor, previously restored in 2016, displayed RPM fluctuations and required attention. Although the motor&amp;rsquo;s bearings had been treated with oil at that time, the spark snubbers were not replaced. The motor had functioned correctly following the initial restoration.
Initial testing involved installing the motor in a 4002 turntable and monitoring its RPM stability over 24 hours. The results are represented by the blue line in the provided graph.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Full Functional Restoration and Installation of Beolover Commander Remote</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-full-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-beolover-commander-remote/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Texas, following an initial assessment. The author mentions a slight delay due to relocating to Albuquerque.
The turntable was mostly original, suggesting a straightforward restoration. The process began with the DC platter motor, which is typical for these units. After nearly 50 years of use, the motor&amp;rsquo;s Oilite bearings needed re-lubrication. This involved disassembling the motor, immersing the bearings in oil, and creating a vacuum to help the oil penetrate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/4002/4004 Relays: Professionally Manufactured PCBs!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 08:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400040024004-relays-professionally-manufactured-pcbs-/</guid><description>I recently updated the design of the Beogram 4000/4002/4004 relay adapter boards to allow for professional manufacturing. I&amp;rsquo;ve begun taking and fulfilling orders with these new boards, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled with how they turned out.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the boards:
These boards are compatible with both the older Siemens relays and the newer National relays commonly found as RPM and signal path grounding relays in the 400x series. They are designed as direct replacements for the original relays.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Inside Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:16:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-inside-work/</guid><description>My work on restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable from Houston continues, focusing on the internal components this time. This update covers the refurbishment of the tangential arm assembly and the replacement of the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s reservoir capacitor.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a current picture of the Beogram 4002 with its chassis and tangential arm assembly removed.
The tangential arm assembly components on this Beogram 4002 are in great condition. My work mainly involved cleaning and lubricating the Beogram chassis parts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Restoration of DC Platter Motor, PCBs and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 15:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restoration-of-dc-platter-motor-pcbs-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>I recently obtained the DC platter motor, circuit boards, and RPM panel from a Beogram 4002 (5513) located in California. I began with the motor, as is customary, because it requires a few days for the oil to fully permeate the bearings.
To begin, I took the motor apart to access the bearings. Then, I submerged the bearings in motor oil and created a vacuum. This process helps to remove air from the bearing material, allowing the oil to penetrate more effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Arrival from Arizona - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) from Arizona. It needed complete functional restoration. The unit arrived without its cover, shipped in a Beolover container, which is a great way to ensure safe transportation.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the unit as it looked when unpacked:
While a little dirty, it&amp;rsquo;s in decent condition except for the worn-out keypad:
Hopefully, these keypads can be professionally refurbished. On a positive note, the base is in good shape, with almost pristine corners:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: DC Motor Restoration and Dependence of RPM Performance on the Value of C10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 18:31:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-and-dependence-of-rpm-performance-on-the-value-of-c10/</guid><description>I recently obtained two DC motors from Beogram 4002 turntables that are being refurbished. One of the motors is pictured here.
The first step in restoring these motors is addressing the brass sleeve bearings, which are often dry after more than 35 years of use. I do this through an oil infusion process, which requires complete disassembly, as shown.
The bearings, visible on the black pad in the front, are submerged in oil and placed under vacuum.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Installing Rebuilt Rubber Pinch Rollers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 03:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</guid><description>Thorough testing of the Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape deck revealed an occasional issue where the leading capstan would cease to move the tape forward. This occurred under specific conditions, particularly when humidity hovered around 60% and room temperature dipped below 65°F. As a result, the supply capstan would continue to push the tape forward, causing it to slip out of place between the erase head and the supply pinch roller. Fortunately, the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s auto-stop function activated quickly enough to prevent damage to the tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: A New Day, a New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</guid><description>I recently got a new dust cover for a Beogram turntable from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, so they have a seamless look, unlike older reproduction covers that were made by fusing together laser-cut pieces. The result is a cover that&amp;rsquo;s indistinguishable from the original.
This photo shows the new cover:
The hinge for the cover was missing the small plastic pieces that prevent the spring mechanism from rubbing against the hinge&amp;rsquo;s metal parts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings with 3D Printed Replacement Parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5523) arm lowering mechanism, I removed the circuit boards for refurbishment. This presented an ideal opportunity to swap the deteriorated transport lock bushings with 3D-printed replacements. The old bushings tend to break down, scattering fragments within the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s casing, often lodging beneath the floating chassis. These fragments can obstruct the chassis&amp;rsquo;s movement, hindering its ability to isolate the turntable and tonearm from the enclosure.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Sensor Arm Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-sensor-arm-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in this Beogram 4000 restoration project was replaced with an LED. Located within the sensor arm, this particular LED presented the biggest challenge due to the tight space. The solution involved creating a custom flexible PCB equipped with a current limiting resistor and a bypass to mimic the higher energy draw of a traditional light bulb. This was necessary because the control system relies on the current to confirm the bulb&amp;rsquo;s functionality.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Houston Beogram #3 Ready for Action Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-houston-beogram-3-ready-for-action-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 15:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-houston-beogram-3-ready-for-action-again/</guid><description>My favorite stage of the Beogram 4002 restoration is here. The only remaining tasks are some enjoyable record-playing tests in my office. I find listening to records through a favorite system while working far more pleasurable than watching television&amp;hellip;and it&amp;rsquo;s a necessary job that someone has to do.
I&amp;rsquo;m truly happy with how this Beogram turned out. Knowing this turntable has been meticulously serviced is a great feeling. It&amp;rsquo;s spotless inside, and Beolover did an exceptional job revitalizing the platter motor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a 3D Printed Installation Tray</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control upgrade, specifically the receiver board insulation. My previous solution, using plastic foil, wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal aesthetically.
To address this, I designed a plastic tray that safeguards the receiver board from the main circuit board&amp;rsquo;s solder points. The tray is designed to click into place without additional screws.
Here are some photos:
Tray and board before assembly:
The tray features three rectangular cutouts to provide clearance for the solder points.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 AC Platter Motor Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-ac-platter-motor-restoration/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 AC platter motor from Massachusetts that had a knocking sound. Adjusting the voltage and tilt did not fix the problem. To address this, I typically disassemble the motor and submerge the housing parts in motor oil. Using a vacuum, I ensure the oil fills the material pores. Below is a picture of the motor upon arrival:
I drilled out the rivets and disassembled the motor:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival From West Virginia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from West Virginia recently arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was in good condition and shipped in a Beolover container.
Initial inspection revealed no significant damage to the dust cover or hinges. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, but the keypad has some wear. This will be addressed by installing a Beolover Commander remote control module, which allows for keypad-free operation.
The plinth is well-preserved, with minimal damage to the front corners, which are prone to wear.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Sub-Chassis and the Platter, and RPM Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 04:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-sub-chassis-and-the-platter-and-rpm-calibration/</guid><description>Today was dedicated to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis on a Beogram 4002 (5513) that I&amp;rsquo;m working on. I aimed to align the platter&amp;rsquo;s aluminum surface with the surrounding panels, center the sub-chassis within the transport locks&amp;rsquo; limits, and ensure the arms were parallel to the aluminum surfaces. It&amp;rsquo;s intricate work involving aligning numerous components. After gaining experience with this process, I achieved a satisfactory result, aligning the Beogram to specifications.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration and Yet Another Exciting Aspect of Achieving RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 22:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</guid><description>To restore the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor, several upgrades are necessary. These include installing modern multi-turn RPM trimmers, a new RPM relay, replacing the RPM trimmer backlights with LEDs, and refreshing the motor bearings with oil. Testing the RPM stability after each step reveals their individual impact on performance.
This particular Beogram 4002 had already undergone most of these improvements, with the exception of the motor restoration.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 8000 Type 5613: Wisconsin project is ready for record play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-wisconsin-project-is-ready-for-record-play/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-8000-type-5613-wisconsin-project-is-ready-for-record-play/</guid><description>The Beogram 8000 turntable has undergone service manual checks and adjustments. The power supply voltages are within acceptable ranges, and the forward/reverse scanning LDR adjustments and tracking force are calibrated. A test play confirms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s readiness for listening tests after component reinstallation.
The supply voltage readings at the filter capacitors and regulator outputs are as follows: +15 VDC, -15 VDC, and +5 VDC.
The forward and reverse scanning sensors (LDR devices) have been adjusted to an idle voltage of around 650 mVdc using a three-pin test connector.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddy Hubbard's 1975 Album "Polar AC"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddy-hubbards-1975-album-polar-ac/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable to its former glory is always fulfilling. This particular restoration involved several meticulous adjustments before I could relish Freddie Hubbard&amp;rsquo;s music.
The first crucial step was aligning the platter and arms flawlessly. Next, I had to align the platter with its surrounding aluminum panels while ensuring the chassis remained suspended, delicately balanced on its spring-loaded arms. This procedure requires precision as the tolerances for these adjustments are minimal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration: A New Tool on the Bench and the Importance of the Orientation of the Top Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-a-new-tool-on-the-bench-and-the-importance-of-the-orientation-of-the-top-bearing/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was acquired for restoration. Evidence suggested prior repair attempts on the motor, including scratches on the bearing assembly and damaged brushes.
Upon disassembly, it was clear the bearings hadn&amp;rsquo;t been properly oiled. A vacuum oil infusion process was conducted on both the top and bottom bearings. After cleaning and reassembly, a short circuit was detected, pointing to faulty spark snubbers.
The old spark snubbers were replaced with modern TVS devices.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (I)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-i-/</guid><description>While I&amp;rsquo;m waiting for a part for a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, I&amp;rsquo;ve started restoring another one with faulty displays. It seems cassettes are making a comeback! I&amp;rsquo;m even hoping for new tapes and maybe even a revival of the Sony Walkman II.
This particular Beocord 9000 has a very dim display:
[Image of dim display]
The &amp;ldquo;Time Cal&amp;rdquo; bulb is also weak, a common issue. I began with the VU meter (or Peak Program Meter), as I haven&amp;rsquo;t refurbished this type before.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Main Board Rework and Start of Speed Test #3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</guid><description>I visited Mouser to acquire some components for my Beogram project. However, upon commencing work on the main board, I realized I lacked a couple of 5KΩ multi-turn trimmers, essential for the 45 RPM and 33 1/3 RPM speed control (labeled 1R14 and 1R15). While I could order the parts, delivery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be possible until Monday, and I was eager to keep the project moving.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a photo of the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main board before removal:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Power Supply and Replacing the Reservoir Capacitors with a 3D Printed Fixture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-power-supply-and-replacing-the-reservoir-capacitors-with-a-3d-printed-fixture/</guid><description>It seems Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen made two versions of the Beogram 4002 (5513) with different power supply setups, both designed with a possible CD4 upgrade in mind. The output board could be swapped for one with a pre-amplifier and CD4 decoder. One version powers the CD4 board directly from the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s 30V rail and uses a single 4000uF capacitor.
My Beogram 4002 uses a separate power supply for the CD4 board, with its own transformer winding, bridge rectifier, and 1000uF capacitor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Adjusting/Calibrating the Detector Arm Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 turntable is nearly ready for use, with most of the necessary adjustments and calibrations finalized.
As planned, the record detection circuit needed adjustment due to a low measurement. Utilizing insights from Beolover&amp;rsquo;s blog post on the Beogram 4002 record detection circuit, the circuit was calibrated to align with the service manual&amp;rsquo;s specifications.
Two components on the main board, 1R26 (a 1MΩ resistor) and 1TR3 (an NPN BC548C transistor), are key in fine-tuning the signal from the record detection circuit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Extraction of Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Having restored a Beocord 5000 before, I&amp;rsquo;ve refined the process of removing the tape mechanism, simplifying the steps from my previous post and video.
I began by removing the plexiglass cover for polishing, which provided better access to the tape mechanism. To prepare for a full recap, I also lifted the preamplifier and radio amplifier boards. The photo shows the unit opened up:
&amp;lsquo;Chartz&amp;rsquo; from Beoworld.org suggested leaving the solenoid in place during removal, which led me to realize that even loosening the solenoid fixture is unnecessary.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) AC-motor turntable purchased from eBay. I had sent the seller specific packaging instructions and a sturdy double-boxed container, which they thankfully followed, resulting in the unit arriving undamaged. Initial observations are as follows:
The aluminum surfaces are generally in good shape, just needing a cleaning. The platter, in particular, has remarkably few imperfections.
The keypad shows typical signs of use, with fingerprints visible on the most frequently pressed keys.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacement of End Groove Detection Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 23:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5501) RPM trimmer panel, the focus shifted to the malfunctioning end groove detection mechanism. This ingenious mechanism utilizes a light bulb, a photoresistor, and an encoder wheel acting as a pulley to detect when the carriage accelerates after the record&amp;rsquo;s final track. By identifying this movement, the mechanism reduces the return time to the home position for records with extended end grooves, such as 12&amp;quot; singles or certain LPs with shorter playtimes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Massachusetts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always wonderful to see a returning customer! Earlier this year, I restored a Beogram 4000 for a client in Massachusetts. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to work on another Beogram 4000 he&amp;rsquo;s sent my way. It seems one can never have too many Beograms!
The Beogram 4000 arrived safely, shipped securely in a Beolover box. It was accompanied by a thoughtful gift for Beolover, for which I am incredibly grateful.
This beautiful reissue of &amp;ldquo;Waltz for Debby&amp;rdquo; by the Bill Evans Trio, a legendary jazz record, is a 180g pressing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Speed Indictor Light Bulbs with RGB LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 11:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-speed-indictor-light-bulbs-with-rgb-leds/</guid><description>During the wait for a 3D-printed part for a Beogram 4002 turntable restoration, the author decided to upgrade its speed indicator lights. Using a method from a previous video, they replaced the incandescent bulbs with RGB LEDs for a more authentic look.
The original setup with incandescent bulbs was documented before the upgrade.
The new setup utilizes both the red and green diodes of an RGB LED for a natural appearance, addressing the issue of amber LEDs failing to illuminate red scale markers properly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion, New Spark Snubbers and an Ultrasonic Cleaning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-new-spark-snubbers-and-an-ultrasonic-cleaning/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 DC platter motor was recently sent in for repair. Initial testing showed the motor was barely functional. To address this, the motor was disassembled, and the bearings were removed for lubrication.
The bearings, designed to be porous and oil-filled, were treated with a vacuum oil infusion process. This process, evidenced by vigorous bubbling, helps to replenish the oil within the bearings over time. After a few days, the bubbling subsided, indicating the bearings were adequately filled with oil, and they were removed from the oil bath.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter with SMD LEDs (III)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 23:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-with-smd-leds-iii-/</guid><description>This article, the third in a series about restoring a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s peak program meters (PPM), focuses on installing and calibrating the rebuilt PPM.
The initial step involved switching the original current limiting resistors with values suitable for modern SMD LEDs. These LEDs are more efficient and brighter, requiring significantly larger resistors to match the original brightness. Testing showed that 470 Ohm and 330 Ohm resistors for red and green LEDs, respectively, produced slightly brighter output compared to the original 180 Ohm and 120 Ohm resistors.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Repair of a Broken Out Leaf Spring in the Tape Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-leaf-spring-in-the-tape-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-leaf-spring-in-the-tape-mechanism/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, a loose part was discovered within the device&amp;rsquo;s casing. This component turned out to be the left leaf spring responsible for securing the head carrier. A comparison with the corresponding right spring revealed that a small ball bearing, crucial for smooth head movement, was missing.
Further investigation determined the ball bearing&amp;rsquo;s diameter to be 2.5 mm, and a readily available supply was procured. The broken plastic piece attached to the loose spring indicated that the original assembly, constantly under tension, had given way.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Some cabinet work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>The Beogram 8002&amp;rsquo;s internal components are ready to be placed back into the cabinet, but the cabinet needs some attention first.
While this Beogram&amp;rsquo;s cabinet is in good condition overall, there are a few things that need to be fixed, as mentioned in the initial assessment (linked in the original text).
The first step was to remove the aluminum deck lid. The previous re-attachment used overly thick double-sided tape that created too much space.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of a Wobbly Carriage Pulley with a New Aluminum Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-a-wobbly-carriage-pulley-with-a-new-aluminum-unit/</guid><description>As I was finishing the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5523), I noticed a concerning noise coming from the carriage when it moved quickly, especially when returning to its starting position. This led me to believe there was an issue with the carriage pulley. Upon inspection, I discovered that the pulley was cracked, which is a common problem with this model. It seems the original plastic can&amp;rsquo;t handle the stress from the setscrew over time and eventually cracks.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the Incandescent Indicator Light Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 13:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-incandescent-indicator-light-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beocord 9000, two indicator lights presented problems. One had a typical issue with a broken lead, while the other had become dim due to a deteriorating filament.
To address this, I opted to use SMD LEDs as replacements, similar to a method I&amp;rsquo;ve used for Beomaster 8000 units, documented on my blog. This provides lasting stability and safeguards against potential shipping damage. However, the Beocord 9000 has more compact reflector housings compared to the Beomaster 8000, necessitating a redesign of the PCBs for the LEDs.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Total Recap - Replacement of all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>This article revisits a complete restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, focusing on the replacement of electrolytic capacitors for improved long-term reliability. While not as crucial as with amplifiers due to lower operating temperatures, capacitor replacement is recommended for optimal performance.
The Beocord 9000, designed for serviceability, allows access to its numerous electrolytic capacitors. Unlike its predecessors, it offers easier access by removing the front and back panels instead of extracting the main circuit boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, known for its unstable RPM, recently arrived for repair. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in excellent cosmetic condition with only minor blemishes.
The keypad appears barely used. However, the hood has some deep scratches, likely from improper storage. Internally, the turntable looks completely original.
Initial testing revealed the arm lowering mechanism is slow, and the automatic RPM switching from 33 to 45 is not functioning, although manual switching works.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoration of the Peak Program Meter Scale Illumination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 08:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoration-of-the-peak-program-meter-scale-illumination/</guid><description>Even though the scale illumination light bulb was functioning in the Beocord 9000 display, my customer opted for a replacement to avoid any potential issues during shipping. This makes sense because these bulbs are fragile and prone to breaking, especially with rough handling. I prefer to replace all bulbs to prevent future problems.
I performed this procedure before on a Beocord 9000 with a broken bulb, as documented on my blog.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting the Floating Chassis Height</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-the-floating-chassis-height/</guid><description>After adjusting the main platter bearing in a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to set the height of the floating chassis. The goal is to make sure the aluminum surface of the platter is level with the surrounding aluminum panels. You can adjust the height by turning the nuts on the leaf springs that hold the chassis and provide vibration isolation. Using an 8 mm hex wrench is recommended.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Finishing Up The Tangential Arm Position Sensor &amp; The Fixed Arm Platter Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-finishing-up-the-tangential-arm-position-sensor-the-fixed-arm-platter-sensor/</guid><description>I was pleased to discover that Beolover successfully refurbished the platter motor for my Beogram 4002. During the packing process for the motor&amp;rsquo;s return, I took the opportunity to calibrate the voltage for two newly installed sensor lamps within the Beogram.
The recently added LED replacement light for the tangential arm position sensor was insufficiently bright. While it functioned, even at maximum output (with the 1R88, 25K ohm trimmer at its highest setting), the voltage measured at the 1TR17 base only reached 0.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Fader Fixed and Putting it Back Together</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</guid><description>I examined the fader on my Beocord 5000 (4715) tape deck and discovered significant corrosion on the Fade In and Fade Out button contacts, preventing them from making a connection. Using DeoxIT D100 applied to a strip of paper, I cleaned the contact pads while pressing the buttons. This successfully removed the corrosion, evidenced by black streaks on the paper. I repeated this process on the remaining buttons, restoring the deck&amp;rsquo;s responsiveness to a like-new condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 DC Motor Restoration - Oil Infusion of Bearings and New Spark Snubbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 01:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-dc-motor-restoration-oil-infusion-of-bearings-and-new-spark-snubbers/</guid><description>A DC motor, removed from a Beogram 4002 in Arlington, VA, was sent in for repair.
The initial step involved taking the motor apart and extracting its bearings for lubrication.
The bearings, resembling small rings, were submerged in motor oil and a vacuum was applied. This process causes air bubbles to emerge from the bearing material, indicating oil infusion.
After a day, the bubbling stopped, signifying that the bearings were saturated with oil.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Initial Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, dropped off by its long-time owner, appears to have been well-maintained.
The control panel buttons show typical wear from use, but the dust cover is in good condition with only minor marks. The tonearm requires adjustment as it sits too low when the turntable is not in use.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s interior is very clean, suggesting it was kept in a good environment.
The original washers for the floating suspension lock-down are intact.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjustments, Cleaning the Aluminum Surfaces and a First Spin with Freddie Hubbard!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjustments-cleaning-the-aluminum-surfaces-and-a-first-spin-with-freddie-hubbard-/</guid><description>Following the installation of a new gold-plated DIN 5 plug, the Beogram 4000 was ready for its initial test. The RPM was fine-tuned using a custom Beolover RPM device, aided by the recently installed precision multi-turn trimmers. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that allowing the unit to warm up for approximately 15 minutes before this adjustment is recommended, as the RPM can fluctuate slightly during this period. For fellow enthusiasts, the Beolover RPM device is available upon request via email or the contact form and includes a separate base for convenient setup and occasional RPM checks.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench/</guid><description>During the holiday season, I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable for repair. My initial assessment showed that it was packaged very well, with some innovative methods used to protect it during shipping.
The dust cover was secured using soft foam blocks to hold the sub-platter and the RPM panel in place.
The MMC20E cartridge was also protected by foam and arrived in good condition.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the cartridge after unpacking:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Montana</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-montana/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-montana/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable from a customer in Montana who purchased it in the 1970s. He wants a complete restoration. This post provides an initial assessment, and a follow-up will detail the work done.
The turntable arrived safely in a protective Beolover shipping container. Upon opening it, the turntable appeared to be in good overall condition, with the aluminum surfaces and plinth corners looking particularly well-preserved.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Polishing and Exchange of the Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration project required a hood restoration. I had two hoods: one had a cracked corner, and the other had a good plexiglass body but a corroded hinge.
Corrosion is common on Beogram 4000 hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s fixable with sanding and repainting, but finding a good hinge is preferable. Luckily, the cracked hood had a usable hinge, so I decided to swap them.
Removing the hinge requires care to avoid damaging the aluminum strip on the back of the hood.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of a Strange Fault Caused by a Shorted Diode D6</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 22:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, a peculiar control system issue persisted even after replacing the reservoir capacitors.
Upon pressing START, the carriage would begin to move but halt after approximately 20 mm, coinciding with the lights turning off. A few seconds later, the lights would illuminate again, and the motor would operate at 45 RPM. In this state, the carriage could be moved using the &amp;raquo; &amp;laquo; buttons, but the arm lowering function was disabled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Seattle en Route to Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</guid><description>An Australian customer purchased a Beogram 4002 on eBay from the US and sent it to me for restoration. Upon its arrival, I discovered it was in poor condition, likely due to storage in a basement or attic. The dust cover was particularly damaged, with scratches on the aluminum trim and the surface itself.
Despite the dust cover&amp;rsquo;s condition, the internal components appeared undamaged, including the hinges, suggesting a successful restoration is possible.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002/4004: Replacement of a Broken Cable Clamp/PCB Holder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-40024004-replacement-of-a-broken-cable-clamppcb-holder/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a broken cable clamp/PCB holder presented an opportunity to test a replacement part file. A fellow Beogram enthusiast from New Zealand shared the file, and in return, received access to parts in my Shapeways store. Photos document the broken clamp, the 3D-printed replacement, and the final installation. The new clamp fits securely with the PCB, keeping the audio cable properly positioned. With the successful trial complete, the part was made available for purchase in my store for other B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reinstalling the Floating Chassis Components</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</guid><description>All the necessary restoration parts for the Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable are now available, marking the start of the reassembly process.
The reinstallation begins with securing the floating chassis, equipped with the tangential arm assembly, back into the Beogram 4002 cabinet. The process starts by fitting the Beolover replacement suspension lock bushings onto the floating chassis. Subsequently, the suspension locks are positioned within the cabinet base. The floating chassis is then carefully lowered onto these locking bolts, and the remaining locking mechanisms are put in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the DC Motor and a Significant Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-dc-motor-and-a-significant-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>A recently acquired Beogram 4002 turntable exhibited significant speed variations during an initial performance test. The frequent and irregular drops in rotations per minute (RPM) pointed to a need for cleaning and lubrication of the DC motor.
The motor was removed from its housing for servicing.
The motor was then disassembled to allow for cleaning and lubrication of its bearings.
Following reassembly and reinstallation of the motor, a 24-hour RPM test was conducted.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Keyboard Keys - Video About Removal and Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</guid><description>After restoring a Beogram 4000, I shipped it to a customer, but two keypad keys came loose during transport. To secure them, I had used tape and foam, but the shipping stress was too much for the delicate leaf spring mechanism holding the keys.
To prevent this from happening again, I created special tools that make it easier to install the keys and shared a video demonstrating their use. These tools, designed to avoid damaging the aluminum, are available to other enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Electrical Work and Initial Tracking Adjustment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-electrical-work-and-initial-tracking-adjustment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 15:12:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-electrical-work-and-initial-tracking-adjustment/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s begin restoring the electronic boards. The main control board needs its capacitors replaced and the RPM relay (along with the RPM trimmers) need attention. Additionally, the output board requires inspection of its phono muting circuit. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that aside from wiring, the muting relay is the sole electrical part interacting with the phono audio signal. The turntable&amp;rsquo;s electronics mainly manage the platter motor, tangential arm, indicator lamps, and user controls, none of which are part of the audio pathway.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Infusing the DC Motor Oilite Bearings with Fresh Oil</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:42:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-infusing-the-dc-motor-oilite-bearings-with-fresh-oil/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5524), the DC motor required attention. The Oilite brass bearings, designed with a &amp;rsquo;lifetime&amp;rsquo; lubricant within their pores, typically need replenishing after approximately four decades. This involves submerging the bearings in motor oil and using a vacuum to extract air from the pores, allowing oil to penetrate. A detailed video demonstrating this process is available here.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse at this specific motor, both extracted from the turntable:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival From California - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 08:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 Type 5513 from California, which needs a complete technical overhaul.
This post will provide an initial evaluation of the unit. It was delivered in excellent shape thanks to the customer&amp;rsquo;s careful packaging in a Beolover-provided shipping container. I was relieved because this device is in fantastic cosmetic shape. In the past, Beolover had a lot of &amp;ldquo;heartbreaking&amp;rdquo; experiences with units that arrived damaged because of inadequate packaging despite initially seeming pristine.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Restoring the Peak Program Meters with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-restoring-the-peak-program-meters-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beocord 9000&amp;rsquo;s Peak Program Meter (PPM), even though it was fully functional. This decision stemmed from my success in restoring a different Beocord&amp;rsquo;s PPM that had several broken segments.
Since the technology behind these PPMs is similar to that of a 7-segment display, I realized that the segments in this unit were also susceptible to future breakage. Therefore, I chose to preemptively address the issue while I had the opportunity.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Exchanging the Rubber Parts in the Tape Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 13:15:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-exchanging-the-rubber-parts-in-the-tape-mechanism/</guid><description>My Beocord 9000 restoration project saw some good progress. I recently installed new rubber tires on the idler wheels of the tape drive mechanism to address a rewinding issue. The deck wasn&amp;rsquo;t rewinding smoothly, becoming very slow and sometimes even stopping at the end of the process. This seemed like a common problem attributed to hardened idler wheel rubber, as suggested by Beoworld.org.
However, upon disassembling the mechanism, I discovered that a previous repair attempt had damaged a crucial friction pad, which was the root cause of the problem.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Adjusting Platter, Sub-Chassis, Arm Lowering Limit and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-adjusting-platter-sub-chassis-arm-lowering-limit-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>To prepare the Beogram 4002 (5513) for testing, several mechanical adjustments were required. The platter needed to be perfectly aligned with the surrounding aluminum plates. This involved balancing the floating sub-chassis within its support brackets. After aligning the chassis and platter, the arm lowering limit was addressed. Finally, the tracking force was calibrated to match the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s weight dial.
Prior to adjusting the sub-chassis, damaged cabinet guidance washers, crucial for securing the top aluminum plates, were replaced with 3D-printed replicas.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reassembly of the Floating Chassis and Some Initial Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</guid><description>After completing the tangential arm assembly checks and cleaning the Beogram 4002 cabinet, it was time to reinstall the floating chassis.
The reassembly began with cleaning and lubricating the three suspension lock down screws, then reinstalling them in the Beogram cabinet.
With all three suspension locks back in place, the platter motor and output board, which had been previously restored, were reinstalled.
The control panel, RPM indicator panel, and arm position scale were then put back in their respective places.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-australia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-australia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Australia recently arrived and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my initial assessment. Despite the packaging using incredibly small packing peanuts (resulting in a big mess!), the turntable arrived in great shape.
The attached image showcases the turntable as I unpacked it:
This Beogram 4000 has a nice dust cover with minimal scratching, good aluminum trim, and intact plexiglass hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely worth keeping and polishing.
Under the dust cover, things are looking good as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors on the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-on-the-pcbs/</guid><description>I began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) by replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards with high-quality 105C capacitors. I made sure to use components from reputable Japanese brands like Nichicon and Rubycon, sourcing them through trusted distributors like Newark and Mouser. The process was straightforward, aside from uncovering a spider web (and its architect) beneath the main PCB. This restoration project also highlighted the existence of at least two different solenoid control circuits within the 5513 series.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor Video Published - Check It Out!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finished my Beogram DC motor restoration video due to high demand! This video will show you how to disassemble the motor and revitalize the Oilite brass bearings by infusing oil under a vacuum. If your Beogram&amp;rsquo;s RPM is inconsistent, this video is for you! Have a look:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>Some time ago, a customer in Texas purchased a Beogram 4000 turntable on eBay from a seller in New York. The turntable was in fair condition, as detailed on the blog (see hyperlink). To address a cracked corner on the dust cover, the decision was made to acquire a second Beogram 4000, allowing the creation of one flawless unit from the two. With the arrival of the second turntable, the restoration began.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Very Oily DC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:44:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-very-oily-dc-platter-motor/</guid><description>I obtained a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor from Berlin, Germany, for restoration. The motor&amp;rsquo;s exterior was noticeably oily, likely due to an attempt to improve its RPM stability through lubrication.
Disassembly was necessary to access and treat the bearings. The motor&amp;rsquo;s interior was also oil-coated. However, this is ineffective for the bearings, as they require vacuum oil infusion. This process removes air trapped within the porous Oilite brass material, enabling new oil to penetrate the bearing effectively.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Checking the Forward/Reverse Scanning LDR Devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-checking-the-forwardreverse-scanning-ldr-devices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:45:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-checking-the-forwardreverse-scanning-ldr-devices/</guid><description>My previous work on this Beogram left me concerned about a potential issue with one of the forward/reverse scanning LDRs (Light Dependent Resistors).
Testing the resistance of both LDRs with +15 VDC on the light source, I noticed a significant difference between them, leading me to believe one was faulty. However, upon removing and re-testing them, the resistance values were much closer.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that my testing method involved a simple setup with an LED work light as a light source.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a Plug-In Ready SMD LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 09:07:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-plug-in-ready-smd-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of my Beogram 4002 (5513), I installed the latest iteration of my SMD LED light source for the tracking sensor.
Previously, I designed a drop-in SMD LED assembly to replace the incandescent bulb fixture, which worked well. However, it still relied on the original, cumbersome tracking sensor sensitivity adjustment process. This process involves carefully positioning the light sensors relative to the light source, a task made difficult by the mechanism&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and the adjustment mechanism&amp;rsquo;s coarseness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Progress Update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-progress-update/</guid><description>The next stage of the restoration involved removing parts from the Beogram chassis. This was necessary to access the tangential arm for repairs and to thoroughly clean the disintegrated transport bushings.
Fragments of the old bushings were scattered throughout the chassis, even within the tonearm cover.
This image shows the Beogram chassis after a thorough cleaning.
Next, 3D-printed replacement bushings from Beolover were installed.
The new bushings fit perfectly. When reattaching the floating chassis, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to align the top and bottom locking washers on their respective threads.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Repair of a Broken Out DIN-7 Jack With 3D Printed Inserts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 18:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-repair-of-a-broken-out-din-7-jack-with-3d-printed-inserts/</guid><description>Repairing the broken DIN 7 jack on the Beocord 9000 was simpler than anticipated. The part is identical to the one used for the Beomaster 8000&amp;rsquo;s Phono input. A 3D printed part, designed previously, was used to replace the fragile tabs on these sockets, which often break and cause the jack to fall into the panel cutout. Images of the broken jack and the 3D printed replacements are included.
A short video demonstrating the installation process and the repaired plug is provided.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: First Listening Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 16:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-first-listening-test/</guid><description>I finished the mechanical adjustments on the Beogram today. After turning on my digital scale, I calibrated and locked the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s tracking force counterweight. Following Beolover&amp;rsquo;s method, I secured the calibrated setting by replacing the M3 counterweight adjustment screw on the back of the tonearm with a tightening nut. This prevents accidental changes during transport or handling.
With the counterweight set, I secured the locking nut and added a touch of glue for extra stability.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Return of an Old Friend from Australia - Dead Solenoid Transistor and a Carriage Motor with a Corroded Lead</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-return-of-an-old-friend-from-australia-dead-solenoid-transistor-and-a-carriage-motor-with-a-corroded-lead/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 15:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-return-of-an-old-friend-from-australia-dead-solenoid-transistor-and-a-carriage-motor-with-a-corroded-lead/</guid><description>Unfortunately, I recently received a well-used Beolover Beogram shipping container from Australia. Inside was a Beogram 4002 (5501) that I had previously restored in 2016. The 5501 model is unique because it represents a short-lived transitional version produced during B&amp;amp;O&amp;rsquo;s shift from the Beogram 4000 to the 4002. Although the 5501 features the analog control system of the 4002 series (unlike the 4000&amp;rsquo;s more sophisticated hard-wired digital logic system, which was sadly simplified in the 4002), it retains the mechanical carriage position switches found in the 4000.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look at a New Arrival from Berlin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look-at-a-new-arrival-from-berlin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look-at-a-new-arrival-from-berlin/</guid><description>My first project in Germany this year is a Beogram 4000 turntable. While the packaging from Berlin was good, the dust cover was cracked in one corner, likely due to inadequate protection by the seller. Thankfully, the turntable itself is in decent cosmetic condition.
The aluminum surfaces are mostly unscathed, with some minor scratches from the tonearm assembly, probably because the transport lock wasn&amp;rsquo;t engaged. The wooden base is also in good shape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Service Manual Checks and Sensor Adjustment for the Third Beogram from Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-checks-and-sensor-adjustment-for-the-third-beogram-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 10:37:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-service-manual-checks-and-sensor-adjustment-for-the-third-beogram-from-houston/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration is nearing completion, moving from the workbench to the test bench. The final phase involved service manual checks and adjustments, along with calibrating the record detection, arm position, and tracking sensors.
Following a guide, the record detection sensor was calibrated by adjusting the 1TR3 collector voltage to 4 VDC for an empty, spinning platter. This voltage should remain consistent with a record on the platter.
Next, the tangential arm position sensor was adjusted to achieve 5 VDC at the 4IC1 collector when illuminated by the sensor lamp through a transparent part of the position scale.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Increasing Tonearm Lowering Delay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</guid><description>After installing a new hood on a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author noticed the tonearm descended too quickly. Adjusting the damper&amp;rsquo;s screw didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem, as the tonearm still dropped rapidly despite the damper slowing down.
Further inspection revealed the damper&amp;rsquo;s linkage was positioned very close to the damper plunger. This proximity meant the linkage moved immediately when the damper activated, even before the damper could build up enough vacuum to slow the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s descent effectively.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Colorado - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 08:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable arrived from Colorado for restoration, carefully packaged in a specialized box. The outer cover had several scratches but could potentially be polished to an acceptable condition. The hinges seemed fine, and the aluminum underneath the cover appeared to be in good shape. The control keypad showed only minor signs of wear.
The corners of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s base were almost pristine. However, upon inspection, the metal frames attached to the plinth were loosening, a common issue caused by deteriorating glue.</description></item></channel></rss>