<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Netherlands on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/netherlands/</link><description>Recent content in Netherlands on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/netherlands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State.</description></item><item><title>People from another place? EU citizenship and the renunciation of national citizenship in Member States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-from-another-place-eu-citizenship-and-the-renunciation-of-national-citizenship-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/people-from-another-place-eu-citizenship-and-the-renunciation-of-national-citizenship-in-member-states/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*This blog post draws from the upcoming second edition of The EU Citizenship Directive (OUP, 2019), co-authored by myself, Elspeth Guild, and Jonathan Tomkin.
Typically, the rules governing the acquisition and loss of nationality are decided by individual Member States. However, this issue is central to EU law because, as stated in Article 20(1) TFEU, EU citizenship is reliant on possessing the nationality of a Member State:</description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?</description></item><item><title>Can a person be a member of both a national parliament and the European Parliament at the same time?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recently, Geert Wilders, the leader of the Dutch PVV party and a newly elected Member of the European Parliament (MEP), declared his intent to pursue legal action to maintain his position as both an MEP and a member of the Dutch national parliament. This begs the question: does such a right exist?
The crux of the matter lies in Article 39 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, which states that every EU citizen possesses the right to vote in and stand as a candidate for European Parliament elections.</description></item></channel></rss>