<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Healthcare on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/healthcare/</link><description>Recent content in Healthcare on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:56:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The keto diet market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 5%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</guid><description>Technavio reports that the keto diet is gaining popularity, as overweight and obese individuals experience faster weight loss and body fat reduction compared to other diets.
This diet emphasizes extremely low carbohydrate intake and high fat consumption, aiming to initiate a metabolic state called ketosis. Ketosis enables the body to burn fat more effectively.
Technavio forecasts that the keto diet market will grow at a rate close to 5% by 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Actxa Spur makes training in your heart rate zone easier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 05:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</guid><description>Actxa has launched the Spur, a wearable fitness tracker that continuously monitors heart rate and provides zone indication. The Spur aims to make heart rate zone training accessible to everyone, not just athletes, by offering a user-friendly alternative to chest straps.
For years, fitness enthusiasts and athletes have used heart rate as a measure of workout intensity. A higher heart rate generally indicates a more intense workout.
The Spur uses a wrist-based sensor to measure resting heart rate and track different heart rate zones: Warm Up, Fat Burning, Cardio, Intense, and Maximum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/actxa-spur-makes-training-in-your-heart-rate-zone-easier/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The intelligent coach for individuals with diabetes is designed to improve long-term quality of life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</guid><description>A new &amp;ldquo;smart coach&amp;rdquo; service aims to assist individuals with type 2 diabetes in developing healthier lifestyle choices for improved long-term well-being. Diabetes, particularly when poorly managed, can result in complications such as vision loss, kidney issues, and nerve damage. It has also been linked to Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;type 3 diabetes.&amp;rdquo;
The global rise of diabetes presents significant healthcare cost concerns. Holmusk, a digital health and data analytics company, highlights that over 415 million people worldwide have diabetes, a figure that continues to grow annually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans struggle with getting a good night's sleep</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/</guid><description>Singaporeans are some of the world&amp;rsquo;s worst sleepers, averaging 6.3 hours of sleep on weekdays and 6.7 hours on weekends. These figures fall short of the global averages of 6.8 and 7.8 hours, respectively, and the recommended eight hours per night. This information comes from the report &amp;ldquo;The Global Pursuit of Better Sleep Health,&amp;rdquo; published by Royal Philips, a global leader in health technology.
Philips conducts an annual global sleep survey in conjunction with World Sleep Day (March 15)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-struggle-with-getting-a-good-night-s-sleep/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Options for Healthcare Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s healthcare landscape, broadband connectivity is crucial, driven by the increasing use of electronic health records, medical imaging, and telemedicine. When establishing an effective EHR environment, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to consider both private lines and public internet bandwidth services.
While both serve a purpose, private lines offer secure internal communication channels ideal for organizations managing sensitive electronic data. Essentially, these lines act as an extension of your network, ensuring restricted access to authorized users only...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers of Singtel and AIA Singapore will enjoy the advantages of digital wellness initiatives offered in collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 05:51:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</guid><description>Singtel and AIA Singapore are joining forces to encourage healthier lifestyles in Singapore. This partnership between leaders in communications technology and life insurance is the first of its kind in the country.
The collaboration aims to digitally reach their combined customer base of over 5 million, motivating them to be active and healthy. They also intend to develop innovative insurance products tailored to the evolving digital habits of their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-singtel-and-aia-singapore-will-enjoy-the-advantages-of-digital-wellness-initiatives-offered-in-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The difficulty of innovating quickly enough to ensure a comfortable life until the age of 100</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</guid><description>An on-site poll at The Longevity Summit – Is Asia ready for 100? in Singapore revealed that the majority (60%) of the 200 Asian business leaders, government officials, and healthcare professionals present didn&amp;rsquo;t believe the current pace of innovation could address the challenges of increasing longevity. Attendees convened to explore how to better integrate Asia&amp;rsquo;s senior population into the workforce and promote healthier, longer lives.
A Call for Total Change Kanwaljit Soin, Founding President of Women’s Initiative for Ageing Successfully, emphasized the need to overhaul the current linear life model...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-difficulty-of-innovating-quickly-enough-to-ensure-a-comfortable-life-until-the-age-of-100/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>