<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dining on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dining/</link><description>Recent content in Dining on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dining/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Starting October 14, the Coffee Lounge at Goodwood Park Hotel will be offering an expanded menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Goodwood Park Hotel, home to the Coffee Lounge known for its Taiwan porridge and local dishes, is launching a limited-time menu enhancement. From October 14th, guests can enjoy new additions to the &amp;ldquo;Design Your Own Local Degustation Set Menu&amp;rdquo; and a special dessert buffet featuring Mao Shan Wang durian.
This year, from October 14th to November 17th, Coffee Lounge&amp;rsquo;s popular dessert buffet will showcase Mao Shan Wang durian pastries alongside its regular offerings during lunch and dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-october-14-the-coffee-lounge-at-goodwood-park-hotel-will-be-offering-an-expanded-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with Amara Sanctuary Singapore's special promotion!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa. Singapore laksa.
To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 53rd birthday, the 5-star Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is offering a National Day special at their Shutters restaurant.
During this National Day celebration, Shutters&amp;rsquo; dinner guests will enjoy a discounted Singapura buffet, priced at S$53++ per adult, down from the usual S$75++. This offer is valid from 6:30 pm to 10:00 pm. The buffet features local favorites like Nyonya laksa, barbequed stingray, and charcoal-grilled satay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In March, Dario Cecchini explores culinary partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 10:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</guid><description>The renowned Bottega di Carna at the Mondrian Singapore Duxton, known for its unique dining experience crafted by &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Butcher&amp;rdquo; Dario Cecchini, is excited to announce upcoming collaborations this March. The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s philosophy centers around respecting the entire animal and utilizing traditional methods to showcase the finest produce and ingredients.
Cecchini Returns with Exciting Collaborations Bottega di Carna X Bold &amp;amp; Braised Hawker Pop-up
March 6th-7th
Cecchini and Bottega di Carna&amp;rsquo;s Head Chef Kenny Huang are joining forces with local Chinatown eatery Bold &amp;amp; Braised at Maxwell Food Centre...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>NOBU presents Harvest in Aomori at InterContinental Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hong Kong. Steamed abalone, sea urchin shijimi dashi jelly, and cured mackerel sashimi with chrysanthemum dressing.
NOBU InterContinental Hong Kong presents the fifth installment of its GOURMET TOUR OF JAPAN series – Harvest in Aomori – which runs from September 12th to October 22nd.
Executive Chef Sean Mell and Executive Sushi Chef Arakai Kaazunari have crafted special lunch and dinner menus that showcase the fall bounty of Aomori Prefecture, a region in northern Japan&amp;rsquo;s Tōhoku region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GwaKu offers tasty and budget-friendly dishes in the center of Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>Source: Gwaku&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This is their famous ayam percik.
GwaKu, a restaurant situated in Q Sentral close to KL Sentral, offers a rotating menu that keeps nearby office workers surprised about their lunch options. For example, one week could feature ayam perchik, while the following week might offer lamb stews.
Mike Ibrahim, the founder of GwaKu, emphasizes their commitment to using fresh, seasonal, and locally sourced ingredients. He explains, &amp;ldquo;By using in-season produce, we can ensure quality and freshness while also benefiting from lower prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AppDine has launched a beta version of its F&amp;B and lifestyle e-commerce marketplace in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: AppeDine. Screenshot of the AppeDine app for consumers.
AppeDine has launched the public beta version of its food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and lifestyle e-commerce platform in Singapore. The marketplace facilitates online transactions tailored for F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle businesses, chefs, and consumers.
AppeDine brings together F&amp;amp;B outlets, temporary events, and promotions in one place, enabling F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle providers to generate revenue from their services and spaces online without upfront investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the street food of Taiwan at Tea Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</guid><description>Tea Valley: Bringing Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Street Food Flavors to Singapore [Image of Tea Valley Downtown East outlet]
Tea Valley (茶食坊), a casual Taiwanese dining chain in Singapore, has ambitious plans for expansion. At a tasting event held at their first location in Downtown East, Director Lawrence Lim shared his vision for growing the brand beyond just new locations, but also in the variety of services they offer.
[Image of Lawrence Lim, Director of Tea Valley]..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinoya in Dubai has been awarded the One to Watch Award for 2022 by MENA's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Kinoya restaurant has been awarded the One To Watch Award 2022 by Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. This recognition is given to up-and-coming restaurants in the region that have the potential to earn a spot on the 50 Best list in future years.
Kinoya&amp;rsquo;s founder, Neha Mishra, also known as the Ramen Queen, opened the restaurant after the success of her home-based supper club, A Story of Food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels will be introducing a Gourmet Food &amp; Wine Festival in Singapore in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Jaan was awarded a Michelin Star in the Singapore Michelin Guide 2016 and secured the 29th spot in Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2016.
AccorHotels, the leading hotel operator in the country, is launching its first-ever Gourmet Food &amp;amp; Wine Festival, anticipated to be one of the most extensive events of its kind in Singapore.
The festival will feature several Michelin-starred chefs. Graham Wilson, Chief Marketing &amp;amp; Distribution Officer for AccorHotels Asia Pacific, stated, “In a city celebrated for its culinary scene, AccorHotels will bring together some of our finest chefs from around the world and showcase the immense talent of Singaporean chefs to create a food festival as lively and diverse as Singapore itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New retail and dining tenants have been announced at City Square Mall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 13:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</guid><description>City Developments (CDL) is updating the dining and retail options at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s City Square Mall.
The Decathlon store at City Square Mall, taken on 21 May.
French sporting goods retailer, Decathlon, launched its first Singaporean store on May 21, 2016. The company, known for its wide selection and reasonable prices, aims to make sports accessible.
“Our 21,500 sq ft store carries over 85,000 innovative, high-quality products across 50 sports. It will help Decathlon achieve its mission of making sports accessible to every Singaporean,” remarked Bastien Grandgeorge, CEO of Decathlon Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-retail-and-dining-tenants-have-been-announced-at-city-square-mall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Festive takeaways and buffets at Hotel Jen Tanglin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 06:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</guid><description>Hotel Jen Tanglin&amp;rsquo;s popular &amp;ldquo;Fully-Loaded&amp;rdquo; holiday takeaway meal is back. This offering features a whole roasted turkey, accompanied by all the fixings, conveniently packaged in a thermal bag. It&amp;rsquo;s designed to easily serve 10 to 12 guests.
According to Vathsala Subramaniam, General Manager of Hotel Jen Tanglin Singapore, they&amp;rsquo;ve crafted a special Asian roasted turkey using the &amp;ldquo;percik&amp;rdquo; style. This approach aims to blend tradition with a distinct Asian flavor. For those with bigger parties, ordering both the Western and Asian style turkeys ensures a diverse culinary experience for everyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/festive-takeaways-and-buffets-at-hotel-jen-tanglin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience sustainable dining at Avani properties in Indochina</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</guid><description>Image Credit: Avani. Plant-based coconut acai bowls are available at the Avani+ Samui Resort.
To create a healthier planet and promote sustainability, Avani Hotels has introduced a variety of eco-friendly and wellness-focused programs.
Avani&amp;rsquo;s flagship hotels in Thailand, Cambodia, and Laos are increasing their efforts to support nearby communities. They are accomplishing this by showcasing regional specialties and advocating for a decrease in reliance on imported goods. They have also implemented zero-waste programs, which include composting systems to handle all organic waste and on-site organic gardens to encourage self-sufficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-sustainable-dining-at-avani-properties-in-indochina/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean restaurant and art gallery are showcasing hypebeast artworks for diners to enjoy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</guid><description>Until March 2021, enthusiasts of modern pop culture and Japanese cuisine in Singapore can experience a unique collaboration that blends contemporary art with specialized dining.
Source: simpleArte by iCare.4u. Artworks by the featured artists participating in Hypebeast@Uni.
Doraemon Here We Go by Takashi Murakami (left), Hero number 12 by Shen Jingdong (right, top left quadrant), Chiho Aoshima, artist (right, top right quadrant), Sky Year by Aoshima (right, bottom right quadrant), and Steven Harrington (right, bottom left quadrant)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bay Hotel Singapore will be offering a Ramadhan buffet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</guid><description>Source: Bay Hotel Singapore. The Ramadhan buffet spread.
Bay Hotel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Rumah Rasa restaurant will offer a special Ramadan buffet every evening from May 16th to June 14th, 2018.
Leading the culinary team, Executive Chef Esa will showcase highlights like chick kut teh, a flavorful broth simmered overnight and accompanied by taupok (fried tofu puffs), dried mushrooms, and garlic, as part of the Ramadan Iftar Menu.
Another standout dish is ayam woku belanga, featuring marinated chicken infused with a special spice blend inspired by the Manado cuisine of North Sulawesi, Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The goal of the Taste The World Dining Series is to demonstrate that food serves as a universal form of communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</guid><description>Gourmet Trails, a luxury travel company, presents the first-ever Taste The World culinary series, taking place from May 4th to 26th, 2024. This festival showcases the unifying power of food, emphasizing its ability to connect people and foster understanding.
Taste The World partners with acclaimed restaurants like Appetite, Hashida, CURE, Canchita, Esquina, Ummi Beirut, and ANJU to offer a diverse range of global cuisines. Proceeds from this event will support the United Nations World Food Programme...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HungryGoWhere is collecting votes for its inaugural foodie awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</guid><description>The inaugural HungryGoWhere Awards voting period has opened. The food review platform HungryGoWhere revealed that public votes will solely decide the 26 award recipients.
Those interested in voting have until February 4th to cast their ballots on the awards website. The awards span five categories: Restaurants, Hawkers, Drinks, Occasions, and Best of the Best. After the voting period ends, participants will be entered into a lucky draw...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself to taste delicious food from various regions at RWS Street Eats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</guid><description>Resorts World Sentosa (RWS) is bringing back its popular food event, RWS Street Eats, after it attracted over 100,000 attendees last year. The event will run from May 3rd to 12th, 2019, and showcase new dishes from across Southeast Asia.
Taking place at the Malaysian Food Street in RWS, this 10-day event will feature hidden culinary gems from Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, Vietnam, and Taiwan. These vendors are local favorites, often known only to the savviest eaters in their respective countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FUMI creates authentic Japanese dining experiences for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</guid><description>Source: FUMI Facebook page. FUMI sushi.
FUMI, a new Japanese eatery, seeks to share the finest Japanese cuisine in Hong Kong within a space adorned with Japanese art, furnishings, and tableware. They offer a range of dining experiences, from elaborate omakase and kaiseki dinners to individual dishes and set lunch options.
Situated in California Tower, FUMI sources the highest quality seasonal ingredients directly from Japan daily. Flown in and delivered straight to their kitchen, these ingredients are often prepared and served within hours of being harvested, guaranteeing freshness in their sushi, sashimi, omakase, and kaiseki preparations, as well as a variety of seasonal menus...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the unique Kampong culinary specials at the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>This June, the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur in Malaysia is offering a special deal for gatherings with colleagues, business contacts, and potential clients. The promotion is valid in their newly renovated ballrooms and private function rooms.
Source: Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur website.
For every ten paying guests, one person can attend for free. The Selera Kampong package is priced at RM155 nett per adult, while the Kampong Boys Special is RM172 nett per adult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rajah revitalizes themed buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 19:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</guid><description>Starting April 4th, the all-day restaurant 21 On Rajah will introduce new lunch and dinner buffets inspired by Mediterranean and Asian cuisine.
Rijsttafel Weekday Lunch Buffet
Source: 21 on Rajah. A selection of dishes from the Rijsttafel weekday lunch buffet.
Inspired by the Dutch &amp;ldquo;rijsttafel&amp;rdquo; – meaning &amp;ldquo;rice table&amp;rdquo; – this lunch buffet presents a diverse array of side dishes served with rice, similar to the local nasi Padang. Chef de Cuisine Faustino Jr and his team have crafted a menu designed to energize diners for the rest of the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Minute List focuses on dining experiences created by talented chefs and baristas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</guid><description>Hurrah! Productions, a TV and digital content agency based in Asia, has introduced The Minute List, a first-of-its-kind video-driven guide for bars and restaurants in Singapore.
This online platform features one-minute videos showcasing popular restaurants, bars, and cafes in the city. It allows users to make direct reservations at these establishments. Featured venues are nominated by industry professionals, such as chefs, bartenders, and baristas. Each nominated venue is presented through a video interview with the head chef, bartender, or barista...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the Peranakan Food Festival at Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>The Peranakan* Food Festival is making a comeback at the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy! The hotel is bringing back this popular food festival with new additions to the menu, such as ayam masak rebung lemak (chicken with bamboo shoots in spicy gravy). Returning favorites include bubur cha cha (tapioca in coconut milk) and much more.
Guests can explore booths showcasing Peranakan heritage at the Feast@East Buffet Restaurant.
From June 10th to 19th, enjoy a variety of seafood at Feast@East Buffet Restaurant, featuring Chilean blue mussels, spanner crabs, and other crustacean favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Observe the fireworks display on February 11 at the Regent Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</guid><description>For the Lunar New Year, The Regent Hong Kong offers various culinary experiences:
Hong Kong Cuisine 1983
Celebrate with symbolic à la carte dishes (HK$468 to HK$980) like Lohei (HK$580) for prosperity, prawns in salted egg yolk (HK$580) for wealth, and braised Wagyu beef cheek (HK$980) for strength. Their HK$438 Good Fortune Turnip Cake Gift Box contains two 800g turnip cakes, one traditional and one smoked with tea leaves, sugarcane, imperatae, and brown sugar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an unexpected Christmas at Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 17:32:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel in Singapore has designed a Christmas menu featuring new versions of classic dishes, playful food presentations, and delightful surprises. These festive meals and unique takeaway options aim to make holiday celebrations even more memorable.
This year&amp;rsquo;s new gourmet takeaway options center around turkey with unique Asian flavors for savory dishes and chocolate-focused sweet treats.
Source: Goodwood Park Hotel. The 12 Treasures turkey is available for takeaways.
12 Treasures Turkey | S$268, serves eight to 10 people - New for 2017..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-unexpected-christmas-at-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>May's Big Street meal promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Big Street. Chilli slipper lobster in prata bag.
Big Street, a restaurant and lounge with air conditioning and multiple levels, is offering a special set meal deal throughout May in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day, available to everyone.
Priced at S$26 per person (minimum of two people), this deal includes an appetizer, soup, main course, and dessert.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the set meal promotion includes:
Appetiser: Fresh garden salad served with crispy chicken..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SJM Resorts will be hosting the inaugural MICHELIN Star Table event in mid-September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</guid><description>Source: SJM resorts. Palace Garden Head Chef Ken Chong will introduce the authentic elegance of fine Cantonese cuisine with his signature dish, crystal king tiger prawn.
SJM Resorts, an official MICHELIN Guide partner in Macao, has introduced its inaugural MICHELIN Star Table experience.
The debut event will be held at the Palace Garden within the Grand Lisboa Palace Resort Macau on September 15th and 16th. It will showcase a six-course menu representing the best of Chinese cuisine through a collaborative effort between two renowned chefs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sjm-resorts-will-be-hosting-the-inaugural-michelin-star-table-event-in-mid-september/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>