<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless/</link><description>Recent content in Wireless on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The L805 photo printer from Epson features a six-colour ink tank system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The L805 ink tank photo printer.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing products, has released its L805 printer. This six-color ink tank photo printer offers wireless printing from mobile devices and boasts the lowest operating expenses on the market. Epson&amp;rsquo;s ink tank printers are unique in that they utilize large ink tanks instead of cartridges.
Building upon the previous L800 model, the L805 incorporates built-in wireless connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony introduces two high-end wireless speakers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 23:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/</guid><description>• Experience immersive, room-filling audio with features like Immersive Audio Enhancement and 360 Reality Audio.
• Effortlessly calibrate the speakers to your environment for optimal sound performance.
• Enjoy a seamless and intuitive music listening experience with intelligent features.
Sony introduces the SRS-RA5000 and SRS-RA3000, premium wireless speakers engineered for an immersive audio experience. These speakers utilize Sony&amp;rsquo;s advanced spatial sound technologies and smart features to deliver sound that envelops the listener...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-two-high-end-wireless-speakers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Altec Lansing Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds come with noise isolation and GPS tracking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 03:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</guid><description>Source: Altec Lansing. The Freedom True Wireless
Bluetooth Earbuds have rechargeable lithium
ion batteries.
Altec Lansing&amp;rsquo;s new Freedom True Wireless Bluetooth Earbuds offer a truly wireless experience, featuring rechargeable lithium-ion batteries integrated into the earbud housings.
These innovative earbuds boast a six-hour battery life, IPX7-rated waterproof construction for sweat resistance, and Bluetooth-based GPS tracking to easily locate misplaced earbuds.
Expected to launch in the second quarter of 2016 with a manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s suggested retail price of US$149...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-altec-lansing-freedom-true-wireless-bluetooth-earbuds-come-with-noise-isolation-and-gps-tracking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Torch Fires Up Mobile Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Torch symbolizes a new era in mobile business communication, much like the Olympic torch marks the start of the Games.
This smartphone combines a touch screen with a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and introduces the BlackBerry 6 operating system. BlackBerry highlights the new OS&amp;rsquo;s ability to aggregate social media and RSS feeds, enable faster web browsing with multiple open tabs, provide universal search functionality, offer enhanced multimedia with a YouTube app, and ensure easy setup and personalization with a user-friendly design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity for Telemedicine and Remote Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The rapid emergence of the Coronavirus pandemic is speeding up existing trends, particularly telemedicine and remote work. Both heavily rely on broadband internet bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available connection options.
Connecting the User
Most remote workers and telemedicine patients connect from home using devices like desktops, smartphones, laptops, or tablets. Home users often prefer cable broadband with speeds of 30 to 100 Mbps, while remote users rely on public WiFi or 4G/5G cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Reclaim is Green and Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 07:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/</guid><description>Contrary to what some might believe, being environmentally conscious doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to break the bank. The Samsung Reclaim M560 for Sprint is a prime example of affordable, eco-friendly technology.
This slider phone boasts a full QWERTY keyboard and a vibrant 2.6-inch color display with a resolution of 320 x 240 pixels, capable of displaying over 262,000 colors. Its 2.0-megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing.
The Reclaim offers swift 3G connectivity on Sprint&amp;rsquo;s network, enabling access to services like Sprint TV, Sprint Music Store, and Sprint Video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-reclaim-is-green-and-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shine On, LG, Shine On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shine-on-lg-shine-on/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:45:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shine-on-lg-shine-on/</guid><description>Looking for a sleek and stylish device that&amp;rsquo;s more than just a pretty face? The LG Shine, available in vibrant red or classic black, is an engineering marvel that combines the functionality of a camera, media player, and cell phone all in one.
Encased in attractive stainless steel, the LG Shine is a quad-band GSM phone compatible with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s 3G network. Its unique 2.2-inch mirror LCD provides a wide viewing angle and adds to its sleek appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shine-on-lg-shine-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shine-on-lg-shine-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are You A Sentio Being?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re someone who likes to stay ahead of the curve in technology without breaking the bank, now is the time to make a move. The LG Sentio, a free high-quality smartphone, is a prime example of getting significant value without spending a lot.
You might be wondering how a high-value phone can be free. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of taking advantage of technological advancements at the right moment and knowing where to find the best deals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verizon Goes After Blue Collar Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 22:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</guid><description>When picturing someone in a hard hat using a cell phone, most people think of a Nextel phone, known for their walkie-talkie feature and durability. However, Verizon is now entering this market, aiming to capture the construction and outdoor enthusiast demographics.
Verizon has the advantage of being a larger company with a wider customer base and a broader phone selection. They have leveled the playing field by adding push-to-talk (PTT) functionality and introducing tougher phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verizon-goes-after-blue-collar-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Intercept Brings Free Android Smartphone to Sprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 05:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</guid><description>A popular new smartphone design combines a 3-inch touchscreen, a slide-out QWERTY keyboard, and the Android operating system. Sprint offers this package in their Samsung Intercept model. Amazingly, you can get this phone for free when you order it online with a new Sprint PCS service plan. There are no additional costs; even shipping is free, and the plans are the same price as in stores.
The Samsung Intercept M910 is a fantastic deal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-brings-free-android-smartphone-to-sprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's a Sidekick and a Running Mate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/</guid><description>The T-Mobile Sidekick Slide is perfect for those who love to stay connected. Its compact design easily fits into your pocket, keeping you in touch even during a workout. While it functions as a cell phone, its primary use lies in its messaging capabilities.
Accessing the full QWERTY keyboard is as simple as sliding the phone open, transforming it into a miniature computer. The large, vibrant display and physical keys enhance the user experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-a-sidekick-and-a-running-mate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lonliness of the Long Distance Landline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</guid><description>Recent data shows people are rapidly ditching landlines. If Alexander Graham Bell were alive today, he&amp;rsquo;d have trouble reaching anyone on his original invention. Instead, he&amp;rsquo;d have much better luck using a cell phone, just like everyone else.
It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that most people own a cell phone, or even multiple old ones. People want to be constantly connected, even when they perhaps shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be. Observe drivers at a stoplight, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely spot several talking on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Behold The Samsung Behold Espresso and Rose</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/behold-the-samsung-behold-espresso-and-rose/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 02:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/behold-the-samsung-behold-espresso-and-rose/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s understandable why you&amp;rsquo;re looking for Samsung Behold reviews; it&amp;rsquo;s one of the most sought-after touchscreen phones on the market.
The Samsung Behold is an advanced smartphone featuring Samsung&amp;rsquo;s innovative TouchWiz interface, taking touchscreen technology to new heights. TouchWiz allows you to personalize your home screen by simply dragging and dropping widgets with your finger, eliminating the need for a mouse or stylus.
Beyond its impressive TouchWiz interface, the Samsung Behold offers an array of desirable features for a touchscreen phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/behold-the-samsung-behold-espresso-and-rose/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/behold-the-samsung-behold-espresso-and-rose/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Paid to Take a Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-take-a-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-take-a-cell-phone/</guid><description>Thinking about a new cell phone but don&amp;rsquo;t want to spend $100? You don&amp;rsquo;t have to! Getting a new phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean emptying your wallet. While discounts are common, you can even find completely free phones.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that the newest smartphones can be expensive, but there are plenty of free options available. The key is to shop online instead of in retail stores.
Online, you can browse cell phone deals and service plans at your own pace, without pressure from salespeople...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-take-a-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-paid-to-take-a-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Upheavals in 2009</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</guid><description>The world of technology is about to undergo another major shift, particularly in telecommunications and computing. While these changes have been in motion throughout 2008, 2009 looks to be the year they truly make their mark. Here are a few potential game-changers:
Wireless Broadband Takes the Lead: Traditional DSL and cable internet services are facing stiff competition from wireless providers. Cell towers, now equipped with broadband capabilities, offer comparable speeds to wired connections, often at slightly higher prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-upheavals-in-2009/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International Cell Phone Calls for Pennies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 21:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</guid><description>Imagine making international calls for as little as two cents a minute! It might sound impossible, but with a new service, you can make calls from the US and Canada to other countries at incredibly low rates.
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about rates like 2.36 cents per minute to China. Yes, you read that right. Still paying exorbitant rates? Get with the times and switch to the TEL3AdvantageMobile Plan before you make another call!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-cell-phone-calls-for-pennies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's Pink Cell Phone Season Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 12:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</guid><description>Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day kicks off the season for pink cell phones, a trend that lasts until Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day. This convergence of technology and pink offers a stylish option for yourself or your significant other.
This year, the Samsung Instinct Pink for Sprint PCS is a top pick. Though usually a pricey phone, it&amp;rsquo;s available at a significant discount with an Everything Plan or Talk/Message/Data Share Plan from Sprint PCS. Families can even get two discounted phones with the right family plan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-pink-cell-phone-season-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning In A Sea Of Free Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 22:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</guid><description>Your cell phone contract ends every two years, allowing you to explore new options. Many people take advantage of this because they&amp;rsquo;re unhappy with their current provider or want to upgrade to the latest technology. While constantly upgrading your phone can be expensive, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get the newest models without breaking the bank.
You can find the most recent phones for little to no cost if you know where to look...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-free-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Captivated By Samsung’s Android Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</guid><description>Ready for the newest smartphones? Check out the Samsung Captivate, available through AT&amp;amp;T. It&amp;rsquo;s a fast, sleek, and runs on the Android operating system – specifically, the Galaxy Android version.
The Samsung Galaxy series is creating a lot of excitement. These phones will have different names depending on the carrier. The Captivate is specifically designed for AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network, and it lives up to its name!
This phone pushes the boundaries of slimness, measuring a mere 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Family Plans for Professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/</guid><description>Typically, &amp;ldquo;family plans&amp;rdquo; bring to mind adding lines for children. However, in the current economic climate, a family plan could be the difference between two working individuals each having a dedicated phone and being forced to share. Sharing a phone is impractical for business, so let&amp;rsquo;s explore these family plans further.
You might not have considered this option for professional use due to the name &amp;ldquo;family plan.&amp;rdquo; These plans are more accurately described as shared minutes plans, but the name &amp;ldquo;family plan&amp;rdquo; has stuck, so we&amp;rsquo;ll use it here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-family-plans-for-professionals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How BlackBerry Touch Screen Technology Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Storm is a unique addition to the BlackBerry lineup, featuring a touch screen instead of the traditional physical QWERTY keyboard. Though the keyboard is now virtual, it still aims to provide a tactile experience.
Why this change? Primarily, to accommodate a larger display screen without increasing the phone&amp;rsquo;s overall size. To achieve this, the physical keyboard was removed, leaving only essential call, menu, and navigation buttons below the screen...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-blackberry-touch-screen-technology-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC HD2 Smartphone With Movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</guid><description>Have you ever been offered a cell phone with two full-length movies already on it? That&amp;rsquo;s only the beginning of what the HTC HD2 smartphone for T-Mobile offers. This phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t just offer entertainment, it delivers it in spades!
The massive touchscreen display immediately suggests this phone is designed for multimedia. It boasts a 4.3-inch screen with 800 x 480 pixel resolution. Those specs sound more like a small computer than a phone, and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first router is introduced by Synology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 08:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</guid><description>Source: Synology. The Synology Router RT1900ac.
Synology has introduced its first router, the Synology Router RT1900ac. This router allows users to connect an external storage device, effectively creating a personal cloud storage solution.
The router boasts combined transfer speeds of up to 1,900 Mbps and utilizes beamforming technology to optimize Wi-Fi signals for individual devices. A mobile app provides users with control over the router&amp;rsquo;s functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-router-is-introduced-by-synology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phones Piling Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phones-piling-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phones-piling-up/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve got a brand new Samsung touch screen phone for Christmas? That&amp;rsquo;s great! You&amp;rsquo;ll definitely enjoy it for the next few years.
However, what about your old phone? The one you were using just yesterday? It still functions, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it? Don&amp;rsquo;t let it become another piece of holiday trash.
Instead of feeling sentimental, consider this: Your Christmas tree will be discarded soon, and all that packaging will be recycled. Why not do the same with your old phone?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phones-piling-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phones-piling-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Overseas For Pennies From Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>With cell phones now serving as both personal and business lines, affordable landline long distance isn&amp;rsquo;t very useful. The real desire is for better rates on mobile phones. Considering you already have domestic calling and internet, the missing piece is inexpensive international calling.
TEL3 recognized this trend and developed their TEL3Advantage service for mobile users in the US and Canada. Many people need to call contacts internationally, but affordable mobile options have been limited until now...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I Shall Call It Cellular Mini-Me</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</guid><description>The change from landlines to mobile phones is accelerating as 3G networks expand coverage to suburban and rural areas. Smartphones like the BlackBerry and iPhone are becoming ubiquitous, prompting questions about the necessity of laptops. Wireless technology offers liberation from desktops, allowing users to communicate, browse, and enjoy videos on the move. However, this freedom is often hindered indoors.
Indoor spaces present a significant obstacle to wireless transmission. Walls and other barriers weaken high-frequency radio signals, leading to dropped calls and poor connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Bill Shock Is So Easy To Avoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission is looking into new regulations due to a high volume of complaints regarding unexpected cell phone charges. While this intervention is welcomed by those who have faced this issue, understanding how to avoid such situations is key.
&amp;ldquo;Bill shock&amp;rdquo; refers to the unpleasant surprise of discovering unexpectedly high charges on your cell phone bill, often leaving you in disbelief and frantically searching for errors. While billing mistakes can occur, these charges are typically accurate, stemming from a lack of awareness regarding contract details or exceeding usage limits, often unknowingly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Vu to an iPhone Kill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</guid><description>The Apple iPhone 3G is the current target for every cell phone company, indicating its leading position in the market. While iPhone enthusiasts might find alternatives underwhelming, the LG Vu smartphone offers a compelling option with unique features.
One standout feature is live TV. The LG Vu CU920 supports AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s MEdia FLO, a subscription-based digital TV service delivered through a dedicated over-the-air broadcasting system, requiring specific hardware in compatible phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Craving the Motorola ZN4 Krave</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</guid><description>The Motorola Krave ZN4&amp;rsquo;s unique design, reminiscent of futuristic helmets, features a protective visor. This &amp;ldquo;touch cover&amp;rdquo; can be lifted to interact with the full touchscreen or closed to shield the display while still allowing access to essential functions like the camera, media, and messages. This design combines the appeal of both flip phones and touchscreen devices, offering a large screen ideal for media consumption and showcasing the capabilities of the phone&amp;rsquo;s 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/craving-the-motorola-zn4-krave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your BlackBerry 8830 Before President Obama</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</guid><description>President Obama famously missed his BlackBerry 8830 after prioritizing security during his initial days in office. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s news that he might be reunited with his BlackBerry, equipped with specialized software for secure communication. You, however, can enjoy the RIM BlackBerry 8830 World Edition right away, even without the special government features. This standard model caters to both personal and business needs.
The BlackBerry 8830 World Edition eliminates the need for separate phones for domestic and international use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Got a Bandwidth Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no limit to how much bandwidth we need, similar to how we always desire more money, health, or chocolate. As we gain more bandwidth, we discover new ways to utilize it. The most sought-after types are wireless, offering flexibility, and fiber optic, providing high capacity. Property owners who provide both to their business tenants might find their properties more appealing than those offering health, wealth, or even delicious chocolate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accessories After The Fact</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 15:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve either already purchased your dream phone or are seriously considering your wireless choices. However, the box might not include every accessory you desire. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we offer a wide variety of accessories at significantly discounted prices (up to 80% off).
For instance, car chargers are essential for professionals on the go. Your device might run low on battery before you can reach an outlet. Even with an AC charger, finding a power source isn&amp;rsquo;t always easy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accessories-after-the-fact/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Your Old RAZR Getting Dull?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 13:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/</guid><description>The Motorola RAZR V3, known for its slim profile, is a highly sought-after mobile phone. Its popularity is evident across various carriers, even prepaid services like AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s GoPhone. While the original RAZR remains desirable, those considering an upgrade will find that the RAZR design has evolved. Newer models offer the classic RAZR aesthetic with enhanced features.
One notable upgrade is the Motorola RAZR 2 V8 with myFaves, available for T-Mobile. Also called the MOTORAZR, this model boasts a slimmer and more tapered design than its boxy V3 predecessor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-old-razr-getting-dull/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Lotus is Square to Be Hip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</guid><description>The LG Lotus LX600, a new and innovative phone in the mobile market, boasts a unique square design. Don&amp;rsquo;t let its shape fool you; this phone is powerful and designed for messaging.
The LG Lotus LX600 is slim, lightweight, and square. It flips open to reveal a full, backlit QWERTY keyboard. Despite this feature, it remains compact, even compared to typical messaging smartphones.
The LG Lotus has a lot to offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience all-day flexibility with the Plantronics BackBeat 100 Series Wireless Headphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</guid><description>Plantronics, a company known for its audio and wearable technology, has introduced the BackBeat 100 Series. These headphones are the newest addition to their BackBeat stereo product line and offer a unique hybrid neckband design for wireless calls and music.
The BackBeat 100 and BackBeat 105 are designed for comfort throughout the day with an ultra-lightweight build. They provide full-range sound with enhanced bass, making them ideal for listening to music and watching videos on the move...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 Bluetooth earphones are now available in Singapore through Huawei's official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</guid><description>Huawei Singapore has introduced the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3, stereo Bluetooth earphones with a groundbreaking open-fit design that incorporates active noise cancellation.
Source: Huawei. Eager customers queue at SITEX to buy the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 on November 30, 2019.
As the new year approaches, Huawei is focused on creating a comprehensive product ecosystem in Singapore, allowing customers to experience seamless connectivity between their smartphones and other devices such as the new Huawei Watch GT 2 and Gentle Monster – Huawei Eyewear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G2 With Google is 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</guid><description>T-Mobile is raising the bar for smartphones with its new G2, a Google phone that seamlessly integrates with Google Voice. This allows for voicemails to be converted to text and read like emails or texts.
Powered by Android 2.2, the G2 boasts a 3.7-inch full touch screen with seven customizable home panels. Users can personalize their experience with thousands of apps and widgets from the Android Market.
One of the G2&amp;rsquo;s standout features is its Adobe Flash Player, unlike a well-known competitor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Motorola ROKR Rocks On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</guid><description>The first iTunes phone, the Motorola ROKR, was a huge success. But instead of fading away, it has evolved into the modern ROKR E8 for T-Mobile. Is it still a great phone? You be the judge.
The sleek black design with red accents makes the Motorola ROKR E8 a striking multimedia phone. It&amp;rsquo;s actually three devices in one: a cell phone, music player, and digital camera. The touch-sensitive keypad adapts to the function you&amp;rsquo;re using...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-motorola-rokr-rocks-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It Really Knows When You Are Sleeping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</guid><description>You might have heard this before:
It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re asleep, It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re awake. It maintains a record of it all, And informs you the next day.
But this isn&amp;rsquo;t about someone monitoring your behavior. This is about understanding your sleep patterns.
If you wake up feeling more tired than when you went to sleep, you might benefit from the Zeo Personal Sleep Coach, a new device that tracks your sleep and provides a visual representation of your sleep quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save the Cell Phone, Save the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</guid><description>Cell phones are frequently overlooked as a source of environmental concern, valuable resources, and potential income. While seemingly harmless, these devices contain toxic materials and represent a significant waste problem due to their short lifespans and frequent replacement.
A cell phone&amp;rsquo;s small size and durable exterior might make it seem environmentally benign, but the internal components tell a different story. Lead, cadmium, arsenic, mercury, plastics, and glass are all found within these devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LMDS Fills the Fiber Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</guid><description>Although fiber optic bandwidth is widely available across the country, connecting businesses to this network over the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; is a different story. It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to realize that less than 20% of commercial buildings are equipped for fiber optic telecommunications services.
This is primarily due to the high cost of installing fiber optic cables, a process that&amp;rsquo;s difficult to justify when businesses already have access to telephone and data services through existing copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lmds-fills-the-fiber-gap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepaid Cell Phones Are Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</guid><description>Are you tired of feeling locked into long, expensive cell phone contracts? While those &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; phones and big discounts might sound appealing, the high cost of multi-year service plans can be daunting. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve even avoided getting a cell phone to escape that commitment. There&amp;rsquo;s another option: a pay-as-you-go service that lets you pay only for what you use.
With Net10, you&amp;rsquo;ll always know exactly what you owe. This service offers a straightforward plan: 10 cents per minute for local, long-distance, and roaming calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepaid-cell-phones-are-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Times Are Tough, Cell Phones Are Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 16:24:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</guid><description>With the current economic climate, most people are looking for ways to save money. Instead of spending lavishly, it&amp;rsquo;s wiser to be cautious and prepare for potential tough times ahead. One way to save money is by finding deals on essential items like cell phone services and devices.
Many people purchase their cell phones from carrier stores or large retailers, but these places often charge a premium for the phones themselves...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/times-are-tough-cell-phones-are-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV2 Sparks Envy Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</guid><description>The LG enV, nicknamed the &amp;ldquo;envy phone,&amp;rdquo; certainly attracted attention. Its successor, the enV2 VX9100, takes it up a notch, especially for those who love texting, gaming, and enjoying media on their phone.
The standout feature of the enV2 is its hidden full QWERTY keyboard. No need to fumble with a virtual keyboard on this phone! It boasts a real keyboard with comfortably sized keys. Keep your enV2 closed for calls, just like any other standard phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Memoir Phone Captures Memories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-memoir-phone-captures-memories/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-memoir-phone-captures-memories/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: the best moments always seem to happen when you&amp;rsquo;re without a camera. That&amp;rsquo;s why a new cell phone with a built-in camera sounds appealing. While not as high-quality as a dedicated camera, it&amp;rsquo;s certainly better than nothing.
The Samsung Memoir eliminates this dilemma by combining a cell phone and a high-quality camera. Designed for both casual and serious photographers, this touch screen phone boasts an impressive 8...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-memoir-phone-captures-memories/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-memoir-phone-captures-memories/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Have The Instinct For Covert Ops?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</guid><description>Ever imagine yourself as a secret agent like Jack Bauer from the show &amp;ldquo;24&amp;rdquo;? The Samsung Instinct phone, especially in sleek black, is your gateway to that world. Packed with features, it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate device for any aspiring operative.
The large, high-resolution touchscreen provides crystal-clear visuals and even vibrates slightly when you touch it, ensuring precise navigation. Its powerful 2.0 Megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing or printing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Shows its Curve in Pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</guid><description>Who says productivity can&amp;rsquo;t be stylish? Why not combine technology and beauty in the business world? It&amp;rsquo;s definitely possible!
The BlackBerry Curve 8330 Pink for Verizon Wireless is a perfect example. This device deserves a spot in a movie, maybe titled &amp;ldquo;Pretty in Pink&amp;rdquo;—although that title is already taken, it perfectly captures the essence of this phone. This classic BlackBerry delivers on productivity while boasting an elegant curved design and a lovely pink exterior...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Delving Into Alltel's Delve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delving-into-alltels-delve/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 03:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delving-into-alltels-delve/</guid><description>Samsung&amp;rsquo;s latest touchscreen phone, the Samsung Delve R800 Black for Alltel, boasts a slim design and is packed with features. Its cutting-edge technology caters to both professional and personal needs.
The standout feature is the responsive touchscreen, which provides access to phone controls and a virtual QWERTY keyboard. Additionally, you can use voice commands to open over a dozen applications. The Delve offers both touch and voice interaction for user convenience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delving-into-alltels-delve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delving-into-alltels-delve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning in a Sea of Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</guid><description>Current estimations show approximately three billion mobile phone users globally, with a billion new devices sold annually. Given that phones are typically replaced every two to three years, this equates to roughly one billion phones becoming obsolete yearly. The question then arises: where do these discarded devices end up?
Contrary to assumptions that they are forgotten in drawers, a recent study revealed that only 44% of old phones remain unused at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Municipal WiFi On The Way Out?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</guid><description>While WiFi hotspots are incredibly convenient for travelers in airports, hotels, and restaurants, city-wide WiFi hasn&amp;rsquo;t been as successful as initially hoped. The recent closure of Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s Metro WiFi in Philadelphia raises questions about the future of this technology, even though broadband internet is thriving.
Despite a significant increase in broadband adoption, with dial-up becoming nearly obsolete, city-wide WiFi providers are struggling. Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s experience in Philadelphia, where they only gained a fraction of their projected subscribers, highlights this challenge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For Free Phone Aficionados Only</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</guid><description>Looking for a free cell phone? Look no further than Cell Phone Plan Finder&amp;rsquo;s free phones section. This site is completely dedicated to showcasing free phones available when you sign up for a service contract.
This screenshot only displays a limited selection. As of today, there are 23 free phone models from leading carriers such as Verizon Wireless, T-Mobile, AT&amp;amp;T, and Sprint.
The selection includes various BlackBerry models like the Bold, Curve, Storm, and Tour...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-free-phone-aficionados-only/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Beats Decade Collection features the Defiant Black-Red colorway for Beats by Dr. Dre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</guid><description>Source: Beats. The Beats Decade Collection.
To commemorate its 10th anniversary, Beats by Dr Dre has unveiled the Beats Decade Collection, a special edition line of products in a striking black and red colorway. This bold design choice pays homage to the brand&amp;rsquo;s origins and the intense emotions evoked by music.
The Defiant Black-Red color scheme is showcased in these models:
Source: Beats. The Beats Studio3 wireless headphones, in folded mode...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Philly Stake With WiFi...Mmm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 19:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/</guid><description>Philadelphia&amp;rsquo;s most exciting new venture is citywide WiFi, generating significant buzz after Earthlink abandoned a similar project. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a completely new endeavor, but rather a revival of the existing infrastructure under new management, a group of local investors confident in their ability to succeed.
Their strategy is based on free access for consumers, a welcome change from the $20 monthly fee for the previous unreliable service. Although a discounted plan was offered, even a reduced cost can be prohibitive for low-income residents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/philly-stake-with-wifimmm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China Telecom is conducting a trial of a connected car concept in partnership with Gemalto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</guid><description>Gemalto, a digital security company, and China Telecom, a major Chinese mobile operator, are collaborating on a connected car project. They are using Gemalto&amp;rsquo;s LinqUs On-Demand Connectivity (ODC) subscription management solution.
The companies recently demonstrated at Mobile World Congress Shanghai how remote provisioning can securely connect mobile devices. They plan to apply this ODC solution to vehicles. This would allow China Telecom&amp;rsquo;s automotive clients to provide their customers with instant in-car connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red, Red, LG Vu Wine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</guid><description>Everyone enjoys a nice wine with dinner, but what about in business or on the go? It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly acceptable when that &amp;ldquo;wine&amp;rdquo; is the new touchscreen phone available from AT&amp;amp;T.
This &amp;ldquo;red wine&amp;rdquo; phone boasts more features than a full-bodied Cabernet. Its compact size of 4.3 x 2.1 x 0.5 inches makes it easy to carry in your pocket or bag. You read that correctly – this device is only half an inch thin!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Duracell batteries provide six times the power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</guid><description>Source: Duracell. To commemorate five decades of providing portable power, Duracell has partnered with TRANSFORMERS: AGE OF EXTINCTION, the fourth film in director Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s globally recognized franchise, in a battle of good and evil.
Duracell, the renowned battery manufacturer, is observing 50 years of providing portable power solutions. Although the traditional battery design remains largely unchanged, battery technology advancements have significantly extended battery life.
Duracell&amp;rsquo;s latest CopperTop AA and AAA batteries, equipped with Duralock Power Preserve Technology, are ideal for devices like wireless mice and keyboards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ethernet Next Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:53:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</guid><description>Feeling constrained by your internet speed? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While your business might be struggling with a slow T1 line, your competitors may have a secret weapon: a new, affordable broadband service called Carrier Ethernet.
This service, rapidly being deployed across the nation, is an extension of the familiar Ethernet standard used in local area networks (LANs). Instead of converting data to different protocols for external connections, businesses can now use Ethernet for seamless, high-speed access to the internet and connections with other facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ethernet-next-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>