<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MFP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mfp/</link><description>Recent content in MFP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:38:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mfp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>For the fourth year in a row, Konica Minolta has been awarded the prestigious BLI 'Line of the Year' award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 19:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-fourth-year-in-a-row-konica-minolta-has-been-awarded-the-prestigious-bli-line-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>Buyers Laboratory (BLI), a recognized independent evaluator for the imaging industry, has given Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s A3 multifunction printer (MFP) family its &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award for an unprecedented fourth consecutive year.
The &amp;ldquo;Line of the Year&amp;rdquo; award is presented annually to companies whose products demonstrate exceptional performance in BLI&amp;rsquo;s rigorous two-month laboratory assessments.
&amp;ldquo;Konica Minolta&amp;rsquo;s success comes down to consistency,&amp;rdquo; said George Mikolay, BLI&amp;rsquo;s Senior Product Editor for A3/Copier MFPs.</description></item><item><title>The LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series from HP offers increased security and versatility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 11:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-laserjet-enterprise-600-series-from-hp-offers-increased-security-and-versatility/</guid><description>Source: HP. The HP Color LaserJet Managed E87660 MFP.
HP has introduced the HP LaserJet Enterprise 600 Series, a line of printers designed to enhance security and productivity.
These multifunction printers (MFPs) offer a combination of strong performance, energy efficiency, and the ability to produce professional-quality documents. They are built with network security in mind, offering protection against cyberattacks. Additionally, the devices incorporate HP JetIntelligence cartridge technology, which utilizes advancements in toner chemistry to further enhance print quality.</description></item><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi.</description></item></channel></rss>