<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Weather on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/weather/</link><description>Recent content in Weather on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/weather/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>YouGov is tracking the impact of the haze</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 17:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</guid><description>Southeast Asia faced significant haze this year, mainly due to regional forest fires. A YouGov survey reveals a high level of awareness about this issue within the region.
Nearly 80% of Asian respondents are aware of the haze originating from Indonesian landscape fires. This awareness is lower in Hong Kong (48%) and Mainland China (44%). However, in Indonesia, Malaysia, and Singapore, the three countries most affected, only 2% of respondents in each country reported being unaware of the haze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-is-tracking-the-impact-of-the-haze/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International SOS offers three tips for managing heatwaves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 02:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</guid><description>As temperatures remain high in mid-2023, individuals may experience heat-related illness symptoms like rashes, cramps, dizziness, headaches, weakness, nausea/vomiting, or even collapse, according to Dr. Chan Yanjun, Medical Director (Singapore and Malaysia) at International SOS.
Dr. Chan emphasizes that heat-related illnesses and fatalities are preventable with appropriate measures.
Increased Risks
Certain groups are more susceptible to heat-related issues like cramps, exhaustion, and stroke: individuals over 65, pregnant or nursing women, those with medical conditions or taking medications, people frequently outdoors, employees near heat sources or in poorly ventilated areas, and those working with hot objects, wearing heavy clothing/gear, or on long shifts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-sos-offers-three-tips-for-managing-heatwaves/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify creates playlists for foggy weather</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:01:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has curated a playlist specifically for the hazy conditions currently affecting Singapore and Malaysia. You can listen to the playlist below.
Interested in learning more?
Stay informed about the hourly air quality readings in Singapore.
Read this WorkSmart Asia blog article about Spotify&amp;rsquo;s mobile-first approach.
Hashtag: #SGHaze..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-creates-playlists-for-foggy-weather/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>