<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Higher Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/higher-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Higher Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 18:45:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/higher-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Making The Move For Higher Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</guid><description>Are you experiencing bandwidth limitations in your organization? With the rapid advancement of online technology, many organizations are facing a shortage of bandwidth. While contacting your service provider to increase your line speed might seem like the solution, they might inform you that you already have the maximum speed available. So, what are your options?
Have you thought about relocating? Bandwidth availability and cost vary significantly by location. Some places have many choices and reasonable prices, while others might not be able to meet your basic needs regardless of your budget.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Rising Rapidly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-rising-rapidly/</guid><description>Enhanced business environments and productivity gains through automation are pushing businesses towards higher bandwidth network solutions. Instead of simply increasing their current T1 or other line services, smart managers are exploring new technology that delivers more bandwidth at a lower cost. Ethernet over Copper is emerging as a leading WAN network service.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a straightforward concept: it&amp;rsquo;s an Ethernet service delivered through existing twisted pair copper wiring.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?</description></item></channel></rss>