<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>XML on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/xml/</link><description>Recent content in XML on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:17:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/xml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choosing unique node values from an eConnect XML document</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-unique-node-values-from-an-econnect-xml-document/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:17:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choosing-unique-node-values-from-an-econnect-xml-document/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently engrossed in a large-scale project that involves importing a massive volume of transactions, exceeding 7 million, into Dynamics GP using eConnect.
To streamline the process, the client provided the data in XML format, allowing me to import transactions by directly sending the XML to eConnect. While this method has advantages, it also presents some hurdles.
One challenge involves the client including the Batch Number within the XML data. This normally wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a problem, but a separate requirement necessitates that I identify each batch number generated from each XML file.</description></item><item><title>If you're developing with XML, it's essential to have a good understanding of XPath.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-re-developing-with-xml-it-s-essential-to-have-a-good-understanding-of-xpath/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-re-developing-with-xml-it-s-essential-to-have-a-good-understanding-of-xpath/</guid><description>My recent experience working on a VB .NET application highlighted the importance of using XPath for XML manipulation. While I recognize my own development shortcomings, encountering code that interacts with XML without leveraging XPath is truly baffling. If you handle XML in your work, investing a few hours learning XPath is essential.
My XML journey began in 1999 with MSXML3, employing DOM and XPath extensively, and later utilizing XSLT for complex web transformations.</description></item></channel></rss>