<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3d Printing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d-printing/</link><description>Recent content in 3d Printing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d-printing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb with a SMD LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 02:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a faulty tracking sensor light bulb. To fix it, I used my custom-designed SMD LED replacement part, which is a direct swap for the original bulb housing. This component was recently updated during a Beogram 4000 restoration to incorporate an integrated intensity trimmer. This trimmer simplifies the process of adjusting the tracking sensor feedback significantly. It enables fine-tuning after the light sensors are mechanically positioned below the light source...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-with-a-smd-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TINKR combines fashion, design, and 3D printing technology in a unique way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</guid><description>TINKR, a company from Singapore, has transitioned its business model from solely offering 3D printing services. They now focus on merging fashion, design, and technology to produce unique corporate gifts.
In a recent announcement, company founders Xiaohui and Freda expressed their passion for blending craftsmanship with technology. They are excited to introduce their latest venture: high-quality, locally and regionally designed prints. They plan to collaborate with various artisans and designers in the upcoming months to create fresh, unique prints with a distinctive style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech Saturday at Suntec will demonstrate the future direction of consumer technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</guid><description>Source: Smart Nation website.
Tech Saturday is a public carnival presented by the Infocomm Development Authority of Singapore to demonstrate the power of technology. In addition to tech exhibitions, visitors can participate in interactive &amp;ldquo;Worksheds.&amp;rdquo;
Located throughout the carnival, these booths provide hands-on technology workshops. With options ranging from circuits to 3D printing, all workshops are free. While pre-registration is closed, same-day registration is available at counters near the Worksheds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advanced Manufacturing Driving Faster WANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</guid><description>The recent &amp;ldquo;Great Recession&amp;rdquo; stands out not just for its severity, but also for the uneven recovery that followed. While businesses have bounced back, job growth has lagged. This unusual trend has been attributed to unexpected gains in productivity, where output increases without a proportional rise in employment. But is this sustainable or merely a blip in the current economic climate?
The saying &amp;ldquo;everything old is new again&amp;rdquo; rings true. While new applications and technologies emerge, they often echo past advancements driven by innovation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Cabinet Repair and Guiding Washers Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/</guid><description>While waiting for audio cables from Sounds Heavenly, I decided to fix up the wooden case of my Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. Both corners were cracked, and the plastic washers that guide the sliding mechanism were gone. The first picture shows one of the damaged corners.
[Image of a cracked turntable cabinet]
Repairing the cracks was simple. Since the case is held together with metal bands, I glued the wood pieces and clamped them until the glue dried...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>