<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tour on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tour/</link><description>Recent content in Tour on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Food tours are available in Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo through Eating Adventures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</guid><description>Source: Eating Adventures website.
Eating Adventures has expanded its food tour services to Hong Kong. The company, already established as the leading provider of food tours in Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo, China, aims to provide travelers with an authentic cultural and culinary experience by guiding them through local neighborhoods.
Wai Zhou, owner of Eating Adventures Food Tours, highlights that while Hong Kong has existing food tour operators, most are not run by locals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Foodie Tour introduces a new tour to Tai Po Market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</guid><description>Source: Hong Kong Foodie.
Hong Kong Foodie has created a food tour in Tai Po Market. This is their third food tour, and it will take people to six family-owned restaurants in Tai Po Market that serve authentic Hong Kong cuisine.
Cecilia Leung, the Founder and Director of Hong Kong Foodie, believes that Tai Po Market is the perfect location for their newest tour because it has many beloved local restaurants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-foodie-tour-introduces-a-new-tour-to-tai-po-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Picking On Cyber Monday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</guid><description>Similar to how Black Friday has become a tradition for in-person shopping, Cyber Monday is now the time for finding exceptional online deals. With that in mind, let&amp;rsquo;s explore a standout product line this year: BlackBerry devices from Research in Motion.
Business users have long favored BlackBerry for mobile communication. RIM has prioritized supporting corporate IT with the performance and security needed for serious business use on the go. But how affordable are these popular BlackBerry models?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-picking-on-cyber-monday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Walk Japan provides distinctive viewpoints of Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:35:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</guid><description>Source: Walk Japan. Viewing Mount Fuji on the Izu Geo Trail.
Walk Japan tours provide travelers with the chance to experience Japan&amp;rsquo;s diverse landscapes throughout the year on a more intimate level. This independent organization offers a fresh perspective on crafting and operating tours within Japan. The company&amp;rsquo;s deep knowledge and strong local connections, cultivated over many years, guarantee guests genuine experiences everywhere they travel.
Japan boasts an abundance of seasonal views...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/walk-japan-provides-distinctive-viewpoints-of-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Explore Japan by walking in February</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explore-japan-by-walking-in-february/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explore-japan-by-walking-in-february/</guid><description>Walk Japan offers several winter tours in February 2020:
Oita Hot Spring Trail This guided tour explores Oita Prefecture, a region of Japan recognized for its scenic countryside, delicious and diverse cuisine, and welcoming people. Oita is also home to the highest concentration of hot springs, supplied by the largest volume of water. These springs come in various forms, from clear to cloudy, and even pungent or effervescent.
Available from February 16-21 at JPY326,000, this tour suits reasonably fit individuals comfortable walking for four hours daily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explore-japan-by-walking-in-february/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explore-japan-by-walking-in-february/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing a new food tour by Isan Explorer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</guid><description>Source: Isan Explorer website.
Isan Explorer, a tour operator specializing in Northeast Thailand, has launched a culinary tour showcasing the cuisine of the lesser-known Isan region.
The day-long tour starts with a visit to a bustling fresh market to gather ingredients for lunch and dinner. Afterward, the tour proceeds to a nearby village.
Participants will enjoy a tasting menu featuring 20 main dishes, such as bamboo shoot curry, sour fish, grilled chicken, steamed mushrooms, green bean salad, and eggplant dipping sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join Jane's Walk for free guided tours around Singapore from May 1 to 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:42:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk website.
Gather your coworkers and spend the first weekend of May discovering Singapore with Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a worldwide initiative of free walking tours led by locals and inspired by Jane Jacobs. The walks encourage people to share their community stories, explore their cities, and connect with their neighbors.
&amp;ldquo;Jane Jacobs, an advocate for walkability, vibrant communities, and citizen involvement in urban development, would be proud! She believed understanding a city requires observation, inquiry, and exploration, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to do just that during the weekend of May 1-3,&amp;rdquo; stated Mai Tatoy, Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk City Organizer in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>