<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TripAdvisor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tripadvisor/</link><description>Recent content in TripAdvisor on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tripadvisor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?</description></item><item><title>Hoi An has the highest number of top hotels according to TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Hanoi and Hoi An are home to Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated hotels. In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized ten top hotels in Vietnam, with three located in Hanoi and three in Hoi An. An additional two hotels in the top 25 are also situated in Hoi An.
The top ten hotels are:
Source: TripAdvisor. The Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel.
Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel: Garnering 1,832 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; ratings out of 2,064 total reviews.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has identified Tokyo, Singapore, and Dubai as some of the top choices in its Cities Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-identified-tokyo-singapore-and-dubai-as-some-of-the-top-choices-in-its-cities-survey/</guid><description>Singapore at night.
The travel website TripAdvisor recently published its second annual Cities Survey, which collected data from over 54,000 user reviews. The survey evaluated cities worldwide based on traveler feedback.
Tokyo received the highest ranking for providing the best overall travel experience. It also earned top scores for its helpful residents, taxi services, public transportation, and clean streets. Tokyo ranked among the top ten cities in 13 out of 16 survey categories.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor simplifies the process of capturing important moments during a trip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 21:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-simplifies-the-process-of-capturing-important-moments-during-a-trip/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the biggest travel website globally as of July 2015 according to comScore Media Metrix, has introduced a &amp;ldquo;Travel Timeline&amp;rdquo; feature for its mobile app. This feature allows users to record and share their travel experiences. When turned on, it automatically generates a timeline of the places visited and photos taken at each location. This timeline can be viewed chronologically or as a route on a map.
Adam Medros, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s SVP of Global Product, highlights the feature&amp;rsquo;s value in documenting and sharing travel memories.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates</description></item><item><title>Three of the top 25 hotels in the world, as listed by TripAdvisor, are located in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</guid><description>TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Choice awards highlights 25 diverse hotels worldwide. Notably, three hotels from Asia secured spots within the top 10. Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s The Upper House claimed the second position, while India&amp;rsquo;s Oberoi Udaivilas and Oberoi Mumbai ranked fifth and ninth, respectively.
The Upper House, nestled in Pacific Place, holds the top spot among hotels in Hong Kong. One reviewer praised it as their &amp;ldquo;best hotel experience,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing its flawlessness. A remarkable 97% of the reviews for this hotel are positive.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas in Vietnam have been recognized with accolades from TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The master bedroom of an oceanfront three-bedroom villa at Six Senses Con Dao, Vietnam.
TripAdvisor, a leading travel platform, has revealed its highest-rated properties for the fourteenth consecutive year. These rankings are determined by analyzing user reviews and feedback from travelers globally over the past year. Three properties - Evason Ana Mandara, Six Senses Ninh Van Bay, and Six Senses Con Dao - have earned the prestigious Traveler’s Choice award, signifying TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s highest honor.</description></item></channel></rss>