<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Building on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/building/</link><description>Recent content in Building on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/building/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony.</description></item><item><title>The Ibn Battuta Gate Office building is experiencing increased demand as Expo 2020 Dubai approaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</guid><description>Source: Seven Tides website.
As Expo 2020 Dubai approaches, Ibn Battuta Gate Offices, a property developed by Seven Tides, is leveraging its prime location in New Dubai. Situated near the Mövenpick Hotel, Ibn Battuta Mall, and a metro station, the office building is attracting significant attention.
The appeal of this location is further enhanced by the planned expansion of Ibn Battuta Mall. The AED160 million project will add 28,000 square meters, including a 350-room hotel, 150 shops, 50 restaurants, and a cinema with 21 screens.</description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures.</description></item><item><title>Malaysia to identify energy-efficient government buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</guid><description>Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Energy Commission, under the Ministry of Energy, Science, Technology, Environment and Climate Change (MESTECC), has introduced the National Building Energy Intensity (BEI) Labelling for Government Buildings.
This program strives to enhance energy efficiency in government-owned buildings within Malaysia, encouraging building owners to prioritize and improve energy conservation. Buildings are assigned a star rating based on their energy efficiency, with a five-star rating indicating the highest level of efficiency.
The initial phase, concluding in late 2018, encompasses 100 buildings belonging to ministries, departments, and agencies under MESTECC and the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Department.</description></item><item><title>The Building and Construction Authority of Singapore advocates for the development of super low energy buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-building-and-construction-authority-of-singapore-advocates-for-the-development-of-super-low-energy-buildings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Building and Construction Authority (BCA) initiated the Super Low Energy (SLE) Programme to advance environmental sustainability within the country. The program includes initiatives like the SLE Buildings Technology Roadmap and the SLE Challenge to promote the development and adoption of cost-effective SLE buildings.
Lawrence Wong, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for National Development and Second Minister for Finance, announced the program at the opening of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW) 2018.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s green building journey commenced in 2005 with the introduction of the BCA Green Mark and three Green Building Masterplans.</description></item></channel></rss>