<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Event on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/event/</link><description>Recent content in Event on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LASALLE Show will begin in April 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</guid><description>From the beginning of April to the end of May, the public and industry professionals are invited to view almost 900 graduating student projects at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s LASALLE College of the Arts yearly graduation showcase.
The projects featured at The LASALLE Show are developed throughout the students&amp;rsquo; final year and embody the culmination of their artistic growth and the realization of their aspirations. The LASALLE Show also provides insights into current trends in contemporary arts and design and highlights the emerging work of young artists...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encouraging female tech professionals to share their experiences at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>CloserStill Media, a global organizer of business technology trade shows, has launched a new initiative to highlight the expertise of women in technology. This initiative features panel discussions with accomplished women in the tech industry, offering aspiring women in technology worldwide opportunities to learn and participate.
The next session is scheduled for May 18-19, 2016, at Cloud Expo Asia and Data Centre World in Hong Kong. The panel, titled &amp;ldquo;Women leaders in technology:– real-life success stories,&amp;rdquo; will be moderated by Stephen Lau, Distinguished Fellow and Secretary General (Honorary) of the Hong Kong Computer Society (HKCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-female-tech-professionals-to-share-their-experiences-at-cloud-expo-asia-and-data-centre-world-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel and DBS have attracted a record number of small and medium-sized enterprises for the 99% SME Shopping Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Pictured showing support for the 99% SME Shopping Week 2017 are (from left): Ted Tan, Deputy Chief Executive of SPRING Singapore; Yeo Hiang Meng, President of the Federation of Merchants’ Association of Singapore; Joyce Tee, Managing Director and Group Head of SME Banking at DBS Bank; Sim Ann, Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Trade and Industry and Ministry of Culture, Community and Youth; Andrew Lim, Managing Director of Business Group, Group Enterprise at Singtel; and Parminder Singh, Chief Commercial and Digital Officer of Mediacorp...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-dbs-have-attracted-a-record-number-of-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-for-the-99-sme-shopping-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Orchard Road in Singapore is adorned with Christmas lights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road is aglow with Disney magic this holiday season. The &amp;ldquo;Disney Magical Moments — Christmas on A Great Street!&amp;rdquo; celebration features illuminated displays of beloved characters. The lights were officially switched on the evening of November 10.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the Toy Story-themed lights outside Plaza Singapura from the opening night.
The lights are arranged in four color-themed zones:
- Orange: Pixar’s Toy Story characters, including Woody, Buzz Lightyear, and their friends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should Brazil be considered a cyber security threat?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 04:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</guid><description>Cybercriminals frequently target major events like the Olympics to spread malware, and the 2016 Rio Games were no exception. While it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to stay vigilant against phishing attempts that exploit current events, a report from Fortinet, &amp;ldquo;FortiGuard Eye of the Storm,&amp;rdquo; highlights why the 2016 Olympics warranted particular concern.
Although cyberattacks at the Olympics are not a recent phenomenon, with incidents dating back to the 2004 Athens Games, Fortinet raised concerns about the Rio Games for two key reasons that could impact attendees and have a ripple effect on those back home:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-brazil-be-considered-a-cyber-security-threat/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAKE UP CALL is coming to Bali in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</guid><description>Source: WAKE UP CALL website. W Hotels is putting on a unique music festival at three locations in 2018, with a Dubai edition planned for 2019.
W Hotels presents WAKE UP CALL, a distinctive music festival hosted at three W Hotels, including the W Bali, alongside venues in the US and Europe.
Merging their love for music with their signature Whatever/Whenever approach, WAKE UP CALL brings the festival experience directly to the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ARTWALK Little India combines elements of the past with modern influences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</guid><description>Source: ARTWALK Little India. Izzad Radzali Shah, Festival, ARTWALK Little India 2018, LASALLE College of the Arts, 2018. Photo: Ng Wu Gang. The multidisciplinary arts festival ARTWALK Little India is a collaboration between LASALLE College of the Arts (LASALLE) and the Singapore Tourism Board (STB), with support from the Little India Shopkeepers and Heritage Association. It returns for its fourth year in January 2018 as a featured event in Singapore Art Week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Founders' Friday session in Singapore by Huawei will showcase Scott Bales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</guid><description>Source: Scott Bales website.
Huawei is launching a new networking series called Founders&amp;rsquo; Friday. The series aims to connect business leaders with professionals to exchange ideas, address difficulties, and develop innovative solutions for advancing the digital world.
The inaugural event, presented alongside the HUAWEI Mate 9, features prominent digital and innovation expert Scott Bales. He will discuss essential principles for fostering a culture of innovation within organizations. Bales, the Managing Director of Singapore-based Innovation Labs Asia, brings over a decade of global experience in innovation, thought leadership, implementation planning, and strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the global culinary journey at THAIFEX Anuga Asia 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 16:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</guid><description>THAIFEX - Anuga Asia 2024, scheduled for May 28th to June 1st, 2024, is set to be the largest and most diverse edition yet, featuring exhibitors from 45 countries and regions and completely booked booth spaces.
_
Source: THAIFEX-Anuga Asia. Hosted buyer programme participants posing for a group picture during THAIFEX-Anuga Asia 2023.
This premier food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) trade show in Asia Pacific has experienced an unprecedented increase in global participation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival showcases performances by exceptionally talented artists with disabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</guid><description>The True Colours Festival, showcasing talented performing artists with disabilities from the Asia Pacific region, will run from March 22nd to 25th, 2018 in Singapore.
The festival will feature up to 20 artist/troupe performances representing Japan, China, India, Korea, Malaysia, Cambodia, Kazakhstan, New Zealand, Australia, and Singapore. Guest artists from the UK and Canada will also be featured. Performances will take place at a multimedia concert experience inside the Singapore Indoor Stadium and at the nearby True Colours Festival Village...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Numerous innovations showcased at Food&amp;HotelAsia 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</guid><description>Display at the Suntec venue.
The Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) and ProWine Asia (PWA) trade shows are predicted to draw tens of thousands of attendees during their joint four-day run in Singapore, from April 24th to 27th.
This year marks the largest event yet. Visitors can explore exhibits from over 3,500 international food, beverage, and hospitality exhibitors throughout 120,000 sq m at FHA. In addition, PWA 2018 features 300 international wine and spirits exhibitors across 7,500 sq m...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk is back in Singapore for its fifth year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 22:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore Peatix website. Aerial view of Queenstown.
Now in its fifth year, Jane’s Walk Singapore is hosting a weekend of free walking tours throughout the city.
Inspired by urbanist, author, and activist Jane Jacobs, Jane’s Walk is a series of free, volunteer-led walking tours. Jacobs advocated for walkable, lively neighborhoods and encouraged community involvement in urban development. Her most renowned work, The Death and Life of Great American Cities, emphasizes the importance of observation, inquiry, and exploration in understanding cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-is-back-in-singapore-for-its-fifth-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Women in Business Asia Pageant hosts a workshop on digital marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</guid><description>Source: Women in Business Asia Pageant Facebook page.
To empower women entrepreneurs, the Women in Business Asia Pageant is holding a masterclass on digital marketing and social media strategies specifically for women in Singapore.
The session, titled &amp;ldquo;Digital Marketing and Social Media Hacks for Women in Business,&amp;rdquo; will run for one hour and teach participants how to build an effective, business-oriented website designed to generate leads. Attendees will discover how to incorporate both original and curated content into their marketing plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-women-in-business-asia-pageant-hosts-a-workshop-on-digital-marketing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vivid Sydney will once again enchant audiences starting on May 27th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</guid><description>The longest-running Vivid Sydney will illuminate Sydney Harbour and other beloved locations for 23 nights, from May 27 to June 18, 2016. This year marks the eighth anniversary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest festival of light, music, and ideas. The festival is owned, managed, and produced by Destination NSW, the NSW Government&amp;rsquo;s tourism and major events agency.
Sandra Chipchase, Destination NSW Chief Executive Officer and Executive Producer of Vivid Sydney, stated that this year&amp;rsquo;s Vivid Sydney promises an incredible program where art, creativity, and innovation converge, captivating both local and international visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk Singapore offers a blend of classic and innovative walking tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Peatix page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk logo.
The annual Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore, a series of free walking tours led by community members, will take place from May 4th to 6th. Inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, these walks encourage participants to share local stories, discover the city, and connect with their neighbors.
While many tours are already at capacity, new spots may open up, so interested individuals are encouraged to check back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IdeaLab gives power to startups in ASEAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 02:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</guid><description>IdeaLab 2016, a focused two-day startup conference, will highlight ASEAN startup collaboration and the Malaysian startup scene. It also features the Malaysian Business Angels Network (MBAN) Summit, attracting investors globally. The organizers aim to bring together 500 top startups, investors, and corporations from the ASEAN ecosystem.
Attendees can participate in various stages. The Ideation Stage features industry leaders discussing critical issues faced by startups in ASEAN. At the IdeaPad Stage, the best ASEAN startups compete before a panel of judges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealab-gives-power-to-startups-in-asean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell presents key features for IT Show 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</guid><description>Dell is featuring special deals on select products at IT Show 2018, happening in Suntec Singapore now through March 18th.
The XPS 13, available in a new rose gold color, starts at S$2,899. This 13&amp;quot; device is touted as the most powerful in its class and the smallest 13&amp;quot; available. It boasts an 8th Gen Intel Quad Core processor, a 4K Ultra HD InfinityEdge display, and introduces Dell Cinema, featuring CinemaColor, CinemaStream with wireless channels, and CinemaSound with Waves MaxxAudio Pro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The exclusive offers available at the 26th edition of The PC Show</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</guid><description>The PC Show, celebrating 26 years of IT and consumer electronics in Singapore, is back. Major brands like Best Denki, Canon, Courts, Creative, Dell, Epson, Harvey Norman, HP, Lenovo, M1, Newstead, Samsung, Seagate, Singtel, and Toshiba will offer exciting products, deals, and competitive prices.
Gillian Loh, Project Manager at Lines Exposition and Management Services, highlighted that attendees often look for great deals and the latest technology at the show. Organizers aim to continually improve the visitor experience, and this year they are introducing dedicated zones for specific interests and providing online updates on deals and new products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural India-ASEAN Writers Festival premieres in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</guid><description>The High Commission of India in Singapore is hosting the first India-ASEAN Writers Festival in Singapore.
This festival is one of many events celebrating 25 years of friendship between India and ASEAN, coinciding with the ASEAN India Pravasi Bharatiya Divas (Overseas Indians Day). The events are scheduled for January 6-7 at the Marina Bay Sands.
The PBD Writers Festival, a key event organized by Singapore-based publishing house Kitaab International on behalf of the High Commission, aims to &amp;ldquo;celebrate the literary ties between India and the ASEAN nations,&amp;rdquo; said Zafar Anjum, Kitaab&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DBS Marina Regatta is filled with exciting activities spread out over two weekends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 08:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest water sports festival, the DBS Marina Regatta, returns for its fifth year with an expanded format spanning two weekends, May 28-29 and June 4-5. The event, which drew over 24,000 attendees last year, will feature regional dragon boat races set against the Marina Bay skyline, the return of Singapore’s only pop-up urban beach, and the debut of Southeast Asia’s tallest inflatable water slide.
This year&amp;rsquo;s regatta will premiere several new features, including themed dragon boat races and competitive kayak races...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dbs-marina-regatta-is-filled-with-exciting-activities-spread-out-over-two-weekends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 5th annual PCCW Global Charity Run will be held in Singapore this June</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</guid><description>Source: PCCW Global Charity Run web page. A picture from the same event in 2017.
The 5th yearly PCCW Global Charity Run will happen this June, and both PCCW employees and the general public can participate.
This run is organized by PCCW Global, a telecommunications company operating in Asia, Africa, Latin America, and the Middle East.
All funds raised from this year&amp;rsquo;s run will be donated to Make-A-Wish Singapore, an organization that grants wishes for children facing life-threatening illnesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</a></p></description></item><item><title>THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023 begins in Bangkok on May 23rd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</guid><description>The upcoming THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023, a premier food and beverage industry event, will take place from May 23-27, 2023 at IMPACT Muang Thong Thani in Bangkok, Thailand. This year&amp;rsquo;s event features 11 signature trade shows, six special shows, and a focus on innovation, bold concepts, and advanced solutions. With approximately 3,000 exhibitors from 43 countries and over 60,000 trade visitors from more than 120 countries anticipated, organizers aim for a total transaction value of 70,000 million baht, including over 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tough Mudder Bali event will take place in the green hills of Jimbaran</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Bali. Event poster.
The ultimate test of physical and mental strength, stamina, and teamwork will premiere in Asia on October 1, 2016, at Jimbaran Hijau (Bali International Park), a multifaceted development in South Bali.
Established in 2010 and known as &amp;ldquo;probably the toughest event on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder is an obstacle course challenging participants to collaborate and conquer physical and mental hurdles in an extreme endurance event...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience cutting-edge VR gaming at Bugis Junction and Bugis+, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</guid><description>This Halloween, shoppers at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bugis Junction and Bugis+ malls can participate in an immersive virtual reality (VR) gaming experience. This event marks the first time malls in Singapore have hosted a VR experience of this magnitude.
The &amp;ldquo;Time Zombies&amp;rdquo; competition invites shoppers to assume the roles of time-traveling detectives. Their mission: to stop the nefarious Dr. Virago, a mad scientist attempting to unleash a zombie apocalypse. This competition utilizes cutting-edge Arctic Fox wireless technology, allowing players to move freely within the virtual world using a wireless headset, eliminating the need for cumbersome cables or backpack computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Promotions for Dell at CEE 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 01:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</guid><description>Dell is promoting several products at the Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) 2017. These products, equipped with 7th Gen Intel Core processors, are designed for an excellent visual experience and enhanced gameplay.
Here are some of the featured products:
Inspiron 13 5000 2-in-1
Original Price: Starting from S$1,699 Show Price: Starting from S$1,299 Features:
Latest 7th Gen Intel Core processor 13.3&amp;quot; FHD (1,920 x 1,080) IPS Truelife LED-backlit touchscreen with wide viewing angles and an infrared (IR) camera Four versatile modes: tent, stand, laptop, and tablet XPS 13 2-in-1..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/promotions-for-dell-at-cee-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural Tough Mudder event in Asia will take place in Bali, Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 06:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Indonesia. Chairi Ibrahim, Project Manager at Seroja Partners (left), Gandrasta Bangko, Business Director at Mesa Race (middle), and Ridzki Syahputera, Partner at Seroja Partners (right) at the launch of Tough Mudder Indonesia.
The world-renowned endurance series, Tough Mudder, has officially launched in Indonesia. Known as &amp;ldquo;Probably the Toughest Event on the Planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder has attracted 2.5 million participants across 200 events in six countries. Its Asian debut will take place on October 1st and 2nd, 2016, in Bali, Indonesia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is something for everyone on Jane's Walks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:46:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global initiative of free walking tours led by community members, is making a comeback from May 6th to 8th. The walks are inspired by Jane Jacobs (1916-2006), an urban planner and advocate who championed community-driven city development. Grounded in the belief that everyone possesses knowledge about their surroundings, these walks celebrate Jacobs&amp;rsquo; ideas worldwide. Participants share stories about their neighborhoods, discover hidden gems, and connect with their neighbors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-something-for-everyone-on-jane-s-walks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival includes a number of groundbreaking inclusive initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</guid><description>Source: True Colours Festival website. Some of the featured performers.
This coming March, twenty artists and groups will come together in Singapore for the first and largest event in the Asia Pacific region to showcase performers with disabilities. From March 22-25, 2018, Singapore will host True Colours Festival – the Asia Pacific Celebration of Artistes with Disabilities. True Colours is presented by UNESCO and The Nippon Foundation (TNF), two global organizations that advocate for the rights of people with disabilities (PWDs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bloem marks 4th anniversary with introduction of new services and partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Sukri Kadola and Ivy Tan cut a cake during Bloem&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s custom floral design company, Bloem, recently commemorated its fourth anniversary. The company marked this occasion by announcing new partnerships and the launch of its Concierge service.
&amp;ldquo;While many believe the economy has presented difficulties for businesses, success is subjective,&amp;rdquo; says Sukri Kadola, Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO. Eighty percent of Bloem&amp;rsquo;s revenue is generated through corporate projects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-disciplinary conversations are reshaping the service economy at KODW 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 04:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Pictured at the KODW 2021 opening ceremony are (from left) Lofai Lo (Director and GM, ViuTV); Dr Lay Lian Ong (Principal, Hong Kong Design Institute &amp;amp; Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education); Victor Tsang (Head of Create Hong Kong); Professor Eric Yim (Chairman of Hong Kong Design Centre); guest of honor The Honourable Edward Yau (Secretary for Commerce and Economic Development); Victor Lo (Chairman, KODW Steering Committee of Hong Kong Design Centre); Professor Kun-Pyo Lee (Dean of The Hong Kong Polytechnic University School of Design), and Dr Edmund Lee (Executive Director of Hong Kong Design Centre)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-disciplinary-conversations-are-reshaping-the-service-economy-at-kodw-2021/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TAKAUD will be hosting its first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</guid><description>Source: _Middle East Pensions Conference _website.
With the support of the Central Bank of Bahrain, TAKAUD, a leading provider of savings, investment, and pension solutions in the MENA region, is gathering government officials and financial service leaders to discuss the development of robust pension plans for citizens and foreign workers across the region.
The first-ever Middle East Pensions Conference will occur in Bahrain on October 18, 2016. The conference aims to raise awareness and encourage action towards bringing Middle Eastern pension standards in line with developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/takaud-will-be-hosting-its-first-ever-middle-east-pensions-conference/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself for the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</guid><description>Get ready for football fever this July as Arsenal, Atlético de Madrid, and Paris Saint-Germain head to Singapore for the 2018 International Champions Cup. This renowned annual tournament showcases top European football clubs competing across North America, Europe, and Asia.
Source: Sports Hub website. Three football clubs will be playing against each other at the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore on July 26, 28 and 30.
Beyond the three matches at the National Stadium on July 26th, 28th, and 30th, fans can immerse themselves in the excitement at the House of Football pop-up in Clarke Quay, Singapore’s vibrant nightlife and dining hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels will be introducing a Gourmet Food &amp; Wine Festival in Singapore in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Jaan was awarded a Michelin Star in the Singapore Michelin Guide 2016 and secured the 29th spot in Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2016.
AccorHotels, the leading hotel operator in the country, is launching its first-ever Gourmet Food &amp;amp; Wine Festival, anticipated to be one of the most extensive events of its kind in Singapore.
The festival will feature several Michelin-starred chefs. Graham Wilson, Chief Marketing &amp;amp; Distribution Officer for AccorHotels Asia Pacific, stated, “In a city celebrated for its culinary scene, AccorHotels will bring together some of our finest chefs from around the world and showcase the immense talent of Singaporean chefs to create a food festival as lively and diverse as Singapore itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SITEX 2016 guarantees an immersive and educational experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</guid><description>Source: SITEX website. Scene from SITEX 2015.
SITEX, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s yearly consumer technology showcase, aims to bridge the gap between individuals and technology. This year, it promises an elevated experience with new interactive activities like a technology-infused dance competition, a dedicated space for children&amp;rsquo;s technology (IMDA Pixel Labs), displays of intelligent systems from NTU, and the SITEX Innovation Alley presented by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SITF). These additions are designed to educate, entertain, and captivate visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preparations for Vivid Sydney start two weeks before Lights On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</guid><description>Sydney is getting ready for Vivid Sydney, a major festival celebrating light, music, and ideas in the Southern Hemisphere. Over 50 light installations and projections will illuminate the city starting May 24th.
Source: Vivid Sydney. An artist&amp;rsquo;s impression by Andrew Thomas Huang &amp;amp; Bemo on the Austral Floral Ballet, part of Vivid Light 2019. For 23 days, Vivid Sydney will transform the city into a captivating display of color with stunning light sculptures and large-scale projections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dream Collective is empowering potential female leaders in Singapore with their first-ever bootcamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</guid><description>Source: The Dream Collective.
The Dream Collective, a global platform for training women in corporate leadership, has introduced the Emerging Leaders Bootcamp - Singapore Edition. This program offers a new approach to female empowerment and initiates a crucial conversation about developing female leadership talent in the corporate world. Modeled after MBA programs from top business schools, the program collaborates with major corporations to find, develop, and empower high-potential young women with leadership skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore to host a coffee consumer festival driven by heritage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</guid><description>Source: La Kopi.
The first-ever La Kopi festival, launched in 2019, is a joyous weekend event celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s coffee and bakery culture. Supported by the Singapore Coffee Association, the festival aims to raise awareness and appreciation for these local staples.
This unique coffee festival will take place at the Singapore Expo Hall from January 25th to 27th, 2019. Spanning 4,000 square meters, the event features nearly 70 vendors from various countries, including Japan, Taiwan, Malaysia, and Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 has been met with an enthusiastic and positive reception</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</guid><description>Source: 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. The 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, was officially opened by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah.
Source: _1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. _Pictured from left to right (back row): Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah, Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, alongside Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Bin Abdullah, Secretary General of Treasury, Malaysia. They are joined by 10 children, each representing a different ASEAN nation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Follow the light from day to night on 28 July in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Canon. The Canon PhotoMarathon XVI will include assignments that extend from day into night.
Returning for its 16th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon XVI is scheduled for July 28th in Singapore. This year, Canon is expanding the event by incorporating community support and introducing new competition elements.
Building upon Canon’s ongoing support of local sports, Canon recently announced a partnership with Olympian Joseph Schooling. In line with the Canon PhotoMarathon’s goal to inspire and connect the photography community, Schooling will reveal one of the competition themes at the event...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, come to DiverseCity in KL to experience a diverse range of performing and visual arts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</guid><description>DiverseCity 2016, also known as the Kuala Lumpur International Arts Festival, ran from August 31st to October 2nd, 2016. The festival showcased a diverse range of artistic expressions, including visual arts, crafts, music, dance, and literature at various locations around Klang Valley in Malaysia. Many events were free to attend.
Taking place annually for five weeks at multiple venues in and around Kuala Lumpur, DiverseCity highlights the rich cultural tapestry of Malaysia and explores the country&amp;rsquo;s close relationship with the ASEAN community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the passion and joy of BMW at the BMW World in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is hosting BMW World of Passion and Joy at the Suntec Singapore International Convention and Exhibition Centre on August 25th and 26th, 2018.
This event offers visitors a chance to experience the latest BMW and MINI models, explore classic BMW heritage cars, and immerse themselves in The MINI Story. Performances and interactive activities will be available throughout the event.
Christopher Wehner, Managing Director of BMW Group Asia, emphasized that the event bridges BMW&amp;rsquo;s past, present, and future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 18th edition of All That Matters will take place from September 11th to 13th, 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</guid><description>All That Matters, a key event for professionals in Asia&amp;rsquo;s music, sports, gaming, digital, marketing, Web3, and entertainment sectors, is back for its 18th year. It will be held from September 11th to 13th at the Hilton Singapore Orchard.
Source: All That Matters organisers. Event poster.
The event combines a daytime conference with a nightly music festival. It offers attendees, including representatives from major labels, sports organizations, distributors, and publishers, a chance to connect with global brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pesta Raya by Esplanade is back in July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</guid><description>The Esplanade – Theatres on the Bay’s 17th annual Pesta Raya – Malay Festival of Arts will take place from July 12th to 15th, 2018. The festival coincides with Hari Raya Aidilfitri, a celebration that lasts until mid-July.
This year, the festival focuses on the history of the Nusantara. Fezhah Maznan, a programmer with The Esplanade Company, stated that Pesta Raya has always celebrated the rich Malay heritage through arts and culture from the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The second year of the 3-in-1 Singapore Festival of Fun promises even more excitement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay. Banner for the Singapore Festival of Fun.
Now in its second year, the massive three-part Festival of Fun combines the Magners International Comedy Festival, Nickelodeon Fiesta, and Clarke Quay StreetFest this March. The festival welcomes street performers from Covent Garden in the UK, beloved Nickelodeon characters, and award-winning comedians from around the globe.
Attendees can join in the festivities while also enjoying the diverse food and drink options at Clarke Quay&amp;rsquo;s many establishments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Singapore is backing F&amp;B and food manufacturers with innovative digital projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</guid><description>RESTAURANT 3.0: Embracing Technology in the Food Industry Enterprise Singapore showcased new digital solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) 2018. These solutions aim to help Singaporean food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and food manufacturing companies expand internationally and enhance their operational efficiency.
The showcased digital initiatives include a B2B online platform for food manufacturers and the RESTAURANT 3.0 exhibition for F&amp;amp;B businesses.
Enterprise Singapore, in collaboration with the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF), launched the &amp;ldquo;SMF SMART App&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Pavilion during FHA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get your hands on StarHub's flyers for CEE 2017 by downloading them now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</guid><description>Source: StarHub.
StarHub, recognized as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most environmentally friendly telecommunications company, will participate in the 2017 Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE).
Details about StarHub&amp;rsquo;s mobile, television, broadband, and bundled services are available in online promotional flyers. These flyers, which include information about the Business Fibre Broadband Bundle, are specifically designed for business customers.
The 2017 CEE will take place at Suntec from June 1st to June 4th. The event will be open from 11 am to 9 pm on levels 1 and 3, and from 12 pm to 9 pm in Halls 403 to 406 on level 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Once a month until October 2016, the Mount Faber Loop in Singapore will be closed to cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</guid><description>Beginning August 6th, Mount Faber Loop will transform into a car-free zone every first Saturday of the month, from 4 pm to 7 pm. This initiative, named &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Lepak at Mount Faber,&amp;rdquo; marks the first car-free event in a Singapore park and will run for three months, ending in October.
Organized by Mount Faber Leisure Group through the &amp;ldquo;Streets for People&amp;rdquo; initiative and supported by NParks, &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Lepak at Mount Faber&amp;rdquo; aligns with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s goal of becoming a &amp;ldquo;car-lite&amp;rdquo; city...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/once-a-month-until-october-2016-the-mount-faber-loop-in-singapore-will-be-closed-to-cars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Business of Design Week 2021 is open to participants from all over the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</guid><description>Source: HKDC. Officiating guests join Business of Design Week 2021’s opening ceremony.
The 19th edition of Business of Design Week (BODW) 2021 has begun. This major Asian design, innovation, and brand event, organized annually by the Hong Kong Design Centre (HKDC) since 2002, will run for a week. The summit showcases a diverse range of speakers and television programs centered around the theme of Global Design Reset.
The event adopts a hybrid format this year, broadcast simultaneously online, on ViuTV, and at various partner venues such as the PMQ in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-of-design-week-2021-is-open-to-participants-from-all-over-the-globe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In March, Clarke Quay will be hosting the largest Singapore Festival of Fun ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:28:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/</guid><description>- This image features carnival performers and comedians
- This ten-day festival includes the Clarke Quay Streetfest, the Magners International Comedy Festival and the Nickelodeon Fiesta.
The third annual Singapore Festival of Fun returns this March with its signature entertainment. From March 14-24, 2019, Clarke Quay will become a carnival showcasing street performers, standup comedy, and games. This ten-day event combines international and local carnival acts featuring acrobatics, juggling, and daring feats with standup comedic talent and distinctive Nickelodeon games celebrating Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 provides a boost to talented young entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 20:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: GES 2016. President Obama waves as he walks off the stage with Mark Zuckerberg, Chairman, CEO, and co-founder of Facebook with successful young entrepreneurs from Africa and South America after a panel discussion that he moderated. This is the occasion where he famously said he still had some time to go before he could wear a t-shirt like Zuckerberg, but could at least remove his jacket.
Former US President Barack Obama believes entrepreneurship is a driving force for economic growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-summit-2016-provides-a-boost-to-talented-young-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In August, an innovation event will be held in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</guid><description>The second one-north Festival, a celebration of research, innovation, creativity, and enterprise, will take place on August 18th and 19th, 2017, at Biopolis in Singapore.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOAcpbDhuBLMHwpNFri5j6kbRVLkScIKw4TiGhwymXBdx3y6jgeTVWIOLN9OP71ghrtTERYqlpvKkMaup28rURdUpbA6fK2EH9AWxwQi-iB9M-tHLvfmrD43zz1zcSGOThoKLcuV0Yd6k/s1600/20170720_125101.jpg)
This advertisement for the one-north Festival was seen at Raffles station.
Organized by A*STAR and JTC, the festival&amp;rsquo;s theme, Pioneering an Innovation Future, centers around future health, living, and work. This year&amp;rsquo;s festival will incorporate Science Centre Singapore&amp;rsquo;s X-periment!, showcasing cutting-edge health innovations.
Highlighting the collaborative spirit of the one-north community, the festival showcases how partnerships between research performers and industry partners drive advancements in research, innovation, and enterprise, benefiting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy and enhancing lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be expanding in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</guid><description>A Nestle Sjora mural was a key feature at the Nestle booth during Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia 2018.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), the largest biennial trade show in the region for food and hospitality, will be split into two separate shows starting in 2020. FHA-HoReCa will take place in early March, and FHA-Food &amp;amp; Beverage will follow at the end of March.
This cake was on display at the Qingdao Kesong Food Company (KFI) booth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit will span two days and focus on the future of commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 11:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Millennial 20/20.
From September 7th to 8th, 2016, Singapore will be the site of the Millennial 20/20 APAC Summit. This two-day event will feature discussions centered around understanding the millennial consumer, with over 130 speakers, interactive exhibits, 50 panel discussions, and 24 keynote presentations and interviews.
Rupa Ganatra, Founding Partner of Millennial 20/20, emphasizes the rapid changes in the marketplace driven by millennials, stating that the summit will be crucial for brands to adapt and remain relevant in this influential movement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-millennial-20-20-apac-summit-will-span-two-days-and-focus-on-the-future-of-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover Clark by participating in the CLARK BIKE TOUR this July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</guid><description>Source: PDOT.
The Philippines Department of Tourism (PDOT), alongside the Clark Development Corporation, announced the upcoming CLARK BIKE TOUR happening in July. This bike tour aims to raise awareness about the significance of health and wellness as a way of life while promoting travel and tourism. It also seeks to highlight Clark as a bike-friendly area.
The event, scheduled for July 30 at the parade ground, anticipates around 400 road bikers, forming 100 teams of four members each, to engage in a non-competitive day-long tour of different attractions within the freeport zone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-clark-by-participating-in-the-clark-bike-tour-this-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The goal of the Taste The World Dining Series is to demonstrate that food serves as a universal form of communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</guid><description>Gourmet Trails, a luxury travel company, presents the first-ever Taste The World culinary series, taking place from May 4th to 26th, 2024. This festival showcases the unifying power of food, emphasizing its ability to connect people and foster understanding.
Taste The World partners with acclaimed restaurants like Appetite, Hashida, CURE, Canchita, Esquina, Ummi Beirut, and ANJU to offer a diverse range of global cuisines. Proceeds from this event will support the United Nations World Food Programme...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Green Building Week has officially begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</guid><description>The DVUCA city management system dashboard uses data from Singapore and other cities to quickly compare water and power consumption. It can even provide granular insights, such as indicating if someone is at their desk.
Singapore Green Building Week has commenced, featuring Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, a Southeast Asian trade show for the region&amp;rsquo;s green building market, and Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional exhibition for HVAC-R*, water, and energy solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An open house event was held at Changi Airport's fourth terminal before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: CAG. CAG organises open house for Changi T4.
The Changi Airport Group (CAG) has invited Singapore residents to preview Terminal 4 (T4) before its official opening. From August 7th to 20th, 2017, the public can attend an Open House for a sneak peek of the new terminal.
Construction on the 195,000 square meter, two-story T4 began in early 2013 and finished in December 2016. Though only half the size of Terminal 3 (T3), it can accommodate 16 million passengers annually, roughly 70% of T3&amp;rsquo;s capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IIA addresses the challenges of internal auditing in the digital era</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fifth yearly Public Sector Internal Audit (PSIA) Conference, themed Rising to the Challenges of the Future, centered on economic shifts and transformations.
The Institute of Internal Auditors (IIA), organizer of the PSIA, emphasized that organizations face mounting hurdles in our increasingly digital world, including cybercrime and technological disruptions. Consequently, internal audits are even more critical for strong governance in both public and private sectors.
To maintain effective and independent assurance, internal auditors must embrace innovation and acquire new skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iia-addresses-the-challenges-of-internal-auditing-in-the-digital-era/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining culture and heritage using technology as a tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</guid><description>The National Museum of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s new exhibit, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents,&amp;rdquo; opens on August 4th and features technologically innovative projects that combine history, art, and technology.
Developed collaboratively with designers, artists, and tech companies, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; offers visitors new ways to experience culture and heritage. This includes immersive virtual and augmented reality exhibits, artificial intelligence-powered conversations, and much more.
Part of a larger initiative to promote digital innovation within the cultural sector, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; showcases seven prototypes from the &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Open Call&amp;rdquo; for digital art and innovation, which concluded in April...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CEE is ready to showcase gadgets and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</guid><description>The 4th Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) will be held from May 23rd to 26th, 2019, at Suntec Singapore Convention Centre. The event is organized by Exhibits Inc., a subsidiary of Sphere Exhibits, which is the events and exhibitions branch of Singapore Press Holdings.
Some of the featured events include:
Singapore Robo Fight 2019 (Level 4, Gamex Booth 8601)
Attendees can use smartphones to control miniature battle robots and engage in virtual combat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingEx has introduced Last Mile Fulfilment Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</guid><description>Last Mile Fulfilment Asia (LMFAsia), a debut trade show and conference centered around last-mile fulfillment in logistics and e-commerce, will premiere in Singapore next year.
This is the first event of its kind to hone in on last-mile fulfillment challenges and prospects in Asia. SingEx anticipates the event will attract around 1,500 attendees, representatives, and exhibitors from the Asian region in its first year. LMFAsia aims to unite four crucial sectors – e-commerce, retail, logistics, and parcel delivery – under one roof to maximize business opportunities for e-commerce in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BDMS Connect Center in Bangkok now offers a wider range of MICE options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</guid><description>Source: Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok. BDMS Connect Center.
The BDMS Wellness Campus is proud to introduce its latest addition, the BDMS Connect Center. This cutting-edge facility, spanning over 3,400 square meters in the heart of Bangkok, is set to redefine the standards of meeting and event spaces.
Dan Smith, General Manager of Mövenpick BDMS Wellness Resort Bangkok, expressed his enthusiasm for the new facility, stating that the BDMS Connect Center is a one-of-a-kind space, emphasizing both functionality and a commitment to wellness and sustainability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bdms-connect-center-in-bangkok-now-offers-a-wider-range-of-mice-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Adobe Symposium 2016 will be sharing important digital marketing trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 16:21:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. Logo for Adobe Symposium 2016.
Over 1,000 professionals in digital marketing, publishing, advertising, content management, and marketing executives will come together at the Adobe Symposium in Singapore on July 28, 2016. This event will provide insights into how innovative global brands have successfully utilized digital trends to deeply understand their customers, create personalized campaigns, and effectively manage content and assets.
With over 50 sessions across four tracks, attendees will witness the latest innovations from Adobe Marketing Cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-adobe-symposium-2016-will-be-sharing-important-digital-marketing-trends/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself to taste delicious food from various regions at RWS Street Eats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</guid><description>Resorts World Sentosa (RWS) is bringing back its popular food event, RWS Street Eats, after it attracted over 100,000 attendees last year. The event will run from May 3rd to 12th, 2019, and showcase new dishes from across Southeast Asia.
Taking place at the Malaysian Food Street in RWS, this 10-day event will feature hidden culinary gems from Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, Vietnam, and Taiwan. These vendors are local favorites, often known only to the savviest eaters in their respective countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The highlight of the Downtown Dubai New Year's Eve Gala is the Burj Khalifa</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</guid><description>To celebrate the arrival of 2015, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Khalifa will showcase a dazzling LED display across its 828-meter height, synchronized with a spectacular fireworks show, according to a report from the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
Emaar Properties, the developer behind Downtown Dubai, is orchestrating a six-part extravaganza for their New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve Gala. The event will feature a captivating blend of fireworks, laser displays, and a light show. A highlight of the celebration will be a special tribute to Dubai, its leaders, and the UAE&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments over the past 43 years, projected onto the specially designed LED screen...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-highlight-of-the-downtown-dubai-new-year-s-eve-gala-is-the-burj-khalifa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Private Museum is taking a new approach to printmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</guid><description>The Private Museum (TPM) in Singapore is hosting an exhibition curated by Zaki Razak, titled Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing. The exhibition runs from May 17th to July 7th, 2019, and features printmaking works by seven artists: Miguel Chew, Weixin Chong, Mona Choo, Urich Lau, Nadia Oh, Shin-Young Park, and Shih Yun Yeo.
Source: Eventbrite page. Poster for Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing.
This is the second exhibition in TPM&amp;rsquo;s Guest Curator series, which aims to promote independent curatorial practices and diverse perspectives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bloem is set to open its flagship store at The Heeren</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/</guid><description>Source: Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This wedding bouquet showcases Bloem&amp;rsquo;s artistry and meticulousness.
Bloem, the floral design studio, is expanding its presence in Singapore with a new flagship store at Robinson&amp;rsquo;s The Heeren. This location will introduce a wider audience to their distinctive and customized floral creations.
Since 2013, Bloem has established a strong reputation for its tailored floral arrangements for corporate clients, according to founder and CEO, Sukri Kadola. The Orchard Road store marks a significant step in the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory, broadening its reach to a larger customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In March, The Island Exchange provides business insights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/</guid><description>Source: HSBC Women&amp;rsquo;s World Championship. Heng.
The Island Exchange is a brand-new festival geared towards ambitious individuals, launching at Sentosa, Singapore, on March 2nd.
Running concurrently with the HSBC Women&amp;rsquo;s World Championship, The Island Exchange is a one-day event featuring a mix of local and international speakers who will be sharing their insights and experiences on cultivating a successful and fulfilling career.
Notable speakers include Nadya Hutagalung, TV personality and UN Environmental Goodwill Ambassador, and Rachel Lim, founder of Love Bonito...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buyers who prioritize design are encouraging gift and premium manufacturers to elevate their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</guid><description>Source: SGS website. SGS 2015 was well attended.
This year&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Gifts Show (SGS), taking place from June 29th to July 1st, sees exhibitors raising their game in response to increasingly design-conscious buyers. As the biggest event of its kind in Singapore, SGS is a trade show for gifts, premiums, lifestyle products, and services, targeting both regional and global markets. Established in 2006, this yearly showcase spans three days and encompasses both an exhibition and industry seminars...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Double 12 Global Shopping Festival aims to attract Alipay users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</guid><description>Source: Alipay Facebook page. Flag advertising the Double 12 Global Shopping Festival.
Alipay, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading online and mobile payment and lifestyle platform operated by Ant Financial Services Group, launched its 2017 Double 12 Global Shopping Festival in Southeast Asia. The festival includes Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, and the Philippines.
Double 12 is a global event spanning 15 countries and territories across four continents. Over 500 brands and 100,000 merchants worldwide participate, offering Alipay users exclusive promotions throughout December...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improve your filmmaking abilities using a smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 05:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</guid><description>Boo (left) with Tan (right).
While using mobile phones for filmmaking only emerged around 2008, recent technological advancements have empowered many phone owners to become filmmakers.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), aim to raise awareness about this potential in the Asia Pacific region and cultivate local talent. Their latest phone, the HUAWEI Mate 30 Pro, boasts features like 4K video recording, ultra-wide angle lens, and ultra slow motion capabilities, making it a capable filmmaking tool...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Emirates Literature Foundation introduces a new digital discussion series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</guid><description>The Emirates Literature Foundation has launched a new project, Literary Conversations Across Borders. This digital initiative aims to promote global cultural understanding by connecting Emirati writers and thinkers with internationally recognized experts for live discussions on significant issues.
The series commences on May 30, 2020, with Indian politician and writer Shashi Tharoor and HE Zaki Nusseibeh, UAE Minister of State for the Office of Cultural Diplomacy. They will examine how the events of 2020 will shape the future, both positively and negatively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore International Festival of Music is ready for its October shows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 13:56:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</guid><description>The Singapore International Festival of Music (SIFOM), Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first classical music festival, returns for its second year. Centered around the theme &amp;ldquo;Myths and Legends,&amp;rdquo; the festival showcases classical music inspired by folklore and fairy tales. From October 13th to 30th, the festival offers free public programs, masterclasses, and ticketed events including orchestral performances, musical theater, and vocal concerts.
The 2016 SIFOM lineup features the festival&amp;rsquo;s own SIFOM Orchestra and Ensemble, Ding Yi Music Company (showcasing Singapore&amp;rsquo;s finest young musicians), and internationally-renowned guests from the Chamber Orchestra of Europe (COE), a distinguished chamber orchestra...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-international-festival-of-music-is-ready-for-its-october-shows/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The carnival at People's Park Complex will feature opera performances, games, and information on cashless services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</guid><description>Zhongguo Remittance and the management of People&amp;rsquo;s Park Complex in Singapore are collaborating on a free event at the mall from August 25th to 27th, 2017.
Attendees can enjoy daily Chinese opera performances at noon, participate in stage games and a shop hunt, and try their luck in lucky draws for prizes. Food sampling will be available, alongside retail booths and demonstrations of CCPay&amp;rsquo;s cashless services, including remittance options through Zhongguo Remittance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Blue Blood VIP Party Series by The Monarchy will debut on March 1st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blue-blood-vip-party-series-by-the-monarchy-will-debut-on-march-1st/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 02:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blue-blood-vip-party-series-by-the-monarchy-will-debut-on-march-1st/</guid><description>Source: The Monarchy. A look at the interior.
Kicking off today, The Monarchy: Blue Blood VIP Party Series welcomes renowned Australian DJ Scott Pullen at 10 pm. This new series at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s The Monarchy promises to extend the classic British cocktail bar experience into the late evening with its exclusive Blue Blood parties.
Pullen, celebrated for electrifying crowds at iconic venues like New York’s Cielo and London’s Trade, brings his global expertise to the decks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blue-blood-vip-party-series-by-the-monarchy-will-debut-on-march-1st/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blue-blood-vip-party-series-by-the-monarchy-will-debut-on-march-1st/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haenyeo Singapore visually captures the story of Jeju's female divers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. HAENYO SINGAPORE will be exhibited in Singapore until November 23rd.
Jose Jeuland, a French photographer based in Singapore, is presenting his debut photography exhibition. This exhibition, hosted at The Fullerton Hotel in Singapore, focuses on haenyo (해녀) - female divers from Jeju Island in South Korea. Epson Singapore, the official print sponsor for the exhibition, provided prints produced on one of their commercial and industrial photographic production printers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kramnik will face Alcántara in a rematch on Chessarena.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</guid><description>Source: World Chess. Vladimir Kramnik (pictured left) is set to have a rematch against José Alcántara (Jospem, pictured right) in August 2024.
World Chess, an organization dedicated to increasing the popularity of chess worldwide, is organizing &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims 2.&amp;rdquo; This event is a rematch following a controversial first &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims&amp;rdquo; match between chess players Vladimir Kramnik and José Alcántara. The event will be broadcasted live with commentary from well-known chess personalities and include interactive elements for viewers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The AirAsia Foundation is investigating the concept of social enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia Foundation website.
The AirAsia Foundation is hosting a conference and marketplace focused on social enterprise on November 7th at Nexus Bangsar South in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This event, Destination: Good – ASEAN Social Enterprise 2015, is the first public event organized by the AirAsia Foundation, the philanthropic branch of the AirAsia Group. Its goal is to initiate a discussion on the role large companies and social enterprises can play in fostering fair, sustainable, and inclusive economies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pre-registered delegates can access a report on industry innovations through Food&amp;HotelAsia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 06:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/</guid><description>To commemorate its 40th anniversary, Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) has partnered with Euromonitor International to release a new white paper.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Smart Innovations Transforming the Food and Hospitality Landscape by 2020,&amp;rdquo; the 20-page report examines significant disruptions influencing the industry. Based on research conducted by UBM and Euromonitor, the white paper incorporates insights from a survey of over 1,000 suppliers and manufacturers across key food, hotel, and food service equipment sectors in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Players from Manchester United and FC Barcelona will be participating in the GET Riyadh 2023 football competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 10:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</guid><description>The Global Esports Tour (GET), a professional esports series by the Global Esports Federation, will commence its third season on August 26-27, 2023. This season&amp;rsquo;s launch event will take place at Boulevard Riyadh City, as a featured part of the Gamers8 festival.
Source: Global Esports Federation. Poster for GET Riyadh 2023.
KONAMI’s eFootball 2023 will be the primary game featured, with a prize pool totaling US$50,000. Professional football players, Lotfi Derradji and Kilyan Katou Judex Faucheux of Manchester United, alongside Alejandro Alguacil Seguira and Saul Adrian Chavez Saucedo of FC Barcelona, will participate alongside esports players...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take a look at the lineup for YouTube FanFest Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: YouTube. Poster for YouTube FanFest Hong
Kong 2018.
The Manulife-sponsored YouTube FanFest returns to Hong Kong on August 3 at the Kowloonbay International Trade &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre (KITEC).
This live event bridges the gap between prominent YouTube creators from Hong Kong and around the globe, offering a platform for fan engagement. YouTube FanFest Hong Kong will feature:
- Matt Steffanina, a US-based dancer, YouTuber, and social media figure known for his dance-centric content..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Every night in Sydney, it's Lights On for Vivid Sydney!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Destination NSW. Vivid Sydney in action.
The tenth anniversary of Vivid Sydney, the world’s largest festival of light, music and ideas, has begun. As Australia’s largest event, Vivid Sydney transforms the city into a captivating display of illumination, sound, and creativity.
The festival commenced with the symbolic &amp;lsquo;Lights On&amp;rsquo; moment, with all eyes on the Sydney Opera House for the &amp;lsquo;Lighting of the Sails&amp;rsquo;. This year&amp;rsquo;s display, created by Australian artist Jonathan Zawada, featured dynamic digital sculptures of commonplace objects and elements from nature, morphing and changing before the viewers&amp;rsquo; eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is gaining traction as a top choice for hosting business events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</guid><description>Source: TCEB.
Thailand, with the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB) at the helm, is establishing itself as a prime location for business events. As the Thai government&amp;rsquo;s primary representative for this sector, TCEB plays a vital role in solidifying Thailand&amp;rsquo;s leading position in the Asian business events industry and Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a top-tier destination for international business events.
The Thai business events sector is projected to experience robust growth in 2015, anticipating over a million visitors and generating approximately US$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore Expo CNY Fair offers daily discounts of S$380 to the first 888 customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</guid><description>Red envelopes containing discounts, called angbaos, can be redeemed for certain products in addition to existing promotions (terms and conditions apply).
Items will be offered at up to 88% off.
The Singapore Expo CNY Fair will distribute complimentary lucky angbao gift packages, each valued at S$380, to the initial 888 attendees daily from January 10th to 12th. The event will be held at Singapore Expo Hall 6, open from 12 pm to 9 pm each day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>