<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monitoring on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/monitoring/</link><description>Recent content in Monitoring on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:26:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/monitoring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fosun Trade Medical Devices introduces a dual-function blood glucose and uric acid tester called BUZUD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</guid><description>Source: BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This image showcases the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System from BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This system allows for convenient at-home testing of both uric acid and blood glucose levels.
BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices, a medical device company, has launched the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System. This innovative device allows users to measure both blood sugar and uric acid levels from the comfort of their homes with ease and a high degree of accuracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CA Technologies reports that CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has been successful in its first 100 days</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 09:46:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</guid><description>CA Technologies, a provider of IT management solutions for securing and managing complex IT environments, has released a new version of its freemium product, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap. This solution helps businesses support agile business services.
Since its release 100 days ago, CA Nimsoft Monitor Snap has seen 5,000 downloads from SMBs, Fortune 1000 companies, and IT service providers across 147 countries. The full-featured version of CA Nimsoft Monitor shares the same codebase and proactively monitors servers, networks, storage, databases, and applications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-reports-that-ca-nimsoft-monitor-snap-has-been-successful-in-its-first-100-days/</a></p></description></item><item><title>For the initial six months, HP Touchpoint Manager is being offered at a discounted rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 20:55:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</guid><description>HP has introduced HP Touchpoint Manager, a cloud-based IT management solution specifically designed for small and mid-sized businesses (SMBs).
Managing IT systems has become more challenging due to the increasing variety of devices and operating systems used in business, from company-provided equipment to personal devices.
HP Touchpoint Manager simplifies IT management for SMBs, helping them ensure device functionality, data security, and IT staff effectiveness. Its adaptability allows it to manage a wide array of devices and operating systems, including iOS, Android, and Windows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/for-the-initial-six-months-hp-touchpoint-manager-is-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>