<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Signal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/signal/</link><description>Recent content in Signal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/signal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Gold Coated DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4000 is progressing well. I&amp;rsquo;ve added a grounding switch and a new gold-plated Neutrik DIN5 plug. The switch allows users to choose between the grounding setup of the older 4000/4002 models (separate signal and system grounds) and the later 4004 models (combined grounds). This option helps prevent ground loops and the resulting humming, depending on the amplifier being used. I wrote a detailed post on this topic a while back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Exploration of Photocell Function in Sensor Arm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is going well, but it appears someone attempted repairs before. The sensor arm insert, containing the light bulb and photocell for record detection, was in disarray.
Upon inspection, a photocell wire was disconnected, another was damaged from being forced back into the aluminum profile, and the lens insert had heat damage, likely from improper soldering. Thankfully, the lenses were unharmed.
After reconnecting the wire, replacing the non-standard light bulb with a Beolover LED insert, and adjusting the TR14 bias to 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Grounding Switch That Allows to Connect System and Signal Grounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</guid><description>During my latest restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I encountered a loud hum when playing records through my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s 4-channel phono input. The issue was resolved by connecting the signal and system grounds. Although the root cause of the hum remains unclear, I decided to install a switch to allow for easy toggling between the original separate grounding configuration and a direct connection between signal and system grounds at the turntable&amp;rsquo;s output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage and Measuring the Voltage Differences Between the Phases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the AC motor requires precise adjustment. The service manual recommends setting the main phase voltage to 6V (RMS) and the frequency to 42.3 Hz for 33 RPM using an oscilloscope. To observe both motor phases, connect the oscilloscope probes across the phase capacitor.
Begin the adjustment by setting the 33 RPM trimmer on the control panel to its neutral position. This allows for fine-tuning the RPM offset potentiometer on the main PCB to achieve the target 42...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>