<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Students on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/students/</link><description>Recent content in Students on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/students/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What impact could Brexit have on the younger generation? EU Referendum Briefing 2.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A UK exit from the European Union, or &amp;ldquo;Brexit,&amp;rdquo; could have significant implications for young people, impacting their education, travel opportunities, and economic prospects.
Education
The EU does not control educational content or matters like tuition costs. Instead, its involvement lies in cross-border educational aspects, including promoting student and teacher mobility through initiatives like the Erasmus program. Established in 1987, this EU law-based program facilitates student exchanges across various educational levels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-could-brexit-have-on-the-younger-generation-eu-referendum-briefing-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that students from third countries have the right to enter school.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</guid><description>Steve Peers
As the new academic year begins, students across the EU are met with a mix of anticipation and anxiety. Juggling academics, finances, personal life, and social activities is a universal experience for students, and those from outside the EU face the added pressure of meeting immigration requirements.
These requirements are standardized by the EU&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Students’ Directive. However, the degree of uniformity across member states remains unclear. Do individual countries retain the right to impose additional entry prerequisites?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-students-from-third-countries-have-the-right-to-enter-school/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Additional research is required to further explore the EU's efforts to attract a greater number of non-EU researchers and students.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU member states, similar to other economically advanced nations, require a growing number of highly skilled workers. Current EU regulations have not significantly increased the influx of students and researchers from other countries, prompting the Commission to propose revisions in 2013. Both the European Parliament (EP) and the Council have agreed on their respective stances for the proposed law and are preparing to negotiate a final version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imbalance in the Right to Free Movement for European Union Citizens: A Focus on Students</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</guid><description>Francesca Strumia*, Connor Brown**
*Lecturer in Law, University of Sheffield
** LLB Law European and International, University of Sheffield
This post reflects the preliminary results of a research project conducted as part of the Sheffield Undergraduate Research Experience programme (SURE). It also builds on a presentation at the International Society of Public Law (ICON-S) annual conference in New York on 2nd July 2015
INTRODUCTION
Growing concerns about limited public funds, diminished international cooperation, and declining support for a more unified Europe have cast a shadow on a key principle: the free movement of people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imbalance-in-the-right-to-free-movement-for-european-union-citizens-a-focus-on-students/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>