<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Convertible on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convertible/</link><description>Recent content in Convertible on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convertible/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Acer introduces new convertible notebooks, the Aspire R 13 and R 14</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</guid><description>Acer has introduced two new convertible notebook lines, the Aspire R 13 and Aspire R 14 Series, both capable of transitioning between various notebook and tablet modes. These notebooks are designed for users seeking the functionality of a traditional notebook with added flexibility.
Source: Acer. The R 13 in one mode.
Acer&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Jason Chen, stated that their objective is to exceed expectations with their products at every price point. He believes these Aspire convertibles are ideal for users who require both portability and productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acer-introduces-new-convertible-notebooks-the-aspire-r-13-and-r-14/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP has released a variety of mobile solutions to enhance business productivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 11:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</guid><description>HP has introduced a suite of commercial mobility solutions aimed at boosting workplace productivity. The offerings include eight new mobile devices and accessories designed to simplify business processes.
Anneliese Olson, HP Asia-Pacific and Japan VP and GM of Personal Computing, highlighted how these products address evolving workplace dynamics, workforce trends, and work styles, ultimately reshaping workflows.
HP has developed a comprehensive mobility solution catering to diverse businesses, including those in specialized sectors like education, field service, healthcare, public safety, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-released-a-variety-of-mobile-solutions-to-enhance-business-productivity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>