<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/community/</link><description>Recent content in Community on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN.</description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>