<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Creativity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/creativity/</link><description>Recent content in Creativity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stars at INSEAD drive innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</guid><description>New research from INSEAD suggests that good mentors are incredibly valuable.
The study, titled &amp;ldquo;Where Do Stars Come From? The Role of Star vs. Nonstar Collaborators in Creative Settings,&amp;rdquo; was published in Organization Science. The authors, Manuel Sosa, Jürgen Mihm, and Haibo Liu, examined the skills needed to effectively combine different elements for maximum creativity and innovation, leading to organizational success.
Their research specifically focused on a new aspect of collaborative creativity: the impact of collaborating with high-achievers (&amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo;) versus average performers (&amp;ldquo;non-stars&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Windows device will soon enhance your creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The possibilities of Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, sketched on a Microsoft Surface by Michael Mindflyer.
Microsoft has launched the latest version of its operating system, the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, offering it as a free upgrade to current Windows 10 users globally. This update, the fourth major one for Windows 10, prioritizes creativity. It aims to make mixed reality and 3D design accessible to Windows users, leading to improvements in gaming, audiovisual content, and mixed reality experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Facebook Singapore has established an office that is truly local and fosters creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 12:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s new South Beach office embodies its transparent and interconnected work environment. Local culture and unique design elements are woven into the fabric of the Singapore office.
Numerous pantries, meeting spaces, and snack areas provide ample opportunities for casual conversation and networking. One such area features a snack stand designed as a traditional pushcart, with treats presented in bamboo steamers.
A Facebook-themed mahjong table offers another avenue for fostering connections and spontaneous interactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>