<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NIC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nic/</link><description>Recent content in NIC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels.</description></item></channel></rss>