<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DTV on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dtv/</link><description>Recent content in DTV on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dtv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dark Side of Spectrum Renewal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</guid><description>Half a century ago, the government embraced urban renewal, demolishing and rebuilding deteriorated urban areas for housing projects or highways leading to suburbs. Similarly, today, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing &amp;ldquo;spectrum renewal,&amp;rdquo; where sections of the radio frequency spectrum are deemed too valuable for older technologies like analog TV and cell phone service, despite their widespread use.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by lack of public demand. Millions of analog TV sets and cell phones are still functional.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 07:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</guid><description>In the previous discussion, we explored how AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon are aggressively acquiring bandwidth for their LTE networks. Now, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the consequences of this insatiable demand for bandwidth as we transition into the 4G era.
While UHF and microwave bandwidth transactions are currently active, this surge won&amp;rsquo;t last indefinitely. The high prices will incentivize existing bandwidth holders to sell to major players heavily investing in 4G deployment. What happens once this bandwidth is depleted?</description></item><item><title>700 MHz Groundhogs Look For DTV Shadow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/700-mhz-groundhogs-look-for-dtv-shadow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/700-mhz-groundhogs-look-for-dtv-shadow/</guid><description>Every year, like clockwork, attention turns to predicting the future, and this year is no different. While many await a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s weather forecast, the telecom industry is focused on a different kind of prediction: the upcoming decision on user rights within the 700 MHz UHF TV band. This decision has significant implications for the future of television broadcasting. One outcome ushers in the era of digital television (DTV), while the other prolongs the use of analog television (ATV) for another 16 weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>