<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Password on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/password/</link><description>Recent content in Password on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/password/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are your passwords secure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-passwords-secure/</guid><description>Intel Security commemorated World Password Day by providing helpful advice on enhancing online security through diverse authentication methods.
Steer Clear of Predictable Logins
Short and seemingly clever passwords are easily guessed. Cybercriminals often begin their attacks by testing common password combinations. Simple keyboard patterns like &amp;ldquo;qwerty&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;12345678&amp;rdquo; are just as insecure as passwords like &amp;ldquo;welcome&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;login.&amp;rdquo;
Craft Strong, Complex Passwords
Longer passwords are always more secure. Incorporate a mix of numbers, lowercase and uppercase letters, and symbols.</description></item><item><title>Generating passwords can be likened to navigating a minefield</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</guid><description>A popular joke on Twitter highlights the struggle of creating secure passwords, mocking the complex requirements that often feel excessive. However, the humor underscores a serious issue: the necessity of strong passwords in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Simple passwords are widely considered inadequate in preventing unauthorized access, leading organizations to ban easily guessable combinations.
Despite this understanding, the recent Adobe security breach revealed that many users still rely on weak passwords. The most common passwords found in the leaked data were alarmingly basic, with &amp;ldquo;123456&amp;rdquo; topping the list.</description></item></channel></rss>