<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Centers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-centers/</link><description>Recent content in Data Centers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-centers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary.</description></item><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs.</description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-cloud-computing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a good reason for the growing interest in cloud computing. The uncertain economic climate makes the pay-as-you-go model increasingly appealing. This, combined with almost instant scalability, results in a computing environment where costs mirror business activity, minimizing the need for large upfront investments.
Cloud computing offers additional advantages, particularly in disaster recovery and business phone systems. Consider the impact of natural disasters like hurricanes or earthquakes on traditional data centers.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Server vs Cloud Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</guid><description>Cloud backup services have gained immense popularity among both individuals and businesses. Most people store at least some files online for easy sharing and mobile access, exceeding the need for encrypted backups. Essentially, there&amp;rsquo;s a massive shift of data towards the cloud.
While online file storage has become second nature, cloud computing hasn&amp;rsquo;t gained the same widespread adoption, despite a clear trend in that direction. However, there are strong indicators suggesting that cloud computing will reach a similar level of popularity as cloud storage within a few years.</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses.</description></item><item><title>Dual Core, Quad Core, Up to 64 Core Managed Dedicated Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</guid><description>The race for faster processors has shifted its focus. Instead of increasing clock speeds, the industry is now prioritizing multi-core and multi-processor designs to improve performance.
The good news is that there are affordable options for powerful processing, including managed dedicated servers with excellent support.
Entry-level systems typically feature dual-core processors. For increased power, users can opt for quad-core or hexa-core (6 cores) configurations. For even greater performance, dual or quad-processor dedicated servers are available.</description></item><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market.</description></item><item><title>Low Cost Cloud Backup For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 00:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-cloud-backup-for-business/</guid><description>Lots of companies are exploring cloud services these days. While not every business needs its own data center or web servers, every business has critical data they can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose. Imagine a natural disaster like a tornado or fire destroying all your physical and digital files – the impact would be significant. Even something as common as a hard drive crash can be devastating.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple and cost-effective way to protect your business without complex outsourcing contracts: backing up your important files to a secure offsite location.</description></item><item><title>From CAPEX to OPEX In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-capex-to-opex-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The cost model for Information Technology is shifting from capital expenditure (CAPEX) to operational expenditure (OPEX) due to economic uncertainty and the rise of cloud computing.
Traditionally, businesses invested heavily in on-site data centers with servers, storage, and network equipment. This approach, while effective, requires substantial upfront capital and incurs ongoing operational costs like electricity, bandwidth, staffing, and software maintenance.
While this capital-intensive model was the norm, the economic downturn made businesses more cost-conscious.</description></item><item><title>Internet Service Without The Outages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 06:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-service-without-the-outages/</guid><description>The internet has become an essential tool for accessing information, connecting with others, and conducting business. It offers a vast repository of knowledge, real-time services, and entertainment options. However, internet outages can occur, causing frustration and disruption.
While complete internet blackouts are rare, local outages can still happen. These outages can be planned maintenance, accidental disruptions, or natural disasters. For businesses and individuals who rely heavily on the internet, these outages can be costly.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Recovery Mirrors Your Servers and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</guid><description>Protecting valuable assets is crucial for any business, which is why backups are essential. However, backups alone can&amp;rsquo;t protect against major disasters that could damage physical infrastructure.
Having a backup located in the company safe won&amp;rsquo;t help if a catastrophic event destroys the entire building. Since many businesses heavily rely on computer systems, replicating the entire IT infrastructure is a wise decision.
You might be wondering about the cost of duplicating server rooms, applications, and data.</description></item><item><title>Green Hosting Reduces Environmental Issues</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-hosting-reduces-environmental-issues/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 04:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-hosting-reduces-environmental-issues/</guid><description>World Environment Day encourages us to consider how we can lessen our environmental footprint. While this often evokes thoughts of making sacrifices, what if there were ways to gain advantages while simultaneously addressing environmental concerns? Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be an appealing approach?
Getting more for less is universally desired, and thankfully, we can achieve this by being discerning about the companies we support. Choosing environmentally conscious businesses doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily equate to higher costs; in fact, many responsible companies share the cost savings from their efficient practices with their customers.</description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged.</description></item><item><title>Can You Benefit From New Cloud Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 01:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-benefit-from-new-cloud-networks/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve been reading about cloud computing and might be wondering if it can help your small or medium-sized business (SMB). While it seems like cloud services are designed for large corporations, they offer significant potential for businesses of all sizes.
The cloud can be even more beneficial for SMBs because it levels the playing field. Large companies often have the resources to build their own private clouds, while smaller companies may struggle with the cost and staffing required for such an undertaking.</description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers.</description></item><item><title>Transforming the WAN Into The Smart WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</guid><description>People tend to think of WAN connections as basic channels for data, similar to how Senator Ted Stevens once described the internet. However, with the shift from on-site data centers to cloud-based systems, VoIP, and video streaming, our needs have outgrown this simple model. This is where the concept of a Smart WAN comes into play.
Instead of treating all data equally, a Smart WAN prioritizes different types of data through a system called Class of Service (CoS).</description></item><item><title>Make Mine Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-mine-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/make-mine-green-hosting/</guid><description>Two major challenges impacting data centers today are power demands and the associated costs, limiting the expansion of online services. Large server farms are often located not for staff convenience, but near ample power sources due to their significant energy consumption.
Information technology requires vast amounts of electricity, particularly for processing large datasets at high speeds. Servers generate significant heat, demanding substantial cooling systems, which further increase energy consumption. Data centers, with their massive energy needs, face challenges as we grapple with power generation limitations.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections.</description></item><item><title>Scalable Cloud Servers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</guid><description>Considering a move to cloud servers but feeling apprehensive about the cost and complexity? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses desire the flexibility and cost-effectiveness of cloud computing without needing excessive processing power.
Scalable cloud servers are a great option for businesses of all sizes, offering pay-as-you-go pricing and easy scalability. Before committing to a major provider, explore options specifically designed for small to medium-sized businesses. These services often provide per-second billing, eliminating wasted expenses, along with free setup and no contractual obligations.</description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions.</description></item><item><title>Tech’s Moo Poo Buy Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-s-moo-poo-buy-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-s-moo-poo-buy-plan/</guid><description>The internet&amp;rsquo;s increasing energy consumption is rapidly becoming a concern. Data centers, responsible for powering websites and online services, are constantly seeking new energy sources as traditional ones dwindle. Surprisingly, livestock, particularly cows, might be the answer.
While it may sound amusing, cow manure possesses the potential to power the internet. Large-scale server farms require substantial energy, and a new approach involves harnessing the bio-energy from animal waste. This process, known as anaerobic digestion, converts manure into biogas, primarily methane, which can then power turbines to generate electricity.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet and Colocation For Texas Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</guid><description>Texas is known for its expansive size, thriving businesses, massive data generation, and a critical need for extensive bandwidth. Alpheus, a Texas-based telecommunications company, is acutely aware of these needs and caters its services to businesses across various sectors including finance, energy, government, healthcare, IT, legal, and media.
Headquartered in Houston, Alpheus boasts a robust fiber optic network that interconnects major Texan cities like Dallas, Fort Worth, Waco, Bryan, Austin, San Antonio, Laredo, McAllen, Harlingen, Corpus Christi, Victoria, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery.</description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user.</description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations.</description></item><item><title>What is Cloud Computing For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is gaining popularity, but what does it mean for businesses beyond giants like Amazon and Google? Essentially, the cloud isn&amp;rsquo;t a new invention. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of structuring technology, similar to the public telephone system, where a central provider manages the complex infrastructure (&amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo;), and users access services through simple devices (&amp;ldquo;thin clients&amp;rdquo;).
This centralized system, known as multi-tenancy, allows numerous users to access resources seemingly simultaneously while remaining isolated.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times.</description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Puts Your Complete Office In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:47:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>You might be interested in cloud services, but the process of ordering and integrating them can be overwhelming. Now, a new solution offers a comprehensive bundle of IT services tailored for small businesses at an affordable price.
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
Small businesses often don&amp;rsquo;t need or can&amp;rsquo;t afford large-scale IT infrastructure. Expensive VoIP phone systems and on-site data centers are impractical for companies with limited staff and resources. While cost savings were previously linked to scale, hosted solutions have revolutionized this.</description></item></channel></rss>