<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chocolate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chocolate/</link><description>Recent content in Chocolate on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chocolate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chocolate is considered the most popular indulgence product in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesians are increasingly understanding the advantages of moderate chocolate consumption, leading to consistent purchases for snacking and special occasions. This trend fueled growth in chocolate confectionery sales in 2016, according to research firm Euromonitor. The company predicts chocolate confectionery will remain the preferred treat for Indonesian consumers of all ages.
Ceres PT, a major player in the Indonesian chocolate market, held a commanding 52% market share in 2016. Euromonitor attributes this success to the company&amp;rsquo;s strong brand reputation, diverse product range, and competitive pricing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During the festive season, you can find exclusive Ferrero Rocher pralines at Pasticceria Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>Celebrities Qi Yu Wu and Joanne Peh are pictured at the event.
Ferrero Rocher has opened its first Southeast Asia store, Pasticceria Ferrero, at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Wisma Atria on Orchard Road. This unique boutique is the only one in the world and will be open for the holiday season.
A sneak peek before the official opening.
The shop offers a unique experience, allowing customers to personalize chocolate boxes with limited-edition Ferrero pralines available only during this special time of year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In India, Swarn Amrit produces sweets made with edible gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</guid><description>Swarn Amrit, a high-end confectionery brand, has introduced a first-of-its-kind product line in India: sweets made with real 24-karat gold. The company believes that gold symbolizes purity, prosperity, and good fortune, and even suggests it may promote longevity.
Swarn Kalash
The new collection features a variety of sweets with names like kalash, mukhi, madhu, yukti, and katak, representing both Indian and international flavors. For example, Swarn Mukhi layers cashews, almonds, pistachios, and gold, while Swarn Madhu combines Belgian chocolate with gold, and Swarn Katak adds a touch of gold to Turkish delight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>