<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WEF on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wef/</link><description>Recent content in WEF on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The World Economic Forum introduces its inaugural online leadership module for professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</guid><description>Professionals can now register for the World Economic Forum&amp;rsquo;s first online leadership program, Global Information Technology Outlook. This six-week module, created for senior executives and fast-track leadership programs, offers a comprehensive overview of important new technologies transforming industries and society.
Professor Klaus Schwab, Founder and Executive Chairman of the World Economic Forum, highlighted the challenges leaders face understanding the increasingly complex and unpredictable world, largely due to rapid technological advancements. He stated that the Forum Academy module addresses this by giving leaders a better grasp of ongoing information technology transformations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-economic-forum-introduces-its-inaugural-online-leadership-module-for-professionals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore ranks second in global competitiveness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 22:57:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</guid><description>The World Economic Forum (WEF) recently published its Global Competitiveness Report for 2016.
The report determined that a global trend of decreasing openness in countries is negatively impacting growth and prosperity. Financial stimuli like quantitative easing are insufficient for sustained growth and must be paired with reforms that bolster competitiveness. For emerging markets, modernizing business practices and investing in innovation are now just as crucial as infrastructure, skilled workforces, and efficient markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranks-second-in-global-competitiveness/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>