<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vietnam on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vietnam/</link><description>Recent content in Vietnam on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vietnam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vietnam receives report card from World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-receives-report-card-from-world-bank/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economy shows resilience due to strong domestic demand and export-focused manufacturing, as highlighted in the World Bank&amp;rsquo;s recent Taking Stock report. The country&amp;rsquo;s mid-term economic outlook appears positive, with GDP projected to grow by 6% in the current year.
The report, a semi-annual assessment of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s economic performance, notes that economic growth decelerated to 5.9% in the first nine months of the year. This slowdown is largely attributed to a severe drought that hampered agricultural output, reduced oil production, and weakened external demand.</description></item><item><title>Azerai offers affordable luxury in Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 18:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-offers-affordable-luxury-in-vietnam/</guid><description>Azerai invites discerning travelers to experience attainable luxury in Vietnam through a collection of acclaimed boutique resorts. Founded by Adrian Zecha, the visionary behind Aman Resorts, the Azerai concept is already present in the culturally rich destinations of Ke Ga, Can Tho, and Hue.
Source: Azerai. Each Azerai resort is designed to envelop guests in sophisticated, understated luxury.
Every Azerai resort aims to immerse guests in refined yet understated luxury. At Azerai Can Tho, this translates to seclusion within low-rise structures on a private islet in the Hau River, reachable only by boat.</description></item><item><title>Hoi An has the highest number of top hotels according to TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Hanoi and Hoi An are home to Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated hotels. In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized ten top hotels in Vietnam, with three located in Hanoi and three in Hoi An. An additional two hotels in the top 25 are also situated in Hoi An.
The top ten hotels are:
Source: TripAdvisor. The Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel.
Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel: Garnering 1,832 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; ratings out of 2,064 total reviews.</description></item><item><title>Azerai reveals special promotions for Chinese New Year in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</guid><description>Source: Azerai. Exterior, Hue. Constructed in 1930 as the residence of the French Resident Superieure, this colonial mansion forms the hotel&amp;rsquo;s heart. The mansion&amp;rsquo;s noticeable facade, characterized by its elongated horizontal lines and nautical motifs, is a testament to Art Deco architectural style. Its two harmonious wings, home to a vast tropical garden and a saltwater pool, were constructed in 2005, reflecting a modern take on Art Deco.
Azerai has unveiled special offers and activities for Chinese New Year at its Vietnamese properties.</description></item><item><title>Vietnam, a country experiencing growth, is attracting investments from various regions, according to UOB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 07:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietnam-a-country-experiencing-growth-is-attracting-investments-from-various-regions-according-to-uob/</guid><description>A recent study by the United Overseas Bank (UOB) suggests Vietnam will experience a surge in investments from nearby countries like Malaysia, Thailand, and Singapore over the next three to five years.
The 2016 UOB Asian Enterprise Survey found that Vietnam is a top expansion target for businesses in Malaysia (38%), Thailand (35%), and Singapore (29%). These nations are among the 28% of surveyed enterprises that selected Vietnam as their preferred expansion destination within the next three to five years.</description></item><item><title>The IMF has finished its 2017 Article IV consultation with Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 05:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imf-has-finished-its-2017-article-iv-consultation-with-vietnam/</guid><description>The International Monetary Fund (IMF) recently finished its regular economic review of Vietnam, finding that the country&amp;rsquo;s economy remains in good shape, supported by strong underlying economic conditions. Despite a slowdown in 2016 to 6.2% growth due to agricultural challenges from drought and saltwater intrusion, as well as reduced oil production, Vietnam’s economy has shown resilience.
While the oil sector continued to struggle in early 2017, strong manufacturing and foreign direct investment, healthy domestic demand, and a resurgence in agriculture are driving overall economic momentum.</description></item><item><title>The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay offers a competitive advantage for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-offers-a-competitive-advantage-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay website. The Grand Ballroom, theatre-style.
The JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, a premier five-star resort in Phu Quoc and a flagship property in Vietnam, provides a range of meeting spaces suitable for various event sizes.
The resort is committed to crafting unforgettable events and immersive experiences for all attendees. Phu Quoc is an up-and-coming destination, now linked by direct flights to major cities like Ho Chi Minh City, Bangkok, and Guangzhou.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels has launched its inaugural five-star international hotel in Vung Tau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 16:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-has-launched-its-inaugural-five-star-international-hotel-in-vung-tau/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The
Pullman Vung Tau.
AccorHotels is introducing the Pullman Vung Tau, the first international five-star hotel in this coastal city just a 90-minute drive from Ho Chi Minh City.
The Pullman Vung Tau offers views of both Back Beach and Front Beach and boasts the largest meeting facilities in Southern Vietnam, making it perfect for business travelers looking for a quick escape from Ho Chi Minh City.</description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge.</description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>Emperor Cruises provides day cruises in Nha Trang</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emperor-cruises-provides-day-cruises-in-nha-trang/</guid><description>Source: Emperor Cruises website.
Emperor Cruises is introducing day cruises departing from the coastal city of Nha Trang, with plans to offer overnight trips in the future. The company highlights Nha Trang&amp;rsquo;s expanding range of attractions, including the Vinpearl Golf Club and upscale hotels like the Intercontinental, Best Western Premier, and Amanoi.
&amp;ldquo;Emperor Cruises wants to provide tourists with the opportunity to admire the sunset, enjoy cocktails, and savor romantic dinners while cruising on one of the world&amp;rsquo;s 29 most beautiful bays,&amp;rdquo; stated Allister Esguerra, Branch Director of Emperor Cruises.</description></item><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp; Spa is offering meeting packages for the year 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 06:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-danang-resort-spa-is-offering-meeting-packages-for-the-year-2017/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa. Executive team members at Hyatt Regegncy Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa will help event planners make any meeting a success.
Located on Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Hoi An coastline and close to Danang, the Hyatt Regency Danang Resort &amp;amp; Spa has announced new meeting packages for 2017.
The resort offers a wide range of event and meeting spaces, both indoors and outdoors on the beachfront. These venues can accommodate up to 250 people.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route.</description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities.</description></item><item><title>Indulge in a luxurious 20 Carat Gold Escape with JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay and Maserati</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 14:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay.
The lobby lounge.
Upon arrival at the sports university-themed JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, guests will be greeted with a luxurious Maserati transfer*. Building on the success of the resort&amp;rsquo;s previous collaboration showcasing DMC&amp;rsquo;s SS2017 womenswear collection, this partnership with Maserati aims to captivate those passionate about sports and automobiles.
Ty Collins, General Manager at JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, states, &amp;ldquo;This collaboration amplifies the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to offering design-focused experiences.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas in Vietnam have been recognized with accolades from TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The master bedroom of an oceanfront three-bedroom villa at Six Senses Con Dao, Vietnam.
TripAdvisor, a leading travel platform, has revealed its highest-rated properties for the fourteenth consecutive year. These rankings are determined by analyzing user reviews and feedback from travelers globally over the past year. Three properties - Evason Ana Mandara, Six Senses Ninh Van Bay, and Six Senses Con Dao - have earned the prestigious Traveler’s Choice award, signifying TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s highest honor.</description></item></channel></rss>