<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Traditional on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traditional/</link><description>Recent content in Traditional on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 03:24:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traditional/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blum &amp; Co transforms the cheongsam into stylish workwear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 03:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blum-co-transforms-the-cheongsam-into-stylish-workwear/</guid><description>Blum, a Singaporean fashion brand, has launched a new line of workwear inspired by the traditional cheongsam.
Source: Blum &amp;amp; Co.
Emerging in the 1920s as a symbol of women&amp;rsquo;s liberation, the cheongsam has undergone stylistic changes throughout the years. Originally a loose-fitting, full-sleeved dress, it evolved to feature a slimmer silhouette with shorter hemlines and a side slit. Despite being prohibited in mainland China following the communist revolution, the cheongsam remained popular in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>The Avex Group introduces high-quality hemp fabric as part of the majotae brand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</guid><description>Avex Group Holdings, a Japanese entertainment company, has introduced &amp;ldquo;majotae,&amp;rdquo; a fabric brand reviving taima-fu, a traditional natural hemp fabric.
The photo above features (from left) Shigekazu Takeuchi, Representative Director of Avex Group Holdings; Masato Matsuura, CEO of Avex Group Holdings; Shinichiro Yoshida, natural fabric expert; Genbei Yamaguchi, obi artisan; and Hiroshi Onishi, CEO of Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings. They were attending the opening reception for the &amp;ldquo;majotae: The Forgotten Fabric&amp;rdquo; exhibition at Daikanyama Hillside Forum on October 22, 2014, in Tokyo, Japan.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes.</description></item></channel></rss>