<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Long Distance Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-service/</link><description>Recent content in Long Distance Service on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call China From Your Car</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-china-from-your-car/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:56:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-china-from-your-car/</guid><description>Imagine needing to make an international call while away from home. With the TEL3 app, you can call internationally from your cell phone for incredibly low rates, like a penny per minute to China.
You might be wondering if international calls can be cheaper on a cell phone than a landline. With the right service, they absolutely can be. TEL3Advantage is an add-on service that lets you make inexpensive international calls from any phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-china-from-your-car/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-china-from-your-car/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>