<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Citrus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/citrus/</link><description>Recent content in Citrus on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/citrus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Immerse yourself in the holiday spirit with the Holiday fragrance by House of Sillage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</guid><description>Source: House of Sillage.
House of Sillage, a high-end perfume maker, introduces its Holiday fragrance for the Christmas season. The perfume features a blend of mandarin, peach, and vetiver, creating a festive aroma.
The design of the fragrance bottle draws inspiration from the illuminated Rockefeller Center Christmas tree in New York City. Its snow globe cap, crafted from 18-karat gold and white gold, depicts a scene of falling snow. The floral and citrus perfume is housed in a hand-polished glass bottle with an ombre lacquer finish.</description></item><item><title>The benefits of pomelo for your health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-pomelo-for-your-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-pomelo-for-your-health/</guid><description>Source: Chulalongkorn University website.
Research by Dr. Sirichai Adisakwattana, an Associate Professor at Chulalongkorn University in Thailand, suggests that concentrated extracts from pomelo fruit possess antioxidant properties, which contribute to overall health, and can reduce fat levels.
To reach these findings, Dr. Adisakwattana created powdered concentrates from six varieties of pomelo. His analysis showed that these concentrates could lower both cholesterol and blood lipid levels.
However, due to the fruit&amp;rsquo;s natural sugar content, the university recommends limiting consumption to a small portion each day.</description></item></channel></rss>