<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tech on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tech/</link><description>Recent content in Tech on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Robert Walters believes that it is possible to both attract and retain tech talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-believes-that-it-is-possible-to-both-attract-and-retain-tech-talent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-believes-that-it-is-possible-to-both-attract-and-retain-tech-talent/</guid><description>A recent survey by Robert Walters reveals that the tech talent shortage is significantly impacting businesses, with 70% of hiring managers requiring three months or more to fill tech positions. This shortage is hindering product development speed and highlighting the urgent need for effective talent acquisition strategies.
The survey, conducted across Southeast Asia, emphasizes the difficulty of finding skilled tech professionals, despite recognizing its importance for business success. In response, Robert Walters has created a guidebook, &amp;ldquo;5 Lessons in Tackling the Tech Talent Shortage,&amp;rdquo; offering valuable insights from industry experts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-believes-that-it-is-possible-to-both-attract-and-retain-tech-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-believes-that-it-is-possible-to-both-attract-and-retain-tech-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check out Shopee Malaysia's Christmas gift ideas!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:02:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, offers a convenient way to shop for Christmas.
Here are some gift ideas available in Malaysia:
Stay Connected
[Image of PINENG PN966 power bank]
This power bank, available in blue and green, ensures you stay connected all day.
[Buy now]
Capture the Moment
[Image of OPPO F1s phone]
The OPPO F1s, dubbed &amp;ldquo;The Selfie Expert,&amp;rdquo; boasts a 5.5&amp;quot; display with 1,280 x 720 pixels resolution, a 13-megapixel rear camera, and a 16-megapixel front camera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-out-shopee-malaysia-s-christmas-gift-ideas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you have digital or tech skills, chances are your salary is above average</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</guid><description>Source: Willis Towers Watson. Report cover.
The financial sector, particularly in digital roles, is experiencing salary stability due to a high demand for tech professionals. This trend persists despite overall economic weakness in other industries, including banking, according to the global advisory firm Willis Towers Watson.
Businesses across all sectors are becoming progressively reliant on data and technology, and the banking industry is no exception. This shift has resulted in a talent competition where technological expertise is more valuable than financial background...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new tech and innovation business club has been introduced in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</guid><description>SPECTRUM, a curated tech and innovation business club, has been established in Singapore. The organization, co-founded by Cheryl Lee and Shirley Crystal Chua, aims to create a globally connected ecosystem for businesses seeking to expand into Asia by providing expert advice, necessary resources, and strategic networks.
SPECTRUM has partnered with Golden Equator and Mistletoe to form a collaborative network of seven strategic groups: innovators, learning institutions, executors, backers, enablers, government agencies, and ecosystem builders and partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-tech-and-innovation-business-club-has-been-introduced-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore Computer Society reveals the top 10 tech companies to work for in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</guid><description>The Singapore Computer Society (SCS), the largest professional organization for infocomm and digital media professionals in the country, has revealed the winners of its &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Company to Work For Award&amp;rdquo;. The announcement took place at the SCS&amp;rsquo;s annual Tech3 Forum conference.
This award recognizes four organizations out of the ten &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Companies to Work For&amp;rdquo; as overall winners. These companies have developed innovative practices and demonstrated workplace excellence within the infocomm and digital media (ICM) industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore companies are considering hiring senior technology professionals to address the shortage of talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</guid><description>Despite job market growth, a 2017 survey by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SiTF) reveals that the infocommunications (ICM) industry struggles to find talent with the right IT and business skills.
The survey of 181 companies found that 75% consider recruiting suitable talent their biggest challenge. This problem particularly affects startups (91%), followed by small and medium enterprises (SMEs) at 76% and multinational corporations (MNCs) at 75%.
Source: SITF. The talent situation in Singapore for ICM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>