<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/technology/</link><description>Recent content in Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking.</description></item><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol.</description></item><item><title>Dial-Up is Alive and Kicking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dial-up-is-alive-and-kicking/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of high-speed internet, it might seem strange to talk about dial-up. Many people consider it outdated technology.
However, dial-up internet access is still relevant. Millions of people still use and appreciate it for browsing the internet and checking emails. This &amp;ldquo;outdated&amp;rdquo; technology remains profitable.
One of the main advantages of dial-up is its affordability. Unlimited access is available for a low monthly cost, making it a budget-friendly option compared to DSL or cable internet.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Comparison Shopping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 17:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-comparison-shopping/</guid><description>Voice over IP (VoIP) is becoming increasingly popular for both home and business phone service. With this new technology rapidly evolving, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to keep up with the latest companies and deals. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to switch to VoIP or simply want a better deal, you need a way to compare your options. That&amp;rsquo;s where a comparison shopping service comes in handy, allowing you to easily evaluate available services and choose the best fit.</description></item><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own Private Cloud Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 03:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-private-cloud-storage/</guid><description>Lots of small and midsize businesses are using cloud storage, particularly for disaster recovery. However, local storage is still necessary. While Storage Attached Networks (SANs) are a common solution, they&amp;rsquo;re expensive and complex. A simpler option exists.
Introducing Drobo, an advanced hard disk storage solution that&amp;rsquo;s surprisingly easy to use. It works with standard 3.5&amp;quot; SATA drives of any capacity, resembling a straightforward multi-bay drive enclosure. Adding or removing drives, even swapping a 1 TB for a 2 TB, is always possible.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.</description></item><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region.</description></item><item><title>I Know Where You Took Your Pictures Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 14:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-know-where-you-took-your-pictures-last-summer/</guid><description>Eye-Fi, the WiFi-enabled memory card, has introduced a new feature: location tagging. Their latest product, Eye-Fi Explore, automatically adds geotags to photos as you take them.
You might be surprised to learn that they haven&amp;rsquo;t actually included a GPS receiver in the small SD card. Instead, it uses a system that determines location based on known WiFi hotspots. This method covers a significant portion of the U.S. population and major metropolitan areas in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Your Next Battery Is a Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</guid><description>Benjamin Franklin&amp;rsquo;s experiment with capturing electricity in Leyden Jars, glass jars with foil conductors that store electric charge, laid the groundwork for modern battery technology.
Today, researchers have developed ultracapacitors, like the Graphene Ultracapacitor from the University of Texas at Austin, which are essentially very small but powerful capacitors. These ultracapacitors use nanometer-thin dielectrics instead of bulky glass jars, allowing them to achieve farad-level capacitance, much higher than the picofarad capacity of a Leyden Jar.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>Contract Expiration Means Opportunity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-expiration-means-opportunity/</guid><description>Business telecom services often come with fixed-price contracts lasting 1 to 3 years, providing price stability but limited cost-saving opportunities. However, the fear of potential price increases upon contract renewal is often overstated. In many cases, businesses can find better deals by exploring alternative providers.
The misconception about limited options arises from a perceived lack of competition. While you may have negotiated what seemed like the best price at the time, there are often numerous competitive service providers not listed in traditional directories.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Duet Combines Voice and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses need both phone and internet services. Their phone systems often start small and expand over time, adding lines as needed. Similarly, internet service might begin with dial-up, transition to DSL, and eventually upgrade to dedicated connections for better reliability.
This piecemeal approach often leads to businesses overspending on telecommunications. Optimizing these systems could potentially cut costs by up to 50%.
The key to saving money is bundling services.</description></item><item><title>Drobo Mr. Storage Roboto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</guid><description>Hard drive space disappears faster than you can imagine, especially with large digital media files like photos and videos. Even large hard drives fill up quickly.
While upgrading or adding hard drives seems like a solution, it creates new problems like managing backups and worrying about data loss from hard drive failures. These tasks can be time-consuming, especially for professionals working with large files. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like you need a personal assistant to manage it all.</description></item><item><title>Is Broadband the Next Oil?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</guid><description>Customers are enraged by the escalating prices of gasoline and heating oil. The cost of oil seems to be limitless, as traders frantically outbid each other for future contracts. It feels like a never-ending cycle of increasing prices. And now, prepare yourself: the next crisis might involve broadband internet.
You might be wondering how broadband, especially internet broadband, could resemble oil. Oil is a natural resource with over a century of extraction history, while broadband is a relatively recent technological invention.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Is The New Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-is-the-new-infrastructure/</guid><description>The current focus on infrastructure often overlooks a critical element: fiber optic broadband. While roads, bridges, and utilities are essential, fiber optic networks are the backbone of the 21st-century economy. Just as electricity revolutionized the 20th century, fiber optics will define this one.
We&amp;rsquo;ve outgrown the limitations of traditional wireline systems. Fiber optic technology, with its capacity for high bandwidth, is the only way to meet the growing demand for data-intensive applications.</description></item><item><title>Smoothstone IP Communications offers Polished VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 21:56:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-ip-communications-offers-polished-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses usually don&amp;rsquo;t spend much effort on their telecommunication systems, often starting with basic necessities like desk phones, internet service, and maybe a simple VoIP system. It&amp;rsquo;s manageable for the owner or an office manager. However, as these businesses grow, their communication needs change. Suddenly, managing communication among numerous employees and locations becomes challenging. Reaching colleagues becomes difficult, and clients experience poor connection quality, leading to apologies. This situation calls for a &amp;ldquo;forklift upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?</description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology.</description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission.</description></item><item><title>What’s Coming with Snow Leopard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-coming-with-snow-leopard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-coming-with-snow-leopard/</guid><description>In the coming month, Apple is set to launch a substantial update for its Mac OS X operating system. This upgrade, priced at a reasonable $29 from the existing Leopard OS X 10.5, promises a range of new features. But what exactly justifies the cost?
Personally, I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to upgrade operating systems beyond the minor updates that are provided automatically for free. Major upgrades often come at a cost and while they typically offer enhanced functionality, they also demand more processing power and memory.</description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price.</description></item><item><title>Visible Means of IT Support</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visible-means-of-it-support/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visible-means-of-it-support/</guid><description>When technology troubles strike, large companies have IT departments on speed dial, but what about independent professionals and smaller businesses? Managing computer issues isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple without a dedicated tech team.
Many individuals and small businesses handle their own computer maintenance, often with limited expertise. While tech-savvy users might possess deep system knowledge and meticulously update their software, others only react when problems arise. This often leads to confusion and frantic trips to the computer store.</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Free Cell Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You were wise to get your new, top-of-the-line smartphone for free when you signed up for service. You understand that service plan costs are consistent, and it&amp;rsquo;s the phone&amp;rsquo;s price that fluctuates.
Now that your contract is up, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to upgrade. As you search for another discounted or free phone, you might wonder what to do with your old one.
Many people keep their old phones, thinking they might be helpful someday.</description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections.</description></item><item><title>Internet to Soothe the Savage Flyer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-to-soothe-the-savage-flyer/</guid><description>Is there anything more frustrating than squeezing into the last seat on a long flight, stuck between grumpy passengers with hours to kill? You yearn for the distraction of emails or online games, but alas, internet access in the air seems like a distant dream.
Fear not, weary traveler! The wait for in-flight WiFi is almost over. Major airlines are preparing to offer internet access on their planes, but it comes at a price.</description></item><item><title>Manage Your Cables Before They Manage You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/manage-your-cables-before-they-manage-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/manage-your-cables-before-they-manage-you/</guid><description>Network cabling can quickly become chaotic and overwhelming, much like weeds taking over an empty lot. Unorganized wiring, often referred to as a &amp;ldquo;rat&amp;rsquo;s nest,&amp;rdquo; is a common problem that creates confusion and makes troubleshooting difficult.
The solution to this problem is simple: organization. While organizing existing cables can be tedious, it is essential and best done sooner rather than later. Designing a structured cabling system from the outset is the most effective approach.</description></item><item><title>Telepresence as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 13:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepresence-as-a-service/</guid><description>Think of telepresence as the next step beyond the telephone and television: instead of sending your voice or an image, you&amp;rsquo;re projecting your presence across distances. While not as futuristic as Star Trek&amp;rsquo;s transporter, it&amp;rsquo;s a powerful tool for businesses, especially now that companies like Cisco and AT&amp;amp;T offer it as a more accessible service. This shift could mark a significant increase in the use of virtual meetings.
Telepresence evolved from video conferencing, which a decade ago was clunky and unreliable.</description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers.</description></item><item><title>The BlackBerry Storm Just Blew In at a Lower Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:51:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on getting a BlackBerry Storm in stores. You can buy one online from Cell Phone Plans Finder with free shipping.
Although I can&amp;rsquo;t disclose the price here, you can easily find it on the cellphone special offers page. You can then order the phone with your preferred Verizon Wireless service package, all delivered directly to you without shipping fees.
The BlackBerry Storm 9530 Black, the first BlackBerry with a touch keyboard, offers a unique experience for those accustomed to physical keys.</description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers.</description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>Cash In Old Gadgets To Buy New Gadgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</guid><description>The holiday shopping season is here, and with it comes the temptation of new electronics and gadgets. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a time to be mindful of spending. One smart solution is to turn your old electronics into cash to fund those new purchases.
It&amp;rsquo;s common to have unused electronics lying around. We hesitate to discard them because they still hold value. This unused tech represents a potential savings account that can help you afford those tempting new gadgets.</description></item><item><title>Take Your Office PC With You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</guid><description>Mobile professionals often rely on their laptops but might find themselves needing files left on their office desktops. Traveling long distances back for these files isn&amp;rsquo;t always feasible.
Imagine accessing your office desktop from anywhere, anytime. This eliminates the worry of having the right files and removes the need for duplicates. Your laptop and a special application are all you need to make any computer your office computer.
GoToMyPC is a remote access software, or KVM application, that allows this.</description></item><item><title>Cheapest T1 On The Block</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheapest-t1-on-the-block/</guid><description>You might think T1 lines are too expensive for your business, but that&amp;rsquo;s not always true. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Originally, T1 lines weren&amp;rsquo;t meant for businesses. Telephone companies developed this &amp;ldquo;T-carrier&amp;rdquo; technology for themselves. However, as the internet grew, so did the need for robust digital communication, which T-carrier services like T1 and DS3 could provide.
Initially, only large corporations used T1 lines because they could easily afford the high cost.</description></item><item><title>SITEX 2016 guarantees an immersive and educational experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sitex-2016-guarantees-an-immersive-and-educational-experience/</guid><description>Source: SITEX website. Scene from SITEX 2015.
SITEX, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s yearly consumer technology showcase, aims to bridge the gap between individuals and technology. This year, it promises an elevated experience with new interactive activities like a technology-infused dance competition, a dedicated space for children&amp;rsquo;s technology (IMDA Pixel Labs), displays of intelligent systems from NTU, and the SITEX Innovation Alley presented by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SITF). These additions are designed to educate, entertain, and captivate visitors.</description></item><item><title>It’s a Camera and a Movie Theater</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-a-camera-and-a-movie-theater/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 12:04:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-a-camera-and-a-movie-theater/</guid><description>Nikon has created a groundbreaking product, the Coolpix S1000pj, that redefines digital cameras. What sets this pocket-sized device apart is its integrated projector, making it more than just a camera; it&amp;rsquo;s a portable theater.
This innovation allows users to capture photos and videos and project them onto any flat surface, with sizes reaching up to 40 inches. While a dim environment optimizes viewing, the ability to share visuals instantly is game-changing.</description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness.</description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment.</description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes.</description></item><item><title>Aggressive Passive Optical Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 02:09:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aggressive-passive-optical-networking/</guid><description>Passive Optical Networking (PON) is becoming a budget-friendly way to bring fiber optic connections directly to homes and businesses. This technology is advancing so rapidly that new PON standards are being surpassed almost as quickly as they are established. For instance, Ericsson is currently showcasing 10 Gbps GPON. Will we soon see speeds of 100 Gbps or even terabits per second?
While it&amp;rsquo;s not happening overnight, bandwidth requirements are definitely increasing for both home and business wide area networks (WANs).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>Blog Action Day For A Less Toasty Tomorrow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</guid><description>Is it hot in there, or is it just me? Hold on to your hats, folks, because global warming is here, and it&amp;rsquo;s not waiting for anyone. We&amp;rsquo;re already seeing the effects, despite what some people might believe. Forget those freezing Midwest winters; the Arctic Ocean is melting at an alarming rate, opening up shipping routes and sparking international interest in its resources. It seems like everywhere you look, there&amp;rsquo;s evidence of climate change, from California wildfires to polar bears struggling to stay afloat.</description></item><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers.</description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP).</description></item><item><title>Sports Camera Lets You Web The Surf</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sports-camera-lets-you-web-the-surf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 19:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sports-camera-lets-you-web-the-surf/</guid><description>Have you ever thought about filming your surfing adventures and sharing them online?
One of the easiest ways to do this is by using a GoPro Surf HERO waterproof digital camera. This camera boasts an ultra-wide 170-degree lens and can be mounted on your surfboard&amp;rsquo;s deck. Alternatively, you can use the stick-on baseplate. Its wide-angle lens can easily fit a 6'2&amp;quot; surfer riding a 6-foot surfboard within the frame.
Simply press the shutter button before paddling out, and the camera will record up to 56 minutes of high-quality video.</description></item><item><title>The implementation of smart technologies is increasing revenues by up to 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</guid><description>A global Avanade study, involving Australian executives, business unit leaders, and IT decision-makers, reveals that a majority of business leaders are already investing in and seeing positive results from incorporating smart technologies in their workplaces. A key motivator is the potential for increased revenue, with business and IT leaders projecting up to a 33% revenue boost from these technologies within the next five years. Furthermore, companies anticipate retraining existing employees, generating new roles, and restructuring their organizations as they predict the repurposing of up to 20% of current roles.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson has unveiled its 10 top consumer trends for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson website. Infographic summarizing the 10 hot consumer trends for 2019.
· Consumers anticipate that smart speakers will participate in family disagreements, much like human family members do.
· Users of virtual assistants believe that devices capable of understanding human emotions will be commonplace within the next three years.
· Users of augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) express a desire for interactive, virtual assistance with practical tasks such as cooking or completing repairs.</description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily.</description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses.</description></item><item><title>Tech Saturday at Suntec will demonstrate the future direction of consumer technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-saturday-at-suntec-will-demonstrate-the-future-direction-of-consumer-technology/</guid><description>Source: Smart Nation website.
Tech Saturday is a public carnival presented by the Infocomm Development Authority of Singapore to demonstrate the power of technology. In addition to tech exhibitions, visitors can participate in interactive &amp;ldquo;Worksheds.&amp;rdquo;
Located throughout the carnival, these booths provide hands-on technology workshops. With options ranging from circuits to 3D printing, all workshops are free. While pre-registration is closed, same-day registration is available at counters near the Worksheds.</description></item><item><title>Goodbye Frame Relay, Hello MPLS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodbye-frame-relay-hello-mpls/</guid><description>Managing communication across multiple business locations can be challenging. While private lines offer a solution, their cost increases with the number of locations. Frame Relay, a private network solution, gained popularity for its reliability, security, and affordability. However, MPLS networks have emerged as a newer technology offering higher bandwidth and lower costs.
Frame Relay bridges the gap between public switched telephone networks and dedicated private lines. It replaces physical wires with virtual circuits, eliminating the need for dedicated circuits that incur costs regardless of usage.</description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies.</description></item><item><title>According to BrandZ, Tencent is currently the most valuable brand in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</guid><description>Tencent, a Chinese company, has become the most valuable brand in Asia and the fastest growing brand globally, achieving a brand value of US$54 billion in the 2014 BrandZ Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands ranking. This success propelled Tencent to the 14th spot globally, surpassing China Mobile.
Source: Millward Brown website.
Deepender Rana, Managing Director of Millward Brown Greater China, emphasized the significance of a market-driven Chinese brand like Tencent taking the lead over state-owned enterprises.</description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>White Spaces Debate Outs Wireless Mics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/white-spaces-debate-outs-wireless-mics/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 18:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/white-spaces-debate-outs-wireless-mics/</guid><description>An unexpected result of the debate about the &amp;ldquo;white space&amp;rdquo; TV spectrum is the exposure of unauthorized wireless microphone users like churches, theaters, and conference rooms. Many have been using unused UHF TV channels undetected for years. They must now cease or face interference from the new owners of the 700 MHz spectrum when those services begin next February. Finding new channels by simply re-tuning is becoming less feasible.
Wireless microphones have become increasingly common in any situation involving vocal performance, from televised concerts to news shows and Broadway plays.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 07:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-ii/</guid><description>In the previous discussion, we explored how AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon are aggressively acquiring bandwidth for their LTE networks. Now, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the consequences of this insatiable demand for bandwidth as we transition into the 4G era.
While UHF and microwave bandwidth transactions are currently active, this surge won&amp;rsquo;t last indefinitely. The high prices will incentivize existing bandwidth holders to sell to major players heavily investing in 4G deployment. What happens once this bandwidth is depleted?</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2017 Budget is on handling uncertainty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Budget website. View of Singapore.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2017 aimed to prepare the nation for the future amidst significant global economic shifts, presenting both obstacles and prospects. Finance Minister Heng Swee Keat stressed the need for companies and workers to develop robust adaptability to navigate these changing economic structures and technologies. He highlighted that digitalization, innovation, and a highly skilled workforce are key for cities and regions to thrive while maintaining global openness and connectivity.</description></item><item><title>USB 3.0 Offers Gbps Data Transfers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:28:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usb-30-offers-gbps-data-transfers/</guid><description>The arrival of USB 2.0 as a replacement for 1.1 nearly achieved the universal connectivity goal of its name. With a tenfold speed increase, USB 3.0, or &amp;ldquo;SuperSpeed,&amp;rdquo; aims to further solidify USB&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
While the existing 480 Mbps speed of USB 2.0 serves many devices well, surpassing the original USB 1.0&amp;rsquo;s 1.5 to 12 Mbps, the need for faster data transfer, especially for video, is evident. This need prompted the shift from FireWire to mini-USB in most video cameras.</description></item><item><title>Marco, it's Polo on Your Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</guid><description>Fashion giant Ralph Lauren is taking shopping to the next level by moving beyond online stores and embracing mobile shopping via cell phones. This shift, known as mobile or m-commerce, is poised to become as significant as e-commerce has been in recent times. Its success relies on internet-enabled smartphones and mobile-friendly websites designed for smaller screens, along with advancements like barcode scanning software and web-connected vending machines.
Why the focus on cell phone shopping?</description></item><item><title>Is That A Game Or A Netbook?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</guid><description>For years, the distinction between computers and video games has been blurry. This is because modern gaming consoles are essentially powerful computers that run games as applications. So it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s latest handheld gaming system, the DSi, boasts netbook-like features such as secure WiFi connectivity, a web browser, and expandable memory.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear: the Nintendo DSi is designed for gamers. It&amp;rsquo;s a handheld console, powered by a battery, and runs Nintendo DS game cartridges.</description></item><item><title>It Really Knows When You Are Sleeping</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-really-knows-when-you-are-sleeping/</guid><description>You might have heard this before:
It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re asleep, It&amp;rsquo;s aware when you&amp;rsquo;re awake. It maintains a record of it all, And informs you the next day.
But this isn&amp;rsquo;t about someone monitoring your behavior. This is about understanding your sleep patterns.
If you wake up feeling more tired than when you went to sleep, you might benefit from the Zeo Personal Sleep Coach, a new device that tracks your sleep and provides a visual representation of your sleep quality.</description></item><item><title>Where Have All The IPs Gone?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-have-all-the-ips-gone/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Where have all the IPs gone? Gone to users every one.&amp;rdquo;
- apologies to Pete Seeger
Have you heard? The internet is full. It&amp;rsquo;s expected to reach its limit in the next few years. This means no new users, websites, or online services. It&amp;rsquo;s like a club that&amp;rsquo;s reached capacity; they&amp;rsquo;ll have to turn people away at the door. &amp;ldquo;Here, take a pager, and we&amp;rsquo;ll call you when it&amp;rsquo;s your turn.</description></item><item><title>Save the Cell Phone, Save the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</guid><description>Cell phones are frequently overlooked as a source of environmental concern, valuable resources, and potential income. While seemingly harmless, these devices contain toxic materials and represent a significant waste problem due to their short lifespans and frequent replacement.
A cell phone&amp;rsquo;s small size and durable exterior might make it seem environmentally benign, but the internal components tell a different story. Lead, cadmium, arsenic, mercury, plastics, and glass are all found within these devices.</description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation.</description></item><item><title>Why Alternative Energy Makes Sense for Technology Companies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 10:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-alternative-energy-makes-sense-for-technology-companies/</guid><description>The digital world&amp;rsquo;s dependence on energy is deeply intertwined and may be its downfall, just as energy production&amp;rsquo;s side effects threaten our physical world. Climate change, for instance, directly impacts the sustainability of Business 2.0.
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume that dirty, resource-intensive energy is a relic of the industrial age, replaced by a cleaner information age, especially online. However, the online world can create a false sense of detachment from the physical resources it relies on.</description></item><item><title>HDBaseT Looks To Unseat HDMI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hdbaset-looks-to-unseat-hdmi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hdbaset-looks-to-unseat-hdmi/</guid><description>HDMI cables, while necessary for digital video, are notoriously expensive and limited in length. Standard network cables, like Cat5e or Cat6, offer a more affordable and longer-reaching alternative. HDBaseT technology may soon bridge this gap, enabling the use of network cables for video transmission.
The HDBaseT Alliance, comprised of industry leaders such as LG, Samsung, Sony, and Valens Semiconductor, is spearheading this development. Their goal is to replace specialized HDMI cables with standard LAN cables, simplifying connections.</description></item><item><title>How Technology Enables The 4-Hour Workweek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-technology-enables-the-4-hour-workweek/</guid><description>Timothy Ferriss&amp;rsquo; book, &amp;ldquo;The 4-Hour Workweek,&amp;rdquo; captivated my attention with its intriguing title and concept. It challenges the conventional 40-hour workweek and suggests a lifestyle where individuals can achieve personal and financial freedom by working less.
Ferriss, who identifies as a &amp;ldquo;vagabond,&amp;rdquo; emphasizes embracing technology and shifting perspectives to design a fulfilling life filled with travel and adventure. He challenges the traditional notion of working tirelessly for decades before retirement, proposing instead a series of &amp;ldquo;mini-retirements&amp;rdquo; interspersed with periods of work.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth Gets Incrementally Finer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet service has been very beneficial for businesses of all sizes. It not only keeps LAN-WAN-LAN connections using the Ethernet protocol, but lease prices are also typically much lower per Mbps than older services like T-Carrier and SONET. But wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have the ideal line speed without settling for a service that&amp;rsquo;s too small or paying too much for unnecessary bandwidth?
Fortunately, XO Communications, a leading Metro Ethernet WAN service provider, now offers a wide range of bandwidth options for businesses with on-net fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion.</description></item><item><title>There Will Be Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</guid><description>The 19th and 20th centuries were defined by the gold rush and oil boom, respectively. Similarly, the 21st century is witnessing a fiber optic revolution. Fiber optic communication has become essential for modern businesses. This era presents lucrative opportunities for entrepreneurs to capitalize on the insatiable demand for high-bandwidth communication. A new technology has emerged, promising to reshape the competitive landscape.
Consider a scenario where two telecommunications providers are discussing the industry.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Expands Across The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 20:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-expands-across-the-nation/</guid><description>If your home or business needs affordable broadband internet, there&amp;rsquo;s good news: a solution might be closer than you think.
CLEAR, a company pioneering 4G Wireless broadband using the WiMAX standard, is expanding its reach to more cities. These include:
Washington DC Metro Grand Rapids, Michigan St. Louis, Missouri Rochester, New York Syracuse, New York Eugene, Oregon Merced, Oregon Salt Lake City, Utah Richmond, Virginia Tri-Cities, Washington Visalia, Washington Yakima, Washington</description></item><item><title>Banish Vampires To Reduce Global Warming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</guid><description>Electronic devices, like hidden vampires, silently drain electricity even when seemingly off. This &amp;ldquo;vampire power&amp;rdquo; not only increases your electricity bill but also contributes to global warming.
These &amp;ldquo;vampires&amp;rdquo; hide within devices, indicated by glowing lights, active displays, running fans, or warm surfaces, even when the device is switched off. Remote-controlled devices are prime suspects, as they constantly use power to stay ready for remote signals. Similarly, wireless networks and devices are notorious power consumers.</description></item><item><title>G.ho.st as the Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</guid><description>If you come across a platform called G.ho.st, don&amp;rsquo;t be spooked by the name. It stands for Global Hosted Operating SysTem, found at http://g.ho.st/. It&amp;rsquo;s essentially an online operating system.
Instead of being restricted to your desktop, G.ho.st allows you to access an operating system anywhere with an internet connection. I decided to try it out myself.
The website was visually appealing, so I launched the G.ho.st virtual computer (VC). Unfortunately, my old Compaq couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle it and displayed an error message.</description></item><item><title>Poken Around For Business Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</guid><description>Modern business networking goes beyond the traditional handshake and business card by utilizing technology to manage contacts. Poken offers a fresh approach to this concept.
Poken, encompassing both a device and a method, modernizes the conventional business card. While physical cards were sufficient in the past, today&amp;rsquo;s digitized world demands more. Although card readers exist, Poken offers a direct electronic solution.
The pokenPulse, resembling a USB flash drive, doubles as a 2 GB storage device and a wireless transponder.</description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held</description></item><item><title>T1 Rex Is On The Kindle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-rex-is-on-the-kindle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 21:50:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-rex-is-on-the-kindle/</guid><description>Have you experienced the joy of reading with electronic ink? More than half a million dedicated readers have transitioned from traditional books to the lightweight Amazon Kindle. Many more are eagerly anticipating the release of the larger Kindle DX later this year. Kindle represents the future of reading, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to be part of their blog collection.
Rest assured, you can still access our content on your computer whenever you like, as that&amp;rsquo;s where it&amp;rsquo;s created and stored.</description></item><item><title>Top-paying technology jobs for 2014 - for those in the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</guid><description>The 2014 Salary Guides published by Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group identify six technology and digital jobs experiencing high demand in the US. This demand may also be reflected in the Asia Pacific region.
Companies are specifically seeking professionals skilled in information and network security, data analysis for business intelligence, and mobile development.
&amp;ldquo;Building a strong online presence and engaging customers through mobile platforms is crucial for businesses today,&amp;rdquo; says John Reed, Senior Executive Director of Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet vs SONET Throw Down</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 07:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vs-sonet-throw-down/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SONET and Carrier Ethernet, two contenders for the top spot in high-speed business bandwidth.
SONET, or Synchronous Optical NETwork, is a fiber optic transmission system using Time Division Multiplexing (TDM). Primarily used by telephone companies to boost their digital trunk capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s known for its redundant data rings over fiber optic cables, which create an automatic failover mechanism in case of a network disruption. While perfect for carrier-grade digitized phone calls, SONET can also handle packetized data including voice, video, and standard T1 or T3 lines.</description></item><item><title>Who Needs A T1 Line at Home?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 12:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-needs-a-t1-line-at-home/</guid><description>T1 lines are famous for their reliability and accessibility wherever there&amp;rsquo;s telephone service, but they might not be suitable for everyone&amp;rsquo;s home broadband needs. The cost alone is a major deterrent for most people. However, in some situations, a T1 line might be the only practical option.
Residential broadband prioritizes affordability to reach a broad market. That&amp;rsquo;s why DSL services can cost under $20 monthly, and Cable broadband with 3 to 6 Mbps typically costs $30 to $40.</description></item><item><title>Have SIM, Will Travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</guid><description>SIM Simminy, SIM Simminy, SIM SIM Siree
Having the right phone is essential for international travel.
Traveling to a foreign country can be exciting, but discovering your cell phone is unusable can put a damper on your trip. Without a working phone, you&amp;rsquo;ll be stuck using expensive hotel phones to stay in touch.
Fortunately, with a little planning, you can avoid this problem. The key is to ensure your cell phone is compatible with the network used in your destination country.</description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway.</description></item><item><title>Why GHz is So Last Century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 09:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ghz-is-so-last-century/</guid><description>GigaHertz, representing a billion cycles per second, has become the standard, making MegaHertz seem outdated. However, as technology advances, even GigaHertz might be surpassed by TeraHertz speeds, potentially rendering current benchmarks obsolete.
In the early days of personal computers, 640 KB of RAM seemed excessive. However, as software evolved, demanding more resources with graphics, images, and the rise of the internet, hardware struggled to keep up. It took decades for platforms to mature and offer sufficient RAM, hard drive space, and processor speeds.</description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Shows its Curve in Pink</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-shows-its-curve-in-pink/</guid><description>Who says productivity can&amp;rsquo;t be stylish? Why not combine technology and beauty in the business world? It&amp;rsquo;s definitely possible!
The BlackBerry Curve 8330 Pink for Verizon Wireless is a perfect example. This device deserves a spot in a movie, maybe titled &amp;ldquo;Pretty in Pink&amp;rdquo;—although that title is already taken, it perfectly captures the essence of this phone. This classic BlackBerry delivers on productivity while boasting an elegant curved design and a lovely pink exterior.</description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity.</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Old or Broken Laptop For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-old-or-broken-laptop-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-old-or-broken-laptop-for-cash/</guid><description>Do you have a pile of old laptops in your basement, even those with cracked screens that ended up in the trash? You might be surprised to learn that those old devices, broken or not, can actually earn you some money.
It&amp;rsquo;s true! Most laptops aren&amp;rsquo;t as worthless as you might think. Throwing them away or sending them to a landfill is not the best approach. Those old circuit boards and components contain harmful materials that can pollute the environment over time.</description></item><item><title>There is a lack of interest among Singapore job seekers in pursuing opportunities in emerging technology roles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-lack-of-interest-among-singapore-job-seekers-in-pursuing-opportunities-in-emerging-technology-roles/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 19:58:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-lack-of-interest-among-singapore-job-seekers-in-pursuing-opportunities-in-emerging-technology-roles/</guid><description>A recent study of tech job postings on Indeed found a shortage of job seekers in Singapore pursuing careers in technology.
To understand the extent of the problem, researchers compared job postings to job searches and overall interest in four areas: cybersecurity, data science, machine learning, and robotics over a two-year period.
Indeed’s research highlighted a significant gap between available cybersecurity jobs and individuals seeking them. The surge in demand for cybersecurity professionals stems from recent high-profile cybersecurity incidents in Singapore and the government&amp;rsquo;s emphasis on cybersecurity.</description></item><item><title>Will Cell Phones Replace Laptop Computers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</guid><description>Laptops have taken over as the primary mobile work tool, but their days may be numbered. They are bulky, heavy, and require constant charging. A simple legal pad is starting to look more appealing in comparison. The search is on for a mobile device that offers the right balance of power and portability. Could the answer be cell phones?
The idea of an all-in-one cell phone is appealing because most people carry one anyway.</description></item><item><title>Tired of Flaky Internet Connections?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</guid><description>Running a business is challenging when your tools are unreliable. You would think technology would make things easier, but it often has the opposite effect. As processes become more complex and interconnected, they seem to become less dependable. A simple cash transaction can turn into an e-commerce nightmare. Why can&amp;rsquo;t things just work flawlessly all the time?
While expecting perfection might be unrealistic, your business systems should function seamlessly most of the time.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>When your business or applications need more bandwidth than T1 lines can offer, even multiple bonded ones, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider fiber optic solutions. But with various options available, how do you choose?
Traditionally, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was the primary fiber optic bandwidth option, pioneered by phone companies. SONET surpasses T-Carrier technology (T1 and T3 lines). While T1 provides 1.5 Mbps over copper and T3 offers 45 Mbps over coaxial cable, SONET scales up to OC-1, OC-3, OC-12, OC-24, OC-48, OC-192, OC-256, and OC-768.</description></item><item><title>I Heard What You Wrote Last Summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-heard-what-you-wrote-last-summer/</guid><description>Ever been stuck in a class or meeting, diligently taking notes but unsure if you&amp;rsquo;re capturing everything accurately? Recording the session with a digital recorder alongside note-taking could help, but then syncing the audio and text becomes a nightmare. What if there was a single device that could automatically synchronize your notes and audio? Thankfully, there is!
The Livescribe Pulse(tm) smartpen records audio as you write. Yes, you read that right—you write, it records.</description></item><item><title>What Can GigE Bandwidth Do For You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 16:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-can-gige-bandwidth-do-for-you/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly common in local area networks, with network cards and backbones now supporting these higher speeds. Companies that rely heavily on digital processes and high bandwidth data transfers are likely already using Gigabit Ethernet. However, they need a way to extend these high-speed transfers beyond their local networks.
Companies with large numbers of employees, extensive customer bases, or applications that generate significant amounts of data can benefit from Gigabit Ethernet WAN connections.</description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget prioritizes innovation to capitalize on opportunities in a changing economic landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</guid><description>In his 2016-17 Budget address, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized the need for the city to adapt to a changing global economy driven by technology and the rise of emerging markets. He highlighted robotics, healthy aging, and smart city initiatives as potential areas for Hong Kong to leverage its strengths.
Tsang announced plans to promote smart production and research in the Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate, utilizing robotics and IT to advance the entire value chain, from research and development to marketing.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>Is Municipal WiFi On The Way Out?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</guid><description>While WiFi hotspots are incredibly convenient for travelers in airports, hotels, and restaurants, city-wide WiFi hasn&amp;rsquo;t been as successful as initially hoped. The recent closure of Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s Metro WiFi in Philadelphia raises questions about the future of this technology, even though broadband internet is thriving.
Despite a significant increase in broadband adoption, with dial-up becoming nearly obsolete, city-wide WiFi providers are struggling. Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s experience in Philadelphia, where they only gained a fraction of their projected subscribers, highlights this challenge.</description></item><item><title>Can The Big Amazon Kindle DX Save The Newspapers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 03:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-big-amazon-kindle-dx-save-the-newspapers/</guid><description>The recent debut of the larger Amazon Kindle DX has been hailed by some as a potential savior for the struggling newspaper industry. However, this nearly $500 device, while innovative, is unlikely to reverse the decline of print newspapers.
It&amp;rsquo;s simply too late and too expensive a solution for an industry facing dire financial straits. Had newspapers embraced electronic delivery methods a decade ago, the outcome might have been different. Now, many are on the brink of collapse, and technology alone cannot salvage them.</description></item><item><title>Fiber to the Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 22:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-to-the-boonies/</guid><description>For a long time, the idea of &amp;ldquo;rural broadband&amp;rdquo; seemed contradictory. While cities enjoyed a variety of high-speed internet options, from DSL and cable to fiber optic connections, rural areas remained stuck with slow dial-up or satellite internet. Although high-speed business lines have become more affordable, fiber optic cables in rural areas were deemed too expensive. However, an organization in Vermont is challenging this assumption.
ValleyFiber, led by Dr. Timothy Nulty, is bringing fiber optic broadband to rural homes and businesses in Vermont&amp;rsquo;s Upper Valley.</description></item><item><title>Is it relevant? Who cares?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 23:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-relevant-who-cares/</guid><description>Recently, I discussed staying relevant in a constantly evolving field with a respected colleague. As someone with potentially decades in my career ahead, this is a topic I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering, especially considering my specialization in Dynamics GP and how other technologies intersect with it. While I&amp;rsquo;m comfortable with my current skill set, I wonder if I should branch out and explore standalone technologies.
My colleague reassured me that my experience, teaching abilities, and the continued relevance of Dynamics GP contribute to my value.</description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications.</description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker.</description></item><item><title>Red, Red, LG Vu Wine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</guid><description>Everyone enjoys a nice wine with dinner, but what about in business or on the go? It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly acceptable when that &amp;ldquo;wine&amp;rdquo; is the new touchscreen phone available from AT&amp;amp;T.
This &amp;ldquo;red wine&amp;rdquo; phone boasts more features than a full-bodied Cabernet. Its compact size of 4.3 x 2.1 x 0.5 inches makes it easy to carry in your pocket or bag. You read that correctly – this device is only half an inch thin!</description></item><item><title>Ignore That PBX Behind the Curtain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:31:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignore-that-pbx-behind-the-curtain/</guid><description>Operating a small business doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to sound like it, especially with tools like virtual PBX systems. These systems can give your two-person office the professional edge of a Fortune 500 corporation.
Traditional PBX systems, standard in large companies, offer features such as individual extensions, direct dialing, call transferring, and outside line access. However, they come with a hefty price tag. iTeleCenter, a virtual PBX solution, offers an affordable alternative that transforms your existing phones into a robust communication system.</description></item><item><title>Media Flos to Mobile TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</guid><description>Television is everywhere. While it started with over-the-air broadcasts, it quickly spread to cable, satellite, and the internet through platforms like YouTube and IPTV. Now, mobile devices like cell phones are the new frontier for watching TV on the go.
Early mobile video relied on downloadable clips using cellular broadband networks like EV-DO. However, these networks struggle with bandwidth limitations, making it difficult to deliver high-quality real-time video without overloading the system.</description></item><item><title>Workaholic and Proud of IT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 22:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workaholic-and-proud-of-it/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re deeply involved in technology, there&amp;rsquo;s a good chance you might identify as a workaholic. Did you know there&amp;rsquo;s a day specifically for acknowledging workaholics? It&amp;rsquo;s not an official holiday, of course, as that wouldn&amp;rsquo;t align with the workaholic spirit. Workaholics Day falls on July 5th, the day after most people are recovering from their Fourth of July festivities.
While others are recovering from fireworks or tending to minor burns, you might find yourself busy with crucial hardware upgrades in a server room.</description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access.</description></item></channel></rss>