<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Greater on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greater/</link><description>Recent content in Greater on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/greater/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item></channel></rss>