<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Irregular Migration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/irregular-migration/</link><description>Recent content in Irregular Migration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/irregular-migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>Are potential asylum-seekers entitled to a Schengen visa?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-potential-asylum-seekers-entitled-to-a-schengen-visa/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
In a recent decision concerning the Koushkaki case, the Court of Justice provided clarity on applying for a Schengen visa. The court effectively ruled that individuals have a right to a visa if they fulfill the established requirements. However, this decision also implicitly raises questions about denying visa applications from potential asylum-seekers.
The judgment
Mr. Koushkaki, an Iranian citizen residing in Iran, applied for a Schengen visa to visit Germany but was denied due to insufficient proof of financial support for his stay and return.</description></item><item><title>Imprison them: the suggestion to revise the EU's Returns Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 17:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprison-them-the-suggestion-to-revise-the-eu-s-returns-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Returns Directive, established to manage irregular migration by non-EU citizens, mandates that Member States issue return decisions to unauthorized individuals and enforce their removal. While the Directive allows for voluntary departure periods, it also outlines rules for detention and entry bans. Initially considered lenient by migrant support groups, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has since interpreted the Directive more broadly.</description></item></channel></rss>