<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NUS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nus/</link><description>Recent content in NUS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10.</description></item><item><title>Many Singaporeans are aware of human trafficking but underestimate its prevalence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</guid><description>The International Organization for Migration’s X Campaign (IOM X), in collaboration with USAID, the US Embassy in Singapore, and Microsoft, recently released findings from their pilot outreach program, IOM X Connect Singapore. This initiative sought to increase awareness about human trafficking in Singapore.
During the project, students from the National University of Singapore (NUS) and Singapore Management University (SMU) utilized the newly developed IOM X Learn, Act and Share App. They tested the knowledge of 100 Singaporean residents on the topic of human trafficking.</description></item></channel></rss>