<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EarthLink on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earthlink/</link><description>Recent content in EarthLink on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earthlink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eastern Tennessee Gets Lit for Business Fiber Optic Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:54:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</guid><description>Nashville, Tennessee, is known for its robust fiber optic network infrastructure. The city&amp;rsquo;s thriving business sector, particularly in healthcare, publishing, banking, transportation, and music, demands high bandwidth, a need that extends across the state.
EarthLink, a leading bandwidth provider, has recently expanded its fiber optic network in eastern Tennessee. The project includes a 343-mile route connecting Nashville to Knoxville, with additional routes linking Knoxville to Chattanooga and Bristol. This network offers connection points in multiple cities, including Cookeville, Oak Ridge, and Cleveland, and major Points of Presence (PoPs) in Knoxville, Morristown, Johnson City, and Bristol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eastern-tennessee-gets-lit-for-business-fiber-optic-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EarthLink Offers Healthcare IT Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</guid><description>The potential for healthcare automation to significantly reduce costs in healthcare settings like doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices, clinics, and hospitals is substantial. However, not all healthcare providers have the necessary IT capabilities to modernize and leverage these new technologies. They might also struggle to meet privacy regulations like HIPAA. This is where large network service providers such as EarthLink Business can bridge the gap. An example of this can be seen in how EarthLink supports Monadnock Community Hospital in Peterborough, New Hampshire, as shown in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>