<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Webinar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/webinar/</link><description>Recent content in Webinar on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/webinar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Deep Dive Now Accessible: Management Reporter!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-deep-dive-now-accessible-management-reporter/</guid><description>I previously shared information about the &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s New Deep Dives&amp;rdquo; series for Microsoft Dynamics GP 2010. We recently released another installment focused on Management Reporter. Access it here! Craig Anderson from MSX Group, an expert in Management Reporter, developed and presented this topic. MSX Group and Craig are leading authorities on Management Reporter, and we were thrilled to leverage their expertise for this installment!</description></item><item><title>Browser Based Video Conferencing and Webinars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/browser-based-video-conferencing-and-webinars/</guid><description>Once restricted to businesses, video conferencing is now accessible to anyone with an internet connection and a web browser. MegaMeeting offers a suite of products for PCs, Macs, and Linux computers that don&amp;rsquo;t require typical downloads or installations. As long as you can use a web browser, you can participate in video conferences and webinars.
MegaMeeting&amp;rsquo;s web-based system utilizes the Flash Player 9 plugin, commonly found in browsers like Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Virtual Business Travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-virtual-business-travel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 05:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-virtual-business-travel/</guid><description>At the start of this new year and decade, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to reconsider some ingrained habits, like business travel. Do you eagerly anticipate it or dread the idea? As a manager, do you advocate for large travel budgets because your team enjoys it and sees a significant return on investment? Or does the thought make you slightly uncomfortable?
If you identify with the latter sentiment, you might discover significant advantages in replacing a large portion of your in-person business travel with virtual alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Your Own Webinars Made Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-webinars-made-easy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-webinars-made-easy/</guid><description>Have you ever considered hosting online presentations for a large audience of employees, clients, or potential customers? While this seems like a complex and expensive endeavor typically reserved for large corporations, there&amp;rsquo;s now an accessible and affordable tool that allows small to medium-sized businesses and even individual entrepreneurs to leverage the power of webinars.
Webinars, essentially web-based seminars, offer a convenient and cost-effective alternative to traditional in-person seminars. Unlike traditional seminars that involve travel expenses, accommodation costs, and limited attendee capacity due to budgetary constraints, webinars eliminate these limitations.</description></item></channel></rss>