<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apparel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apparel/</link><description>Recent content in Apparel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apparel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24.</description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>TINKR combines fashion, design, and 3D printing technology in a unique way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 02:38:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-combines-fashion-design-and-3d-printing-technology-in-a-unique-way/</guid><description>TINKR, a company from Singapore, has transitioned its business model from solely offering 3D printing services. They now focus on merging fashion, design, and technology to produce unique corporate gifts.
In a recent announcement, company founders Xiaohui and Freda expressed their passion for blending craftsmanship with technology. They are excited to introduce their latest venture: high-quality, locally and regionally designed prints. They plan to collaborate with various artisans and designers in the upcoming months to create fresh, unique prints with a distinctive style.</description></item><item><title>Benetton will concentrate on empowering women through their new collection, A Collection of Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benetton-will-concentrate-on-empowering-women-through-their-new-collection-a-collection-of-us/</guid><description>The idea that women sharing their experiences and learning from each other is crucial for creating a brighter future is the driving force behind A Collection Of Us. This new United Colors of Benetton collection, launching in four parts throughout October 2015, December 2015, February 2016, and April 2016, embodies this philosophy.
Each capsule within the collection reimagines a core aspect of Benetton&amp;rsquo;s brand identity—heritage, technique, color, and performance—giving it a fresh and modern significance.</description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available.</description></item><item><title>AIN has added English and Chinese websites for those interested in fashion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 20:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ain-has-added-english-and-chinese-websites-for-those-interested-in-fashion/</guid><description>Source: AIN English website.
A Korean women&amp;rsquo;s fashion brand is aiming to become a global name, focusing particularly on mainland China, Hong Kong, and Singapore.
AIN has seen positive results selling on international e-commerce platforms. To further expand its reach, the company has launched English and Chinese websites through cafe24, a leading Korean e-commerce platform. AIN&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Park A-In, shared that customers appreciate the brand&amp;rsquo;s distinct, contemporary designs and overall aesthetic.</description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions.</description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains.</description></item><item><title>BLUEPOPS, a fashion brand specializing in plus-sized clothing, is now expanding its presence on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bluepops-a-fashion-brand-specializing-in-plus-sized-clothing-is-now-expanding-its-presence-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>Source: BLUEPOPS website.
BLUEPOPS, a Korean online retailer specializing in plus-size women&amp;rsquo;s apparel (sizes M to XXL), is taking a hands-on approach by creating its clothing lines.
According to owner Jo Yeong-hwa, focusing on elegance is crucial. She believes that to keep customers happy, the website needs to consistently introduce new products with a distinct brand identity.
BLUEPOPS conducts customer surveys biannually. Through a recent survey, they discovered that customers rely heavily on product details when making purchasing decisions.</description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method.</description></item><item><title>Belstaff has opened its flagship store in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/belstaff-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-japan/</guid><description>Source: Belstaff.
The renowned British heritage brand, Belstaff, recently celebrated the grand opening of its flagship store in Tokyo, Japan. Situated within the expansive Ginza Six retail complex, the new store occupies a prime location within this 47,000 square meter shopping destination. This strategic move underscores Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s growing presence in the Japanese market and its commitment to global retail expansion.
Upon its debut, the Tokyo flagship presents a curated selection of Belstaff&amp;rsquo;s offerings, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s complete menswear collection and, for the first time in Tokyo, its womenswear line.</description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces black clothing featuring heat management technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-black-clothing-featuring-heat-management-technology/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Climachill apparel.
Adidas recently debuted its new Climachill clothing line, featuring a black training t-shirt designed with technology that regulates body heat to keep wearers cool in hot weather. Ideal for warm and humid weather, Adidas Climachill maximizes cooling without sacrificing comfort or style.
Dr. Maarten Hupperets, Director of Future Sport Science at Adidas, explains, &amp;ldquo;When we exercise, our body&amp;rsquo;s core temperature can rise by 3 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI.</description></item></channel></rss>