<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MEN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/men/</link><description>Recent content in MEN on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/men/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Fall/Winter 2015 Collections have been launched by CH Carolina Herrera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</guid><description>CH, a subsidiary brand under the Carolina Herrera fashion house, has launched their Fall/Winter 2015 collections for both men and women. The Women’s Collection uses vibrant pops of color like reds, sky blues, and fuchsias, which stand out against a darker color scheme with white and ivory accents.
Formal evening wear is designed using luxurious fabrics like silks, lace, and jacquard. The feminine looks are completed with signature CH Carolina Herrera details like bows and ruffles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Men's cufflinks that can be customized are now offered on Indiegogo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</guid><description>CuffloCs, customizable cufflinks designed for men, are seeking funding on Indiegogo. These unique cufflinks feature a secure compartment for holding small items. According to creator Josh Jablonski, CuffloCs can accommodate a variety of small objects, such as jewelry charms, pebbles, or even photographs.
Source: Indiegogo.
&amp;ldquo;The screw/on off design ensures the security of your items within the double-sided glass, and the cufflink can be effortlessly disassembled to switch up the design,&amp;rdquo; explains Jablonski on his Indiegogo page...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/men-s-cufflinks-that-can-be-customized-are-now-offered-on-indiegogo/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>