<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TTIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ttip/</link><description>Recent content in TTIP on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ttip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Negotiating the T-TIP: Why Putting the Cart Before the Horse is a Doomed Constitutional Strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-t-tip-why-putting-the-cart-before-the-horse-is-a-doomed-constitutional-strategy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 19:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-t-tip-why-putting-the-cart-before-the-horse-is-a-doomed-constitutional-strategy/</guid><description>Emanuela Matei*
* Associate Researcher at the Centre of European Legal Studies, Bucharest. Juris Master in European Business Law (Lund University, June 2012), Magister legum (Lund University, June 2010), BSc in Economics &amp;amp; Business Administration (Lund University, June 2009).
Introduction
In June 2015, the European Commission urged the termination of bilateral investment treaties (BITs) within the EU. These agreements were established between Austria, Romania, Slovakia, Netherlands, and Sweden. The Commission&amp;rsquo;s rationale was that EU membership necessitates Member States to resolve internal matters under EU law, superseding any other legal frameworks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-t-tip-why-putting-the-cart-before-the-horse-is-a-doomed-constitutional-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-t-tip-why-putting-the-cart-before-the-horse-is-a-doomed-constitutional-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the European Parliament's Closed Reading Rooms: Shedding Light on Transparency in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Dr Vigjilenca Abazi
Assistant Professor of European Law
Maastricht University
Documents related to various topics, such as Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (TTIP) negotiations, EU Food Safety Authority oversight, and tax justice, share a common factor: accessing them requires select Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to participate in closed reading rooms. This blog post will examine how this departure from transparent parliamentary oversight is becoming increasingly common and question its potential impact on public access to documents requests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's upcoming trade policy is beginning to form with the release of the Opinion on the EU/Singapore FTA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s authority regarding trade agreements has been debated for years in the European Court of Justice (ECJ), as it significantly affects the balance of power between the EU and its Member States concerning international economic policies. Treaty revisions, especially the Treaty of Lisbon, have altered these rules, making this issue even more important due to recent controversies surrounding EU trade negotiations (notably with Canada and the USA) and the UK-EU trade talks post-Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-upcoming-trade-policy-is-beginning-to-form-with-the-release-of-the-opinion-on-the-eu-singapore-fta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>