<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Local Loop on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/local-loop/</link><description>Recent content in Local Loop on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/local-loop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Reviving The Local Loop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-reviving-the-local-loop/</guid><description>Local loop usage has decreased as people switch from traditional phone lines to wireless or internet-based phone services. This has prompted some to suggest that these copper lines be completely removed. However, just as this idea emerges, new technology is giving these old lines a new purpose.
Fiber optic connections may be the future, but they’re not widely available yet. Only a small percentage of businesses currently have fiber, due to lack of demand, high installation costs, or limited infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country.</description></item></channel></rss>