<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Codeshare on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/codeshare/</link><description>Recent content in Codeshare on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/codeshare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China have partnered on a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China, China&amp;rsquo;s national airline, have partnered to provide travelers with expanded options and easier connections. This agreement comes after Hawaiian launched its new non-stop service to Beijing, operating three times a week.
&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to collaborate with Air China to expand our reach beyond Beijing, allowing our customers to conveniently explore more Chinese cities with a single ticket from Honolulu,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Dunkerley, Hawaiian Airlines President and CEO.</description></item><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas.</description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals.</description></item><item><title>Etihad and Fiji Airways establish codeshare partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</guid><description>Fiji Airways and Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, have established an interline agreement. This partnership enables both airlines to sell tickets to and from a wider range of destinations. Passengers can now travel between 17 cities in the Middle East, 29 cities in Asia, and three cities in Australia to and from Fiji, along with other destinations.
James Hogan, President and CEO of Etihad Airways, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, stating that Fiji is an excellent vacation destination and enhances Etihad&amp;rsquo;s global network.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines expands its presence in the United States with a new codeshare agreement with Asiana Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines has broadened its codeshare partnership with Asiana Airlines, expanding its network beyond Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon International Airport to include Honolulu, Seattle, and Los Angeles.
These Star Alliance members have been codesharing on flights between Singapore and Seoul-Incheon since September 2005. Singapore Airlines currently offers four daily flights on this route, with one continuing to San Francisco, while Asiana operates daily flights.
Asiana also places its code on Singapore Airlines-operated flights extending beyond Singapore to Jakarta, Indonesia; Perth, Australia; Auckland, New Zealand; and Cape Town, South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Garuda and Turkish Airlines have formed a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines have partnered to offer codeshare flights between Jakarta and Istanbul. This agreement is valid until October 24, 2015.
The joint flight schedule for Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines is shown below:
Source: Garuda Indonesia. CGK represents Soekarno–Hatta International Airport in Jakarta, Indonesia, while IST stands for Atatürk International Airport in Istanbul, Turkey. STD indicates departure time, and STA refers to arrival time. +1 signifies arrival on the following day.</description></item></channel></rss>