<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Femtocell on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/femtocell/</link><description>Recent content in Femtocell on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/femtocell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I Shall Call It Cellular Mini-Me</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 10:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</guid><description>The change from landlines to mobile phones is accelerating as 3G networks expand coverage to suburban and rural areas. Smartphones like the BlackBerry and iPhone are becoming ubiquitous, prompting questions about the necessity of laptops. Wireless technology offers liberation from desktops, allowing users to communicate, browse, and enjoy videos on the move. However, this freedom is often hindered indoors.
Indoor spaces present a significant obstacle to wireless transmission. Walls and other barriers weaken high-frequency radio signals, leading to dropped calls and poor connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-shall-call-it-cellular-mini-me/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part III</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 04:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iii/</guid><description>A significant disagreement is occurring regarding the allocation of the electromagnetic spectrum. Wireless carriers and broadcasters, alongside government entities and satellite providers, are vying for their share. However, the spectrum is a finite resource. Although market forces like auctions and sales play a role, innovative solutions are crucial for optimizing spectrum utilization.
One such innovation, inspired by the concept of &amp;ldquo;white space&amp;rdquo; in printing, targets unused portions of the spectrum. Just as blank areas exist on a printed page, gaps remain between allocated TV channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iii/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>