<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mintel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mintel/</link><description>Recent content in Mintel on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mintel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair.</description></item><item><title>Australians are worried about the amount of sugar in fizzy drinks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</guid><description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s carbonated soft drink (CSD) market is experiencing ongoing challenges due to consumer worries about sugar content, as reported by Mintel, a global market intelligence firm.
Mintel predicts that the total sales volume of CSDs in Australia will likely decrease by 2.3% in 2017, following a 4.7% drop from 2014 to 2016.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research suggests that growing awareness of sugar&amp;rsquo;s negative effects has prompted many Australians to reevaluate their sugar consumption.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress.</description></item><item><title>The top goal for urban Australians is to spend more time with their family</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/</guid><description>The increasing presence of technology in everyday life has led many Australians to desire a better work-life balance. Market intelligence agency Mintel reports that 38% of Australians are hoping to achieve this balance in the coming year.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that more than half of Australians living in metropolitan areas (51%) want to prioritize spending time with family in the next year. This desire is even more pronounced in families with three or more members, reaching 60%.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry is increasingly prioritizing sustainability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</guid><description>The beauty industry needs a complete overhaul in its approach to sustainability and zero waste, focusing on every part of the process, according to market intelligence agency Mintel. The company highlights &amp;ldquo;Sub-Zero Waste&amp;rdquo; as a major trend that will shape the global beauty and personal care markets in the years to come.
The zero-waste movement is picking up speed as consumers become increasingly affected by environmental problems like natural disasters and water scarcity.</description></item><item><title>2030 Food: Sustainable, Healthier, Personalized</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</guid><description>- Businesses for Good: In the future, successful companies will be those committed to improving the well-being of both the planet and its people.
- Personalized Nutrition: Technological advancements will allow consumers to create highly customized approaches to enhance their physical and mental health.
Source: Mintel.
- Tech-Driven Food Solutions: Consumer confidence in food science and technology will grow as these become essential for securing the food supply. Mintel, a market research firm focused on consumer insights, has identified three significant trends expected to shape the global food, drink, and food service industries in the coming decade:</description></item></channel></rss>