<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DHL on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dhl/</link><description>Recent content in DHL on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dhl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DHL introduces new freight service from Taiwan to Austria for shipments smaller than a full container</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 20:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-introduces-new-freight-service-from-taiwan-to-austria-for-shipments-smaller-than-a-full-container/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding has introduced a new weekly Less-than-Container-Load (LCL) service originating in Taiwan and arriving in Vienna, Austria, by way of Koper, Slovenia. This service, departing every Monday from Keelung or Kaohsiung, allows Taiwanese exporters to ship cargo with a 35-day transit time to Vienna.
Kelvin Leung, CEO, Asia Pacific at DHL Global Forwarding, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to understanding industry trends and supporting exporters. He highlighted the increasing demand for Asian products in Eastern Europe and positioned the new service as a way to strengthen trade partnerships and improve the speed and efficiency of services for Taiwanese businesses.</description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019.</description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>