<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Level Playing Field on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level-playing-field/</link><description>Recent content in Level Playing Field on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level-playing-field/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement.</description></item><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration.</description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the Environment and Climate Provisions in the Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Introduction
The start of the new year marked a significant shift in the UK-EU relationship, ending the Brexit transition and ushering in the provisional Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). This post delves into the TCA&amp;rsquo;s environmental and climate change provisions, drawing on prior analyses of the TCA&amp;rsquo;s overview, social security provisions, human rights aspects, and dispute settlement mechanisms. (Updated as of April 28, 2021, to reflect the final TCA article numbering).</description></item><item><title>Negotiating the future relationship between the UK and EU: the EU's mandate for negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 07:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/negotiating-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-eu-s-mandate-for-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Thanks to Georgina Wright, of the Institute for Government, for a &amp;rsquo;track changes&amp;rsquo; version of the negotiation mandate. The usual disclaimer applies.
This week, the UK-EU future relationship negotiation process progressed. The EU Council approved the negotiation mandate, differing from the initial proposal. This post provides an updated analysis, comparing the final mandate to the political declaration, highlighting differences between the EU and UK&amp;rsquo;s positions that are expected to make negotiations difficult.</description></item></channel></rss>