<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Options on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-options/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Options on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternative Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>For those living and working in rural areas, limited internet options can be a major problem. While major providers often only service cities, there are ways to stay connected without spending a fortune or waiting years for expanded infrastructure.
Forget DSL or cable – those are rare finds outside city limits. While universal telephone service guarantees basic phone lines (and thus, very slow dial-up internet), there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for fast, affordable internet: the existing cell phone network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speed of Metro Ethernet Zooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</guid><description>Forget Superman, when it comes to speed and affordability, Metro Ethernet is the real superhero of business bandwidth solutions. It surpasses conventional options like T1 and DS3, offering significantly faster speeds at a lower cost.
Metro Ethernet is in high demand, rapidly becoming the go-to choice for businesses. Its speed can be significantly higher than what you&amp;rsquo;re currently using, and it&amp;rsquo;s generally more cost-effective per Mbps compared to other options, including T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Stimulus For The Boonies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 04:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</guid><description>Rural America is on the verge of a major internet transformation thanks to a new broadband stimulus program. This program aims to bridge the digital divide by providing $7.2 billion in funding to states, enabling them to improve internet access significantly.
While South Korea is making strides in providing gigabit internet speeds to its citizens, many Americans struggle with significantly slower connections. This disparity stems from two main issues. Firstly, rural areas often lack the infrastructure and competition found in metropolitan areas, resulting in limited internet options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-stimulus-for-the-boonies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Burstable Bandwidth Offers Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</guid><description>Most businesses purchase dedicated WAN bandwidth to support their voice and data services. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a more cost-effective option called burstable bandwidth.
Take business broadband service as an example. A dedicated DS3 connection provides a constant 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads. This full capacity is always available, whether you&amp;rsquo;re sending a large file or backing up data. When not fully utilized, the line remains idle.
The recent drop in DS3 prices has made it a common choice for medium to large businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/burstable-bandwidth-offers-flexibility/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>