<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EoDS3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eods3/</link><description>Recent content in EoDS3 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eods3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises.</description></item></channel></rss>