<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-networking/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Networking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 19:35:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Bandwidth Fosters Productivity Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-fosters-productivity-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 19:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-bandwidth-fosters-productivity-improvement/</guid><description>Increasing your bandwidth could be one of the quickest and most affordable ways to boost employee productivity. When your LAN and WAN bandwidth are optimized to match the speed of your business operations, you remove a major obstacle to improved performance and potentially even increase your profits.
While it might seem unrelated, the effectiveness of telephone and computer networks directly impacts employee performance. When considering efficiency and speed, any delay naturally hinders productivity.</description></item><item><title>Biggest Cisco Router Yet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biggest-cisco-router-yet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biggest-cisco-router-yet/</guid><description>The launch of Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest and most powerful routing platform, the CRS-3 Carrier Routing System, confirms that the information age is in full swing. This system is a significant improvement over its predecessor, the CRS-1, which is widely used as a core router for internet traffic and data centers.
The CRS-3&amp;rsquo;s impressive 322 Terabits per second throughput is noteworthy, but equally important is Cisco&amp;rsquo;s acknowledgment of the changing nature of internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 03:49:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20x20-mbps-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>If you need a significant bandwidth upgrade but find traditional options limited or excessively expensive, consider 20x20 Mbps Ethernet over Copper (EoC). This technology delivers a symmetrical 20 Mbps upload and download speed over readily available twisted pair copper cable.
This professional-grade service provides dedicated, full-duplex bandwidth, allowing simultaneous uploads and downloads at maximum speed. In contrast, T1 lines offer a base speed of 1.5 Mbps and require bonding multiple lines to achieve higher bandwidth, becoming cost-prohibitive beyond 10-12 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections.</description></item></channel></rss>