<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lubricating on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lubricating/</link><description>Recent content in Lubricating on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:24:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lubricating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Strange Solenoid and an Alien 7812 Impostor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 00:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-strange-solenoid-and-an-alien-7812-impostor/</guid><description>As I was testing the restored tonearm carriage on my Beogram 8000 with some recently purchased Genesis reissues (Trespass, Foxtrot, Nursery Crime, etc.), I decided to turn my attention to the Beogram 4000 I had recently acquired from Italy. The most critical issue was its malfunctioning solenoid, which appeared unusual and unlike standard B&amp;amp;O components.
Upon disassembling the damper/solenoid assembly, I discovered a makeshift repair job. The original solenoid had been replaced with a different one, and a nail was used as a plunger to activate the solenoid linkage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Lubricating and Adjusting the Solenoid to Tonearm Linkages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-lubricating-and-adjusting-the-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkages/</guid><description>Following the solenoid replacement and removal of the faulty voltage regulator on my Beogram 4000 restoration project, the arm mechanism remained sluggish. This indicated a need to lubricate the connection between the damper and tonearm lift. Additionally, the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s horizontal alignment was significantly off. While attempting to adjust this with the set screw on the tonearm counterweight&amp;rsquo;s connecting arm, I discovered it was glued in place with epoxy, preventing screwdriver access - likely another consequence of a previous repair attempt.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 Type 4923: Tapehead cleaning and playback testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-tapehead-cleaning-and-playback-testing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 01:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-type-4923-tapehead-cleaning-and-playback-testing/</guid><description>This update on the Beocord 5000 Type 4923 focuses on mechanical adjustments and tape head maintenance.
The post begins by addressing the sluggish opening and closing of the cassette drawer. While the belt had been replaced, the issue was traced to friction in the drawer slide mechanism. After disassembling and cleaning the mechanism, applying dry lubricant to the metal posts, and reassembling it, the drawer now operates smoothly.
The cassette assembly also underwent a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition.</description></item></channel></rss>