<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Market on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/market/</link><description>Recent content in Market on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth.</description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available.</description></item><item><title>Less expensive smartphones are available for those in developing markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</guid><description>To prepare for future growth, smartphone manufacturers are looking beyond China to other emerging markets. Although China represented a third of global smartphone shipments in 2013, the International Data Corporation (IDC) indicates this market is reaching its saturation point.
IDC reports that smartphones constitute over 80% of China&amp;rsquo;s total phone sales. Consequently, they predict that India and Africa will be the primary sources of the next half billion smartphone customers.</description></item><item><title>INVADE aims to connect landlords and retailers in Singapore through matchmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</guid><description>INVADE, the first real-time retail space booking platform in Singapore, has officially launched. The platform allows businesses to instantly find and book retail spaces. Over 35,000 retail businesses, startups, and entrepreneurs have already become INVADE members.
The idea for INVADE came from Singaporeans Koh Cheng Guan and Kent Teo. Having experience working with major landlords, marketing pop-up and retail spaces, and organizing flea markets, they recognized the challenges entrepreneurs face in finding suitable retail spaces and the landlords&amp;rsquo; need to utilize vacant space.</description></item><item><title>ACCA predicts a growing market demand for professional business and advisory services in ASEAN and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-predicts-a-growing-market-demand-for-professional-business-and-advisory-services-in-asean-and-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-predicts-a-growing-market-demand-for-professional-business-and-advisory-services-in-asean-and-china/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), the world&amp;rsquo;s largest global professional accounting body, has published a new report, supported by the Singapore Accountancy Commission, that explores the future demand for professional business and advisory services.
Source: ACCA Global website. Cover for
the Market demand for Professional
Business and Advisory Services report.
The report highlights the increasing demand for professional services, particularly those related to data science, analytics, and artificial intelligence, by corporations, including small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs).</description></item></channel></rss>