<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Halal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/halal/</link><description>Recent content in Halal on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/halal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tea Forté Singapore presents three mooncake collections as part of the Autumn in Abundance series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</guid><description>Source: Tea Forté.
Tea Forté Singapore, a specialty tea company, has introduced its new Autumn in Abundance mooncake collection, featuring traditional baked mooncakes with reduced sugar, the Creative Infused line, and a special Luxury selection.
The company suggests pairing the traditional mooncakes with its organic white ginger pear tea, the Creative Infused collection with the organic green mango peach tea, and the Luxurious selections with its orchid vanilla tea.</description></item><item><title>Buffets for Iftar are available at 21 on Rajah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</guid><description>Source: 21 on Rajah.
The buffet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a venue to hold a corporate Iftar gathering in Singapore during Ramadan, consider the halal-certified 21 On Rajah. Situated within Days Hotel Singapore at Zhongshan Park, this all-day dining restaurant is presenting a selection of Mediterranean and Asian Iftar buffets each evening.
Chef de Cuisine Faustino Picardo Ines Jr and his culinary team have crafted diverse menus throughout the week.</description></item><item><title>The Al Meroz Hotel in Bangkok provides halal-certified menus and MICE services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 02:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-meroz-hotel-in-bangkok-provides-halal-certified-menus-and-mice-services/</guid><description>Source: Al Meroz Hotel website. The Grand Meroz Banquet Hall.
Located in Bangkok, Thailand, the Al Meroz hotel aims to provide an authentic Islamic experience for all guests, regardless of faith. The hotel features Arabesque architecture and serves halal-certified cuisine in a non-alcoholic setting, reflecting Islamic hospitality. Staff members are trained in Muslim traditions and attire, while also embodying the warmth and welcoming nature that Thailand is known for.</description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests.</description></item><item><title>Rasel offers artisanal catering services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rasel-offers-artisanal-catering-services/</guid><description>Rasel Catering Singapore, a top-tier halal catering service, has enhanced its offerings to become a leader in the industry.
Alan Tan, Co-Founder and Managing Director of Rasel Catering Singapore, highlighted the company’s focus on meeting the evolving needs of a global clientele. He stated, “Rasel caters to international events and weddings, recognizing the sophisticated tastes of today’s customers and their demand for high-quality halal food. Our service goes beyond just the food itself—we leverage our expertise to elevate the entire experience for our customers.</description></item><item><title>Joo Chiat Kim Choo introduces halal rice dumplings at 7-Eleven Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:54:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Joo Chiat Kim Choo/7-Eleven.
- Halal rice dumplings from Kim Choo Kid are now sold at all 7-Eleven stores in Singapore.
- Customers can choose from two flavors: Nonya Chicken and Salted Chicken. For convenience, the leaves have been removed.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 7-Eleven stores now offer a halal version of the famous Joo Chiat Kim Choo rice dumplings. Part of the Neo Group, this top rice dumpling maker in Singapore is known for its Nonya dumplings, made with a recipe handed down through generations.</description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar.</description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes.</description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market.</description></item><item><title>The Concorde Hotel Singapore is introducing mooncake gift sets in elegant mirror chests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 06:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website. Mooncakes from the Concorde Hotel will come in LED mirror chests.
The Concorde Hotel in Singapore is known for its unique mooncake packaging, and this year is no exception. This year, the mooncakes will be presented in a special LED mirror chest that lights up when opened.
Customers can choose from a variety of mooncake flavors, including bamboo charcoal with red dragon fruit and black sesame, golden jade lotus with a single yolk, pure lotus, white lotus, pure lotus with a single yolk, and white lotus with a single yolk.</description></item><item><title>This year, Concorde Hotel is arranging mooncakes in a vertical stack</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website.
For this Mid-Autumn Festival, Concorde Hotel Singapore is offering a selection of classic baked mooncakes. Customers can choose from traditional fillings like pure lotus paste, pure lotus with single or double yolks, and a less sweet white lotus with single yolk. Prices range from S$60 to S$68 for a box of four, including GST. Additionally, they offer a &amp;ldquo;Supreme Manju&amp;rdquo; flavor at S$64 for a box of four.</description></item><item><title>Foh San provides mooncake corporate orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</guid><description>Foh San, a restaurant originally known for its dim sum, has become a popular provider of both dim sum and mooncakes. They offer a diverse selection of halal mooncakes, with both baked and non-baked options available. Customers can purchase these mooncakes in elegant presentation boxes designed to hold either two or four mooncakes. Additionally, there is a premium box option which includes four mooncakes and a special gaharu (agarwood or oud) tea.</description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become a leading global e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Aladdinstreet.com.sg, a global e-marketplace specializing in premium and halal products, has officially launched. Catering to both businesses and individual consumers, the platform offers a range of halal-certified products alongside premium items that don&amp;rsquo;t require certification.
Since its initial announcement in July 2016, Aladdinstreet.com.sg has carefully selected 200 merchants for inclusion on the site, formalizing agreements with nearly 60. Approximately half of these merchants provide halal-friendly or halal-certified products, encompassing diverse categories such as food, beverages, vitamins, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, fashion, and more.</description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey.</description></item></channel></rss>