<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Job on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/job/</link><description>Recent content in Job on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:07:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/job/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The FastGig app has been released to connect flexible workers with job opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fastgig-app-has-been-released-to-connect-flexible-workers-with-job-opportunities/</guid><description>FastCo, the company known for its Asian non-executive job platform FastJobs, has launched FastGig, an app designed for the expanding gig economy. FastCo claims this is one of the first apps specifically for gig workers in Southeast Asia.
FastGig, operating as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first workforce-as-a-service (WaaS) platform, connects skilled flexible workers with companies facing staffing shortages, particularly during peak seasons.
Julian Tan, FastCo&amp;rsquo;s Founder &amp;amp; CEO, highlights FastGig as a solution to a significant market gap, providing flexibility for both workers and businesses and transforming Singapore&amp;rsquo;s gig economy.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is implementing measures to ensure that esports becomes a profitable industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-implementing-measures-to-ensure-that-esports-becomes-a-profitable-industry/</guid><description>Source: SCOGA. From left: Matthias Beyer, Partnerships Lead, Southeast Asia at Twitch, Dennis Ooi, Honorary Secretary of (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA), Kelvin Tan, President and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Nicholas Khoo, Chairman and Co-Founder of SCOGA, Raiford Cockfield III, Director of APAC Partnerships at Twitch, and Dr Charles Ling, COO, Informatics Education.
As esports&amp;rsquo; popularity explodes globally, the (Singapore) Cybersports &amp;amp; Online Gaming Association (SCOGA) has established new partnerships to cultivate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s esports landscape.</description></item><item><title>First Advantage reported that ten percent of job candidates in the Asia Pacific region are dishonest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-advantage-reported-that-ten-percent-of-job-candidates-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-dishonest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 14:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-advantage-reported-that-ten-percent-of-job-candidates-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-dishonest/</guid><description>First Advantage, a company that specializes in background verification, has found that over 10% of resumes from job applicants in the Asia Pacific region contain inconsistencies. This issue is particularly prominent in Australia, where 12% of candidates were found to have significant discrepancies on their resumes. The company noted a higher rate of alerts related to criminal records and employment history checks among Australian candidates compared to other countries.
First Advantage recommends that companies implement screening practices not only to comply with industry regulations, ensure employee competence, and mitigate physical, legal, and financial risks but also to safeguard their brand reputation.</description></item><item><title>The uptrend in online hiring in Singapore is being led by the IT, BFSI, and advertising industries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 06:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</guid><description>Singapore saw an increase in online recruitment in November 2018, with a 5% rise in job postings compared to the same period in 2017, as reported by the Monster Employment Index (MEI). This represents a significant jump from the 1% growth recorded in October 2018.
The IT, telecom, BPO/ITES sector experienced the most substantial growth, surging by 22% year-on-year, marking its highest point since March 2018. BFSI and advertising also demonstrated positive trends, rising by 16% and 15% respectively compared to the previous year.</description></item><item><title>The future of work revolves around extracting valuable business insights from data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 01:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</guid><description>The rise of robotics and artificial intelligence (AI) is a significant development for the workforce. The shortage of skilled professionals across industries has made automation increasingly appealing to employers. It is evident that automation and AI have the potential to replace a considerable portion of tasks currently performed by humans.
Reactions to this trend are varied, ranging from optimism to apprehension. An Oracle study reveals that 93% of individuals would readily follow instructions from robots in the workplace, demonstrating a high level of trust in automation.</description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>Strong job market in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>A new report by recruitment firm REED indicates that 78% of employees in Hong Kong received a pay raise in the last year. The report, titled REED 2015 Salary Survey and Market Insight, covers 14 countries across Asia, Australia, Europe, and the Middle East.
REED predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s thriving job market will continue to grow in 2015, driven by substantial foreign investments. The financial, digital marketing, e-commerce, and sales &amp;amp; marketing industries are expected to be particularly strong.</description></item><item><title>Top-paying technology jobs for 2014 - for those in the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/top-paying-technology-jobs-for-2014-for-those-in-the-united-states/</guid><description>The 2014 Salary Guides published by Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group identify six technology and digital jobs experiencing high demand in the US. This demand may also be reflected in the Asia Pacific region.
Companies are specifically seeking professionals skilled in information and network security, data analysis for business intelligence, and mobile development.
&amp;ldquo;Building a strong online presence and engaging customers through mobile platforms is crucial for businesses today,&amp;rdquo; says John Reed, Senior Executive Director of Robert Half Technology and The Creative Group.</description></item><item><title>The demand for HR and admin professionals is increasing in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</guid><description>For the first time since March 2018, HR and administrative (admin) jobs in Malaysia experienced a 2% year-over-year increase in December.
This job category also saw recent positive short-term growth, with a 4% rise month-over-month and a 2% increase over three months. The Philippines echoed this positive trend, with online hiring demand for HR and admin professionals surging by 22% year-on-year.
Demand for HR and admin interns remained strong in Malaysia and the Philippines, representing the highest demand among all surveyed occupations at 13% and 5%, respectively.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item><item><title>According to LinkedIn, 65% of employees in Singapore are planning to change jobs in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</guid><description>Although hiring in Singapore experienced a significant drop of 34% in December 2022 compared to the previous year, and despite economic uncertainties, professionals are adopting a forward-thinking approach to their careers. They are investing in skill development and actively pursuing opportunities for advancement. LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that a considerable 65% of professionals are contemplating job changes in 2023.
The desire for enhanced financial stability amidst rising living costs is a primary driver behind this job search trend.</description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date.</description></item></channel></rss>