<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Phone Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phone-systems/</link><description>Recent content in Phone Systems on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phone-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed Hosting PBX Gets You Out Of The Telephone Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 08:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-pbx-gets-you-out-of-the-telephone-business/</guid><description>A lot of businesses find themselves managing their own phone systems simply because they need phones to operate, even though it&amp;rsquo;s not their core business. This has become the norm, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be this way anymore.
Companies previously invested in extensive phone systems because the productivity gains from each employee having a direct line outweighed the costs. In the past, a single phone line sufficed, but with the information age, constant communication became essential, driving the need for dedicated telecom departments.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Installers Business Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</guid><description>For businesses selling or installing business telephone systems, there&amp;rsquo;s a valuable networking service to know about. It can provide you with more warm leads and expand your product offerings without any extra cost.
This service is the VAR Partner Network, an online platform run by Telarus, Inc. Telarus is a master agency that works with many different voice and data carriers. But it offers much more than that. Through its VAR Network, Telarus actively connects with businesses seeking not just communication services, but also equipment sales and installation.</description></item></channel></rss>