<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sudden on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sudden/</link><description>Recent content in Sudden on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sudden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): First Contact and Two Dead Transistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 that was already being repaired but needed further troubleshooting. The unit is in good cosmetic condition with minor wear. Upon inspection, the platter motor ran when turned on, but the carriage remained static.
Further investigation revealed that transistor TR20, responsible for the carriage motor control, was faulty. Replacing this component restored carriage movement.
However, the carriage would move only slightly before returning to its starting position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): More RPM Measurements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/</guid><description>Following up on the Beogram 4002 (5513) from the previous day, I conducted an overnight RPM (revolutions per minute) performance test using my BeoloverRPM device.
The resulting measurement curve demonstrates excellent performance, typical of DC motor models. It shows minimal fluctuations (less than 0.05%) over time, aligning with the service manual&amp;rsquo;s specifications. The initial upward slope, lasting a couple of hours, is a common trait in the 551x and 552x models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Initial RPM Performance Characterization</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 09:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/</guid><description>This post follows up on my initial writing about the Beogram 4002 (5513). I used my recently created BeoloverRPM device to assess the unit&amp;rsquo;s RPM performance.
This test clearly showed the suspected rapid speed changes. The graph below displays the RPM over a roughly 24-hour period.
The abrupt negative spikes in the graph indicate that the DC motor and its control system require attention.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): RPM Performance Measurement after Restoration of DC Motor and Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</guid><description>Following the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable&amp;rsquo;s DC motor and control system, a 24-hour RPM performance test was conducted using a custom-built RPM monitoring device.
The initial performance, measured before the restoration, revealed noticeable, abrupt drops in RPM, indicating typical wear and tear in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings. These dips, while moderate in this instance, would have been audible due to their 1% magnitude.
After the restoration, which included rebuilding the motor and replacing RPM-related components, the significant RPM fluctuations were eliminated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Random Stop Issue Fixed - Defective Photo Resistor in the Spindle RPM Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, previously restored, began experiencing a problem where the OFF function would randomly activate during playback as if the button was pressed.
Prior to delving into the solution, the circuit diagram is presented for reference.
Transistor TR17, within the &amp;lsquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rsquo; section, is responsible for initiating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s OFF function. When its base is grounded, the collector rises to approximately 18V, causing the arm to lift and return to its resting position.</description></item></channel></rss>