<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SSL VPN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssl-vpn/</link><description>Recent content in SSL VPN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ssl-vpn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advantages of SSL VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</guid><description>Cybersecurity is a significant concern for all internet users. With frequent news of hacking, data breaches, identity theft, and malicious bots, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that people are anxious about the security of their sensitive information, especially with the move towards cloud-based storage. This has led to a surge in interest in virtual private networks (VPNs).
Why would one choose a virtual private network over a traditional one?
The answer lies in our need for widespread connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item></channel></rss>