<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Messenger on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/messenger/</link><description>Recent content in Messenger on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/messenger/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facebook enhances the Messenger chat platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
During Facebook&amp;rsquo;s F8 conference, the company launched Messenger Platform. With over 40 apps available for download, users can enhance their conversations through GIFs, photos, videos, audio clips, and more.
Source: Facebook. Users will be prompted to install new apps.
Source: Facebook. Messenger will allow businesses and customers to communicate directly, replacing traditional methods like email or phone calls.
Facebook also provided a sneak peek of Businesses on Messenger.</description></item><item><title>Yahoo's latest Messenger is designed for socializing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-s-latest-messenger-is-designed-for-socializing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yahoo-s-latest-messenger-is-designed-for-socializing/</guid><description>Yahoo has launched a brand new Yahoo Messenger, available on mobile devices, the web, and within Yahoo Mail on desktop computers. This updated version of Yahoo Messenger simplifies the process of sharing, liking, and interacting with messages, images, and animated GIFs.
According to Jeff Bonforte, Senior VP of communication products and engineering at Yahoo, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to present the next generation of Yahoo Messenger. While it has always been a key offering for us, it was time for a complete overhaul, a rebuilding from the ground up, to reinvest in a product that holds such significance in our company&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item></channel></rss>