<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Survey on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/survey/</link><description>Recent content in Survey on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/survey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore National Administrative Professionals Week is here. If you need someone to talk to, I'm here for you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 18:37:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</guid><description>A recent survey conducted by Zyllem, a delivery service, in honor of Singapore Administrative Professionals Day 2016, showed that 93% of respondents believe that Administrative Professionals are the unsung heroes of Singaporean businesses.
However, the survey also revealed that 64% of coworkers admitted to taking their Admin Professionals for granted. They frequently rely on them to perform tasks outside their job description, including delivering umbrellas to colleagues stuck in the rain, sending forgotten passports to colleagues at airport check-in, performing first aid, and even providing early morning wake-up calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-national-administrative-professionals-week-is-here-if-you-need-someone-to-talk-to-i-m-here-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The popularity of cosmetic surgery is increasing globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/</guid><description>Cosmetic surgery is becoming increasingly popular. Over 23 million cosmetic procedures, both surgical and non-surgical, were performed globally in 2013, as reported by the International Society of Aesthetic Plastic Surgery (ISAPS). This international society comprises over 2,700 board-certified aesthetic plastic surgeons across 95 countries.
Botulinum toxin (Botox) injections were the most common cosmetic procedure performed.
Dr. Carlos Uebel, ISAPS President, highlighted the improved data collection strategy for the report, stating that the society aimed to enhance the comprehensiveness and statistical soundness of the survey methodology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-cosmetic-surgery-is-increasing-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Think about the possibility of working in the Middle East to increase your savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</guid><description>A new study by Business Name Generator (BNG) reveals salary trends in 28 cities worldwide, focusing on four sectors: marketing, HR, creative, and tech.
Tech
Doha takes the lead as the highest-paying city for tech professionals, boasting an average annual salary of £127,888. Data scientists emerge as top earners, commanding an average yearly salary of £361,877. After factoring in the annual cost of living (£26,382), Doha still provides the highest disposable income for tech workers, reaching £101,506 annually...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/think-about-the-possibility-of-working-in-the-middle-east-to-increase-your-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is your company using mobile for recruiting?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</guid><description>Mobile interaction is crucial for successful recruitment in India. In 2014-15, almost half of companies surveyed by TimesJobs reported receiving 10-20% of job applications via mobile phones, significantly up from the previous year.
With mobile phones widespread, 65% of organizations in India now have mobile recruitment strategies, a 10% increase from the previous year, according to a TimesJobs.com survey.
Jobseeker behavior has shifted dramatically, with 85% of online job searching now done on smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bankers in the APAC region predict a decrease in M&amp;A activity under President Trump's administration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</guid><description>A recent survey of 300 Asia Pacific mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) professionals conducted by Intralinks, a secure platform used by dealmakers for content sharing, found that 75% of respondents believe a potential presidency under Donald Trump would negatively impact M&amp;amp;A activity in the region. This mirrors the global sentiment revealed by Intralinks&amp;rsquo; survey of 1,500 M&amp;amp;A professionals worldwide.
Intralinks&amp;rsquo; Global M&amp;amp;A Sentiment Survey shows 75% of Asian dealmakers consider Trump the most detrimental presidential candidate for M&amp;amp;A activity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Herbalife has found that women in Singapore who work are less active than men</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</guid><description>Herbalife, a worldwide nutrition company, has found some differences in the health outlooks and routines of working men and women in Singapore. Their Nutrition at Work survey showed that, compared to men, women in Singapore tend to stay at their desks longer, eat lunch at their desks more, and have more difficulty being active during a typical workday.
“Our aim as a global nutrition company is to provide members and customers with high-quality nutrition products that support healthy eating and active lifestyles,” said Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-has-found-that-women-in-singapore-who-work-are-less-active-than-men/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the behavior of luxury travelers from China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</guid><description>A recent study on Chinese luxury travelers, conducted by Marriott International and the Hurun Research Institute, reveals evolving travel preferences among young, affluent Chinese travelers aged 18 to 36. These travelers seek personalized experiences, value-added services throughout their journey, and seamless integration of technology.
The study indicates a preference for digital platforms, with WeChat emerging as the primary source for travel information, followed by official accounts, recommendations from friends, and travel professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intralinks APAC respondents predict that waves in China will have an impact on M&amp;A</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</guid><description>Dealmakers in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region believe that China&amp;rsquo;s economic and market activity will be the biggest influence on mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) in the region over the coming six months.
This insight comes from a survey of over 1,600 global M&amp;amp;A professionals conducted by Intralinks, a leading provider of M&amp;amp;A deal management and secure collaboration solutions. The survey, conducted between October 4 and 11, 2016, gathered responses from dealmakers across APAC, Europe, the Middle East and Africa, North America, and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intralinks-apac-respondents-predict-that-waves-in-china-will-have-an-impact-on-m-a/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investors are increasingly optimistic about placing foreign direct investment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore achieved a top-ten ranking in the 2016 AT Kearney Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) Confidence Index. The city-state climbed five positions, representing the most significant advancement in the rankings, securing the 10th spot.
This index provides a future-oriented assessment of how political, economic, and regulatory shifts are likely to influence FDI inflows into various countries in the coming years. Since its inception in 1998, the study has consistently identified the preferred global destinations for FDI, with the index rankings closely mirroring actual global FDI inflows...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The implementation of smart technologies is increasing revenues by up to 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</guid><description>A global Avanade study, involving Australian executives, business unit leaders, and IT decision-makers, reveals that a majority of business leaders are already investing in and seeing positive results from incorporating smart technologies in their workplaces. A key motivator is the potential for increased revenue, with business and IT leaders projecting up to a 33% revenue boost from these technologies within the next five years. Furthermore, companies anticipate retraining existing employees, generating new roles, and restructuring their organizations as they predict the repurposing of up to 20% of current roles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Workers value recognition more than money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</guid><description>Source: ACCA report. Tone at the top influences corporate behaviour the most, according to 61% of respondents.
A recent report by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) titled &amp;ldquo;Culture and channelling corporate behaviour: ACCA member survey&amp;rdquo; found that workplace recognition is the most significant motivator for employees across all ages, industries, and locations. Notably, this recognition even outweighs monetary rewards.
The survey, conducted with support from the Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC), gathered insights from nearly 2,000 ACCA finance professionals globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workers-value-recognition-more-than-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are now blending their physical and digital experiences. How should companies respond?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 14:27:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</guid><description>A new study emphasizes the importance of personalization in merging online and offline shopping experiences for &amp;ldquo;phy-gital&amp;rdquo; consumers. The study found that while companies are embracing digital technologies, they are lagging in implementing personalization strategies that consumers desire.
The study revealed that personalized promotions significantly influence purchasing decisions, encouraging consumers to buy familiar products and explore new ones. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect between consumer expectations and company investments. While consumers value enhanced search and comparison features, companies prioritize features like shopping lists and social elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-now-blending-their-physical-and-digital-experiences-how-should-companies-respond/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Within the next five years, one-third of young Arabs intend to launch their own businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</guid><description>According to the 2016 ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey, over one-third of young Arabs plan to launch their own businesses within the next five years. The survey indicates that young Arabs believe governments could do more to support them, such as promoting affordable lending, enhancing training and education opportunities, and reducing bureaucratic hurdles.
When asked if their generation is more likely to start businesses than previous ones, 54% agreed. GCC youth were the most optimistic at 62%, compared to 54% in North Africa and 44% in the Levant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If apps don't offer speed, simplicity, and security, consumers will not hesitate to abandon them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:48:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</guid><description>Source: CA Technologies infographic.
People are pickier than ever about the apps they use, so businesses that don&amp;rsquo;t offer a good app experience could lose a significant portion of their customers. A regional study* sponsored by CA Technologies shows that mobile and desktop applications in the Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) region have become key to earning customer loyalty.
Software: the New Battleground for Brand Loyalty – A survey of 1,449 consumers and 259 business decision-makers across five APJ nations pinpointed three major factors influencing the customer experience: Source: CA Technologies infographic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-apps-don-t-offer-speed-simplicity-and-security-consumers-will-not-hesitate-to-abandon-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra discusses the obstacles of maintaining productivity in a workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</guid><description>Source: Jabra research report.
According to audio and communications company Jabra, modern workplaces face difficulties in fostering productivity due to common hurdles employees experience daily. These include distractions, poorly structured meetings, and technology that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as intended.
Jabra&amp;rsquo;s 2015 research report, Productivity at the Office – Challenges, highlights that while companies invest in resources and tools to help office workers collaborate and focus, employees still encounter obstacles. These include constant distractions, unproductive meetings, and challenges utilizing technology meant to enhance their output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contract positions are the perfect solution for companies in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent survey by Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, indicates a rise in contract employment in Singapore. The Singapore Contracting Survey reveals that hiring managers are increasingly turning to skilled contract workers due to difficulties in obtaining approval for permanent positions. Many companies are implementing hiring freezes, often mandated by their headquarters, leading managers in Singapore to seek adaptable, temporary staffing solutions.
The survey, which polled over 300 professionals in Singapore with contracting experience, explored the advantages and disadvantages of contract work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM reports that early adopters of cloud-based software are experiencing tangible benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 18:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</guid><description>IBM has revealed that nearly half of the businesses utilizing Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) are gaining a competitive edge, rather than just reducing expenses. This insight comes from a recent global survey conducted by the IBM Center for Applied Insights, involving over 800 IT and business decision-makers.
The study confirms that SaaS offers a wide range of advantages beyond lowering overall costs. It demonstrates that organizations strategically and collaboratively implementing SaaS are better equipped to execute programs that drive business growth compared to those slower to adopt SaaS...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent Euromonitor survey reveals sugar as a new culprit in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has observed a growing global trend of consumers turning against sugar. This shift in attitude stems from heightened awareness of its health implications.
Consumers are actively trying to decrease or eliminate sugar from their diets, with a significant 42% actively looking for food labels indicating low or no added sugar, according to Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Global Consumer Trends Survey.
&amp;ldquo;Sugar is now widely perceived as a health risk, with some even equating it to tobacco in terms of toxicity,&amp;rdquo; says Gina Westbrook, Director of Strategy Briefings at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region anticipate an increase in fraud over the next five years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 20:24:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</guid><description>A new report by Experian Asia Pacific, titled &amp;ldquo;The Economics of Fraud: Mitigating Risk Amidst Fast Growth and Innovation,&amp;rdquo; found that 59% of Asia Pacific businesses anticipate an increase in fraud over the next five years. This has led to more than half (51%) of these businesses investing more in fraud prevention.
The report, which explores the current fraud landscape for businesses in Asia Pacific, reveals some key findings about fast-growing markets:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore companies are considering hiring senior technology professionals to address the shortage of talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</guid><description>Despite job market growth, a 2017 survey by the Singapore Infocomm Technology Federation (SiTF) reveals that the infocommunications (ICM) industry struggles to find talent with the right IT and business skills.
The survey of 181 companies found that 75% consider recruiting suitable talent their biggest challenge. This problem particularly affects startups (91%), followed by small and medium enterprises (SMEs) at 76% and multinational corporations (MNCs) at 75%.
Source: SITF. The talent situation in Singapore for ICM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-companies-are-considering-hiring-senior-technology-professionals-to-address-the-shortage-of-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is the third best city in APEC for living and conducting business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</guid><description>A new study presented at the APEC 2015 CEO Summit has positioned Singapore as the third most desirable city for living and conducting business within the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) region.
Conducted by PwC, the &amp;ldquo;Building Better Cities&amp;rdquo; study aims to provide city leaders with insights into their current standings and to encourage collaboration and knowledge sharing among APEC cities to tackle persistent challenges.
The study examines the role urban centers play in APEC&amp;rsquo;s economic and social progress, emphasizing their growing global influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Singaporeans are aware of human trafficking but underestimate its prevalence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</guid><description>The International Organization for Migration’s X Campaign (IOM X), in collaboration with USAID, the US Embassy in Singapore, and Microsoft, recently released findings from their pilot outreach program, IOM X Connect Singapore. This initiative sought to increase awareness about human trafficking in Singapore.
During the project, students from the National University of Singapore (NUS) and Singapore Management University (SMU) utilized the newly developed IOM X Learn, Act and Share App. They tested the knowledge of 100 Singaporean residents on the topic of human trafficking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-singaporeans-are-aware-of-human-trafficking-but-underestimate-its-prevalence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson reveals insights on video consumption habits of consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Looking for effective ways to invest your marketing budget? The recent Ericsson ConsumerLab TV &amp;amp; Media Report might offer some valuable insights.
Now in its fifth year, the study surveyed 1,000 individuals in Singapore for the first time. The results reveal that 80% of Singaporeans engage in streaming TV or video content at least once a week, while 72% continue to watch traditional broadcast programs. Globally, 75% of consumers stream content multiple times weekly, compared to 77% who watch scheduled broadcast TV programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>