<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Indirect Effect on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/indirect-effect/</link><description>Recent content in Indirect Effect on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/indirect-effect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>The law on civil liability for Internet publishing clarified by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-law-on-civil-liability-for-internet-publishing-clarified-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Analyzing the Papasavvas Case: Intermediary Liability in the Digital Age This post examines the recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling in the Papasavvas case, which explores the definition of &amp;ldquo;intermediary&amp;rdquo; in EU information technology law. This issue has become increasingly complex since the drafting of the eCommerce Directive in 2000, as the digital landscape has evolved to include services blurring the lines between content providers and transmitters.</description></item></channel></rss>