<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Activated on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/activated/</link><description>Recent content in Activated on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/activated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance.</description></item></channel></rss>