<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>QR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qr/</link><description>Recent content in QR on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>