<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Apple IPad on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apple-ipad/</link><description>Recent content in Apple IPad on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/apple-ipad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is The End Of Cellular Phone Near?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 02:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</guid><description>Cell phones are essential to modern life, but a recent development calls into question the future of cellular service. The release of the Apple iPad and its allowance of VoIP applications over 3G cellular networks, along with AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network adjustments for this capability, signal a potential shift in the telecommunications landscape.
Why is this significant? Cellular networks have historically blocked VoIP due to its potential to congest networks and cannibalize voice call revenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-of-cellular-phone-near/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smartphone Charger and Backup Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</guid><description>We all know the struggle of low battery life. It always seems to happen at the worst possible time, leaving us stranded. If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of being tethered to a wall outlet, the ZAGGsparq 2.0 might be the solution.
This handy device is both a charger and a backup battery. You can charge your USB devices, which seems like almost everything these days, and it provides up to four times the charge of your device&amp;rsquo;s battery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-charger-and-backup-battery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>iPad Jones. I’ve Got An iPad Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 12:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in e-book readers since the Amazon Kindle was released. The idea of carrying many books conveniently is appealing. Even better is the ability to enlarge the font size for reading without glasses. Plus, not needing shelf space for dusty books is a definite advantage. However, I haven&amp;rsquo;t purchased one because I don&amp;rsquo;t read books constantly anymore. The interactive nature of the internet holds my attention more effectively. An e-book reader combined with an internet-capable computer would be amazing!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ipad-jones-i-ve-got-an-ipad-jones/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>