<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asymmetrical Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asymmetrical-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Asymmetrical Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asymmetrical-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions.</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Service Access For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-service-access-for-business/</guid><description>Having internet access is essential for businesses today, whether they operate primarily online or from a physical location. It&amp;rsquo;s how businesses connect with customers, suppliers, remote employees, and even their own offices. But is the internet service used by businesses the same as what individuals use at home?
There are actually different options for internet service, each with unique features: dedicated or shared bandwidth, symmetrical or asymmetrical speeds, wired or wireless connection, copper or fiber optic cables, and varying levels of bandwidth and cost.</description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>