<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colocation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation/</link><description>Recent content in Colocation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Infrastructure as a Service Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 01:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</guid><description>Cloud computing is widely understood to have three main levels: Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS), Platform as a Service (PaaS), and Software as a Service (SaaS). The most fundamental of these is IaaS, which forms the basis for the other two. IaaS essentially refers to providing basic hardware and operating system software over the internet.
Infrastructure is fairly self-explanatory: it&amp;rsquo;s the foundational hardware and software needed for computing. When considering cloud infrastructure, the comparison is often made with having your own data center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/infrastructure-as-a-service-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Windfall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</guid><description>When budgets are strained, expanding into new markets and generating much-needed revenue often depends on increasing Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. However, more bandwidth usually means higher expenses, creating a difficult situation.
It&amp;rsquo;s generally accepted that increasing bandwidth leads to increased costs. For instance, 10 Mbps will likely cost more than 1 Mbps, although there might be a volume discount. But is it possible to get more bandwidth while paying less overall?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses currently using T1 lines for dedicated internet or point-to-point connections might be seeking ways to increase bandwidth without the high costs of upgrading to DS3 fiber optic cable. Metro Ethernet offers a solution. But how can you find it?
Locating Metro Ethernet service is straightforward with the right approach. Similar to finding anything else, the key is knowing where to look. A specialized tool designed to locate and map available Ethernet bandwidth in your vicinity is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation and Connectivity in Miami</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</guid><description>Miami, Florida, serves as a strategic location for businesses aiming to connect with South America, Central America, the Caribbean, and regions across the Atlantic. Telx, a prominent provider of colocation services, offers comprehensive solutions tailored to meet these connectivity needs.
Telx has established a strong reputation in the financial services sector by delivering ultra-low latency connections to electronic trading floors. Their extensive network encompasses 15 colocation facilities within the United States and global connectivity to over 800 carriers, ensuring comprehensive and reliable connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Leverages Your IT Staff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, most companies, including large and well-known ones, are hesitant to increase their staff. This poses a challenge for IT departments, which are often unable to grow to meet rising demands and may face hiring freezes or even staff reductions. How can this situation be managed effectively to prevent a decline in morale and productivity?
One solution is to find a way to increase the output of each team member without negatively impacting their well-being or overloading them with work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Siren Song of Cloud Computing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 14:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</guid><description>The pervasiveness of cloud computing, services, and networks in technological discussions today is undeniable. This buzz might even remind you of the catchy tune, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Computing,&amp;rdquo; by Loose Bruce Kerr (a playful nod to Joni Mitchell).
Similar to the shift from mainframes to networked PCs and back to a centralized system in the cloud, cloud services represent a significant technological advancement. While security and connectivity concerns exist, the widespread adoption of cloud services could make purchasing and updating software seem as outdated as physical switches on computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-siren-song-of-cloud-computing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation vs Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</guid><description>The choice between &amp;ldquo;make&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;buy&amp;rdquo; is about deciding whether to handle tasks internally or outsource them. IT managers frequently face this dilemma when contemplating between managing an on-site data center and opting for a colocation facility. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a third option: the cloud.
While both colocation and cloud services are obtained from external providers, the differences between them are significant from an operational standpoint.
Colocation facilities shine by offering a physical space designed for IT needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Multiple Data Center Dilemma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</guid><description>The increasing number of mergers and acquisitions has left many companies with a surplus of data centers. Instead of choosing one data center to become the central hub, companies should consider the unique characteristics of each facility, such as equipment, applications, and staffing. Furthermore, consolidating data centers necessitates a reassessment of connectivity.
While internal network traffic often surpasses external traffic, the rising reliance on cloud services demands greater Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Diverse Connections For Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</guid><description>The reliability of data connections is crucial for data centers and colocation facilities to ensure service availability. Having multiple separate network connections is not enough; you need multiple diverse data connections from different providers that take different routes to your facility.
Simply having multiple connections from a single provider offers limited protection because a catastrophic failure could take down the entire connection. This risk is amplified in your own facility, where a single connection runs for miles and is vulnerable to disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diverse-connections-for-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Making The Move For Higher Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</guid><description>Are you experiencing bandwidth limitations in your organization? With the rapid advancement of online technology, many organizations are facing a shortage of bandwidth. While contacting your service provider to increase your line speed might seem like the solution, they might inform you that you already have the maximum speed available. So, what are your options?
Have you thought about relocating? Bandwidth availability and cost vary significantly by location. Some places have many choices and reasonable prices, while others might not be able to meet your basic needs regardless of your budget...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telecom Providers Build Their Own Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</guid><description>As cloud computing companies start to establish themselves, internet service providers and similar carriers are developing their own cloud services. This creates a challenge for IT professionals and business owners who need to choose the best option.
It’s important to recognize that cloud computing is still in its early stages. Like any new technology, it will take time for it to fully develop. As the technology progresses, we will see a lot of activity from many different companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-providers-build-their-own-clouds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Type of Data Center Connectivity Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</guid><description>When thinking about moving to a colocation center or building a data center or private cloud off-site, you&amp;rsquo;ll face both opportunities and difficulties in setting up your network connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the key factors and uncover potential cost-saving opportunities.
The main difference between on-site and remote data centers, including colocation facilities, lies in how you manage network connections. On-site, you have full control over your local wiring. Off-site, you lease connections through service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Booming For Telx Interconnection and Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</guid><description>Despite the current economic downturn, data center provider Telx is experiencing a surge in construction at their main Chicago facility. This might seem counterintuitive during a recession, but it makes sense considering the ongoing technological transformation in business and finance.
Companies have shifted from manual processes to computer-based systems, leading to a client-server model that boosted efficiency and productivity. Now, forward-thinking companies are seeking new strategies for a competitive edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting With a Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve considered cloud computing as a potential solution for your business but hesitate due to the investment and commitment. Now, a free trial for cloud hosting presents the perfect opportunity to explore its benefits.
Cloud hosting is a practical step for businesses exceeding their shared hosting capacity and considering VPS or dedicated servers. Cloud hosting surpasses these alternatives by offering flexibility and cost advantages.
VPS and dedicated servers eliminate the need for capital expenditures and infrastructure management associated with running a data center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-with-a-free-trial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Routes To Europe and Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/</guid><description>Numerous American companies establish branches in the UK and Europe, while multinational corporations operate globally. A prevalent solution for connecting these international offices, including cloud services, is low-latency fiber optic routes. The term &amp;ldquo;low latency,&amp;rdquo; once obscure, gained prominence with the shift from traditional phone lines to VoIP. Previously, it primarily described delays in satellite communication.
The question arises: why the emphasis on low-latency fiber routes now? Aren&amp;rsquo;t fiber connections inherently low latency?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-routes-to-europe-and-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes High Frequency Trading Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</guid><description>Computerized trading, including high frequency trading, is now the norm in the stock market. As seen on CBS News, algorithms can automatically execute trades when specific conditions are met.
A key challenge of automated trading is ensuring fairness by synchronizing timing for all participants. The New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) addressed this by creating a data center that standardized access time to 65 microseconds for everyone. However, this only applies to trading within the NYSE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Connections Bridge The Atlantic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 05:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</guid><description>The immense volume of data flowing through global fiber optic networks highlights our interconnected world. While intercontinental cables have existed for years, low latency networks are becoming increasingly vital.
High-frequency trading, particularly the use of automated programs, drives the demand for low latency. These programs compete to execute trades milliseconds or even microseconds faster than competitors, a feat impossible for human traders. This speed makes the physical path between traders and exchanges critical, with the delay on this path known as latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting in Clouds and Colos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</guid><description>There are many hosting choices available. Shared hosting is popular among individuals and small businesses due to its affordability and acceptable performance. However, as your needs grow, you face a decision: self-hosting or a managed solution.
While setting up a website previously required technical expertise in server management, Linux and Windows hosting have become increasingly user-friendly and widely accessible. Even large enterprises accustomed to managing their servers in-house are reconsidering colocation and cloud solutions, driven by cost and resource optimization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 04:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</guid><description>When you have a website or online store, you&amp;rsquo;re already familiar with web hosting. But did you know there are different types of web hosting? One type you might not know about is managed hosting, which can be more reliable and affordable than trying to handle everything yourself.
In the early days of the internet, businesses often set up their websites by getting server software and using one computer as the web host...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>