<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Financial Regulation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial-regulation/</link><description>Recent content in Financial Regulation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/financial-regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gaining Entry to the EU's Financial Services Market in the Absence of a Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (Twitter: @KulpaBart)
Introduction
When Boris Johnson became British Prime Minister, a no-deal Brexit appeared increasingly possible. UK-based financial services firms were left wondering if and how they would be able to continue serving clients in the remaining 27 EU countries. These firms currently depend on &amp;ldquo;passporting rights,&amp;rdquo; which allow them to operate across borders. According to The Economist, in 2016, 5,476 British financial services firms used 336,421 European passports to offer their products across the EU.</description></item><item><title>The European Commission's suggestions for environmentally-friendly finance and the efforts of financial regulators to promote sustainability.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</guid><description>Thomas Piticchio The rising popularity of green politics has led investors to demand more sustainable investment options and increased transparency regarding their money&amp;rsquo;s whereabouts and usage. Consequently, financial intermediaries are introducing &amp;ldquo;green&amp;rdquo; financial products. These products are undergoing regulatory development by the European Commission, aiming to direct capital towards sustainability and clarify what defines a sustainable investment.
In 2018, the European Commission tasked a group of specialists from social, financial, and academic fields to formulate a sustainable finance strategy.</description></item><item><title>Imprisoning bankers: the latest EU Directive on enforcing criminal penalties for market abuse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU politicians likely feel a sense of relief as they&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a group even less popular than themselves: bankers. This unpopularity has only intensified as the global financial crisis and resulting austerity measures continue to impact ordinary citizens across numerous Member States. Politicians understand that targeting disliked groups rarely hurts them in the polls, leading EU institutions to enact legislation that could imprison bankers for specific wrongdoings.</description></item><item><title>The Future of Europe: A Preview of the Five Presidents' Report on EMU Completion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 14:49:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-europe-a-preview-of-the-five-presidents-report-on-emu-completion/</guid><description>Menelaos Markakis, DPhil student at University of Oxford, Academy of Athens scholar
In June 2015, the leaders of the EU and Euro area institutions released a report outlining a plan for strengthening and finalizing the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU). This report, based on crisis-combatting measures, offers numerous suggestions for improving the EMU&amp;rsquo;s governance and deepening economic integration within the Euro area. The EU Presidents suggest advancing towards a unified economic, financial, fiscal, and political system.</description></item></channel></rss>