<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KSA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ksa/</link><description>Recent content in KSA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:57:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ksa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Value Added Tax (VAT) has been implemented in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 05:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/value-added-tax-vat-has-been-implemented-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>In anticipation of the January 1, 2018 Value Added Tax (VAT) launch, the KSA General Authority for Zakat and Tax introduced a mobile app on December 30, 2017. This app provides key information about VAT and helps consumers verify VAT registration status of businesses.
The app&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;check&amp;rdquo; function allows consumers to scan the barcode on a VAT registration certificate or enter the business&amp;rsquo; Commercial Registration Number or 15-digit VAT identification number from an invoice to confirm registration.</description></item><item><title>ITFC and Catalyst Group collaborate to enhance trade for small and medium enterprises in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 06:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itfc-and-catalyst-group-collaborate-to-enhance-trade-for-small-and-medium-enterprises-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>The International Islamic Trade Finance Corporation (ITFC) and Catalyst Group, a Jeddah-based real estate company, have partnered to support small and medium-sized enterprise (SME) trade development in Saudi Arabia. This collaboration will launch ITFC’s KSA SME Program, starting with a pilot SME Trade Development Program (TDP) in Saudi Arabia, with the intention of expanding to other countries.
This agreement aligns with Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Vision 2030 SMEs Trade Development Program, which focuses on supporting businesses&amp;rsquo; export capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>Al Rajhi's initiative to promote card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-rajhi-s-initiative-to-promote-card-spending/</guid><description>Al Rajhi Bank has introduced its &amp;ldquo;House, Car and Salary&amp;rdquo; campaign, offering over SR4 million in prizes to encourage the use of its Mada and credit cards within Saudi Arabia and internationally.
The grand prize, exclusively for Saudi citizens, includes a house, a BMW 7 Series car, and a year of monthly SR20,000 payments. Four additional winners will receive a BMW 7 Series car each, while seven others will get a year of monthly SR20,000 payments.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016.</description></item><item><title>KSA is progressing with the privatization process</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</guid><description>The National Center for Privatization &amp;amp; PPP (NCP) is a new Saudi Arabian agency created to empower the nation&amp;rsquo;s private sector. Along with Supervisory Committees (SCs) established to oversee each privatization sector, the NCP will manage the transfer of government assets to private ownership.
Formed in April 2017 by the Council of Ministers, the NCP and the SCs are the first of their kind in the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year.</description></item><item><title>Wego collaborates with the Saudi Tourism Authority to boost tourism interest in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wego-collaborates-with-the-saudi-tourism-authority-to-boost-tourism-interest-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Wego, a leading online travel platform in the Middle East and North Africa, has partnered with the Saudi Tourism Authority to promote tourism in Saudi Arabia.
The collaboration will focus on attracting travelers from the region to destinations like Riyadh and Jeddah, showcasing Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s diverse landscapes, including deserts, mountains, and coastlines. Wego has observed significant interest in travel to Saudi Arabia, with a surge in flight and hotel bookings since travel restrictions were lifted.</description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI.</description></item><item><title>The MICE industry in KSA is expanding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-industry-in-ksa-is-expanding/</guid><description>In 2017, Saudi Arabia held more than 10,129 business events that were approved by the Saudi Exhibition and Convention Bureau (SECB), reflecting a 16% rise from the previous year.
The healthcare, education, technical, and communications industries made up the largest portion of business events within the 22 targeted economic sectors in 2017. The Riyadh region hosted 47% of these events, claiming the most business activity for the year. Following Riyadh, the Makkah region held 32% of events and the Eastern Province hosted 17%.</description></item><item><title>Budget airline flyadeal plans to extend its reach to more destinations in the Middle East in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s new low-cost airline, flyadeal, was officially launched on August 23 at King Abdulaziz International Airport in Jeddah. The event showcased flyadeal&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft, named &amp;ldquo;Al-Nayyir&amp;rdquo; (meaning &amp;ldquo;bright star&amp;rdquo;), which arrived from the Airbus delivery center in Hamburg, Germany.
Source: flyadeal. The budget airline flyadeal was inaugurated at a ceremony on August 24. The airline’s colors – a distinct palette of purple and lime – was on full display at the delivery event, along with members of the cabin crew, which gave guests a tour of the unique features onboard.</description></item><item><title>E-commerce sellers in Saudi Arabia are invited to join Maroof</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) cautions against the online sale or promotion of counterfeit products. This practice violates the Anti-Commercial Fraud Law and Trademark System, with potential consequences including imprisonment of up to three years and fines reaching SR1 million.
MCI recommends that entrepreneurs register with Maroof (http://www.maroof.sa/), a free e-service. Registration enhances businesses&amp;rsquo; credibility by officially documenting their information with the ministry. Maroof offers transparency through customer feedback, allowing shoppers to assess e-store quality.</description></item><item><title>Flynas has teamed up with Pegasus Airlines to provide flights from Saudi Arabia to Turkey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</guid><description>Source: flynas. Aerial view of Turkey.
The Saudi Arabian airline flynas has partnered with Turkish budget airline Pegasus Airlines to expand its flight offerings in Turkey. This collaboration will initially allow flynas passengers to travel to five new Turkish destinations: Antalya, Ankara, Adana, Hatay, and Trabzon. This will be achieved by utilizing Pegasus Airlines&amp;rsquo; extensive network of domestic flights operating from Istanbul&amp;rsquo;s Sabiha Gökçen International Airport.
Bander Al Mohanna, Group CEO of NAS Holding, stated that Pegasus Airlines is a leading Turkish airline with over two decades of experience in innovation within the country&amp;rsquo;s aviation industry.</description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia has announced the release of its 2017 budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s King Salman bin Abdulaziz recently announced the nation&amp;rsquo;s budget for 2017. The budget is set at SAR890 billion, representing an 8% rise from the previous year. It is anticipated to significantly reduce the kingdom&amp;rsquo;s deficit by a historic 33%.
King Salman emphasized the strength and resilience of the Saudi economy, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our economy is firm and it has sufficient strength to cope with the current economic and financial challenges.</description></item><item><title>Players from Manchester United and FC Barcelona will be participating in the GET Riyadh 2023 football competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 10:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/players-from-manchester-united-and-fc-barcelona-will-be-participating-in-the-get-riyadh-2023-football-competition/</guid><description>The Global Esports Tour (GET), a professional esports series by the Global Esports Federation, will commence its third season on August 26-27, 2023. This season&amp;rsquo;s launch event will take place at Boulevard Riyadh City, as a featured part of the Gamers8 festival.
Source: Global Esports Federation. Poster for GET Riyadh 2023.
KONAMI’s eFootball 2023 will be the primary game featured, with a prize pool totaling US$50,000. Professional football players, Lotfi Derradji and Kilyan Katou Judex Faucheux of Manchester United, alongside Alejandro Alguacil Seguira and Saul Adrian Chavez Saucedo of FC Barcelona, will participate alongside esports players.</description></item></channel></rss>