<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online Meetings on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-meetings/</link><description>Recent content in Online Meetings on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-meetings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Services With Free Trial Offers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-services-with-free-trial-offers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 02:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-services-with-free-trial-offers/</guid><description>Numerous businesses are turning to cloud services to reduce capital expenses and ongoing operational costs. This rapidly growing field has many vendors vying for market share, making it challenging to determine the ideal services for your needs.
For small businesses with limited budgets, ensuring maximum value for their IT and communication spending is crucial. One effective approach is to test services through free trials before committing. With this in mind, we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of cloud-based services offering trial periods.</description></item><item><title>Going Green Office Tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-green-office-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 11:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-green-office-tips/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s commemorate Earth Day by remembering that every day presents an opportunity to minimize waste and enhance energy efficiency. This approach is not only ethically sound but also financially beneficial. Let&amp;rsquo;s pinpoint some straightforward adjustments we can implement and evaluate their impact as we progress.
My compact office used to be unbearably hot in the summer and excessively warm even during Northern Illinois winters. Upon closer inspection, it became evident that several computers, a monitor, a TV, printers, overhead lights, and desk lamps were emitting a substantial amount of heat.</description></item></channel></rss>