<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FHA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fha/</link><description>Recent content in FHA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>