<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LinkedIn on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/linkedin/</link><description>Recent content in LinkedIn on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/linkedin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delta is launching Delta Innovation Classes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 01:46:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</guid><description>Delta Air Lines has devised a novel method for premium customers to distinguish themselves and share contact information, using a compelling offer.
As stated on the Delta Innovation Class website, the airline is offering a &amp;ldquo;mentoring program – that just so happens to take place at 35,000 feet.&amp;rdquo;
This program, Delta Innovation Class, a play on flight classes, gives one fortunate customer a complimentary seat next to a notable figure or celebrity on a designated flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delta-is-launching-delta-innovation-classes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The skills you possess will be valuable in securing future employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:50:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Legrand illustrates how LinkedIn is innovating by connecting existing skills with the needs of emerging jobs.
Olivier Legrand, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at LinkedIn, suggests that many individuals already possess some qualifications for in-demand jobs without realizing it.
During his keynote, &amp;ldquo;Job titles are out, skill sets are in,&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Computer Society&amp;rsquo;s Tech3 Forum, Legrand stated that LinkedIn aims to connect its members not only with employers but also with suitable companies, relevant jobs, and essential skills for future career prospects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-skills-you-possess-will-be-valuable-in-securing-future-employment-opportunities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Policies that bring about transformation could result in an increase in the number of women in leadership positions in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>This image, created by Blue Willow, depicts a generic office discussion. The artist was not given specific genders for those sitting or standing.
Recent LinkedIn data from Australia, India, and Singapore reveals a significant lack of female leadership in the Asia-Pacific region.
For example, women make up almost half of Australia&amp;rsquo;s workforce but only hold 35% of leadership roles. This figure has remained stagnant since 2020. India (23%) and Singapore (38%) show similar imbalances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/policies-that-bring-about-transformation-could-result-in-an-increase-in-the-number-of-women-in-leadership-positions-in-the-apac-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates provides LinkedIn Learning courses during flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates will offer LinkedIn courses inflight.
Emirates has teamed up with LinkedIn to offer a selection of LinkedIn Learning courses on its inflight entertainment system, ice. This makes Emirates the first international airline to provide these courses during flights.
This new addition to the ice system will launch in November and reflects Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to offering passengers fresh and diverse entertainment options. The free LinkedIn Learning courses, led by experts, range from 20 minutes to over two hours in length...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrating Social Media And Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</guid><description>We navigate two distinct realms: the digital sphere of communication, online activities, and social media, and the physical world of tangible experiences, relationships, and work. Although these realms overlap, their connection has been tenuous until recently.
Poken has emerged as a solution to bridge this gap between the digital and physical. As expected, it comprises both physical and virtual elements.
The tangible aspect is a device called Poken, resembling a digital avatar or a flash drive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>