<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video/</link><description>Recent content in Video on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology.</description></item><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession.</description></item><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson.</description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand.</description></item><item><title>The EOS M6 Mark II from Canon offers exceptional video production capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eos-m6-mark-ii-from-canon-offers-exceptional-video-production-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Canon the EOS M6 Mark II.
Canon has expanded its EOS M series of mirrorless cameras with the new EOS M6 Mark II. This stylish and portable camera is significantly lighter and smaller than a typical mid-range DSLR.
Edwin Teoh, Head of Marketing for Canon Singapore, highlights the EOS M6 Mark II&amp;rsquo;s portability and enhanced features, emphasizing its ability to capture life&amp;rsquo;s important moments. He also points out the camera&amp;rsquo;s advanced video capabilities, catering to the increasing popularity of videography and vlogging.</description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new 4K HDR camcorders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:41:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-4k-hdr-camcorders/</guid><description>Sony has introduced three new 4K HDR1 camcorders—the XDCAM PXW-Z90, the NXCAM HXR-NX80, and the Handycam FDR-AX700—all featuring Sony&amp;rsquo;s Fast Hybrid AF system.
Source: Sony. Sony launches new 4K HDR camcorders.
These compact camcorders all share the same fast and dependable autofocus system, designed specifically for their 1.0-type stacked Exmor RS CMOS image sensor. This allows them to capture high-quality footage with excellent clarity and offer a variety of shooting options.</description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats.</description></item><item><title>Blackmagic Design presents 4K Pocket Cinema Camera and DaVinci Resolve 15 at Broadcast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackmagic-design-presents-4k-pocket-cinema-camera-and-davinci-resolve-15-at-broadcast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 07:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackmagic-design-presents-4k-pocket-cinema-camera-and-davinci-resolve-15-at-broadcast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Blackmagic Design. Camera, video editing software slated for an Asia Pacific launch at Broadcast Asia.
Blackmagic Design is introducing the Pocket Cinema Camera 4K and DaVinci Resolve 15 to the Asia Pacific market at Broadcast Asia. Though intended for professional filmmakers, the line between pro-grade gear and high-end solutions for business or personal use is becoming increasingly blurred.
“Blackmagic Design is committed to making top-tier video production accessible to everyone, fostering a truly creative post-production and television industry,” remarked Grant Petty, Blackmagic Design CEO.</description></item><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers.</description></item><item><title>HTC HD2 Smartphone With Movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</guid><description>Have you ever been offered a cell phone with two full-length movies already on it? That&amp;rsquo;s only the beginning of what the HTC HD2 smartphone for T-Mobile offers. This phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t just offer entertainment, it delivers it in spades!
The massive touchscreen display immediately suggests this phone is designed for multimedia. It boasts a 4.3-inch screen with 800 x 480 pixel resolution. Those specs sound more like a small computer than a phone, and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing.</description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces new phone and software: Beauty is in the eye of the beholder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-new-phone-and-software-beauty-is-in-the-eye-of-the-beholder/</guid><description>Building on its legacy of smartphone innovation, HTC has introduced its latest top-tier HTC Desire model, the HTC Desire EYE, alongside new mobile imaging software and a collaborative video editing app.
Source: HTC. The new Desire EYE smartphone in submarine blue.
The waterproof* 4G Desire EYE, powered by the Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 processor, is engineered to be the ultimate multimedia device. Dual 13MP cameras (front and rear) deliver high-quality images and allow for one-handed photography.</description></item><item><title>The Aneka Plus pack on Singtel CAST now features Tribe from Astro</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The show &amp;ldquo;Qadr&amp;rdquo; from Tribe is now available through CAST.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CAST platform now includes Tribe, a regional video service by Astro. Showcasing content from Astro&amp;rsquo;s Malay channels, like Astro Ria and Astro Prima, Tribe will be part of CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus package.
For the first time in Singapore, viewers can access Astro&amp;rsquo;s premium on-demand Malay programs anywhere. Tribe offers complete seasons of drama series, variety shows, movies, and award shows.</description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality.</description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Sony has introduced the Picture This Festival for the Planet competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</guid><description>Sony Pictures Television Networks (SPTN), working with the United Nations Foundation, has launched the Picture This Festival for the Planet. The short-film competition encourages emerging filmmakers, storytellers, and changemakers globally to share their visions for a positive future for the planet.
Representing over 70 countries, participants are invited to submit videos inspired by the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The SDGs are a collection of global goals adopted by the United Nations to address poverty, protect the planet, and promote prosperity for everyone.</description></item><item><title>The 5-Min Video Challenge has been introduced by the Singtel Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</guid><description>Source: The 5-Min Video Challenge website. Invitation to enter the local rounds.
Singtel Group launched The 5-Min Video Challenge to promote creative content across its global markets. The competition is a collaborative effort among Singtel&amp;rsquo;s associates, including Optus, AIS, Airtel, Globe, and Telkomsel. Winning videos will be shared with over 600 million customers within the Singtel Group.
Content creation is a key element of the Group&amp;rsquo;s strategy for customer engagement in a world where mobile devices are everywhere and demand for online video entertainment is high.</description></item><item><title>The video-on-demand service HOOQ has been launched in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: HOOQ. Bithos.
HOOQ, a leading premium video-on-demand service targeting the Asian market, has officially launched in Singapore. This expansion follows successful launches in the Philippines, Thailand, India, and Indonesia, bringing their reach to a potential audience exceeding 1.6 billion people.
Established in Singapore in 2015, HOOQ is a joint venture between Singtel, Sony Pictures Television, and Warner Brothers. This partnership represents a significant collaboration between major media companies to revolutionize entertainment consumption in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Biotherm Homme releases kite surfing video in collaboration with The Dose skincare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 04:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
Biotherm Homme, a high-end men&amp;rsquo;s skincare brand, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; a product line designed to address the daily needs of men across four areas: feeling refreshed, energized, youthful, and charismatic.
To showcase &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; Biotherm Homme has also created an immersive 360° video featuring Youri Zoon, a world champion kitesurfer, as he executes awe-inspiring stunts. Want to learn more? Experience it firsthand.</description></item><item><title>Kaltura has launched a new personal video capture tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaltura-has-launched-a-new-personal-video-capture-tool/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaltura-has-launched-a-new-personal-video-capture-tool/</guid><description>Kaltura, a video technology company, has introduced Kaltura Personal Capture, a new product for personal video capture. This tool allows anyone in an organization to easily create videos in minutes, without needing special equipment.
With Kaltura Personal Capture, users can record both their screen and camera simultaneously with a single click. The software also includes an innovative automatic slide detection feature. When a user is recording their screen and has a PowerPoint presentation in presenter mode, Kaltura Personal Capture automatically identifies and captures the slides.</description></item><item><title>Singtel releases National Day video and shows support for SEA Games 2017 athletes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 04:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-releases-national-day-video-and-shows-support-for-sea-games-2017-athletes/</guid><description>Singtel has launched its first significant National Day video celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s independence. Released after August 9th, the company aims to motivate Singaporeans to maintain the spirit of &amp;ldquo;Majulah,&amp;rdquo; meaning &amp;ldquo;onward&amp;rdquo; in Malay, even after the National Day festivities.
Lian Pek, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP for Group Strategic Communications and Brand, explained that the slightly delayed release is intentional. Singtel wants to extend the enthusiasm from the National Day celebrations and inspire ongoing national pride and a desire to contribute to Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Vuclip Global Video Insights reveals that Malaysian consumers are seeking uncomplicated entertainment options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:06:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-vuclip-global-video-insights-reveals-that-malaysian-consumers-are-seeking-uncomplicated-entertainment-options/</guid><description>Vuclip, a leading mobile video-on-demand (VOD) service in emerging markets, has published its Global Video Insights (GVI) 2015 Survey. The study examines video consumption trends and device preferences among Malaysian consumers.
Source: Vuclip. Prakash.
Malaysian consumers value several features in an over-the-top (OTT) content player. The most important are a seamless user interface (61%), uninterrupted viewing experience (58%), high-definition video quality (56%), and access to the newest videos (54%). Other desirable features include adjustable streaming quality (47%), video downloads (46%), and simultaneous multiple video downloads (45%).</description></item><item><title>The Minute List focuses on dining experiences created by talented chefs and baristas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</guid><description>Hurrah! Productions, a TV and digital content agency based in Asia, has introduced The Minute List, a first-of-its-kind video-driven guide for bars and restaurants in Singapore.
This online platform features one-minute videos showcasing popular restaurants, bars, and cafes in the city. It allows users to make direct reservations at these establishments. Featured venues are nominated by industry professionals, such as chefs, bartenders, and baristas. Each nominated venue is presented through a video interview with the head chef, bartender, or barista.</description></item><item><title>Facebook introduces a user-friendly, streamlined video advertising format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</guid><description>Over one-third of mobile internet users in Saudi Arabia are receptive to video advertisements, exceeding the global average of 22%.
Facebook is introducing &amp;ldquo;Slideshow,&amp;rdquo; a new, user-friendly video ad format designed to increase reach across various devices and connection speeds.
In a blog post announcing Slideshow, Facebook highlights a recent report indicating that people in regions like the Philippines, where connectivity can be slow, costly, or both, and where feature phones are common, are even more receptive to video ads.</description></item><item><title>AdAsia Holdings introduces new video production services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</guid><description>Source: AdAsia website. Drones can give bird&amp;rsquo;s eye views of scenes.
AdAsia Holdings, an advertising company, has introduced AdAsia Video Production, a new service within its AdAsia Digital Platform that caters to video and animation production needs.
Clients can utilize this service for a range of video formats, from traditional productions to drone footage, 360-degree videos, and animations. Video quality options span from 140p to 2,160p. The produced materials can be featured on the AdAsia Video Network as well as other distribution channels.</description></item><item><title>The most popular videos on YouTube in Hong Kong for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</guid><description>Content related to local news, tutorials, and parodies were the most popular on YouTube in Hong Kong this year.
A wider variety of music genres are gaining traction.
YouTube Hong Kong Rewind 2019 highlights this year&amp;rsquo;s trending videos, showcasing categories like the Top 10 Trending Videos, Top 10 Trending Local Music Videos, Top 10 Trending International Music Videos, and Top 10 Emerging Channels.
Music, in various forms like music videos, live shows, remixes, and covers, remains a favorite among Hong Kong viewers.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singtel's Chinese New Year short film is on building connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singtel-s-chinese-new-year-short-film-is-on-building-connections/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Stills from the festive video emphasizing the importance of positive connections.
Singtel released its yearly short film for the Lunar New Year season. This year&amp;rsquo;s film uses humor to highlight the importance of connecting with others and nurturing relationships. The lighthearted short, His Grandfather’s Road, portrays a heated encounter between two families during the holiday rush. However, their road rage takes an unexpected turn when they discover shared ground and end their confrontation amicably.</description></item><item><title>Viu, a service provided by Vuclip, delivers an average of 20 videos per month to viewers in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Vuclip, a PCCW Media company, has released key engagement data for its OTT service, Viu, based on an analysis of app and desktop viewership.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOh1EZVWoEhfM9h_KB5E2oDQtVX9NIYnObrOM6oWpK6xB_fWBVmqMwQv5MQtoq5jTe338bKg_10JMMP4wDeSWDCbwHwC8jKXx1VMXkYHCYTrGVSsm8QO-dG0eKaUelNE4fQSA8esO5InKk/s1600/image.png)
Source: Viu Malaysia website.
In the two months since its launch in Malaysia, Viu has seen average user engagement of 20 videos per month. Peak viewing times are after work hours, with Wednesday to Sunday being the most popular days.
Korean dramas, Bollywood films, and Malaysian TV series rank among the top ten most-watched content, highlighting the strong demand for Asian entertainment.</description></item><item><title>TikTok has introduced the #NDP2019 challenge to celebrate Singapore's National Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tiktok-has-introduced-the-ndp2019-challenge-to-celebrate-singapore-s-national-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 14:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tiktok-has-introduced-the-ndp2019-challenge-to-celebrate-singapore-s-national-day/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 54th birthday, TikTok, the short-form video app, is launching a special hashtag challenge just for Singapore: #NDP2019.
TikTok users in Singapore are invited to express their national pride using the country&amp;rsquo;s colors, red and white, in their videos. They can use special NDP stickers and add the #NDP2019 hashtag to their posts. Ten lucky users who participate will have the chance to win limited-edition National Day TikTok merchandise.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Network Expansion Underway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</guid><description>Our society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to bandwidth is evident with the recent launch of a massive dark fiber network project by Allied Fiber. This project will encircle the US with 548 dark fibers and 300 tower sites.
Fiber optic communication is experiencing a resurgence and this time it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. Unlike the failed attempt in the 1990s, the unused fiber optic cables laid then are likely to be utilized soon due to the resurfacing of the telecommunication revolution.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing complimentary content and data to commemorate Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 51st birthday on August 9th, Singtel is offering customers complimentary mobile data, alongside free access to Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO.
Postpaid mobile users will enjoy free data from 12:01 am to 11:59 pm on August 9th, allowing them to connect with family and friends on social media, stream music, and watch videos.
From August 5th to 9th, Singtel TV subscribers will have free access to over 140 channels, including popular options like Disney Channel, National Geographic Channel HD, FOX Movie Premium HD, KBS World HD, Astro Ria, and Sun TV.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues.</description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H.</description></item></channel></rss>