<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Redundancy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/redundancy/</link><description>Recent content in Redundancy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/redundancy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently.</description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?</description></item></channel></rss>