<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WHO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/who/</link><description>Recent content in WHO on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/who/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease.</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization recommends restricting the use of personal audio devices to less than one hour per day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:12:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-recommends-restricting-the-use-of-personal-audio-devices-to-less-than-one-hour-per-day/</guid><description>Source: WHO.
The World Health Organization (WHO) cautions that over a billion adolescents and young adults risk noise-induced hearing loss. This danger stems from unsafe listening practices with personal audio devices like smartphones and exposure to high sound levels at entertainment venues, including sporting events.
WHO analysis of data from developed and developing nations reveals that nearly half of teenagers and young adults aged 12-35 experience unsafe sound levels from personal audio devices.</description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone.</description></item><item><title>WHO dismisses the likelihood of a worldwide Ebola outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</guid><description>On August 11th, the World Health Organization (WHO) released a statement regarding the Ebola virus disease (EVD) outbreak in West Africa. They emphasized that nations with strong health systems are unlikely to experience an epidemic. This is due to the way the virus spreads and past experiences with outbreaks.
The WHO also noted that while fear has led to increased global vigilance and suspicion of the virus, this heightened awareness makes it more likely that cases will be detected and managed quickly, thus limiting further transmission.</description></item></channel></rss>