<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Government on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/government/</link><description>Recent content in Government on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/government/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three new programs to assist Singaporean businesses in their digital transformation efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 01:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/</guid><description>Singapore has launched new initiatives to boost digitalization among its enterprises, especially small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), which are considered the backbone of the nation&amp;rsquo;s economy. S Iswaran, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, announced three key initiatives at an industry networking event.
Minister Iswaran delivering the opening address.
The Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) and Enterprise Singapore launched &amp;ldquo;Start Digital&amp;rdquo;, an initiative under the &amp;ldquo;SMEs Go Digital&amp;rdquo; program. Start Digital will give new SMEs a head start by providing two free foundational digital solutions for a minimum of six months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-programs-to-assist-singaporean-businesses-in-their-digital-transformation-efforts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Clever D Block Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</guid><description>During the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction, a small frequency band known as D Block went unsold because it didn&amp;rsquo;t reach its reserve price. This is unfortunate because D Block was supposed to play a crucial role in establishing a nationwide public service network. This plan, which could serve as a model for other initiatives, deserves further consideration, especially in challenging economic times.
The idea for D Block originated after the September 11, 2001, attacks, when communication breakdowns hampered rescue efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India has implemented measures to prepare for Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</guid><description>India is actively monitoring the situation to prevent the Ebola virus disease (EVD) from entering the country. Three dedicated helplines (2306 3205, 2306 1469, and 2306 1302) were set up at the Health Ministry on August 9th to address public inquiries.
While India has no confirmed or suspected Ebola cases, the World Health Organization (WHO) alerted the government about an Indian passenger who shared a flight with an Ebola patient traveling from Monrovia (Liberia) to Lagos (Nigeria), both experiencing outbreaks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commonwealth has adopted the Living Lands Charter and has launched the Blue Charter project incubator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</guid><description>Commonwealth leaders have formally agreed to the Living Lands Charter: A Commonwealth Call to action on Living Lands (CALL). This charter represents a commitment from all 54 member countries to protect global land resources and collaborate on climate change, biodiversity loss, and sustainable land management.
This non-binding agreement, announced at the close of the 2022 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in Kigali, Rwanda, is the result of almost two years of discussions and negotiations with member countries, United Nations Rio Conventions, and other involved parties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KSA is progressing with the privatization process</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</guid><description>The National Center for Privatization &amp;amp; PPP (NCP) is a new Saudi Arabian agency created to empower the nation&amp;rsquo;s private sector. Along with Supervisory Committees (SCs) established to oversee each privatization sector, the NCP will manage the transfer of government assets to private ownership.
Formed in April 2017 by the Council of Ministers, the NCP and the SCs are the first of their kind in the Middle East and North Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ksa-is-progressing-with-the-privatization-process/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SPRING Singapore reviews its accomplishments in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 02:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</guid><description>Despite a slowing economy in 2016, SPRING Singapore, a government agency supporting business growth, reported that over 16,000 companies enhanced their capabilities.
These companies participated in projects backed by the Capability Development Grant (CDG) and Innovation &amp;amp; Capability Voucher (ICV) programs. SPRING estimates these projects will generate S$7.8 billion and create approximately 21,400 skilled jobs upon completion, representing a 13% and 43% increase from 2015 respectively.
A record-breaking 2,400 projects received CDG support, almost double the previous year and the highest in five years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spring-singapore-reviews-its-accomplishments-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Verify the authenticity of KSA sales and promotions using this app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 14:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</guid><description>Source: MCI. HE the Minister of Commerce and Investment Dr Majid bin Abdullah Al Qasabi launched the Sales app on 31 January 2017.
The Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) in Saudi Arabia has introduced a mobile application called &amp;ldquo;Sales.&amp;rdquo; This app allows the public to access the MCI&amp;rsquo;s database of authorized sales and promotional offers. The goal is to help users find genuine deals and discounts quickly.
Through the app, consumers can browse information on more than 27,000 retail locations and over 700,000 licensed products registered with the MCI...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/verify-the-authenticity-of-ksa-sales-and-promotions-using-this-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Government support for research and development in Singapore SMEs and startups has been increased</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</guid><description>The Singapore government is increasing its support for research, development, and commercialization (R&amp;amp;D&amp;amp;C) activities undertaken by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups. This support encompasses financial assistance through grants, participation in business incubator programs, and favorable tax structures, as highlighted by Lim Chuan Poh, Chairman of the Agency for Science, Technology and Research (A*STAR), during his guest speaker appearance at the Developer and Global Entrepreneur Day, part of IBM&amp;rsquo;s XCite event in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2023 goals of Singapore's Digital Government Blueprint are outlined</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</guid><description>Source: GovTech Singapore website.
Infographic, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s _Digital
Government Blueprint. _
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy Prime Minister, Teo Chee Hean, who also oversees National Security, recently introduced the Digital Government Blueprint (DGB) at the Smart Nation Innovations Week Opening Symposium. This blueprint outlines the government&amp;rsquo;s goal to utilize data and emerging technologies to enhance services for citizens, businesses, and public officials. It also aims to foster a digital economy and society, aligning with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation vision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-commerce sellers in Saudi Arabia are invited to join Maroof</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) cautions against the online sale or promotion of counterfeit products. This practice violates the Anti-Commercial Fraud Law and Trademark System, with potential consequences including imprisonment of up to three years and fines reaching SR1 million.
MCI recommends that entrepreneurs register with Maroof (http://www.maroof.sa/), a free e-service. Registration enhances businesses&amp;rsquo; credibility by officially documenting their information with the ministry. Maroof offers transparency through customer feedback, allowing shoppers to assess e-store quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2018 Budget is on technology, innovation, and building capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Budget 2018 site. View of Singapore skyline.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Trade and Industry (MTI) anticipates more broad-based economic growth across sectors in 2018, albeit at a moderated pace compared to the heights of 2017, according to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Financial Minister Heng Swee Keat during his Budget 2018 speech.
Minister Heng emphasized the need for Singapore to adapt to three major shifts in the coming decade:
Asia&amp;rsquo;s increasing global economic influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IE Singapore and UOB will assist Singaporean companies in their international expansion efforts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ie-singapore-and-uob-will-assist-singaporean-companies-in-their-international-expansion-efforts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 21:49:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ie-singapore-and-uob-will-assist-singaporean-companies-in-their-international-expansion-efforts/</guid><description>International Enterprise (IE) Singapore and United Overseas Bank (UOB) have partnered to support Singaporean companies engaged in international trade and expansion. This collaboration marks IE Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first strategic partnership with a Singaporean bank.
This partnership aims to provide Singaporean businesses with tailored trade and financing solutions, enhanced access to in-market networks, business partners, and service providers across Asia, including connections with UOB&amp;rsquo;s global clientele.
The agreement was formalized by Chua Taik Him, Deputy CEO of IE Singapore, and Frederick Chin, Managing Director and Head of Group Wholesale Banking at UOB...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ie-singapore-and-uob-will-assist-singaporean-companies-in-their-international-expansion-efforts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ie-singapore-and-uob-will-assist-singaporean-companies-in-their-international-expansion-efforts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has revealed a budget for 2016 that is favorable to small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: Budget in Brief document on Singapore Budget website.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, introduced a new program to bolster businesses and industries while stimulating growth through innovation. Building on the Quality Growth Programme from Budget 2013, this initiative, called the Industry Transformation Programme (ITP), seeks to foster innovation and productivity. The goal is to empower Singaporean companies to become more resilient and capitalize on the anticipated global economic upswing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget prioritizes innovation to capitalize on opportunities in a changing economic landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</guid><description>In his 2016-17 Budget address, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized the need for the city to adapt to a changing global economy driven by technology and the rise of emerging markets. He highlighted robotics, healthy aging, and smart city initiatives as potential areas for Hong Kong to leverage its strengths.
Tsang announced plans to promote smart production and research in the Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate, utilizing robotics and IT to advance the entire value chain, from research and development to marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is urging the public to take an active role in digital defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 02:35:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</guid><description>Source: Tableau. Minister Maliki addresses the audience.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for Defence &amp;amp; Foreign Affairs, Dr. Mohamad Maliki Bin Osman, was the guest of honor and keynote speaker at Tableau Software&amp;rsquo;s 5th annual Public Sector Day. During his speech, he emphasized the importance of digital defense in the digital age.
Dr. Maliki highlighted how digital technology&amp;rsquo;s interconnected nature has increased vulnerability to cyberattacks, disinformation campaigns, and the spread of fake news...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-urging-the-public-to-take-an-active-role-in-digital-defense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An innovative social media project, fueled by the power of crowdsourcing, is revolutionizing Korean brand marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 01:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Bitter, Sweet, Seoul,&amp;rdquo; a feature-length film directed by Park Chan-wook, is the culmination of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s first international crowdsourced film project.
Source: PR Newswire
The Seoul Metropolitan Government, as part of a global brand marketing campaign to showcase the diverse experiences and emotions Seoul has to offer, invited individuals worldwide to submit short video clips about the city through YouTube and a dedicated microsite.
The initiative generated almost 12,000 submissions, totaling an impressive 159 hours, 35 minutes, and 4 seconds of footage from around the globe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-innovative-social-media-project-fueled-by-the-power-of-crowdsourcing-is-revolutionizing-korean-brand-marketing/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>