<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social/</link><description>Recent content in Social on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Letv reaches one million Facebook likes within two months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</guid><description>Source: Socialbakers.
Letv, a company that has yet to formally debut in India, has already amassed a following of one million on Facebook in just 60 days. According to Socialbakers, Letv is currently the top and fastest-growing phone brand page in India. In contrast, it took Xiaomi India more than 400 days to achieve the same milestone*.
Over the past month, Letv has consistently ranked high in Facebook popularity, rivaling established brands like HTC, Motorola, Lava, Vivo, and Xiaomi in India.</description></item><item><title>Huawei P9 and India Photo Project introduce Monochrome award in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</guid><description>Source: Instagram. Top Instagram posts for the contest hashtag #ipp_ma2016 at the time of writing.
Huawei, in partnership with the Instagram-based India Photo Project, has introduced the &amp;ldquo;Monochrome&amp;rdquo; award to commemorate World Photography Day on August 19th. This competition, running from August 20th to August 31st, aims to discover India&amp;rsquo;s top black and white Instagram photographer.
The judging panel comprises Sumit Dayal, recognized as CNN&amp;rsquo;s Indian Instagrammer of the Year in 2015, Tara Bedi, the first Instagram employee from India, Devika Daulet Singh, Director of PHOTOINK, a prominent photography gallery, and Neeraj Priyadarshini, the Photo Editor at the Indian Express.</description></item><item><title>A new worldwide network of mobile social influencers has been introduced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</guid><description>VOLTU, a new performance-based social influencer network focused on mobile acquisition, has been officially launched by mobile advertising technology pioneer Glispa Global Group. Building on Glispa&amp;rsquo;s successful history of creating custom influencer campaigns for clients like Square Enix and Youzu, VOLTU connects advertisers with global content creators to increase app installs, brand awareness, and user engagement.
Influencer marketing is a proven method for engaging consumers because it utilizes genuine and relatable content made by consumers for consumers.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item><item><title>Bayara excels in creating engaging digital activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bayara-excels-in-creating-engaging-digital-activities/</guid><description>Bayara, a Middle Eastern brand famous for dried fruits, nuts, and spices, hosted a unique iftar (Ramadan fast-breaking meal) at The Oberoi in Dubai. The buffet featured recipes submitted by their social media followers.
Source: Bayara. Jean-Marc Lourau, CEO of Bayara, congratulated the winners whose dishes were featured at the buffet and also shared the progress that Bayara has made over the last 25 years that they have been in the market.</description></item><item><title>Twitter has revealed its inaugural collaboration with Singaporean musician @Sezairi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</guid><description>● #SezairiQA and live songs on Twitter and Periscope @ 6:30pm on August 31, 2016 ● #SezairiLive debut show at Twitter APAC HQ in Singapore @ 7:30pm on September 2, 2016 ● Winners of @Sezairi photo caption contest get free tickets to #SezairiLive event
Singaporean singer Sezairi (@Sezairi) will be performing live (#SezairiLive) on Twitter, Periscope, and at Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters. The performances follow a pre-listening party (#SezairiPreLP) on Twitter held the previous week.</description></item><item><title>Tickets for the Nathan Hartono showcase are now available through Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tickets-for-the-nathan-hartono-showcase-are-now-available-through-singtel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 23:10:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tickets-for-the-nathan-hartono-showcase-are-now-available-through-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Nathan Hartono recently held a live performance on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page.
Nathan Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance video, broadcasted on Singtel’s Facebook page last week, has garnered over 99,000 views and is still climbing. This event is a continuation of Singtel’s Christmas tradition of giving back to the community and supporting the Singtel Touching Lives Fund.
During the event, organized by Singtel to celebrate the festive season and spread generosity, fans could interact with Hartono and request song dedications for their loved ones.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Weixin have collaborated to introduce a new social gifting feature</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-weixin-have-collaborated-to-introduce-a-new-social-gifting-feature/</guid><description>Source Starbucks. Starbucks and Weixin launch a new social
gifting feature.
Starbucks and Tencent have launched &amp;ldquo;Say it with Stars,&amp;rdquo; a new gifting feature on the Chinese social media platform Weixin. This follows their strategic partnership announced in December 2016.
This service allows users to send gifts instantly, such as Starbucks beverages or digital gift cards. Belinda Wong, CEO of Starbucks China, stated their goal is to deepen connections between people by allowing them to express feelings like love and gratitude through the act of giving Starbucks.</description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank celebrates reaching 100,000 Facebook Likes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</guid><description>Alizz Islamic Bank has achieved a significant milestone by reaching 100,000 likes on Facebook. This achievement places them among the top two banks in Oman to attain this level of popularity on the platform.
Over the past year, Alizz Islamic Bank has significantly bolstered its social media presence, driven by a strong belief in its ability to enhance customer service. In addition to their Facebook success, they have also surpassed 30,000 followers on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>TalentBin by Monster searches through social networks to find potential candidates for recruitment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</guid><description>Source: Monster website.
Monster recently launched its TalentBin platform across multiple regions to help businesses locate and engage skilled professionals. Functioning as a specialized search engine for talent, the software grants recruiters access to a pool of potential candidates who might not be easily discoverable through traditional methods. This is achieved by analyzing and leveraging professional information individuals share on various social media platforms.
TalentBin not only automates and simplifies the process of identifying potential candidates through site monitoring, data interpretation, and profile matching but also makes hiring more efficient, allowing recruiters to achieve more in less time.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>The Minute List focuses on dining experiences created by talented chefs and baristas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</guid><description>Hurrah! Productions, a TV and digital content agency based in Asia, has introduced The Minute List, a first-of-its-kind video-driven guide for bars and restaurants in Singapore.
This online platform features one-minute videos showcasing popular restaurants, bars, and cafes in the city. It allows users to make direct reservations at these establishments. Featured venues are nominated by industry professionals, such as chefs, bartenders, and baristas. Each nominated venue is presented through a video interview with the head chef, bartender, or barista.</description></item><item><title>GMC uses Instagram to showcase PanoGrams and highlight #GMCprecision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:09:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gmc-uses-instagram-to-showcase-panograms-and-highlight-gmcprecision/</guid><description>Source: GMC.
GMC launched a new Instagram campaign using panoramic photography and the hashtag #GMCprecision.
The month-long US campaign, which began on May 22nd, highlights the meticulous design of GMC vehicles. Using Instagram&amp;rsquo;s new Carousel format, GMC is one of the first car companies to create “PanoGrams.&amp;quot; This format lets users swipe through a series of pictures in a single ad, similar to a multi-page spread in a magazine. These PanoGrams form one panoramic image and include a link to GMC&amp;rsquo;s website for further details.</description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations.</description></item><item><title>The AirAsia Foundation is investigating the concept of social enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia Foundation website.
The AirAsia Foundation is hosting a conference and marketplace focused on social enterprise on November 7th at Nexus Bangsar South in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This event, Destination: Good – ASEAN Social Enterprise 2015, is the first public event organized by the AirAsia Foundation, the philanthropic branch of the AirAsia Group. Its goal is to initiate a discussion on the role large companies and social enterprises can play in fostering fair, sustainable, and inclusive economies.</description></item><item><title>Instagram outperformed Facebook during the Rio 2016 Olympics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</guid><description>Source: ComScore. Social network interactions between Facebook and Instagram for July 2016 around the Olympic games, which ran from 5 to 21 August.
ComScore, a media measurement company, found that Instagram was the top platform for engagement during the 2016 Rio Olympics, even though Facebook, its parent company, was primarily used for pre-event official content sharing.
In June, the UK ranked third globally in unique visitors to the official Rio Olympics website (RIO2016.</description></item></channel></rss>