<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-connections/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Connections on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Leverages Your IT Staff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s economy, most companies, including large and well-known ones, are hesitant to increase their staff. This poses a challenge for IT departments, which are often unable to grow to meet rising demands and may face hiring freezes or even staff reductions. How can this situation be managed effectively to prevent a decline in morale and productivity?
One solution is to find a way to increase the output of each team member without negatively impacting their well-being or overloading them with work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-leverages-your-it-staff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Combine T1 Lines For Higher Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 15:30:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</guid><description>T1 lines have been a popular choice for small and medium-sized businesses for many years due to their reliability, security, dedicated bandwidth, and accessibility. While their affordability has increased in recent years, their speed has remained a limitation. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution to overcome this without sacrificing the benefits of T1 technology: bonding.
Bonding is a standard industry technique that allows you to combine the bandwidth of multiple T1 lines. This effectively merges them into a single, faster connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/combine-t1-lines-for-higher-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Bandwidth Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</guid><description>DS3 WAN connections are a popular choice for businesses that need more bandwidth than T1 lines offer but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for a full OC-3 fiber optic SONET service. However, exploring alternative options might be beneficial due to cost or performance considerations.
There are several bandwidth options available today that might be a better fit than your existing DS3 connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some alternatives.
DS3 bridges the gap between copper wireline and fiber optic bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two T1 Lines For The Price of One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</guid><description>Companies are transmitting more data than ever before, putting a strain on their WAN connections. You might assume that increasing bandwidth in this economic climate would be difficult, but what if you could get double the capacity for the same price?
While it sounds unbelievable, many competing providers offer deals that effectively give you two T1 lines for the price of one. Skeptical? Compare current T1 prices to what you might have paid a few years ago on a multi-year contract, especially in major cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center On Demand in the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The sophistication of cloud communications services is constantly increasing, representing a logical progression in the cloud computing revolution. With data servers already transitioned to the cloud, numerous businesses are questioning the necessity of maintaining costly and aging PBX phone systems.
Transitioning business phone systems to the cloud is becoming increasingly practical. Beginning with Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, this shift eliminates the need for substantial hardware and traditional phone lines. Instead, handsets connect to the company network and a high-bandwidth WAN connection links to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-on-demand-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>