<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ink on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ink/</link><description>Recent content in Ink on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The L805 photo printer from Epson features a six-colour ink tank system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-l805-photo-printer-from-epson-features-a-six-colour-ink-tank-system/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The L805 ink tank photo printer.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing products, has released its L805 printer. This six-color ink tank photo printer offers wireless printing from mobile devices and boasts the lowest operating expenses on the market. Epson&amp;rsquo;s ink tank printers are unique in that they utilize large ink tanks instead of cartridges.
Building upon the previous L800 model, the L805 incorporates built-in wireless connectivity.</description></item><item><title>The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-C869R offers a cost-effective solution for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 12:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-workforce-pro-wf-c869r-offers-a-cost-effective-solution-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. The WF-C869R printer.
Epson recently introduced a new printer with a Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS) that offers both high speed and quality while significantly reducing costs. The WorkForce Pro WF-C869R boasts a high page yield and a low cost per page, which can lead to considerable savings for businesses compared to using laser printers.
The printer&amp;rsquo;s high-capacity ink packs come in two options: standard packs that yield up to 22,500 black and 22,000 color pages, and larger packs that yield up to 86,000 black and 84,000 color pages.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new business printer capable of printing up to 75,000 pages in a single run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-business-printer-capable-of-printing-up-to-75-000-pages-in-a-single-run/</guid><description>Epson helps businesses reduce printing expenses with its Replaceable Ink Pack System (RIPS). RIPS utilizes high-capacity ink packs that hold significantly more ink than traditional cartridges. This system combines the convenience of cartridges with the high-volume output of ink tanks.
Source: Epson.
The Epson WorkForce Pro WF-R8591 is the first printer in Southeast Asia to offer this technology. Using a complete set of ink packs, the WF-R8591 can print approximately 75,000 pages* before replacements are needed.</description></item></channel></rss>