<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Opt-Outs on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/opt-outs/</link><description>Recent content in Opt-Outs on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/opt-outs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dear Daily Telegraph, I am writing to emphasize the importance of the UK choosing to participate in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This letter, penned by Steve Peers, was featured in prominent publications such as the Daily Telegraph, The Guardian, and BBC News. It urges support for the UK&amp;rsquo;s continued participation in the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. Interested parties are invited to add their names to the list of signatories.
An Open Letter to Parliament
As Parliament prepares to vote on the UK&amp;rsquo;s involvement in certain EU measures, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as a critical point of discussion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-daily-telegraph-i-am-writing-to-emphasize-the-importance-of-the-uk-choosing-to-participate-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-eaw/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>