<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remote Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-access/</link><description>Recent content in Remote Access on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud On The Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</guid><description>Big corporations are shifting their data centers to the cloud for financial and logistical benefits, enabling work from anywhere. But what about smaller businesses? Can they enjoy similar advantages?
One cloud solution often overlooked due to its existence before the cloud trend is GoToMyPC. Although not typically associated with the cloud, it embodies the concept.
GoToMyPC enables remote login to your computer. But isn&amp;rsquo;t accessing your desktop from a restaurant, running office applications, conceptually similar to using a private cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take Your Office PC With You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</guid><description>Mobile professionals often rely on their laptops but might find themselves needing files left on their office desktops. Traveling long distances back for these files isn&amp;rsquo;t always feasible.
Imagine accessing your office desktop from anywhere, anytime. This eliminates the worry of having the right files and removes the need for duplicates. Your laptop and a special application are all you need to make any computer your office computer.
GoToMyPC is a remote access software, or KVM application, that allows this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-your-office-pc-with-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>G.ho.st as the Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</guid><description>If you come across a platform called G.ho.st, don&amp;rsquo;t be spooked by the name. It stands for Global Hosted Operating SysTem, found at http://g.ho.st/. It&amp;rsquo;s essentially an online operating system.
Instead of being restricted to your desktop, G.ho.st allows you to access an operating system anywhere with an internet connection. I decided to try it out myself.
The website was visually appealing, so I launched the G.ho.st virtual computer (VC). Unfortunately, my old Compaq couldn&amp;rsquo;t handle it and displayed an error message...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ghost-as-the-machine/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>