<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MPLS Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-networking/</link><description>Recent content in MPLS Networking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managed IP Services Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</guid><description>Companies are increasingly interested in cloud services because they can save money and access capabilities that they might not otherwise be able to afford. Cloud services offer a wide range of IP services and can be accessed in-house, privately, or purchased from a provider. While providers offer different services, they all deliver their services over IP networks, leading to the term &amp;ldquo;managed IP services.&amp;rdquo;
Managed services allow carriers or service providers to take responsibility for operations, a task typically handled by on-site IT staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits Of An MPLS Mesh Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</guid><description>When your company grows to have multiple locations like branches, data centers, or factories, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a way to connect them all on the same network. The best way to do this is with an MPLS Mesh Network.
Smaller companies with only two locations usually start by connecting the locations with a point-to-point T1 or Ethernet line. While this works, using an MPLS network might be more cost-effective depending on the distance between locations and the availability of T1 or Ethernet services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>