<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IBM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ibm/</link><description>Recent content in IBM on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ibm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is in a position to lead the way in the 21st century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>A new IBM study suggests that the 21st century has the potential to be known as the &amp;ldquo;Indian century&amp;rdquo; as India prepares to take a leading role on the global stage. Over half of the executives surveyed believe that better governance and reduced regulation are key to sustained economic growth. Building robust social infrastructure was identified as the second most important factor for economic productivity. Over 40% also highlighted the significance of quality physical infrastructure and a skilled workforce for driving growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM reports that early adopters of cloud-based software are experiencing tangible benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 18:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</guid><description>IBM has revealed that nearly half of the businesses utilizing Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) are gaining a competitive edge, rather than just reducing expenses. This insight comes from a recent global survey conducted by the IBM Center for Applied Insights, involving over 800 IT and business decision-makers.
The study confirms that SaaS offers a wide range of advantages beyond lowering overall costs. It demonstrates that organizations strategically and collaboratively implementing SaaS are better equipped to execute programs that drive business growth compared to those slower to adopt SaaS...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-reports-that-early-adopters-of-cloud-based-software-are-experiencing-tangible-benefits/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating the digital landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</guid><description>Business leaders from major telecommunications and media companies recently met to talk about how to thrive in a digital world. IBM iX, the consulting firm that organized the gathering, emphasizes that these challenges are relevant to every industry.
A key takeaway was the urgent need for companies to disrupt themselves before someone else does. This involves understanding emerging digital trends and investing in ways that increase market share and profits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IBM Kenexa Talent Suite leverages big data to benefit HR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</guid><description>IBM has introduced a new software-as-a-service (SaaS) product designed to provide Chief Human Resources Officers (CHROs) and other executives with valuable insights from employee data.
The cloud-based IBM Kenexa Talent Suite helps organizations enhance the efficiency and accuracy of their hiring processes, boost workforce productivity, and foster employee connections in ways that positively influence business outcomes.
This software empowers HR teams to analyze extensive employee data, encompassing work history, social interactions, skills development, and individual interests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tech companies are the most prevalent in the minds of LinkedIn members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>IBM, HP, Accenture, Google, and Tata Consultancy Services are the top five most followed companies by LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s over 50 million members in the Asia Pacific region. Notably, all these companies are multinational tech companies.
[Image of the LinkedIn Top 5 most followed companies]
Source: LinkedIn
However, this trend varies by country. While Google ranks among the top three in Singapore, Australia, Hong Kong, and Japan, it is absent from the list in India, Indonesia, Malaysia, and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tech-companies-are-the-most-prevalent-in-the-minds-of-linkedin-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>