<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cash for Gadgets on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cash-for-gadgets/</link><description>Recent content in Cash for Gadgets on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:47:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cash-for-gadgets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get After Christmas Cash From Old Gadgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-after-christmas-cash-from-old-gadgets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-after-christmas-cash-from-old-gadgets/</guid><description>The holiday season brings joy and new gadgets, but also the dreaded credit card bills come January. Need some extra cash to counter those expenses? Consider selling your old electronics!
It&amp;rsquo;s a win-win: you earn money and declutter your home. While you enjoy your new devices, those older models they replaced can be turned into cash.
You might be tempted to keep old devices &amp;ldquo;just in case,&amp;rdquo; but realistically, when was the last time you actually used an older model after upgrading?</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Old or Broken Laptop For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-old-or-broken-laptop-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-old-or-broken-laptop-for-cash/</guid><description>Do you have a pile of old laptops in your basement, even those with cracked screens that ended up in the trash? You might be surprised to learn that those old devices, broken or not, can actually earn you some money.
It&amp;rsquo;s true! Most laptops aren&amp;rsquo;t as worthless as you might think. Throwing them away or sending them to a landfill is not the best approach. Those old circuit boards and components contain harmful materials that can pollute the environment over time.</description></item></channel></rss>