<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Trunk on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-trunk/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Trunk on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-trunk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines.</description></item><item><title>Why, Oh Why, PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-oh-why-pri/</guid><description>You might know the terms PRI, T1 PRI, Telephone PRI, PRI Trunk, or ISDN PRI, but what do they actually mean, and why choose this service?
PRI stands for Primary Rate Interface. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the ISDN or Integrated Services Digital Network and is a step up from BRI or Basic Rate Interface. Simply put, PRI is a digital line connecting to your PBX phone system. It combines numerous phone lines into a single digital line, leading to cost savings on monthly phone bills.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center.</description></item></channel></rss>