<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/re/</link><description>Recent content in RE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/re/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC revolutionizes photography with the RE camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</guid><description>HTC is launching a new camera called the RE, aiming to change how people take pictures. This waterproof handheld device can capture time-lapse photos and even act as a remote viewfinder for smartphones.
Source: HTC blog.
HTC CEO Peter Chou emphasizes their dedication to innovation, stating that the RE camera will allow people to experience photography in a new way. The RE&amp;rsquo;s grip sensor activates upon pickup, removing the need for a power button...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-revolutionizes-photography-with-the-re-camera/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>