<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Suspects' Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suspects-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Suspects' Rights on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/suspects-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU here to rescue legal aid, or to put it to rest? Evaluating discussions on the proposed Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</guid><description>by Claire Perinaud (FREE Group Trainee)
Access to legal aid is crucial for individuals facing criminal charges, enabling them to mount a proper defense. The EU is developing legislation to address this right, but its impact remains uncertain.
Progress of the Procedural Rights Roadmap
EU legislation concerning the procedural rights of suspects and accused individuals in criminal cases has been developing gradually since late 2009, following years of unsuccessful attempts.</description></item><item><title>Advocating for children? The Directive on procedural safeguards for children suspected or accused in criminal proceedings.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advocating-for-children-the-directive-on-procedural-safeguards-for-children-suspected-or-accused-in-criminal-proceedings/</guid><description>Protecting Young Suspects in the EU: A Look at the New Directive If we don&amp;rsquo;t stand up for children, then we don&amp;rsquo;t stand for much.
Marian Wright Edelman
Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
Ensuring fair treatment within the criminal justice system is crucial, and this fairness necessitates different safeguards based on individual circumstances. Children, being particularly vulnerable, require special protective measures, as recognized by international standards such as the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child and the Council of Europe Guidelines on child-friendly justice.</description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992.</description></item><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome.</description></item><item><title>A.T. v Luxembourg: The Beginning of the EU-ECHR Narrative on Rights to Criminal Defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 02:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</guid><description>Alex Tinsley, Legal &amp;amp; Policy Officer (Head of EU Office) at Fair Trials, based in Brussels. Twitter: @AlexLouisT In a judgment issued on April 9, 2015, the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruled in the case of A.T. v. Luxembourg. This ruling, which will become final unless reviewed by the Grand Chamber, determined that Luxembourg violated Article 6 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). The judgment expands upon the principles established in Salduz v.</description></item></channel></rss>