<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Great Repeal Act on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/great-repeal-act/</link><description>Recent content in Great Repeal Act on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/great-repeal-act/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Great Repeal Bill and the Legacy of Henry VIII: Threatening Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</guid><description>Joelle Grogan, Lecturer, Middlesex University
The Great Repeal Bill is ironically named because it won&amp;rsquo;t actually repeal much EU law. Instead, when Brexit concludes, it will initially shift existing EU law into British law. While this maintains some stability during the transition, the bill also includes a concerning element: a Henry VIII clause. This clause, named after the king who gave himself sweeping legislative power, allows the government to alter primary legislation with minimal parliamentary scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the legal challenges of the Brexit transition period: A bridge over troubled waters?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-legal-challenges-of-the-brexit-transition-period-a-bridge-over-troubled-waters/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
In a recent speech outlining the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit plans, Prime Minister Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s approach resembled Machiavelli&amp;rsquo;s strategies more than Leonardo da Vinci&amp;rsquo;s artistry. Nonetheless, her speech provided a glimpse into the legal structure the UK government envisions for its relationship with the EU during a transitional period after Brexit. While the main points of the Florence speech have been previously discussed, this piece delves deeper into the legal framework and its implications for EU27 citizens in the UK during this transition.</description></item><item><title>Mastering the art of releasing control - the Charter of Fundamental Rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Eduardo Gill-Pedro, Post-Doctoral Researcher, Faculty of Law, Lund University: Eduardo.gill-pedro@jur.lu.se
The UK Government&amp;rsquo;s proposition to exclude the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights (the Charter) from UK law after Brexit (clause 5(4) of the EU Withdrawal Bill) has drawn criticism from opposition parties. The Labour party views this as a non-negotiable issue and refuses to endorse any bill that doesn&amp;rsquo;t integrate the Charter into UK law. Keir Starmer, the Shadow Brexit Secretary, previously stated that Labour would only back a deal that meets its &amp;ldquo;six tests,&amp;rdquo; one being the preservation of &amp;ldquo;rights and protections&amp;rdquo; to avoid a decline in standards.</description></item><item><title>The Data Protection Bill and UK-EU Data Transfers: A Story of Brexit and Data Protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 13:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Elif Mendos Kuşkonmaz, PhD student at Queen Mary, University of London[*]
Introduction
A Bosnian folk song tells the story of a Pasha who died from a severe illness. When his wife heard about his passing, she died from grief. Similarly, now that the UK has chosen to leave the European Union, will the same fate befall data protection laws once the UK exits the EU?
The UK&amp;rsquo;s current data protection law, the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), incorporates the EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 Data Protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>Opinions on Scotland's Position in Europe: Analysis of the Scottish Government's latest suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The Scottish government recently released its anticipated paper exploring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s position within Europe. While acknowledging the government&amp;rsquo;s support for both EU membership and Scottish independence, the paper concentrates on potential outcomes should Brexit occur while Scotland remains part of the UK. Accusations that the paper dismisses referendum results, regarding either Brexit or Scottish independence, or simply rehashes arguments for independence are unfounded.
The paper essentially presents two main options: a UK-wide approach to Brexit that considers the concerns of Scottish voters, or, if that fails, a separate approach specifically for Scotland.</description></item><item><title>Miller's ruling: Representative Democracy Makes a Comeback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miller-s-ruling-representative-democracy-makes-a-comeback/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK Supreme Court recently issued its judgment in the Miller case (and a similar Northern Ireland case) regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU. This post will summarize the judgment&amp;rsquo;s main points and examine its implications for Brexit and Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role. Professor Mark Elliott has already provided a thorough legal analysis, which can be found elsewhere.
The case revolves around two central issues: Parliament&amp;rsquo;s role in initiating Article 50 and the role of devolved legislatures.</description></item></channel></rss>