<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>History on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/history/</link><description>Recent content in History on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingPost releases stamps showcasing classic board games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</guid><description>Source: SingPost. The new traditional board games stamp issue.
Singapore Post (SingPost) is releasing a new set of five square stamps on April 27th. Each stamp features a hand-drawn image of a traditional board game popular in Singapore during the 1970s and 80s: Chinese chess, the diamond game, aeroplane chess, snakes and ladders, and checkers.
Chinese chess (1st local denomination) is a strategic board game for two players simulating a battle between two armies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the rich history and art at Apricot Hotel in Hanoi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 20:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</guid><description>Source: Apricot Hotel website.
Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s latest luxury hotel, Apricot Hotel, is now open in the heart of Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s cultural and political center, with a grand opening planned for later this summer*. The 10-story Apricot Hotel, formerly the Phú Gia Hotel, a renowned gathering place for the city&amp;rsquo;s elite since the 1920s, holds significant historical weight.
This five-star hotel offers stunning views of Hoan Kiem Lake and Hanoi&amp;rsquo;s Old Quarter. It boasts 123 neo-classical rooms, two restaurants, a lobby lounge, a cafe, a rooftop bar with a heated swimming pool, meeting rooms, a spa, and a fitness center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-rich-history-and-art-at-apricot-hotel-in-hanoi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The book Soirees, Sojourns &amp; Stories details the most memorable moments of the Raffles narrative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</guid><description>Raffles Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, a leader in luxury hospitality known for its iconic properties, has released Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories.
Created in partnership with Rizzoli New York, the 200-page slipcased book, Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories by Natasha Fraser-Cavassoni, explores the development of Raffles&amp;rsquo; heritage of elegance and exceptional service around the world. It covers the period from the opening of its flagship hotel in Singapore in 1887 to the recent debut of Raffles Warsaw in Poland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa introduces the Amara Heritage Trail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/</guid><description>Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is launching its first-ever Amara Heritage Trail. This tour allows guests to explore the resort&amp;rsquo;s hidden natural surroundings, conservation efforts, and historical significance.
Source: Amara Sanctury Resort Sentosa. The petai tree is one of 26 heritage trees in Sentosa protected by the Heritage Tree Scheme under Singapore’s National Parks Board. The seeds are edible.
The resort sits on ten acres of land that once housed British military barracks and air raid shelters built between 1897 and 1905 and later renovated in the 1920s...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pesta Raya by Esplanade is back in July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</guid><description>The Esplanade – Theatres on the Bay’s 17th annual Pesta Raya – Malay Festival of Arts will take place from July 12th to 15th, 2018. The festival coincides with Hari Raya Aidilfitri, a celebration that lasts until mid-July.
This year, the festival focuses on the history of the Nusantara. Fezhah Maznan, a programmer with The Esplanade Company, stated that Pesta Raya has always celebrated the rich Malay heritage through arts and culture from the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examining culture and heritage using technology as a tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</guid><description>The National Museum of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s new exhibit, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents,&amp;rdquo; opens on August 4th and features technologically innovative projects that combine history, art, and technology.
Developed collaboratively with designers, artists, and tech companies, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; offers visitors new ways to experience culture and heritage. This includes immersive virtual and augmented reality exhibits, artificial intelligence-powered conversations, and much more.
Part of a larger initiative to promote digital innovation within the cultural sector, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; showcases seven prototypes from the &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Open Call&amp;rdquo; for digital art and innovation, which concluded in April...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>