<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FCC Auction on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fcc-auction/</link><description>Recent content in FCC Auction on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fcc-auction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Clever D Block Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</guid><description>During the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction, a small frequency band known as D Block went unsold because it didn&amp;rsquo;t reach its reserve price. This is unfortunate because D Block was supposed to play a crucial role in establishing a nationwide public service network. This plan, which could serve as a model for other initiatives, deserves further consideration, especially in challenging economic times.
The idea for D Block originated after the September 11, 2001, attacks, when communication breakdowns hampered rescue efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking For Spectrum In All The White Spaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:51:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</guid><description>With the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction concluded, the wireless industry is feeling a sense of scarcity. All the valuable over-the-air spectrum, much like desirable beachfront property, has seemingly been claimed.
However, instead of viewing the spectrum as fully allocated, consider it as a landscape inhabited by powerful entities, like T-Rexes in the Cretaceous period. These dominant players, representing major TV stations, control their portions of the spectrum, leaving little room for newcomers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-spectrum-in-all-the-white-spaces/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>