<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Turkey on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/turkey/</link><description>Recent content in Turkey on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:51:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving From Telexplainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/</guid><description>Wishing you a joyous and safe Thanksgiving filled with loved ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the agreement between the EU and Turkey on refugees and migration considered a treaty?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</guid><description>Maarten den Heijer*, Thomas Spijkerboer**
*Assistant professor of international law at the Universiteit van Amsterdam
**Professor of migration law at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.
The European Parliament recently inquired about the legal standing of the EU-Turkey Statement of March 18th, which initiated the return of asylum seekers from Greece to Turkey. Concerns arose because the agreement bypassed the standard EU treaty procedure outlined in Article 218 TFEU. The Parliament seeks clarification on whether the Council views this statement as a binding treaty and, if not, whether Turkey is aware of its non-binding status...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the draft EU/Turkey agreement on migration and refugees legally sound?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent legal debates have arisen concerning the proposed EU/Turkey agreement on refugees. While general points were discussed last month, a leaked draft of the final deal necessitates a closer examination before the finalizing summit.
The agreement, framed as an EU-Turkey statement, builds upon the March 7, 2016, statement with added elements. It is crucial to note that as a statement, it won&amp;rsquo;t be legally binding, requiring no formal EU or national approval beyond the summit&amp;rsquo;s endorsement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:14:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving/</guid><description>Have a safe and enjoyable Thanksgiving!
- John..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving/</a></p></description></item><item><title>World Heritage Map now for sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 01:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</guid><description>Source: UNESCO website.
The UNESCO World Heritage Centre and National Geographic Maps have released the most recent edition of the World Heritage map. This project received generous support from Turkey, and the map can be purchased on the World Heritage Centre website.
The map features an image of Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Historic Areas of Istanbul, the location of the next World Heritage Committee meeting in July 2016.
The poster-sized map displays all 1,031 World Heritage sites, along with pictures and detailed captions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-heritage-map-now-for-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay is expanding its presence in Turkey through partnerships with ZIRAAT BANK and Garanti Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</guid><description>Ziraat Bank in Turkey has partnered with UnionPay International to enable UnionPay card acceptance across all its ATMs and POS terminals within the year. This initiative aims to broaden the reach of UnionPay cards within Turkey and enhance the experience for visiting UnionPay cardholders.
UnionPay anticipates that this collaboration will increase the acceptance rate of UnionPay cards at Turkish ATMs from 50% to nearly 70% by year-end. Similarly, POS terminal acceptance is projected to rise from 80% to almost 90%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving 2011</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:33:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</guid><description>Wishing you a cozy and enjoyable Thanksgiving!
We&amp;rsquo;re excited to share a special Black Friday surprise with you tomorrow&amp;hellip;..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-2011/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Work together at a beach resort and form new relationships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</guid><description>While new coworking spaces and startup events are constantly emerging, forging meaningful connections with startups outside of one&amp;rsquo;s immediate location can still be challenging. Coworking Camp aims to bridge this gap with its upcoming six-week program. This program offers startups and digital nomads a chance to network and explore business opportunities with like-minded individuals in a relaxed and comfortable environment.
Source: Coworking Camp website.
Matthias Zeitler, Chief Coworker, highlights the program&amp;rsquo;s focus on fostering valuable connections and providing a space for rejuvenation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice resolves the issue of posting third-country workers within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Amedeo Arena, Assistant Professor of European Law - University of Naples &amp;ldquo;Federico II&amp;rdquo; School of Law
Judgment of the court (Second Chamber) of 11 September 2014, Essent Energie Productie BV v. Minister van SocialeZaken en Werkgelegenheid, Case C-91/13.
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) has consistently maintained that, in contrast to workers from EU Member States, Turkish nationals do not possess the right to freedom of movement within the European Union...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas has teamed up with Pegasus Airlines to provide flights from Saudi Arabia to Turkey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</guid><description>Source: flynas. Aerial view of Turkey.
The Saudi Arabian airline flynas has partnered with Turkish budget airline Pegasus Airlines to expand its flight offerings in Turkey. This collaboration will initially allow flynas passengers to travel to five new Turkish destinations: Antalya, Ankara, Adana, Hatay, and Trabzon. This will be achieved by utilizing Pegasus Airlines&amp;rsquo; extensive network of domestic flights operating from Istanbul&amp;rsquo;s Sabiha Gökçen International Airport.
Bander Al Mohanna, Group CEO of NAS Holding, stated that Pegasus Airlines is a leading Turkish airline with over two decades of experience in innovation within the country&amp;rsquo;s aviation industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The program in the European Union that allows Syrian refugees in Turkey to seek humanitarian admission.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 13:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</guid><description>Laura Robbins-Wright
PhD Candidate in Government, London School of Economics and Political Science
On December 15, 2015, the European Commission put forward a suggestion for a program to offer humanitarian entry to Syrian refugees residing in Turkey. This proposal follows earlier EU initiatives, including a plan to relocate refugees within the EU and a program for resettling refugees from other countries. It also builds upon an action plan from October 2015 and a more recent decision to give €3 billion to a Refugee Facility designed to better coordinate aid for Syrian refugees in Turkey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-program-in-the-european-union-that-allows-syrian-refugees-in-turkey-to-seek-humanitarian-admission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It is time for the EU to address the origins of informal agreements in EU migration law when cooperating on migration with third countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</guid><description>Dr Céline Hocquet, Teaching Fellow, Birmingham Law School, University of Birmingham
Photo credit: Issam Barhoumi, via Wikimedia Commons
As the EU proposes yet another collaboration with a non-EU nation to manage migration beyond its borders, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to critically examine the EU&amp;rsquo;s externalization policy and its use of informal cooperation. This analysis should consider the historical, legal, and political context of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external migration and asylum policy.
From the EU-Turkey to the EU-Tunisia deal?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The opening date for Six Senses Kaplankaya is May 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:09:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</guid><description>![Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEg6jRBaFFB8FLc8GWUouGmkRpZIrrVyWlKYCZ1pRPjPgJhTMuDR2tOLPpVhKP-eWibrLG1ZGt42dmOjjJoSeU_SwAl_HlA8BkuquNMt_lQ5P90CQTn7bDyCDPtU74R2ApXfx4oJxuNUaZo/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;Six Senses hotel in Turkey opens May 1.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The Six Senses Kaplankaya.
The Six Senses Kaplankaya resort, which became part of Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas on May 1, 2017, commences its new season on May 1, 2018. The property now aligns with Six Senses&amp;rsquo; standards of design, sustainability, and wellness, offering a distinct guest experience focused on achieving equilibrium and well-being by engaging all the senses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-opening-date-for-six-senses-kaplankaya-is-may-1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Garuda and Turkish Airlines have formed a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines have partnered to offer codeshare flights between Jakarta and Istanbul. This agreement is valid until October 24, 2015.
The joint flight schedule for Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines is shown below:
Source: Garuda Indonesia. CGK represents Soekarno–Hatta International Airport in Jakarta, Indonesia, while IST stands for Atatürk International Airport in Istanbul, Turkey. STD indicates departure time, and STA refers to arrival time. +1 signifies arrival on the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Assessing the Legal Implications of the EU/Turkey Refugee Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 14:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</guid><description>Steve Peers analyzes the legal and political implications of the recent EU-Turkey agreement on refugees. The agreement, while legally controversial, aims to address the refugee crisis and restore order.
A key point of contention is the return of migrants arriving in Greece to Turkey. While the agreement states this will be done in accordance with international law, returning all migrants without considering individual circumstances raises concerns about collective expulsion, a violation of EU and international law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-legal-implications-of-the-eu-turkey-refugee-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evaluating the new proposal on "Safe countries of origin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission recently introduced several new immigration and asylum initiatives. Three proposals, in particular, suggest binding measures: a temporary relocation measure for asylum-seekers, a permanent relocation system for asylum-seekers, and a regulation establishing a common list of &amp;ldquo;safe countries of origin.&amp;rdquo; This list would include Western Balkan countries and Turkey. This article will focus on the &amp;ldquo;safe country of origin&amp;rdquo; rules.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the UK, Ireland, and Denmark are not subject to these measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>