<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Florist on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/florist/</link><description>Recent content in Florist on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/florist/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves.</description></item><item><title>Bloem marks 4th anniversary with introduction of new services and partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Sukri Kadola and Ivy Tan cut a cake during Bloem&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s custom floral design company, Bloem, recently commemorated its fourth anniversary. The company marked this occasion by announcing new partnerships and the launch of its Concierge service.
&amp;ldquo;While many believe the economy has presented difficulties for businesses, success is subjective,&amp;rdquo; says Sukri Kadola, Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO. Eighty percent of Bloem&amp;rsquo;s revenue is generated through corporate projects.</description></item><item><title>Developing mutually beneficial solutions for both vendors and clients</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/developing-mutually-beneficial-solutions-for-both-vendors-and-clients/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:37:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/developing-mutually-beneficial-solutions-for-both-vendors-and-clients/</guid><description>Source: Bloem. A flower arrangement created to complement the color palette of the room at Park Hotel, Farrer Park and reflect the elegance of the setting.
Modern customers are more challenging than ever, but expecting them to change is futile. This was the message from Sukri Kadola, founder and CEO of creative consultancy Bloem, during his presentation titled &amp;ldquo;Confessions of a Perfectionist and how he tamed the Bridezilla and other impossible customers.</description></item><item><title>Bloem is set to open its flagship store at The Heeren</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-is-set-to-open-its-flagship-store-at-the-heeren/</guid><description>Source: Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This wedding bouquet showcases Bloem&amp;rsquo;s artistry and meticulousness.
Bloem, the floral design studio, is expanding its presence in Singapore with a new flagship store at Robinson&amp;rsquo;s The Heeren. This location will introduce a wider audience to their distinctive and customized floral creations.
Since 2013, Bloem has established a strong reputation for its tailored floral arrangements for corporate clients, according to founder and CEO, Sukri Kadola. The Orchard Road store marks a significant step in the brand&amp;rsquo;s growth trajectory, broadening its reach to a larger customer base.</description></item></channel></rss>