<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Single Market on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-market/</link><description>Recent content in Single Market on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-market/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations.</description></item></channel></rss>