<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Single Permit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-permit/</link><description>Recent content in Single Permit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/single-permit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections.</description></item><item><title>Quit this job and shove it: the updated EU legislation on non-EU migrant workers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
*Text updated Dec 22 2023, to add a link to the agreed text of the Directive, and April 12 2024, on its final adoption Photo credit: Lasse Fuss, via Wikimedia commons
While the recent agreement on asylum legislation has garnered significant attention, an equally important development occurred with the EU Member States and European Parliament reaching an agreement on amending the &amp;lsquo;single permit Directive,&amp;rsquo; a law governing non-EU migrant workers.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item></channel></rss>