<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Freedom of Expression on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-expression/</link><description>Recent content in Freedom of Expression on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/freedom-of-expression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>Evaluation of the updated EU Council Guidelines on Freedom of Expression in both digital and physical spaces.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluation-of-the-updated-eu-council-guidelines-on-freedom-of-expression-in-both-digital-and-physical-spaces/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods from the University of Essex, and co-author of Steiner and Woods, EU Law, discusses new EU guidelines on freedom of expression.
The European Union Council recently established guidelines for freedom of expression. These guidelines, falling under the Foreign Affairs Council, are designed for application within the framework of the Union’s Common Foreign and Security Policy, similar to previous guidelines addressing issues like torture, capital punishment, and human rights advocates.</description></item><item><title>Divergence in regulations after Brexit: Copyright law as a preview of future changes.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:21:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/divergence-in-regulations-after-brexit-copyright-law-as-a-preview-of-future-changes/</guid><description>Martin Kretschmer, Professor of Intellectual Property Law (CREATe Centre, University of Glasgow)
The UK&amp;rsquo;s departure from the European Union has resulted in the first instance of regulatory divergence. As the UK exits the single market, existing regulations are starting to show cracks.
In response to a question from MP Jo Stevens, former Intellectual Property Minister Chris Skidmore indicated the UK would not implement the latest EU Copyright Directive, despite the UK&amp;rsquo;s prior support for it in the EU Council.</description></item><item><title>The complexities of the new EU Media Freedom Act</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</guid><description>Samira Asmaa Allioui, research and tutorial fellow at the Center for International and European Studies at the University of Strasbourg
Photo credit: Bin im Garten, via Wikimedia Commons
Journalists face various pressures. Recent years have seen media freedom, particularly media pluralism, under threat.
On December 15, 2023, the European Council and Parliament reached an agreement on regulations to protect media freedom, pluralism, and editorial independence within the European Union. The EU Media Freedom Act (EMFA) aims for greater transparency in media ownership and safeguards against government surveillance and spyware targeting journalists.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens.</description></item><item><title>A Story of Two Institutions: Regulation of Hate Speech in Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</guid><description>Clotilde Pégorier, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The regulation of hate speech has recently resurfaced as a crucial legal and political topic in Europe. While the complexity of this issue and the varying views on balancing legislation with rights protection are well-known, the contrasting approaches of the EU and the Council of Europe, two closely linked entities, is notable. This difference raises questions about its underlying reasons and broader legislative ramifications in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Is Delfi restricting freedom of expression online in Estonia?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Media Law, University of Essex
Under what circumstances can online freedom of expression be restricted? The recent decision from the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber in the case of Delfi v. Estonia tackles this question, focusing on comments made in response to a news article. This ruling presents thought-provoking issues concerning both human rights and EU law, which will be examined in this analysis.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the Big Brother Watch case: part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:23:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-big-brother-watch-case-part-2/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
(These observations on the judgment follow part 1 of the analysis, which explained the Court’s reasoning).
The Big Brother Watch judgment can be interpreted in two ways: as confirmation that mass surveillance is permissible (para 314) or as an acknowledgment that the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act (RIPA) framework was inadequate. This implies that the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), which inherited some of RIPA&amp;rsquo;s shortcomings, is also lacking.</description></item><item><title>Balancing religious tolerance with freedom of expression in ECHR case law: Is there a right to insult?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-religious-tolerance-with-freedom-of-expression-in-echr-case-law-is-there-a-right-to-insult/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights has reignited the debate about whether freedom of speech should have limitations, particularly when it comes to potentially offensive remarks targeting religious beliefs, such as those of the Muslim faith. This presents an opportunity to analyze the case&amp;rsquo;s background and determine what, if any, restrictions on free speech are justifiable in such instances.</description></item><item><title>The European Commission introduces an anti-SLAPP initiative known as 'Daphne's Law'.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-introduces-an-anti-slapp-initiative-known-as-daphne-s-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 02:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-introduces-an-anti-slapp-initiative-known-as-daphne-s-law/</guid><description>Professor Justin Borg-Barthet, University of Aberdeen*
*Advisor to a coalition of press freedom NGOs on the introduction of SLAPPs, co-author of the CASE Model Law, lead author of a study commissioned by the European Parliament, and member of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s Expert Group on SLAPPs and its legislative sub-group
Background
At the time of her assassination on October 16, 2017, Maltese journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia faced 48 defamation lawsuits across various courts.</description></item><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 09:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497</description></item><item><title>AG Kokott dismisses challenges to the legality of the Tobacco Products Directive - what does this mean for standardized packaging laws in Member States?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</guid><description>Jonathan Griffiths, Reader in Intellectual Property Law, Queen Mary University of London
The Tobacco Products Directive (Directive 2014/40/EU, revising Directive 2001/37/EC) implements strict rules for selling tobacco products. This includes requiring larger image and text health warnings on cigarettes and rolling tobacco, tighter marketing regulations for tobacco products (including e-cigarettes), and a ban on marketing tobacco products with &amp;ldquo;characterizing flavors,&amp;rdquo; such as menthol cigarettes.
On December 23rd, Advocate General Kokott presented her Opinions on three cases regarding the validity of specific parts of the Directive.</description></item><item><title>New ECHR ruling on freedom of expression and internet comment liability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 13:54:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-echr-ruling-on-freedom-of-expression-and-internet-comment-liability/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent case before the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) raises the question of whether internet site providers should be held accountable for comments made by users. This issue gained significance following the court&amp;rsquo;s ruling in MTE v. Hungary.
Considering the importance of intermediaries in the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth, there are arguments for not treating them like traditional publishers. Instead, they could be granted some immunity regarding content posted by others.</description></item><item><title>Could this be a parody? The Advocate-General's viewpoint on the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-this-be-a-parody-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-on-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-this-be-a-parody-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-on-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>Sabine Jacques, a PhD student at the University of Nottingham&amp;rsquo;s School of Law specializing in parody exceptions, discusses the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s (AG) opinion on the Deckmyn case. The case grapples with the interpretation of copyright exceptions for parodies within EU law, specifically Article 5(3)(k) of the Infosoc Directive, which permits member states to allow exceptions for caricature, parody, or pastiche.
Jacques highlights the timely relevance of the opinion, given the ongoing debate over copyright exceptions and the delayed implementation of a parody exception in the UK.</description></item><item><title>We have the freedom to laugh at anything, but not everyone can appreciate it!" Examining the boundaries of freedom of expression through parody: the ruling of the CJEU in the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 04:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception
at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
The Advocate-General recently issued an opinion on parody, sparking significant interest in the topic. This opinion, while not yet available in English, has been the subject of discussion in legal circles. Further amplifying this attention, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has now released its own judgment on the matter.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU interprets the e-commerce Directive regarding Facebook's responsibility for defamatory posts.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, several legal decisions have addressed how individuals can control their information online. Two cases, GC et al and Google v CNIL, focused on how search engines should interpret their obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This post will focus on a third case, Glawischnig-Piesczek v Facebook, which examined how the e-Commerce Directive&amp;rsquo;s prohibition on general monitoring applies to &amp;ldquo;stay down&amp;rdquo; notices. The case raises a broader question about the consistency of different internet regulations, including those related to intellectual property, child exploitation, and terrorism.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU judgment in NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford has erased the blurry line between employment discrimination and the right to freedom of expression.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Ph.D. Researcher in International Studies at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case C‑507/18, NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford, centers around the balance between freedom of expression and the harmful impact of discriminatory language. Advocate General Eleanor Sharpston aptly used bird metaphors in her opinion, likening discriminatory statements to volatile birds that can quickly spread their harmful effects.</description></item><item><title>Copyright and the Internet: Poland vs. Parliament and Council (Case C-401/19), Advocate General's Opinion, July 15, 2021</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 20:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copyright-and-the-internet-poland-vs-parliament-and-council-case-c-401-19-advocate-general-s-opinion-july-15-2021/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
The rise of &amp;ldquo;Web 2.0&amp;rdquo; and social media has enabled widespread content sharing, but also raised questions about managing user rights and the role of online platforms in addressing challenges that their services might facilitate. One issue is the use of filtering technologies, particularly their impact on users&amp;rsquo; freedom of expression. Courts have previously voiced concerns about these techniques in copyright cases.</description></item><item><title>The ECHR provides clarification on the use of hidden cameras in relation to human rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-echr-provides-clarification-on-the-use-of-hidden-cameras-in-relation-to-human-rights/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Bremner v Turkey provides clarity on the use of hidden cameras by journalists and potential human rights violations. The case involved an Australian citizen, Bremner, who was secretly filmed in his apartment discussing Christianity for a documentary about &amp;ldquo;foreign peddlers of religion&amp;rdquo; in Turkey. The program aired footage of Bremner with his face unblurred.</description></item><item><title>A case involving Facebook, defamation, and free speech is currently pending in the CJEU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Preliminary Notes on the Pending Case Glawischnig-Piesczek v. Facebook Ireland Limited
Dr Paolo Cavaliere, University of Edinburgh Law School, paolo.cavaliere@ed.ac.uk
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon release a potentially groundbreaking decision regarding political speech and internet platform liability. The court will address two related but distinct issues: the extent of platforms&amp;rsquo; responsibility to remove illegal content, specifically if it applies to content similar to posts previously deemed unlawful, and whether such obligations apply beyond the court&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction.</description></item></channel></rss>