<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Human Rights on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-rights/</link><description>Recent content in Human Rights on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/human-rights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Great Repeal Bill and the Legacy of Henry VIII: Threatening Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</guid><description>Joelle Grogan, Lecturer, Middlesex University
The Great Repeal Bill is ironically named because it won&amp;rsquo;t actually repeal much EU law. Instead, when Brexit concludes, it will initially shift existing EU law into British law. While this maintains some stability during the transition, the bill also includes a concerning element: a Henry VIII clause. This clause, named after the king who gave himself sweeping legislative power, allows the government to alter primary legislation with minimal parliamentary scrutiny...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-great-repeal-bill-and-the-legacy-of-henry-viii-threatening-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The complex human rights protection system in Europe: facing challenges, embracing opportunities, and managing risks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</guid><description>Lecture at Waseda University Tokyo, 14 March 2016
Jörg Polakiewicz
Professor at the Europainstitut of the University of Saarbrücken and Director of Legal Advice and Public International Law (Legal Adviser), Council of Europe.[1]
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to be presenting at Waseda University in Tokyo. Thank you to Professor Koji Tonami and Professor Kaoru Obata for making this lecture possible.
I am consistently impressed by the comprehensive understanding of fundamental rights protection within Japan&amp;rsquo;s legal system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complex-human-rights-protection-system-in-europe-facing-challenges-embracing-opportunities-and-managing-risks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new approach by the Bundesverfassungsgericht regarding constitutional complaints: balancing conflicting rights and applying Union law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</guid><description>Lucia Serena Rossi, Judge at the Court of Justice of the European Union*
* Personal opinions expressed in this article are not representative of the Court&amp;rsquo;s views.
** Originally published in Italian as ‘Il “nuovo corso” del Bundesverfassungsgeright nei ricorsi diretti di constituzionalità: bilanciamento fra diritti confliggenti e applicazione del diritto dell’Unione’ on Federalismi.it, February 5, 2020, ISSN 1826-3534.
Table of contents:
Balancing Competing Fundamental Rights in the EU&amp;rsquo;s Multilevel System...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Judicial oversight of suspected violations of fundamental rights in the execution of Eulex Kosovo and the Advocate General's Ćapeta's Opinion in Joined Cases C-29/22 P and C-44/22 P.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 19:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</guid><description>Antje Kunst*
Photo credit: Sharon Hahn Darlin, via Wikimedia Commons
In a recent legal opinion, Advocate General Ćapeta addressed the question of whether individuals can sue the European Union for damages related to alleged fundamental rights violations during an EU mission. The case involved KS and KD, whose family members disappeared and were killed in Kosovo in 1999. They allege that Eulex Kosovo, an EU mission tasked with investigating such crimes, failed to adequately investigate their cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-oversight-of-suspected-violations-of-fundamental-rights-in-the-execution-of-eulex-kosovo-and-the-advocate-general-s-apeta-s-opinion-in-joined-cases-c-29-22-p-and-c-44-22-p/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mastering the art of releasing control - the Charter of Fundamental Rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Eduardo Gill-Pedro, Post-Doctoral Researcher, Faculty of Law, Lund University: Eduardo.gill-pedro@jur.lu.se
The UK Government&amp;rsquo;s proposition to exclude the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights (the Charter) from UK law after Brexit (clause 5(4) of the EU Withdrawal Bill) has drawn criticism from opposition parties. The Labour party views this as a non-negotiable issue and refuses to endorse any bill that doesn&amp;rsquo;t integrate the Charter into UK law. Keir Starmer, the Shadow Brexit Secretary, previously stated that Labour would only back a deal that meets its &amp;ldquo;six tests,&amp;rdquo; one being the preservation of &amp;ldquo;rights and protections&amp;rdquo; to avoid a decline in standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mastering-the-art-of-releasing-control-the-charter-of-fundamental-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice's initial decision on detaining asylum-seekers within the Dublin system and its implications for the rule of law in immigration detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</guid><description>Tommaso Poli, LL.M. candidate in Human Rights and Humanitarian Law at the University of Essex, School of Law.
The detention of those seeking asylum is a contentious issue within immigration law. While not initially covered by the European Common Asylum System (CEAS), it is now addressed in several of the second-phase CEAS measures. These measures include the Asylum Procedures Directive, the Reception Conditions Directive, the Qualification Directive, the Dublin Regulation, and the EURODAC Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Litigation in England involving business and human rights post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Anil Yilmaz Vastardis, Lecturer in Law, Human Rights Centre, University of Essex
Following the UK&amp;rsquo;s decision to leave the European Union, there is widespread uncertainty about the future. While political questions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit dominate the discussion, the consequences extend far beyond, impacting individuals worldwide, including victims of human rights abuses perpetrated by British corporations. A key concern revolves around the fate of EU laws implemented in the UK, either through legislation or direct application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/litigation-in-england-involving-business-and-human-rights-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies will now have to comply with new EU human rights reporting requirements, which go beyond the current rules in the UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/</guid><description>Authored by Anil Yilmaz, Lecturer in Law at the University of Brighton, and Rachel Chambers, PhD candidate at the University of Essex.
Background The European Union, as stated in Article 3(3) of the Treaty on the European Union, aims to establish a unified internal market and foster sustainable growth. This growth should be characterized by balanced economic advancement, price stability, and a highly competitive social market economy. This economic model strives for full employment, social progress, and robust environmental protection and improvement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-will-now-have-to-comply-with-new-eu-human-rights-reporting-requirements-which-go-beyond-the-current-rules-in-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The potential threat to human rights protection posed by the CJEU and the EU's accession to the ECHR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</guid><description>The CJEU’s Opinion on EU Accession to the ECHR: Taking the Football Home Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) finally issued its ruling on the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed accession to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). This intricate judgment brings up numerous legal points. This post will present a concise summary of the ruling, examine its implications, and offer an initial critique of the Court&amp;rsquo;s reasoning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-threat-to-human-rights-protection-posed-by-the-cjeu-and-the-eu-s-accession-to-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Data Retention Directive provides the context for the background.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</guid><description>By Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
As the Snowden leaks continue to make waves, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) is set to rule on a case (Digital Rights Ireland, Seitlinger and Others) that could potentially invalidate the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive in its present form. This directive mandates that private companies retain large amounts of their users&amp;rsquo; telecommunications data, just in case law enforcement needs it for criminal or terrorism investigations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Summary of a new report: Is Restoring the Borderless Schengen Area an Impossible Mission?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: BlueMars, via Wikimedia Commons
A new report I wrote for the Swedish Institute of European Policy Studies (SIEPS) analyzes the potential effects of the recently approved changes to the Schengen Borders Code. This blog post summarizes the key findings of the report.
The report addresses concerns regarding the increasing trend of Schengen countries reinstating border checks within the zone for extended periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU General Court's ruling in the WS and Others v Frontex case: Failure to hold accountable human rights violations at EU external borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</guid><description>Francesca Romana Partipilo, PhD candidate in International Law at Sant&amp;rsquo;Anna School of Advanced Studies (Pisa)
Photo credit: Rock Cohen, via Wikimedia commons
(see also critique of the judgment, by Melanie Fink and Jorrit Rijpma)
On September 6th, the EU General Court dismissed a case brought by a Syrian family claiming material and emotional damages from Frontex. They alleged experiencing anguish, fear, and suffering due to Frontex&amp;rsquo;s actions during a return operation conducted jointly with Greece on October 20th, 2016...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a Member State to be expelled or suspended from the EU? An updated summary of Article 7 of the Treaty on European Union.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The re-election of Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Orban government has led some critics to demand Hungary&amp;rsquo;s expulsion from the EU. This raises questions about the possibility of such an action and the available sanctions the EU can impose on its members.
This post revisits and updates earlier discussions on this topic, focusing on the &amp;lsquo;Article 7&amp;rsquo; process for addressing breaches of the rule of law and other EU values by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-member-state-to-be-expelled-or-suspended-from-the-eu-an-updated-summary-of-article-7-of-the-treaty-on-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Does repealing the Human Rights Act comply with EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK&amp;rsquo;s new government plans to revoke its Human Rights Act (HRA), a move with legal and political ramifications. While the overlap with EU law is complex, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to examine the potential conflicts and consequences.
Assuming the UK remains part of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and doesn&amp;rsquo;t intend to disapply the EU Charter of Rights domestically, the government&amp;rsquo;s objective seems to be weakening domestic human rights protection and separating it from the ECHR, potentially impacting groups considered undesirable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/does-repealing-the-human-rights-act-comply-with-eu-law/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>