<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness.</description></item></channel></rss>