<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fruit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fruit/</link><description>Recent content in Fruit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:41:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fruit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There is increasing interest in cold pressed juices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</guid><description>Source: Techsci Research.
A TechSci Research report projects the global cold-pressed juice market to experience a significant growth rate, exceeding 10% annually, between 2016 and 2022. This anticipated growth is attributed to several factors, including increased disposable incomes, heightened consumer awareness, effective marketing campaigns by industry leaders, widespread product availability, and a strong global distribution network.
Global GDP per capita, adjusted for purchasing power parity, rose from US$14,020.31 in 2012 to US$15,470.</description></item><item><title>The benefits of pomelo for your health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-pomelo-for-your-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-pomelo-for-your-health/</guid><description>Source: Chulalongkorn University website.
Research by Dr. Sirichai Adisakwattana, an Associate Professor at Chulalongkorn University in Thailand, suggests that concentrated extracts from pomelo fruit possess antioxidant properties, which contribute to overall health, and can reduce fat levels.
To reach these findings, Dr. Adisakwattana created powdered concentrates from six varieties of pomelo. His analysis showed that these concentrates could lower both cholesterol and blood lipid levels.
However, due to the fruit&amp;rsquo;s natural sugar content, the university recommends limiting consumption to a small portion each day.</description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa.</description></item><item><title>The new snowskin flavors at Goodwood Park are ideal combinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with new snowskin mooncake flavors that perfectly pair two complementary ingredients. This year, the hotel is even introducing its first-ever chocolate mooncake.
One of the new additions is the Yuzu Lychee Snowskin Mooncake, featuring the bright citrus flavor of yuzu combined with sweet lychee pieces. Another highlight is the limited-edition Dark Chocolate Crunchy Hazelnut Snowskin Mooncake. This decadent treat consists of a crunchy hazelnut chocolate center surrounded by rich dark chocolate mousse, all encased in a snowskin made with crushed vanilla beans and caramel.</description></item><item><title>Improving heart health with cranberry juice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</guid><description>Drinking cranberry juice every day could potentially lead to healthier blood sugar and cholesterol levels, according to recent research.
In a study involving overweight but otherwise healthy participants, those who drank two glasses (450ml) of a cranberry-based beverage daily for two weeks showed improvements in blood sugar stability, reducing spikes and dips often associated with cravings and fatigue. These benefits continued when the two-glass intake was maintained.
After eight weeks of daily consumption, the same cranberry beverage was also linked to higher levels of &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; HDL cholesterol, known for promoting artery health by removing &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; cholesterol.</description></item></channel></rss>