<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Grand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grand/</link><description>Recent content in Grand on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/grand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The doors of Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort are now open</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-doors-of-grand-mercure-qingdao-nanshan-resort-are-now-open/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort.
AccorHotels has recently added the Grand Mercure Qingdao Nanshan Resort to its portfolio. This marks the second Grand Mercure establishment in Qingdao, following the Grand Mercure Qingdao Airport, and the fourteenth in Greater China.
Michel Molliet, Chief Operating Officer of AccorHotels Greater China, expressed enthusiasm, stating that the resort is a valuable addition to the Grand Mercure network in Shandong province&amp;rsquo;s largest coastal city.</description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy introduced black bean mooncakes to their selection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy.
At the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, this Mooncake Festival, indulge in a modern take on classic handmade mooncakes created by Head Chef Lester Wang.
With over 20 flavors, Chef Wang&amp;rsquo;s baked and snowskin mooncakes offer a delightful blend of traditional and contemporary tastes. Popular choices include Jia Wei Durian, Signature Italian Dark Coffee, and Raspberry with Dark Chocolate mooncakes.
This year&amp;rsquo;s selection introduces two new flavors: traditional baked mooncakes with black bean paste and the ‘Ying Yang’ snowskin mooncake, featuring a harmonious blend of white lotus and black bean fillings.</description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream.</description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces.</description></item></channel></rss>