<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Computer Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computer-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Computer Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/computer-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goose Your Technical Service Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</guid><description>Are you seeing a decline in business lately? You might have just as many inquiries, but customers seem hesitant to commit. This is likely due to the current economic climate, not anything you&amp;rsquo;re doing wrong. However, there are ways to stimulate your business and potentially even increase your income.
While these ideas apply to many businesses, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on those offering telephone or computer networking technical services. If this describes your business, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck!</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item></channel></rss>