<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Advertising on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advertising/</link><description>Recent content in Advertising on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:35:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/advertising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Criteo emphasizes that e-commerce must be integrated into the retail strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, predicts that mobile will play an even greater role in the e-commerce industry this quarter.
Eric Eichmann, President and COO of Criteo, believes that 2015 will be a year of significant change for e-commerce as consumer online shopping habits continue to evolve rapidly. The increased use of multiple devices presents a challenge for marketers targeting consumers. Eichmann suggests that advertisers who adapt quickly by investing wisely in solutions such as cross-device targeting and mobile-optimized websites and apps will be best equipped to meet consumer demand and boost sales.</description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region.</description></item><item><title>Vanity, Thy Number is Toll Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-thy-number-is-toll-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 23:21:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-thy-number-is-toll-free/</guid><description>Vanity definitely has a place in business. Any technology that provides a competitive advantage, including a vanity toll-free number, is worth considering.
What distinguishes a vanity number from a regular toll-free number is the connection between letters and numbers on a standard telephone keypad. While the &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; button lacks letters, numbers &amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; through &amp;ldquo;9&amp;rdquo; each have three letters assigned to them.
This letter-number association allows phone numbers to be dialed as words.</description></item><item><title>Facebook claims that only native and video advertisements provide substantial value</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Head of Ad Tech, Dave Jakubowski, recently stated that exchanges and banners lack significant value in a blog post. He highlights that Facebook conducted a test using &amp;ldquo;a buying platform&amp;rdquo; within Atlas, their ad solution. The test revealed that despite reaching real people accurately, many ads were low-quality or fraudulent.
Although effective in removing these poor ads, Facebook was surprised by the sheer volume of ineffective inventory. The test also demonstrated that only native and video ad formats yielded substantial value.</description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats.</description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors.</description></item><item><title>Criteo provides a mobile advertising solution that allows ads to be displayed within mobile apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 23:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-a-mobile-advertising-solution-that-allows-ads-to-be-displayed-within-mobile-apps/</guid><description>Everyone wants to advertise on smartphones and tablets, but it&amp;rsquo;s not as easy as it sounds. Research from Flurry shows that mobile users are primarily engaged with specific apps, like email or Facebook, rather than browsing the mobile web. This limits the opportunities for advertisers to reach their target audiences.
Criteo, a company specializing in performance display advertising, has developed a solution to this challenge. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched a beta version of their mobile in-app performance display advertising solution, offering businesses a cost-effective way to engage with and convert mobile users.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions.</description></item><item><title>Cash In With Custom Toll Free Numbers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-with-custom-toll-free-numbers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:42:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-with-custom-toll-free-numbers/</guid><description>The most valuable asset for many businesses, besides their employees, is their toll-free number.
A toll-free number&amp;rsquo;s value comes from the investment in advertising and effort to link it to the business. Catchy, memorable numbers advertised across different media become synonymous with the brand. Examples like 1-800-flowers, 1-800-contacts, and 1-800-petmeds show how effective this is, even boosting online visibility as top search results.
Consider your own business: do customers have an easy, memorable way to reach you?</description></item><item><title>A new worldwide network of mobile social influencers has been introduced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 08:28:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-worldwide-network-of-mobile-social-influencers-has-been-introduced/</guid><description>VOLTU, a new performance-based social influencer network focused on mobile acquisition, has been officially launched by mobile advertising technology pioneer Glispa Global Group. Building on Glispa&amp;rsquo;s successful history of creating custom influencer campaigns for clients like Square Enix and Youzu, VOLTU connects advertisers with global content creators to increase app installs, brand awareness, and user engagement.
Influencer marketing is a proven method for engaging consumers because it utilizes genuine and relatable content made by consumers for consumers.</description></item><item><title>Deep linking achieves a significant milestone in mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deep-linking-achieves-a-significant-milestone-in-mobile-technology/</guid><description>Instead of relying on traditional search engine strategies, using deep links to guide potential customers straight to the point of sale might be more effective at boosting conversion rates for e-commerce.
A recent study by Lotlinx, a company specializing in deep-linking inventory platforms for the auto industry, reveals that deep-linking attracts double the number of genuine shoppers and doubles their engagement compared to conventional search engine marketing approaches.
Criteo, TapCommerce, and ActionX have recently collaborated to introduce a standardized specification and best practice guide for deep-linking within mobile applications.</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing In Lieu of Outsourcing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</guid><description>Over recent years, outsourcing has become increasingly popular as a way to meet business needs. However, since the Great Recession, crowdsourcing has emerged as a new and growing trend. This approach leverages the collective talent of a group to find solutions for specific tasks.
Crowdsourcing provides a decentralized approach to problem-solving, unlike traditional methods of assigning tasks to employees or contractors. Imagine needing a building sold – you&amp;rsquo;d hire a real estate agent.</description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping.</description></item><item><title>Digital advertising measurement in Singapore is not meeting expectations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-advertising-measurement-in-singapore-is-not-meeting-expectations/</guid><description>Source: IAB Singapore.
A new study by the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Singapore, titled &amp;ldquo;State of Digital Measurement in Singapore,&amp;rdquo; reveals that senior marketers believe digital advertising measurement in Singapore is lagging behind.
The study shows that senior marketers rate the sophistication of digital measurement in Singapore at an average of four out of ten, with ten representing the level of advanced markets. Mobile measurement is identified as the most significant area needing improvement.</description></item><item><title>You're Not Paying For Business Cards?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/youre-not-paying-for-business-cards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/youre-not-paying-for-business-cards/</guid><description>Business cards are essential for sharing contact information and promoting your business. While elaborate designs can be expensive, affordable options are widely available.
Don&amp;rsquo;t order thousands of cards unless necessary. Career changes and relocation make large quantities wasteful. Smaller businesses and individuals have cost-effective alternatives to company-issued cards.
Consider purchasing blank business card stock from office supply stores. These are compatible with printers and copiers. You can create your designs using graphic design software, word processors, or pre-designed templates.</description></item><item><title>Where to Get a 1-800 Number Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 20:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</guid><description>Want a 1-800 number without the high price tag? You can get one for just $5! Maintaining the number costs a mere $5 monthly, with incoming calls at 6.9 cents per minute—a small price for most businesses, and one with significant potential benefits.
Why? Because anyone dialing your 1-800 number found it through an advertisement, business card, flyer, newspaper, television, billboard, or radio. They have a reason for calling, usually translating to a motivated customer.</description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations.</description></item></channel></rss>