<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trimmer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trimmer/</link><description>Recent content in Trimmer on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trimmer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Trimmer Illumination Very Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</guid><description>After reviving the circuit boards of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I focused on improving the dim backlighting of the 33 and 45 RPM adjustment scales. I removed the panel containing these adjustments for easier access.
Taking off the light covers revealed the bulbs.
A closer look showed that the bulbs were not the correct type, leading to the weak illumination. I replaced these bulbs with my custom-designed SMD LED replacements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-trimmer-illumination-very-low/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Scales Light Bulbs with LEDs and a Further Improvement of the RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), SMD LEDs were used to replace the incandescent bulbs that illuminate the RPM trimmer scales on the control panel. This modification involved using replacement boards that could be directly soldered onto the existing light bulb solder points.
Images of the replacement boards and the installed LEDs are provided. These LED assemblies are available to other interested individuals. A video demonstrating the installation process is also available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-scales-light-bulbs-with-leds-and-a-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Main Board Rework and Start of Speed Test #3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</guid><description>I visited Mouser to acquire some components for my Beogram project. However, upon commencing work on the main board, I realized I lacked a couple of 5KΩ multi-turn trimmers, essential for the 45 RPM and 33 1/3 RPM speed control (labeled 1R14 and 1R15). While I could order the parts, delivery wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be possible until Monday, and I was eager to keep the project moving.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a photo of the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main board before removal:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-main-board-rework-and-start-of-speed-test-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of the RPM Trimmer Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 04:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the PCB restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5523), the next step was to swap the RPM trimmer illumination bulbs with LEDs. This change enhances the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s long-term stability and the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM consistency. The RPM trimmers are integral to the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s feedback circuit, which maintains a steady RPM. Incandescent bulbs generate heat, affecting the trimmers and potentially causing RPM fluctuations. The cooler-running LEDs effectively address this issue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmer-light-bulbs-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs of the RPM Trimmer Scales with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</guid><description>During my current restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5523), I replaced the incandescent bulbs that light up the RPM trimmer adjustment scales. I swapped them with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies for longer-lasting illumination, which is beneficial for those aiming to use their Beogram long-term. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the latest iteration of the LED boards before installation:
Fellow enthusiasts can acquire these assemblies. This video demonstrates the LED board installation process, starting with removing the trimmer panel and its existing light bulbs:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-of-the-rpm-trimmer-scales-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bemaster 6000 (2702) restoration: the FM preset board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 11:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/</guid><description>As part of the equipment restoration, cleaning is essential. After over four decades, units accumulate a substantial amount of dust, as depicted in an earlier post. The FM preset board was no exception, exhibiting both dust and corroded trimmer contacts. These open trimmers are situated beneath the front panel, where gaps allow dust infiltration.
[Image]
To remove and clean the trimmers, desoldering their three contacts is necessary. They can then be slid out of the main black plastic housing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with SMD LED Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 20:02:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002s model 550x has a unique characteristic: the 33 RPM scale light faintly glows when plugged in, even without pressing start. This is because the 550x models use a different method for switching platter speeds compared to earlier models.
Unlike the Beogram 4000 and later DC motor models that use a relay, the 550x utilizes electronic RPM switching, evident by the lack of a relay click when changing speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-smd-led-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Incandescent Light Bulbs in the RPM Indicators with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 07:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</guid><description>During the ongoing restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the incandescent bulbs illuminating the RPM trimmer scales were replaced with LEDs for enhanced longevity. Custom-designed circuit boards housing SMD LEDs were crafted to seamlessly replace the original bulbs, ensuring a direct fit.
These LED assemblies are offered to fellow enthusiasts, with an instructional video demonstrating their installation available online.
The following images detail the RPM trimmer panel, initially showcasing the rear view with original bulbs in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-the-rpm-indicators-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors in the Beogram 4000, I focused on upgrading the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs. LEDs offer greater long-term stability and are generally preferable replacements for incandescent bulbs, except in cases where the original circuitry or aesthetics demand otherwise. Given that the control panel&amp;rsquo;s lighting is internal and not directly visible, LEDs are a suitable replacement. In this instance, one of the bulbs illuminating the position scale had failed, causing the entire scale to go dark due to the series arrangement of the two bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, RPM Relay and Trimmers on the Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild on this Beogram 4002 (5513), the main PCB was addressed. All electrolytic capacitors were swapped with high-quality, Japanese-made, 105C-rated capacitors. The existing Tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail dramatically, were preemptively replaced with modern equivalents to avoid any potential issues. Images illustrate the original board and the sections targeted for capacitor replacement.
The author designed a replacement for the original Siemens relay using a modern, fully encapsulated SMD relay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: An Entertaining Afternoon Exploring the Record Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem arose with its record detection system. While it functioned correctly at the 12-inch LP position, it frequently failed to detect records at the 7-inch singles position. This malfunction was observed when the turntable, starting without a record on the platter, bypassed the LP position but stopped at the singles position.
An examination of the circuit diagram revealed the signal path of the detection system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-an-entertaining-afternoon-exploring-the-record-detection-circuit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board – a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of Main and Output Printed Circuit Boards, and a New Reservoir Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the PCBs after addressing the decayed transport lock bushings. The main PCB was first, as shown below:
In addition to replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay and trimmers were targeted due to their susceptibility to corrosion and impact on RPM stability. The following image highlights the RPM section in its initial condition:
Modern, encapsulated 25-turn trimmers replaced the old ones, and a new relay was installed (interested enthusiasts can obtain a replacement relay by email or through the contact form)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>