<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Indonesia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/indonesia/</link><description>Recent content in Indonesia on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/indonesia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The launch of Fairfield by Marriott Belitung has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-fairfield-by-marriott-belitung-has-been-announced/</guid><description>Marriott International has expanded its Fairfield by Marriott brand with the opening of a new hotel in Belitung, Indonesia.
Source: Fairfield by Marriott Belitung website. The Fairfield by Marriott Belitung.
Mike Fulkerson, Vice President of Brand &amp;amp; Marketing for Marriott International Asia Pacific, stated that Fairfield by Marriott is experiencing rapid growth in the region, with 47 properties in development in Asia Pacific and over 400 globally. He highlighted the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing a relaxing and dependable experience at a good value, enhanced by Indonesian hospitality, making the Belitung location an ideal retreat for travelers.</description></item><item><title>The demand for milk and yogurt-based beverages is increasing in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Increased advertising in mass media, along with more television shows and magazine content focused on health topics, have made Indonesian consumers more aware of the advantages of drinking milk from 2011 to 2016, according to Euromonitor.
Ultrajaya Milk Industry &amp;amp; Trading Company leads the drinking milk market, holding a 23% value share in 2016. Its most recognized brand is Ultra. Euromonitor attributes the company&amp;rsquo;s success in flavored milk to its strong marketing and enhanced distribution.</description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation.</description></item><item><title>Bank Mandiri is seeking submissions for the Young Entrepreneur award 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</guid><description>Bank Mandiri, a prominent bank in Indonesia, launched its yearly competition called Mandiri Young Entrepreneur (WMM) in 2015.
Kartika Wirjoatmodjo, the Director of Finance &amp;amp; Strategy at Bank Mandiri, stated that this competition aims to discover young individuals with entrepreneurial potential who can contribute to Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s growth. Kartika added that the competition also intends to inspire a passion for entrepreneurship and innovation among students and graduates, encouraging more young entrepreneurs to emerge.</description></item><item><title>WAKE UP CALL is coming to Bali in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</guid><description>Source: WAKE UP CALL website. W Hotels is putting on a unique music festival at three locations in 2018, with a Dubai edition planned for 2019.
W Hotels presents WAKE UP CALL, a distinctive music festival hosted at three W Hotels, including the W Bali, alongside venues in the US and Europe.
Merging their love for music with their signature Whatever/Whenever approach, WAKE UP CALL brings the festival experience directly to the hotel.</description></item><item><title>Choose from a variety of MICE packages available in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Three travel companies — Chōsen, The Slate, and Samujana — have designed productivity programs for businesses and workgroups. These programs offer a variety of environments to help teams achieve their best results.
For adventure junkies Source: Chosen website. A view of Bali.
Chōsen provides experiences tailored for teams that thrive on new adventures and challenges:
Activities include cliff jumping, canyoning, surfing, and cooking classes. Accommodation is available at their estate in Bali and other locations, including New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate is considered the most popular indulgence product in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:39:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chocolate-is-considered-the-most-popular-indulgence-product-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesians are increasingly understanding the advantages of moderate chocolate consumption, leading to consistent purchases for snacking and special occasions. This trend fueled growth in chocolate confectionery sales in 2016, according to research firm Euromonitor. The company predicts chocolate confectionery will remain the preferred treat for Indonesian consumers of all ages.
Ceres PT, a major player in the Indonesian chocolate market, held a commanding 52% market share in 2016. Euromonitor attributes this success to the company&amp;rsquo;s strong brand reputation, diverse product range, and competitive pricing.</description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery.</description></item><item><title>Escape to Bintan Lagoon Resort for a Global Wellness Day retreat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</guid><description>Bintan Lagoon Resort (BLR) is commemorating this year&amp;rsquo;s Global Wellness Day with a special getaway package full of wellness activities on June 10th and 11th.
A quick 75-minute ferry trip from Singapore, BLR is nestled on 300 hectares of lush land, boasting a private 1.5km beach. With a wide range of over 50 indoor and outdoor activities, from adventurous to relaxing, and delicious, healthy culinary options, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Discover the surrounding areas of Hotel Indigo in the new Neighbourhood 15 campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 02:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-surrounding-areas-of-hotel-indigo-in-the-new-neighbourhood-15-campaign/</guid><description>Hotel Indigo&amp;rsquo;s new brand campaign, &amp;ldquo;Neighbourhood 15,&amp;rdquo; highlights the unique character of each hotel&amp;rsquo;s surrounding area, specifically within a 15-minute radius. The campaign showcases local businesses and individuals who contribute to the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s vibrant atmosphere.
A two-minute video featuring the Hotel Indigo Bali Seminyak Beach, the brand&amp;rsquo;s first resort location, introduces viewers to nearby attractions like Surf School Bali, Divine Earth restaurant, and Bali Barber. Starting in October, a series of videos will delve deeper into these local businesses, offering insights and personal stories.</description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region.</description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes.</description></item><item><title>Starting in September, Ulu Cliffhouse will be providing a clifftop beach club playground</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-september-ulu-cliffhouse-will-be-providing-a-clifftop-beach-club-playground/</guid><description>Source: Ulu Cliffhouse.
Opening in September 2017, Ulu Cliffhouse, a &amp;ldquo;clifftop playground&amp;rdquo; created by a group of artists, is ready to change what it means to be a beach club in Bali, Indonesia.
The 50,000 square foot clifftop retreat will provide a stylish area with a 25-meter infinity pool, an on-site spa, a boutique, private beach access, and a variety of food and beverage options, including a terraced restaurant and a cliffside bar, all with breathtaking panoramic views.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the waters of Indonesia aboard Rascal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:03:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-waters-of-indonesia-aboard-rascal/</guid><description>Source: Rascal.
Rascal, a refurbished traditional Indonesian Phinisi* yacht outfitted with modern engines, navigation, and entertainment systems, promises the ultimate adventure.
Guests enjoy personalized service on board, experiencing renowned Indonesian hospitality amidst chic tropical decor.
The removal of Rascal&amp;rsquo;s mast and sails allows for five ensuite double cabins across two spacious decks. Both indoor and outdoor areas are designed for relaxation.
The top deck, soaring 21 feet high, doubles as a diving platform.</description></item><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor.</description></item><item><title>The e-marketplace is focused on small and medium-sized retailers in Java</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 11:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</guid><description>Since its launch, Ula, a marketplace app revolutionizing distribution and credit for traditional retail, has experienced a tenfold growth. Customers are returning to make purchases up to three times their original volume.
Ula emphasizes its success by pointing out that despite the challenges of COVID-19, stores made more purchases in May than ever before.
Launched in January 2020 and headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia, Ula is a multi-category wholesale e-commerce marketplace that blends the technology and tools of modern retail with the cost-effectiveness of traditional micro-retail.</description></item><item><title>The first Nongsa Regatta took place in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Nongsa Regatta Facebook page.
The first Nongsa Regatta will take place at Nongsa Point Marina &amp;amp; Resort in Batam, Indonesia, from January 27th to 31st, 2016. This period coincides with the strongest point of the northeast monsoon. The competition welcomes yachts, sporting boats, and racing multihulls. Additionally, there will be races for dinghies and traditional &amp;ldquo;kolek&amp;rdquo; boats.
Having hosted the Singapore Straits Regatta for almost two decades, the resort possesses extensive experience in regattas.</description></item><item><title>The Tough Mudder Bali event will take place in the green hills of Jimbaran</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 04:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tough-mudder-bali-event-will-take-place-in-the-green-hills-of-jimbaran/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Bali. Event poster.
The ultimate test of physical and mental strength, stamina, and teamwork will premiere in Asia on October 1, 2016, at Jimbaran Hijau (Bali International Park), a multifaceted development in South Bali.
Established in 2010 and known as &amp;ldquo;probably the toughest event on the planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder is an obstacle course challenging participants to collaborate and conquer physical and mental hurdles in an extreme endurance event.</description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests.</description></item><item><title>The Asian Food Network has launched a website in Bahasa Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asian-food-network-has-launched-a-website-in-bahasa-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 16:27:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asian-food-network-has-launched-a-website-in-bahasa-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: asianfoodnetwork.com. Snippet from the Bahasa Indonesia website.
The Asian Food Network (AFN), a prominent TV and online food channel specializing in Asian cuisine and culture, has introduced an Indonesian language website to reach over 200 million Indonesian speakers.
AFN aims to provide a unified digital and linear experience that offers entertainment, convenience, and a community for Asian food enthusiasts. As part of this goal, the website aligns with Discovery Networks Asia Pacific (DNAP)&amp;rsquo;s strategy to enhance its offerings for the substantial Indonesian-speaking audience.</description></item><item><title>MatahariMall.com in Indonesia is growing its O2O network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</guid><description>Source: MatahariMall.com website.
The online shopping platform MatahariMall has broadened its Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD and eLocker services through a partnership with PT Pos Indonesia in Jakarta. This collaboration uses an online-to-offline approach, enabling customers to receive, return, and pay for their online purchases at physical locations.
This partnership introduces more Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD points at designated post offices. Additionally, MatahariMall will install eLockers at strategic post office locations across Jakarta, Bogor, Depok, Tangerang, Bekasi, and Bandung.</description></item><item><title>Smartfren Android users will receive a smart start screen from Celltick</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
The MySmartfren app.
Celltick, a company that provides mobile marketing solutions, has teamed up with Indonesian telecommunications company Smartfren Telekom (Smartfren) to introduce a smart home screen for Android users.
Smartfren aims to give its 12 million subscribers quick access to their most-used apps and features, along with special deals. This will be achieved through a personalized version of Celltick&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; app, pre-installed on Smartfren Android devices.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Tough Mudder event in Asia will take place in Bali, Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 06:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-tough-mudder-event-in-asia-will-take-place-in-bali-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: Tough Mudder Indonesia. Chairi Ibrahim, Project Manager at Seroja Partners (left), Gandrasta Bangko, Business Director at Mesa Race (middle), and Ridzki Syahputera, Partner at Seroja Partners (right) at the launch of Tough Mudder Indonesia.
The world-renowned endurance series, Tough Mudder, has officially launched in Indonesia. Known as &amp;ldquo;Probably the Toughest Event on the Planet,&amp;rdquo; Tough Mudder has attracted 2.5 million participants across 200 events in six countries. Its Asian debut will take place on October 1st and 2nd, 2016, in Bali, Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank will provide assistance for a geothermal energy project in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</guid><description>The World Bank is providing $55.25 million in grants to bolster Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s Geothermal Energy Upstream Development Project, which promotes investment in geothermal energy production.
The Clean Technology Fund (CTF) is supplying $49 million for infrastructure and exploratory drilling, while the Global Environment Facility (GEF) is providing an extra $6.25 million to build geothermal exploration expertise, including due diligence safeguards. The Indonesian Ministry of Finance and PT Sarana Multi Infrastruktur, a state-owned infrastructure financing firm, will match the CTF funding.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia has the highest number of brand advocates for Garuda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia, the national airline, has earned the highest level of brand advocacy among Indonesian consumers, according to a YouGov BrandIndex analysis.
With a score of 87.5, Garuda secured the top position, surpassing Singapore Airlines (77.2) and Bank Central Asia (76.5).
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s rankings utilize a net promoter score methodology to determine which brands have the highest percentage of current and former customers who would recommend them to family or friends. The top 10 list includes several automotive brands, with Toyota ranking 4th (75.</description></item><item><title>The ideal location for candy in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT is a dominant player in the Indonesian confectionery market, particularly recognized for its Mentos brand.
According to a report on the Indonesian confectionery sector by market research firm Euromonitor, the wide array of inexpensive sugary treats, combined with robust marketing campaigns from prominent manufacturers, has propelled sales in this category within Indonesia.
Holding a commanding 23% market share in 2016, Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT remains the leader in the sugar confectionery sector.</description></item><item><title>Purify and detoxify on weekends in July and August at REVĪVŌ in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: REVĪVŌ. Throughout July and August, cleansing and detox retreats are offered every weekend.
The luxurious REVĪVŌ wellness resort in Bali, Indonesia, has introduced weekend-long cleansing and detox retreats for July and August.
Guests can choose to participate for one or two days. Kicking off at 10:00 am each Saturday, the program begins with a cold-pressed juice, followed by yoga, Pilates, or meditation. Afterward, attendees enjoy kombucha (a fermented tea beverage) and a detox lunch at the NŪTRIŌ restaurant.</description></item><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Three new routes have been announced by Air Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</guid><description>AirAsia is expanding its network in Indonesia and the Philippines with three new routes starting on March 27th. The airline will now offer flights from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia to Pontianak, Indonesia, from Johor Bahru, Malaysia to Medan, Indonesia, and from Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia to Cebu, Philippines.
The Indonesian routes will operate twice a week, while the Kota Kinabalu to Cebu route, operated by AirAsia Zest, will operate four times a week.</description></item><item><title>Customers in five Asian locations can now purchase Indonesian products on Bukalapak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/</guid><description>The Indonesia-based e-commerce platform Bukalapak has introduced BukaGlobal, a new service connecting over 4 million Indonesian sellers with the international market. Bukalapak claims this makes them the first Indonesian e-commerce platform with global reach, furthering their goal of supporting the digitalization and international expansion of Indonesian small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs).
Bukalapak Co-Founder and President, Fajrin Rasyid, explained that BukaGlobal aims to tackle logistics issues in the region, including the high cost of postal and courier services.</description></item><item><title>SilkAir introduces a new daily flight from Singapore to Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:31:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-introduces-a-new-daily-flight-from-singapore-to-bali/</guid><description>Starting December 12, 2014, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines, will introduce a daily flight service to Denpasar, Indonesia, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, stated, “The increase in flights demonstrates the Singapore Airlines Group&amp;rsquo;s dedication to expanding our service offerings and providing our customers with more choices and convenience. By connecting the networks of both airlines, we can improve connectivity options for our customers through our combined network, reaching 99 cities across 35 countries.</description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor announces the winners of the 2015 Certificate of Excellence for hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 04:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-announces-the-winners-of-the-2015-certificate-of-excellence-for-hotels/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website.
Many hotels in the Asia Pacific and the Middle East have earned praise from their guests on TripAdvisor. For example, the Sheraton Bandung Hotel &amp;amp; Towers in Indonesia received a TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence award this year.
Akhmad Fadholi, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, shared that the award was a source of pride for the entire team. He expressed gratitude to past guests who left reviews on TripAdvisor, emphasizing that customer recognition is the best kind of approval.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Meliá Hotels opened at least 11 new locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-meli-hotels-opened-at-least-11-new-locations/</guid><description>Meliá Hotels International is adding at least 11 new hotels to its portfolio in 2015, including the Sol House Kuta Bali in Indonesia.
Source: Meliá Hotels website.
The recently opened 317-room Meliá Doha, which began welcoming guests in January, is the first Spanish hotel in Qatar. Located within Bin Samikh Tower, a prominent skyscraper in Doha&amp;rsquo;s West Bay district, the hotel enjoys a prime position on the Qatari coast.
The urban German brand, Innside by Meliá, is expanding its Middle Eastern presence with the upcoming Innside Dubai, a 125-room hotel.</description></item><item><title>Elite Havens is proud to announce the addition of three new properties in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/elite-havens-is-proud-to-announce-the-addition-of-three-new-properties-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: Elite Havens. Caption: Elite Havens expands its Bali Collection with three new villas.
Elite Havens, a high-end villa rental and management company in Asia, has expanded its Bali offerings with three new properties:
Sol Y Mar - Uluwatu, Bali, Indonesia
Situated on Nunggalan Beach, Sol y Mar is a four-bedroom villa featuring a private pool.
Villa Dhanika - Badung, Bali, Indonesia
Nestled amidst Balinese rice paddies, Villa Dhanika is a five-bedroom retreat with an Olympic-sized swimming pool and an outdoor jacuzzi.</description></item><item><title>The 12th WIEF could provide a boost for Indonesian SMEs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-12th-wief-could-provide-a-boost-for-indonesian-smes/</guid><description>Experts at a public dialogue titled &amp;ldquo;Seizing the Benefits of Disruptive Technology for Manufacturers in Increasing Labor Productivity&amp;rdquo; emphasized that disruptive technology can work alongside traditional, labor-intensive methods. The event was organized by The Habibie Center, in partnership with the Indonesian Ministry of Finance and the World Islamic Economic Forum Foundation, as a precursor to the 12th World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF).
Dr. Zamroni Salim, a Senior Economic Researcher at the Indonesian Institute of Sciences (LIPI), explained that disruptive technologies don&amp;rsquo;t always clash with conventional labor models.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces the first non-stop flight between Bali and Auckland that operates year-round</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced a new daily flight route connecting Dubai, UAE to Auckland, New Zealand, with a stop in Bali, Indonesia. This decision comes as a response to the growing popularity of Bali as a travel destination and aims to enhance connectivity options for travelers flying to New Zealand.
This addition brings the total number of daily Emirates flights to New Zealand to three. It complements the existing non-stop daily Airbus A380 service from Dubai to Auckland and another daily A380 service from Dubai to Christchurch, New Zealand, which includes a stopover in Sydney, Australia.</description></item><item><title>Discover the hidden secrets of Balinese sarongs with the Sarong Concierge program at the Ritz-Carlton Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 22:37:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-hidden-secrets-of-balinese-sarongs-with-the-sarong-concierge-program-at-the-ritz-carlton-bali/</guid><description>The Ritz-Carlton, Bali has introduced a new program called the Sarong Concierge to enhance its immersive cultural experiences. Guests can participate in this half-day journey led by Tresna Dewi, the resort&amp;rsquo;s Sarong Concierge, to learn about various Balinese textiles and their creation.
Known as &amp;lsquo;kamen&amp;rsquo; in Balinese, these fabrics are transformed into beautiful, intricately made sarongs. Worn by both men and women across Southeast Asia and the Arabian Peninsula, sarongs hold cultural significance in Bali and are worn for various occasions.</description></item><item><title>Barter and location-based services contribute to Jualo's success in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Chaim Fetter, a Dutch programming prodigy and entrepreneur, has balanced building businesses with a spirit of exploration and philanthropy. As a teenager, he created his first online venture, developing e-commerce websites. He spent his twenties traveling in Southeast Asia before establishing the Peduli Anak Foundation in 2005 to support former street children in Lombok, Indonesia.
Source: Jualo website.
Last year, Fetter transitioned the foundation&amp;rsquo;s leadership to a local team, relocating to Jakarta to pursue a new business venture, Jualo.</description></item><item><title>AC Ventures is investing in women-led businesses in Indonesia, with a total value of US$421 billion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 01:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ac-ventures-is-investing-in-women-led-businesses-in-indonesia-with-a-total-value-of-us-421-billion/</guid><description>Source: AC Ventures. Wong speaks at the Women’s CEO Forum.
Helen Wong, Managing Partner at AC Ventures, a venture capital firm focused on early-stage investments, urged for concrete actions to support women investors. She highlighted that investing in female founders in Indonesia presents a significant opportunity exceeding US$421 billion annually.
Wong made these remarks during her address at the Women’s CEO Forum held in Jakarta. This event was an officially recognized side event of the ASEAN Business &amp;amp; Investment Summit (ABIS) 2023.</description></item><item><title>Excelity Global will be providing HR and payroll services in Indonesia through Cekindo Bisnis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 07:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/excelity-global-will-be-providing-hr-and-payroll-services-in-indonesia-through-cekindo-bisnis/</guid><description>Excelity Global Solutions, the largest payroll service provider in Asia, has partnered with Cekindo Bisnis Grup to offer its services in Indonesia. Excelity Global, which operates in 19 countries across Asia Pacific, provides payroll outsourcing and human capital management cloud services.
Indonesia, with a large SME market, presents a significant opportunity for Excelity. SMEs make up over 98% of companies in Indonesia and contribute significantly to the country&amp;rsquo;s GDP.
By collaborating with Cekindo, a provider of market-entry and corporate secretarial services, Excelity aims to simplify HR and payroll processes for businesses in Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia has relocated its Surabaya operations to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</guid><description>AirAsia has relocated its operations from Terminal 1 to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport.
All AirAsia domestic and international flights to and from Surabaya will keep their original schedules and operate as usual.
Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport opened on February 14th. The terminal is designed to be environmentally friendly and can accommodate 6 million passengers annually. It features 40 check-in counters, an updated baggage handling system, six gates for domestic use, three gates for international flights, 12 avirobridges, and 14 parking stands for both narrow and wide-bodied aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks Indonesia has launched the Starbucks Mobile App</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Use the mobile app to make purchases at Starbucks.
Starbucks Indonesia has launched its mobile app, offering customers a quick and easy way to pay at over 260 stores across the country.
Expanding upon the cashless Starbucks Card system introduced in 2013, the Starbucks Indonesia mobile app (available on iPhone and Android) allows customers to pay for purchases by scanning a barcode linked to their registered Starbucks Card.</description></item><item><title>Garuda and Turkish Airlines have formed a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines have partnered to offer codeshare flights between Jakarta and Istanbul. This agreement is valid until October 24, 2015.
The joint flight schedule for Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines is shown below:
Source: Garuda Indonesia. CGK represents Soekarno–Hatta International Airport in Jakarta, Indonesia, while IST stands for Atatürk International Airport in Istanbul, Turkey. STD indicates departure time, and STA refers to arrival time. +1 signifies arrival on the following day.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art.</description></item><item><title>Join us at the Pullman Jakarta Indonesia to celebrate the holy month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-the-pullman-jakarta-indonesia-to-celebrate-the-holy-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>The Pullman Jakarta Indonesia hotel has a special offer for corporate groups during Ramadan. For groups of 50 or more, they offer a deluxe Iftar (breaking the fast) package for Rp450,000 per person. This package features a selection of traditional Iftar snacks and drinks, along with an Indonesian buffet.
To make a reservation or get more details, you can contact Ms. Sarat via email at H8491-SM4@accor.com or by phone at +62 21 3192 1111.</description></item><item><title>Epson's Print your Passion fashion show showcased digitally-printed textiles as the main attraction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 05:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-s-print-your-passion-fashion-show-showcased-digitally-printed-textiles-as-the-main-attraction/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. This image features a model walking the runway in an outfit from the BI.ON.IC collection.
Epson, known for its digital imaging and printing solutions, teamed up with Indonesian fashion brand Sky and Thai designer Thanit Tiansivarat. They presented their digitally printed collections at Jakarta Fashion Week 2017 during Epson&amp;rsquo;s Print Your Passion fashion show.
Sky, led by designers Amot Syamsuri Muda and Andrea Risjad, unveiled their 46-piece BI.</description></item><item><title>Gum continues to be a profitable product in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gum-continues-to-be-a-profitable-product-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:34:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gum-continues-to-be-a-profitable-product-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Indonesia experienced growth in the gum confectionery market in 2016, primarily driven by better distribution channels for gum products, particularly chewing gum, facilitated by the expansion of modern retail stores. Market research firm Euromonitor notes that consumers are increasingly drawn to the advantages of gum, such as breath freshening and teeth whitening properties.
Euromonitor reports that PT Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia maintained its dominance in the gum market, holding a 58% value share in 2016.</description></item><item><title>Indonesian brands are at the top of the Brandindex 2016 rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesian-brands-are-at-the-top-of-the-brandindex-2016-rankings/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Indonesia.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 reveal a diverse range of popular brands in Indonesia. Garuda, the national airline, claims the top spot, followed by tech giant Samsung and Danone&amp;rsquo;s mineral water brand, Aqua.
These brands were evaluated based on BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which gauges public perception by asking respondents whether their exposure to a brand in the past two weeks, whether through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth, was positive or negative.</description></item></channel></rss>