<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airways on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airways/</link><description>Recent content in Airways on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airways/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enjoy a complimentary stay at a luxurious hotel in Doha when you transit overnight with Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Doha skyline.
Qatar Airways has teamed up with Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA) to launch a stopover package, aiming to highlight Qatar as a top destination for travelers.
The package allows transit passengers to explore Doha with complimentary luxury hotel stays and transit visas. This unique deal is part of their larger &amp;ldquo;+Qatar&amp;rdquo; campaign, encouraging those passing through to consider extending their trip.
The promotion invites all Qatar Airways transit passengers to include Doha in their travel plans by offering a free one-night stay at some of the country’s top four- and five-star hotels in the capital.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi.</description></item><item><title>Etihad updates baggage policy and fare structure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
The national airline of the United Arab Emirates, Etihad Airways, is rolling out a new, clearer fare system starting September 14, 2015. This system aims to offer travelers more choices when booking their flights.
Eight new &amp;ldquo;Fare Choices&amp;rdquo; will be introduced, allowing travelers to customize their bookings to fit their needs. These transparent Fare Choices come with different baggage allowances, levels of flexibility, and included benefits that previously needed to be purchased separately.</description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel.</description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company.</description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight.</description></item><item><title>Etihad and Fiji Airways establish codeshare partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</guid><description>Fiji Airways and Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, have established an interline agreement. This partnership enables both airlines to sell tickets to and from a wider range of destinations. Passengers can now travel between 17 cities in the Middle East, 29 cities in Asia, and three cities in Australia to and from Fiji, along with other destinations.
James Hogan, President and CEO of Etihad Airways, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, stating that Fiji is an excellent vacation destination and enhances Etihad&amp;rsquo;s global network.</description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways releases statement regarding military coup in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 13:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-releases-statement-regarding-military-coup-in-thailand/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has recommended that passengers on flight EY407 from Bangkok to Abu Dhabi be prepared to show their passports and tickets if asked by military personnel. This applies when traveling to Suvarnabhumi Airport during the curfew, which is in effect from 10:00 PM to 5:00 AM local time. The airline advises, &amp;ldquo;Guests are advised to allow extra time to reach the airport.&amp;rdquo;
Due to the suspension of public transportation starting at 9:00 PM local time and possible limited taxi services, Etihad suggests that hotel guests consider booking airport limousine services through their hotels.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways has implemented improvements to its baggage policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Starting September 14, 2015, Etihad Airways will launch its new Fare Choices tariff program, which includes changes to its baggage policy. The airline claims these updates will benefit travelers, particularly those enrolled in the Etihad Guest loyalty program.
This new policy aims to provide more flexibility and align Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; baggage policies with partner airlines by catering to individual customer needs. Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, states: “This is about offering a fair and transparent baggage concept that is an industry best practice.</description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy the first 15 minutes of free Wi-Fi on Qatar Airways, courtesy of Ooredoo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo. The MoU was signed by (from left) Waleed Al Sayed, CEO, Ooredoo Qatar and Qatar Airways Group Chief Executive, His Excellency Akbar Al Baker.
Ooredoo and Qatar Airways have established a partnership where Ooredoo will sponsor Qatar Airways&amp;rsquo; in-flight Wi-Fi for the next three years. This agreement will make Ooredoo the sole sponsor for Wi-Fi on all Qatar Airways flights equipped with the service.
This sponsorship allows passengers to use their personal electronic devices to connect to the internet, check emails, and send SMS/MMS messages once the service is active during their flight.</description></item></channel></rss>