<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Employment Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employment-law/</link><description>Recent content in Employment Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employment-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Finally, a Directive safeguarding platform work - What's next?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</guid><description>Catherine Jacqueson, Professor of EU law and Alberto Barrio, postdoctoral researcher on the WorkWel-project, Law Faculty, University of Copenhagen
Photo credit: conceptphoto.info, via Flickr On April 24th, the European Parliament officially approved the directive designed to protect platform workers. Although formal endorsement from the Council is still pending, this is largely a formality. The directive&amp;rsquo;s passage, despite the challenges and last-minute negotiations, signifies a victory. Initially, the Council presented resistance, making its unexpected adoption of the compromise agreement on March 11th surprising...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finally-a-directive-safeguarding-platform-work-what-s-next/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's decision on the importance of parenthood in EU law slips away from us.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Most EU laws and court decisions on sex discrimination focus on improving women&amp;rsquo;s job opportunities and ensuring equal treatment in the workplace. A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Maistrellis case tackles these issues from a different perspective: a father&amp;rsquo;s access to parental leave when the mother isn&amp;rsquo;t employed or looking for work. This judgment brings up important questions about how EU employment and discrimination laws affect family life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit and Labour Standards during COVID-19: Will they Align or Separate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 08:18:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</guid><description>Jeff Kenner, Professor of European Law, University of Nottingham*
The COVID-19 pandemic has taken center stage, demanding an urgent worldwide response that is yet to materialize. In light of this global crisis, the issue of Brexit, particularly its self-serving nature and political maneuvering, has understandably faded from the minds of both policymakers and the public. However, despite the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s onset in mid-March 2020, which coincided with the start of negotiations for a new EU-UK partnership and led to widespread lockdowns across Europe, the UK government remains steadfast in its refusal to extend the post-Brexit transition period beyond the December 31, 2020, deadline established in the October 2019 EU-UK Withdrawal Agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-and-labour-standards-during-covid-19-will-they-align-or-separate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council needs to quickly establish a legal framework similar to the CEOS for employees working in CSDP missions: Analysis of the Jenkinson case (Case C-46/22 P)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:26:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</guid><description>Antje Kunst*
Photo credit: Jan-Tore Egge, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
In a January 18, 2024, ruling, the European Union Court of Justice dismissed an appeal by Irish citizen Mr. Jenkinson. This decision impacts thousands of individuals working in EU international missions governed by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). While the Court sided with the defendants (the Council, Commission, European External Action Service, and Eulex Kosovo), their victory is questionable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-needs-to-quickly-establish-a-legal-framework-similar-to-the-ceos-for-employees-working-in-csdp-missions-analysis-of-the-jenkinson-case-case-c-46-22-p/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The White Paper on Brexit: A Dire Situation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The UK government recently published its Brexit White Paper after much delay. The result is underwhelming and lacks substance, akin to a disappointing effort.
The White Paper is essentially a rehash of Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s previous speech with some added statistics and graphs, much of which is either outdated, inaccurate, or incomplete. It lacks a thorough examination of post-Brexit possibilities and their respective advantages and disadvantages, likely because the paper provides little concrete information about these options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-white-paper-on-brexit-a-dire-situation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU employment law and irregular migrants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Determining the employment rights of undocumented migrants is complex. On one hand, granting them full access to employment law protections could incentivize unauthorized migration. On the other hand, applying standard employment laws to all workers, regardless of immigration status, could prevent the exploitation of undocumented migrants and deter employers from hiring them to save money.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed this issue in the Tumer case, which focused on the application of the EU Directive on insolvent employers to undocumented migrants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-employment-law-and-irregular-migrants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Workplace Privacy: The Strasbourg Grand Chamber Provides Clarity on Legal Standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The Bărbulescu case examined the permissible extent of employer monitoring of employee communications, including internet usage, particularly when private conversations might be mixed with work-related ones. An employee, dismissed for violating a company policy prohibiting personal use of work equipment, sued his employer in Romania. He lost and appealed under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), which protects privacy rights, arguing that his employer&amp;rsquo;s monitoring of his communications violated the precedent set by Copland v UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on discrimination against EU citizen workers just a futile effort?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</guid><description>Despite public debate regarding EU citizens working in different Member States (&amp;ldquo;EU workers&amp;rdquo;), the Council and European Parliament have agreed on new legislation concerning this topic. Recently approved by the European Parliament, the new Directive focuses on enforcing existing rules against discrimination toward EU workers and will likely be adopted by the Council soon. Member States are given two years to implement this Directive.
The Directive itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t modify existing rights related to EU worker free movement, but instead, clarifies the enforcement and application of rights granted by Article 45 TFEU and Regulation 492/2011...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it necessary to apply the Charter in reconstructing the hierarchy of employment law norms?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</guid><description>The Uncertain Future of UK Employment Law in a Post-Brexit World Niall O’Connor, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The Charter and Brexit
Boris Johnson famously downplayed the significance of the Charter of Fundamental Rights during the Brexit campaign. He argued in a Telegraph article that the Charter&amp;rsquo;s provisions, such as the right to establish a school or pursue an occupation anywhere in the EU, are not &amp;ldquo;fundamental rights&amp;rdquo; as commonly understood and questioned their enforceability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-necessary-to-apply-the-charter-in-reconstructing-the-hierarchy-of-employment-law-norms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking beyond austerity: the future of employment law in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Catherine Barnard, Trinity College Cambridge
Contrary to critics, the EU social model (ESM) is not dead, argues Professor Barnard. Although facing significant challenges, the ESM has historically demonstrated a capacity for renewal. This post explores potential future directions for the model.
While some believe a Social Union is necessary for Europe, this post focuses on a potentially more agreeable agenda for the EU-28, particularly in the area of employment law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has ruled that holiday pay can be passed on as inheritance, stating "I'll rest when I'm dead.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-ruled-that-holiday-pay-can-be-passed-on-as-inheritance-stating-i-ll-rest-when-i-m-dead/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 04:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-ruled-that-holiday-pay-can-be-passed-on-as-inheritance-stating-i-ll-rest-when-i-m-dead/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Death is inevitable, and sadly, it can occur during an individual&amp;rsquo;s working years, before they can retire. This leads to the question: can employment rights be passed down as inheritance?
EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t dictate the specifics of inheritance laws within individual member states. However, it comes into play when inheritance involves cross-border elements like taxation (impacting the free movement of capital) or the choice of applicable law and jurisdiction, governed by a regulation effective from 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-ruled-that-holiday-pay-can-be-passed-on-as-inheritance-stating-i-ll-rest-when-i-m-dead/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-ruled-that-holiday-pay-can-be-passed-on-as-inheritance-stating-i-ll-rest-when-i-m-dead/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the European Labour Authority: A New EU Agency Based in Bratislava</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</guid><description>Bartłomiej Bednarowicz, PhD Researcher at the Faculty of Law of the University of Antwerp
Background
Bratislava was chosen by the Council to host the headquarters of the newly established European Labour Authority (ELA). Initially proposed by President Juncker in 2017, the ELA&amp;rsquo;s primary goal is to simplify and enhance the fairness of EU labor mobility within the internal market. This initiative stemmed from the European Pillar of Social Rights (EPSR) and was introduced alongside other measures aimed at promoting social fairness within the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quit this job and shove it: the updated EU legislation on non-EU migrant workers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
*Text updated Dec 22 2023, to add a link to the agreed text of the Directive, and April 12 2024, on its final adoption Photo credit: Lasse Fuss, via Wikimedia commons
While the recent agreement on asylum legislation has garnered significant attention, an equally important development occurred with the EU Member States and European Parliament reaching an agreement on amending the &amp;lsquo;single permit Directive,&amp;rsquo; a law governing non-EU migrant workers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Striving for fairness and adequacy: The proposal for minimum wages in the European Union.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 14:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Antwerp
Almost a year after promising an initiative on minimum wages, the European Commission presented its controversial proposal for a directive on this issue on October 28, 2020. This proposal has been met with criticism, particularly regarding the Commission&amp;rsquo;s authority on this matter, potential impacts on the autonomy of social partners and collective bargaining, and concerns about how this might affect the competitive advantage of member states with currently lower wages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/striving-for-fairness-and-adequacy-the-proposal-for-minimum-wages-in-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Explaining the European Court of Justice's decisions on headscarf bans in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 22:54:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued rulings on whether employers can prohibit employees from wearing headscarves at work. These rulings have garnered significant attention, although some of it stems from misunderstandings. This post aims to provide a clear explanation of the rulings.
Background
The EU has established laws against discrimination based on sex, nationality, race, disability, age, sexual orientation, and religion. While the ECJ has frequently addressed cases related to the first three grounds, the recent judgments in G4S v Achbita and Bougnaoui mark the first instance where the court has been asked to interpret workplace discrimination based on religious grounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/explaining-the-european-court-of-justice-s-decisions-on-headscarf-bans-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Close partners: The highest courts of member states and the enforcement of EU legislation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 11:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Two high courts in France and Spain recently issued significant rulings concerning how lawyers and domestic courts should apply EU law. Although dealing with distinct issues, both decisions are important for properly implementing EU law. As noted a few weeks prior, national high courts are becoming crucial in EU law, a trend the Court of Justice should encourage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/close-partners-the-highest-courts-of-member-states-and-the-enforcement-of-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protection for fixed-term workers against unfair dismissal and mistreatment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union (EU) has increasingly addressed the rise of non-standard employment through measures like agreements on part-time and fixed-term work, and a Directive on agency work. The fixed-term work rules, in particular, have spurred many legal cases in the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). However, until recently, the court had not fully considered the connection between these rules and national laws on unfair dismissal, particularly for university researchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protection-for-fixed-term-workers-against-unfair-dismissal-and-mistreatment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Referendum Briefing 6: The Impact on EU Employment and Equality Law Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers suggests that while some claim there would be a &amp;ldquo;bonfire of rights&amp;rdquo; if the UK left the EU, particularly in employment and equality, others argue that the EU has no bearing on these laws in the UK. This post will demonstrate that EU law has significantly improved employment and equality rights in the UK, especially for women in the workplace.
A study of all UK cases reaching the EU court concerning these issues reveals that 60% of cases involving equal treatment for women resulted in findings that UK law was inadequate, leading to improved workplace protections for women...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Returning from Austerity to Legitimacy: An Overview of the European Pillar of Social Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 08:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</guid><description>This piece explores how Juncker can use ‘The European Pillar of Social Rights’ to convey a strong message: that the EU champions dignity, autonomy, and social justice.
Claire Kilpatrick (EUI), Elise Muir (Veni Fellow, Maastricht) and Sacha Garben (College of Europe, Bruges)
The EU has faced skepticism from its citizens about its commitment to prosperity and better living and working conditions, especially since the financial crisis and the subsequent implementation of austerity measures in various countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-from-austerity-to-legitimacy-an-overview-of-the-european-pillar-of-social-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What approach should the CJEU take in addressing religious discrimination in the workplace?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer at the Faculty of Laws at UCL and the author of Religion and the Public Order of the European Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’Ordre juridique de l’Union Europeenne (Bruylant 2013).
Recent weeks have seen two opinions from Advocates General of the Court of Justice of the European Union concerning religious expression in the workplace. This follows a period where religious issues were largely absent from Luxembourg case law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Appeal ruling in Benkharbouche and Janah: State immunity, remedies, and rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Benkharbouche v Sudan and Janah v Libya delves into significant aspects of public international law, the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, highlighting their interplay within the current British constitutional framework. The cases involved employment law claims brought by two domestic workers against the Sudanese and Libyan embassies, respectively. The embassies invoked state immunity under a UK law based on a Council of Europe Convention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>