<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private Branch Exchange on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-branch-exchange/</link><description>Recent content in Private Branch Exchange on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-branch-exchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>End of the Premises Contact Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business telephone systems have evolved significantly. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from single-line phones to switchboards, automated systems, and sophisticated call center PBXs. However, one thing remained constant: these systems were all located on-site.
What’s Wrong With Premises Equipment?
Keeping everything in-house seems appealing because it gives you control over functionality, access, and services. You might even believe that in-house systems are more reliable than off-site solutions.
On-premises systems offer visibility and control.</description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls.</description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office.</description></item><item><title>Rise Of The Cloud Hosted PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</guid><description>Traditional, in-house PBX systems might be nearing obsolescence with the emergence of cloud-hosted solutions like AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s AirePBX. This innovation signifies a return to an older model where the service provider manages the switching system, but with modern technological advancements.
This shift back to provider-managed systems, reminiscent of early telephone networks, offers significant cost advantages due to increased competition and the use of existing network infrastructure for VoIP services. Businesses no longer need to invest in separate wiring or proprietary equipment, leading to more competitive offerings and feature-rich options.</description></item></channel></rss>