<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX Telephone Systems on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-telephone-systems/</link><description>Recent content in PBX Telephone Systems on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-telephone-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SIP Trunks vs ISDN PRI</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 21:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses have moved past analog phone lines, embracing PBX systems and ISDN PRI for their communication needs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new player in town: SIP Trunking. This technology offers potential cost and performance benefits for companies looking to enhance their voice services. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare SIP Trunks with ISDN PRI to understand the best choice for your organization.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that both technologies rely on digital telephony, eliminating analog transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-isdn-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Who Still Needs a T1?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</guid><description>Despite the buzz around copper and fiber Ethernet and advancements in cable broadband, the longstanding business connectivity solution, T1, receives little attention. This raises the question: Is T1 becoming obsolete or does it still hold relevance?
T1 remains prevalent. New installations persist, demonstrating its enduring popularity. Its longevity, coupled with declining prices comparable to Ethernet over Copper services, contributes to its continued relevance.
T1 is essential for businesses requiring dedicated professional-grade bandwidth, secure point-to-point connections, or reliable telephone trunking, particularly in remote locations with limited connectivity options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-still-needs-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Voice Goes Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world: companies are ditching their traditional PBX phone systems for cloud-based communication solutions like hosted PBX or hosted VoIP. This transition also incorporates mobile devices.
For example, Megapath&amp;rsquo;s Hosted Voice Mobile allows you to make and receive calls using a single number across multiple devices – desk phone, computer, and smartphone. Having one consistent number simplifies communication and avoids confusing clients with a business card full of numbers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reducing Call Center Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 23:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</guid><description>Running a call center, whether onshore or offshore, comes with inherent costs. While labor is a significant factor, telecommunications expenses shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be overlooked, especially with larger centers. These expenses can quickly escalate due to high call volumes and data usage.
Fortunately, there are ways to reduce these costs without compromising service quality. Many assume they already have the best deals on voice and data services, especially with high usage. However, this might not be the case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reducing-call-center-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>