<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content Delivery Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery-network/</link><description>Recent content in Content Delivery Network on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Need a Content Delivery Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The way we deliver content online is evolving rapidly. While you could once manage a website with just a computer and a few phone lines, today&amp;rsquo;s high-definition video and nationwide audiences demand far more resources. This is where content delivery networks (CDNs) come in.
Think of a CDN as a specialized web hosting service. Just as you can host your website on your own server or outsource it, you can also choose between managing your content distribution or relying on a CDN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest Evidence Of An Ethernet Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</guid><description>A powerful force is transforming the telecommunications industry, shifting it from traditional telegraphy and telephony to a digital packet-based system. This revolution, driven by Ethernet technology, is swiftly changing how our communication networks operate.
This shift towards Ethernet in metropolitan and long-distance networks highlights the dominance of digital networks, especially local area networks (LANs), in communication. While voice calls once dominated global traffic, data and video now reign supreme. Video, in particular, is driving the expansion of content delivery networks (CDNs) to handle high-definition content efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-evidence-of-an-ethernet-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You Can Afford a Content Delivery Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The internet is great for communication, allowing businesses to connect with anyone globally at a low cost and creating countless opportunities. However, this popularity has led to congestion, potentially slowing down websites.
You can work around this issue without sacrificing connectivity. Large content providers use Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) to bypass internet congestion. CDNs don&amp;rsquo;t connect directly to users but deliver content through servers near service providers, resulting in faster speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T Sees the Video Tsunami Coming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</guid><description>Video streaming is predicted to consume massive amounts of bandwidth, pushing the limits of what&amp;rsquo;s available. Even the concept of &amp;ldquo;unlimited&amp;rdquo; bandwidth offered by providers today comes with hidden caps due to network strain.
AT&amp;amp;T is one company actively addressing this challenge, not just by increasing general internet capacity but by adding 400 Gbps to its Content Delivery Network (CDN).
Think of a CDN as a dedicated express lane running parallel to the public internet highway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>