<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2002JTBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2002jtbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 2002JTBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2002jtbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Complete Functional Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-complete-functional-restoration/</guid><description>This document details the refurbishment process of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable with an AC motor. The unit was received from a customer in Oklahoma, and an initial evaluation was documented previously here.
Upon arrival, the unit was partially disassembled, revealing its internal components. One of the first tasks involved addressing a loose spring in the shut-off switch, which was successfully reinserted to restore functionality.
The restoration began with the carriage assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival From Oklahoma - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in good condition.
While the dust cover is intact, it does have some scratches and might need polishing or replacement. The turntable itself is in good shape, with only minor blemishes on the aluminum surfaces and minimal wear on the keypad. Using a soft cloth to operate the keypad or installing a remote control module would help preserve its condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item></channel></rss>