<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Industry on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/industry/</link><description>Recent content in Industry on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/industry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vertiv declares utilities as the most crucial industry globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 18:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/</guid><description>A new study from Vertiv, formerly Emerson Network Power, has found that utilities, including electricity, gas, nuclear power, and water treatment, are the world&amp;rsquo;s most critical industries.
Vertiv assembled a group of international experts in critical infrastructure to develop a system for quantifying and ranking the criticality of various industries based on 15 criteria. Public transportation, particularly rail and air travel, came in second place, followed by telecommunications, upstream oil and gas operations, and cloud and colocation services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vertiv-declares-utilities-as-the-most-crucial-industry-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates NBD observes improvement in Dubai's economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</guid><description>Source: Emirates NBD. Emirates NBD Dubai Economy Tracker Index: Sector
summary. Seasonally adjusted, 50 = no-change.
Data from April shows a continuing upswing in private sector output. Compared to March, all three major sub-sectors reported greater new business growth. Employment figures are increasing again, but at a slower rate than the survey average. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s private sector companies reported continued recovery and growth momentum since the survey&amp;rsquo;s record low in February...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-nbd-observes-improvement-in-dubai-s-economy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CIER Employment Index indicates a decrease in employment rates in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 15:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</guid><description>The Chinese job platform Zhaopin and the China Institute for Employment Research (CIER) at Renmin University have published their CIER Employment Index Report for July to September 2015.
The report&amp;rsquo;s index, which measures the ease of finding a job, rose consistently from 2011 to 2014. However, mirroring the economic slowdown, the job market has weakened, leading to a decline in the CIER Index for the past two quarters. The index dropped from its peak of 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cier-employment-index-indicates-a-decrease-in-employment-rates-in-china/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>