<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Top on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/top/</link><description>Recent content in Top on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:53:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The best beauty products chosen by Shopee Malaysia for the month of July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</guid><description>Shopee, a Southeast Asia-focused mobile marketplace designed for simple and secure online buying and selling, monitors top-selling items across various categories. Here are some of the best-selling beauty products on Shopee Malaysia during July:
Source: Shopee Malaysia portal. Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream.
Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream
According to its Shopee description, this cream is enriched with natural organic herbs to provide an immediate whitening effect that can last up to 12 hours.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV set top boxes will now include the Netflix app for seamless integration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 09:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-set-top-boxes-will-now-include-the-netflix-app-for-seamless-integration/</guid><description>Singtel is integrating the Netflix app into their TV set-top boxes. This means customers can easily access Netflix content directly on their TVs.
Subscribers with set-top boxes connected to Singtel Fibre Broadband can find Netflix on Channel 404 or by using the Quick Access Button on their remote. This feature will be rolled out gradually and should be available to all customers by the end of April.
Through an exclusive partnership, Singtel is offering customers up to nine free months of Netflix when they re-contract or sign up for eligible mobile, fiber broadband, and Singtel TV plans.</description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments.</description></item><item><title>Today is the day for the landrush of .global, .website, and .press domain names</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 18:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-the-day-for-the-landrush-of-global-website-and-press-domain-names/</guid><description>Starting August 27th, Singapore time, several top-level domain names will be up for grabs in a &amp;ldquo;landrush&amp;rdquo; phase, according to online brand specialist IP Mirror.
The &amp;ldquo;sunrise&amp;rdquo; phase, reserved for trademark holders to register their brands, precedes this period. During the landrush phase, anyone can secure remaining domain names at a premium price.
IP Mirror highlights &amp;ldquo;.global&amp;rdquo; as a particularly appealing option, signifying a broad international reach. This domain&amp;rsquo;s landrush phase lasts from August 27th to September 4th.</description></item><item><title>China has a strong presence in the new City Momentum Index by Jones Lang LaSalle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</guid><description>Five cities in Asia Pacific and the Middle East — Dubai, Wuhan, Shanghai, Hong Kong and Singapore — are among the top 10 in Jones Lang LaSalle&amp;rsquo;s new City Momentum Index (CMI). This index identifies cities worldwide with significant short-term socio-economic and commercial real estate momentum, as well as strong long-term growth potential.
Jeremy Kelly, Director of Global Research at Jones Lang LaSalle, explains that city momentum is not solely determined by GDP growth.</description></item><item><title>Booking.com has recognized Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments as a top performer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 06:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</guid><description>Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments, managed by Flora Hospitality Dubai, has received recognition for its exceptional performance based on guest feedback on Booking.com.
Source: Booking.com website. Flora Creek Delluxe Hotel Apartments receives an 8.6 rating from guest reviews.
This award acknowledges the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to outstanding hospitality. The overall scores reflect a blend of factors such as cleanliness, comfort, location, amenities, staff service, value, and the quality of complimentary Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>Three of the top 25 hotels in the world, as listed by TripAdvisor, are located in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</guid><description>TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Choice awards highlights 25 diverse hotels worldwide. Notably, three hotels from Asia secured spots within the top 10. Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s The Upper House claimed the second position, while India&amp;rsquo;s Oberoi Udaivilas and Oberoi Mumbai ranked fifth and ninth, respectively.
The Upper House, nestled in Pacific Place, holds the top spot among hotels in Hong Kong. One reviewer praised it as their &amp;ldquo;best hotel experience,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing its flawlessness. A remarkable 97% of the reviews for this hotel are positive.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's Influential Brands are identified by Gen X</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Leading Brands Chosen by Generation X
A consumer-driven award program spearheaded by Brand Alliance has identified the top Influential Brands in Singapore, as determined by the upwardly mobile Generation X (Gen X) demographic.
Source: Brand Alliance. Brand Alliance presented the 2013 Influential Brands awards in November 2013. The 2014 Influential Brands conference is scheduled for November 10, 2014.
The survey highlighted over 100 prominent brands resonating with consumers in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>