<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MAN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/man/</link><description>Recent content in MAN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/man/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Services over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:35:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-services-over-copper/</guid><description>Connecting networks logically often involves Ethernet, a technology that has recently expanded its reach beyond local boundaries. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) connections are increasing in availability and often come at a lower cost compared to other options.
EoC enables standard Ethernet services to be delivered through existing copper telephone wiring. Unlike typical Cat 5E or Cat 6 wiring, EoC is compatible with older copper infrastructure not initially intended for Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>What Makes a Great MAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-a-great-man/</guid><description>Access to Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs), previously limited to large corporations, is now feasible for small and medium-sized businesses. If your company requires communication between multiple locations within a city, a metro network might be beneficial.
Metro Ethernet is the modern solution for data connections in major cities and surrounding areas. There are two main types: E-Line and E-LAN. E-Line provides a direct Ethernet connection between two points, such as a business and its data center, warehouse, factory, or branch office.</description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards.</description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority.</description></item><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service.</description></item><item><title>Fast Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 02:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>100 Mbps Ethernet, also known as Fast Ethernet, has been a networking standard for a long time. Most network devices today come equipped with Network Interface Cards (NICs) that support 10/100 Mbps or 10/100/1000 Mbps speeds. While 100 Mbps is sufficient for smaller networks, larger organizations often opt for Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet (10 GigE) at 10,000 Mbps for high-performance needs. However, connecting to metropolitan or long-distance networks often results in significantly slower speeds.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals.</description></item><item><title>MAN and MEN - Metropolitan Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-and-men-metropolitan-networking/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are the solution for expanding local networks across different locations within a city. Unlike confined on-site wiring, MANs tackle the challenge of connecting across larger distances.
Traditionally, businesses leased dedicated lines like T1 or DS3 from telecom companies to link their offices. However, this method proved costly and demanded self-management. MANs offer a practical alternative by providing shared fiber optic infrastructure, leading to cost savings and scalability for businesses.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Networks Interconnect in Arizona</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-networks-interconnect-in-arizona/</guid><description>Ethernet is quickly gaining popularity as the preferred protocol for metropolitan and wide area networks. It&amp;rsquo;s predicted that IP networks using standard Ethernet services will eventually replace the outdated Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). The main obstacle to this is the fragmented nature of Ethernet service providers, comprising a mix of established and newer carriers with limited service areas. However, E-NNI technology is emerging as the solution to connect these disparate networks.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used.</description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN is the New SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-is-the-new-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Throughout the last century, high-speed communication lines have transitioned from analog copper lines to digital copper lines and finally to digital fiber optic lines. The technology driving fiber optics has also advanced from time-sliced synchronous multiplexing to packet-based protocols, reflecting the shift towards network-based computing in almost every industry. While older SONET telco lines remain functional, upgrading to Ethernet WAN, the latest fiber optic technology, offers significant advantages.</description></item><item><title>MAN Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 12:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/man-up/</guid><description>Is your network letting you down and slowing down productivity? Are there too many users trying to access data through your WAN interface, causing a bottleneck? Are you tired of facing complaints about the slow network? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your network!
Your old frame relay or T1 connection might have been sufficient when data transfer was minimal, but it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough for today&amp;rsquo;s demands. The volume of data flowing between customers, vendors, and other locations has overwhelmed these outdated connections.</description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Wavelength Services for San Francisco and Silicon Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-wavelength-services-for-san-francisco-and-silicon-valley/</guid><description>AboveNet is expanding its high-capacity fiber optic network services by offering new low-latency wavelength services. These services will be available in the San Francisco Bay Area and Silicon Valley, including key locations like Santa Clara and San Jose, California.
AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave solutions utilize ROADM (Reconfigurable Optical Add/Drop Multiplexer) technology, enabling dynamic wavelength add/drops for various protocols such as Ethernet, TDM, storage, and video transport. This results in flexible service options, scalability, and fast provisioning.</description></item><item><title>Biotherm Homme releases kite surfing video in collaboration with The Dose skincare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 04:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
Biotherm Homme, a high-end men&amp;rsquo;s skincare brand, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; a product line designed to address the daily needs of men across four areas: feeling refreshed, energized, youthful, and charismatic.
To showcase &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; Biotherm Homme has also created an immersive 360° video featuring Youri Zoon, a world champion kitesurfer, as he executes awe-inspiring stunts. Want to learn more? Experience it firsthand.</description></item><item><title>WAN Computer Network Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 15:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-computer-network-connections/</guid><description>Computer networks are commonly grouped into LANs, MANs, and WANs. Your local network, or LAN, is designed and maintained according to your needs, either by you or a hired professional. Connecting your LAN to another one across a city or globally requires MAN or WAN services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for metro and long-distance connections.
The main distinction between MANs and WANs lies in their scale. MANs, or Metropolitan Area Networks, serve a specific city and its surrounding areas, making them suitable for businesses with multiple offices within the same city, a primary site and a remote data center, or a factory and satellite offices.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH.</description></item><item><title>600 Mbps Ethernet vs OC12 SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</guid><description>Companies that need bandwidth in the fractional Gigabit range have often relied on OC12 SONET fiber optic service. While it remains a solid high-speed choice, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering 600 Mbps Ethernet as well. Comparing these two options might yield some surprising results.
OC-12 (622 Mbps) is the next tier up from OC-3 (155 Mbps) in the SONET optical carrier hierarchy. This service is widely available in Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and as a dedicated internet access connection for mid-sized internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks.</description></item><item><title>How To Find Better Metro E Service Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 06:51:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-better-metro-e-service-prices/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) services are widely available and offer a practical solution for businesses operating within a metropolitan area to connect their various locations. However, securing the most cost-effective Metro E services requires careful consideration.
Metro Ethernet is a type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) designed to meet the local connectivity needs of businesses. Unlike traditional wide-area networks, MANs focus on providing high-speed connections within a specific city or region.</description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet WAN to Complement Your LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:25:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-wan-to-complement-your-lan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your company&amp;rsquo;s Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at blazing speeds of 1 Gbps or more, making internal network operations seem almost instantaneous. However, accessing resources outside your physical location can feel painstakingly slow. Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be convenient if your LAN could extend across cities or even to remote offices? You might be surprised to learn that this is a possibility.
Yes, The WAN is Ethernet Networks can be broadly categorized as either owned or leased.</description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology.</description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services.</description></item><item><title>Fractional and Full Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 21:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-and-full-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern applications require increasingly high bandwidth. A 10 Mbps connection, considered entry-level, is often insufficient for businesses. Many need at least 100 Mbps WAN bandwidth to support real-time applications like VoIP and video conferencing, as well as latency-sensitive cloud connections. This ensures optimal performance even during peak usage. Larger businesses and those with technology-heavy needs might even require Gigabit connections, which are now readily available and more affordable than in the past.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item></channel></rss>