<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Discovery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discovery/</link><description>Recent content in Discovery on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:54:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discovery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Global Day of Discovery at Renaissance Hotels worldwide is celebrated on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Renaissance Hotels is hosting its third annual Global Day of Discovery on June 26th at over 150 locations. On this day, almost every hotel will offer guests and community members the opportunity to explore something new. These events, designed by hotel Navigators, include musical performances, culinary experiences, art displays, cultural activities, and unique local excursions.
This day marks the start of the Renaissance Hotels&amp;rsquo; Summer of Discovery calendar, a summer-long series of exclusive events at all 157 hotels worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia will be able to watch a Hong Kong food series on Discovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</guid><description>Discovery Channel has released a new show, Kung Food! Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Grandmasters of Cuisine. This show delves into the intricate and special world of Hong Kong cuisine from the viewpoint of Michelin-starred chefs.
Source: Discovery Channel. Chef Chaneton of Mono at a market in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong dominates Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2021 list with 11 restaurants featured. Chefs David Lai, Guillaume Galliot, Hideaki Sato, Ricardo Chaneton, Richard Ekkebus and Vicky Cheng, all recognized by Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, were chosen to discuss their passion for Hong Kong and illustrate how they craft their culinary masterpieces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>