<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Competitive Carriers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competitive-carriers/</link><description>Recent content in Competitive Carriers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competitive-carriers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses.</description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple.</description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Corporate Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</guid><description>For medium to large businesses, a 100 Mbps connection speed is becoming the new norm. While this might seem excessive and expensive, it&amp;rsquo;s actually neither. In essence, Fast Ethernet is taking over the role of DS3.
A decade ago, a 1.5 Mbps T1 line was considered high bandwidth. Today&amp;rsquo;s need for 100 Mbps reflects the significant evolution of application requirements. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from basic video conferencing to high-definition, two-way video and telepresence.</description></item><item><title>EoC and EoTDM Complement Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:35:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-and-eotdm-complement-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a significant disparity in bandwidth offered by traditional telecom services, particularly between smaller businesses and large corporations. Smaller businesses often rely on slower T1 lines (1.5 Mbps), while larger corporations enjoy significantly faster speeds (100-1000 times faster) through fiber optic connections.
However, technologies like Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and Ethernet over TDM (EoTDM) are bridging this gap by enabling a broader range of bandwidths on existing copper infrastructure. This allows for a smoother transition between T1 speeds and gigabit or even higher speeds.</description></item><item><title>3 Mbps T1 vs EoC Throwdown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 03:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-t1-vs-eoc-throwdown/</guid><description>A significant battle is occurring in the telecommunications market between traditional T1 lines and the newer Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services. Both technologies aim to provide businesses with increased bandwidth at lower costs, catering to the growing reliance on internet connectivity, remote data center access, and cloud-based services.
The core of this competition lies in how these technologies utilize existing copper telephone wiring to deliver data services. While T1 lines have long been the standard, EoC presents a compelling alternative with potentially higher bandwidth at competitive prices.</description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Steal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-steal/</guid><description>Everyone appreciates a bargain, especially for telecommunications services. The current prices for Ethernet might even make you wonder if they&amp;rsquo;re legitimate. To see just how competitive these prices are, take a moment to compare Ethernet costs for your business locations.
The reason Ethernet services are so affordable now is due to rapid technological advancements. Until recently, traditional telephone company services were the only option. Today, competition has introduced alternatives that have completely changed the landscape.</description></item><item><title>T1 Bonding Buys Breathing Room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</guid><description>Businesses often face the challenge of needing more resources, like network bandwidth, without the budget to acquire them. This is particularly true for WAN bandwidth. Companies often start with a modest plan, assuming they can upgrade when demand (and revenue) increase. However, in times of economic uncertainty, business activity might grow while revenue lags. So how can businesses meet their needs without overspending?
One solution is incrementalism, specifically &amp;ldquo;just in time&amp;rdquo; incrementalism.</description></item></channel></rss>