<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Traffic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-traffic/</link><description>Recent content in Network Traffic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-traffic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>Qwest Brings 100 Gbps to Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-brings-100-gbps-to-your-business/</guid><description>Qwest is increasing its long haul network bandwidth from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. The implementation of this upgrade is underway and will continue throughout the following year.
What implications does this have for your company? Qwest provided examples of the speed of 100 Gbps point-to-point network traffic. Imagine downloading 138 DVDs (4.7 Gigabytes each) in just 60 seconds. A 2-hour HD movie or presentation could be transferred in a mere 9 seconds.</description></item><item><title>The Multiple Data Center Dilemma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</guid><description>The increasing number of mergers and acquisitions has left many companies with a surplus of data centers. Instead of choosing one data center to become the central hub, companies should consider the unique characteristics of each facility, such as equipment, applications, and staffing. Furthermore, consolidating data centers necessitates a reassessment of connectivity.
While internal network traffic often surpasses external traffic, the rising reliance on cloud services demands greater Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance.</description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining.</description></item></channel></rss>