<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Charity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/charity/</link><description>Recent content in Charity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:13:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/charity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Kissing Hand For The Sandy Hook Elementary Students</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 20:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/</guid><description>A children&amp;rsquo;s book about a raccoon hesitant to start school offers a heartwarming solution for children struggling with the idea of returning to the classroom.
The recent tragedy at Sandy Hook Elementary School in Newtown, Connecticut, has left many young students grappling with trauma and fear. The horrific event, where students and educators lost their lives, has created a sense of anxiety about returning to school for the spring semester. Finding a way to comfort these children and help them cope with their fears is a significant challenge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-kissing-hand-for-the-sandy-hook-elementary-students/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Last Minute Online Gifts For Good</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 09:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</guid><description>_On Christmas Eve, instead of the typical peaceful house,
your home is filled with stress as you realize you forgot a gift.
Despite your best efforts, you overlooked someone on your list.
The pressure is on to find a solution quickly.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that can save your holiday!
Search online and find the K.I.N.D site for the perfect gift.
You&amp;rsquo;ll not only deliver a thoughtful present but also make a difference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-minute-online-gifts-for-good/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Someline Apple Tree app will produce apples for charity as long as you refrain from using your phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 19:20:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</guid><description>Source: Google Play.
Libern Lin, a student entrepreneur attending Republic Polytechnic in Singapore, has expanded his app, Someline Apple Tree, with financial support from the Singapore Computer Society (SCS).
The app incentivizes real-life interactions by rewarding users with digital apples for reducing phone usage. Lin, the app&amp;rsquo;s creator, explained that they wanted to use the app&amp;rsquo;s concept for a good cause. So, they used the S$30,000 grant from SCS to add a charitable component to the app in line with IDA&amp;rsquo;s Code for Charity*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-someline-apple-tree-app-will-produce-apples-for-charity-as-long-as-you-refrain-from-using-your-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is extending its Change for Good program to additional flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Hainan Airlines flight attendants distributing Change for Good donation bags to passengers.
Hainan Airlines is significantly expanding its successful in-flight donation program, Change for Good, to include 16 more routes. The program, which supports UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s initiatives for children, was initially introduced in September 2013 on the Beijing-Haikou route.
As the first mainland China-based airline to partner with UNICEF&amp;rsquo;s Change for Good alliance, Hainan Airlines aims to raise a minimum of RMB 10 million over five years, starting from September 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-extending-its-change-for-good-program-to-additional-flights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bare Your Sole 2016 barefoot walkathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 14:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</guid><description>Source: Habitat for Humanity Singapore.
&amp;ldquo;Bare Your Sole,&amp;rdquo; the annual barefoot walkathon organized by Habitat for Humanity Singapore, returns to raise funds and awareness for those in need within Singapore. Now in its tenth year, the event will be held at OCBC Square on September 10th at 7:30 am.
The 2.5km and 5km charity walkathon will benefit Project HomeWorks, a local initiative dedicated to improving the living situations of the elderly, ill, and disabled individuals facing challenging conditions across Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bare-your-sole-2016-barefoot-walkathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-this-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CruCycle brings a fresh perspective to the fitness scene in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</guid><description>Krewfit recently introduced CruCycle, a new spin studio concept in Singapore, to fitness and fun enthusiasts. The studio&amp;rsquo;s classes operate on the principle of &amp;ldquo;Riding with the Pack,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing group workouts, teamwork, and camaraderie. This makes CruCycle&amp;rsquo;s workouts perfect for corporate team-building events.
Source: Crucycle.
The Ding siblings – Valerie, Calvin, and Beatrice – founded, own, and operate CruCycle. The inspiration for the studio came from their upbringing in Los Angeles, California...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crucycle-brings-a-fresh-perspective-to-the-fitness-scene-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beautiful.me is inviting shoppers in Singapore to donate rice to those in need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</guid><description>Source: Beautiful.me. Beautiful.me partners with Community Chest. From left: Elise Wong, CRM Executive, Beautiful.me; Mae Kng, Senior Associate Director, Community Chest; Olive Tai, MD, Beautiful.me; Wileen Chen, Manager of Relations &amp;amp; Engagement, Community Chest.
Beautiful.me, in partnership with rice importer and distributor Hak Yong Company and the Singapore Community Chest, has initiated the Giving Is Beautiful campaign. This project encourages Singapore&amp;rsquo;s online shoppers to contribute funds to provide rice to those in need...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Registration is now open for the Bare Your Sole walkathon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</guid><description>Source: Habitat for Humanity.
Habitat for Humanity Singapore&amp;rsquo;s yearly walkathon, Bare Your Sole, is back for its seventh year on May 30th.
This event unites individuals from all backgrounds to highlight the challenges faced by those living in poverty who lack access to basic necessities like shelter and shoes.
The funds gathered from the 2km and 4km barefoot walkathon will support Habitat for Humanity Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Project HomeWorks program. This local initiative focuses on enhancing the living situations of seniors, individuals with illnesses, and those with physical disabilities residing in one-room apartments in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-is-now-open-for-the-bare-your-sole-walkathon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Barter and location-based services contribute to Jualo's success in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Chaim Fetter, a Dutch programming prodigy and entrepreneur, has balanced building businesses with a spirit of exploration and philanthropy. As a teenager, he created his first online venture, developing e-commerce websites. He spent his twenties traveling in Southeast Asia before establishing the Peduli Anak Foundation in 2005 to support former street children in Lombok, Indonesia.
Source: Jualo website.
Last year, Fetter transitioned the foundation&amp;rsquo;s leadership to a local team, relocating to Jakarta to pursue a new business venture, Jualo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson hosts its first charity event of the year-end</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 16:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</guid><description>Source: Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson. The poolside.
Ibis Styles Singapore on MacPherson will host its first charity event with the Friends of The Disabled Society (FDS) as part of their year-end festivities.
The public can purchase various handicrafts and accessories on November 17, 2016, at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s lounge area and poolside. All proceeds will go to FDS. The hotel will also host a dinner for FDS on December 3, 2016, as part of the holiday celebrations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-styles-singapore-on-macpherson-hosts-its-first-charity-event-of-the-year-end/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>