<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lampedusa on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lampedusa/</link><description>Recent content in Lampedusa on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lampedusa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>How can the EU address migrant fatalities in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>The recent tragedies in the Mediterranean Sea have added to the already significant number of migrant deaths. EU officials are responding to this urgent issue, and this is what their response should include.
First, a large-scale search and rescue operation is needed. The EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Triton&amp;rsquo; operation, which replaced the Italian &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum,&amp;rsquo; is insufficient for saving lives. It was incorrectly assumed that ending &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum&amp;rsquo; would deter migrants and reduce deaths.</description></item></channel></rss>