<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Framework Decisions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/framework-decisions/</link><description>Recent content in Framework Decisions on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/framework-decisions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How committed are Member States to safeguarding fundamental rights through the EU's common rules on detention?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-committed-are-member-states-to-safeguarding-fundamental-rights-through-the-eu-s-common-rules-on-detention/</guid><description>By Debbie Sayers, Legal Research Consultant, http://interalia.org.uk
In early February 2014, the Commission released a concerning report regarding &amp;ldquo;common rules on detention.&amp;rdquo; The report revealed that a mere 18 out of 28 EU member states had implemented any of the intended instruments. This study was purely quantitative and did not assess the effectiveness of the rules or their impact on individuals.
The inadequate implementation of these fundamental commitments to enhance detainee rights is worrisome.</description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state.</description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro.</description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework.</description></item><item><title>What's all the fuss about the draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</guid><description>Cian C. Murphy, The Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London
The transnational public sphere continues to be gradually suppressed. The European Union&amp;rsquo;s initial legislative response to recent killings by Islamic State militants in Europe and elsewhere is a draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism, which was published last month. The Directive, which seeks to expand the scope of EU law in national criminal law regarding terrorism, will replace the Framework Decision on Combating Terrorism, which was initially approved in 2002 and revised in 2008.</description></item></channel></rss>