<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Flynas on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flynas/</link><description>Recent content in Flynas on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/flynas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas has teamed up with Pegasus Airlines to provide flights from Saudi Arabia to Turkey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</guid><description>Source: flynas. Aerial view of Turkey.
The Saudi Arabian airline flynas has partnered with Turkish budget airline Pegasus Airlines to expand its flight offerings in Turkey. This collaboration will initially allow flynas passengers to travel to five new Turkish destinations: Antalya, Ankara, Adana, Hatay, and Trabzon. This will be achieved by utilizing Pegasus Airlines&amp;rsquo; extensive network of domestic flights operating from Istanbul&amp;rsquo;s Sabiha Gökçen International Airport.
Bander Al Mohanna, Group CEO of NAS Holding, stated that Pegasus Airlines is a leading Turkish airline with over two decades of experience in innovation within the country&amp;rsquo;s aviation industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>