<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Discount on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discount/</link><description>Recent content in Discount on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discount/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New website offers discounted gym classes in Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</guid><description>Source:
FILLMYCLASS.
Similar to discounts for last-minute travel bookings, you can find more affordable gym classes at the last minute too.
A new website called FILLMYCLASS has launched in Melbourne, Australia. This website connects fitness enthusiasts with open spots in fitness classes at gyms and studios nearby.
FILLMYCLASS founder Daniel Waide states, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about flexibility. The aim is to encourage more people to be active. Offering the ability to select classes that fit their schedule at any gym or studio increases the likelihood of people becoming and staying active...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to GfK, Singaporean travelers frequently plan their trips with less than a month's notice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</guid><description>A Jetstar aircraft at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Companies can potentially reduce travel expenses by adopting strategies used by individual travelers. A study by GfK revealed that roughly 76% of trips originating in Singapore were booked no more than one month before the travel date.
Laurens van den Oever, Global Travel Director at GfK, suggests that this trend of booking close to the travel date is likely due to airlines offering discounted fares for last-minute flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-gfk-singaporean-travelers-frequently-plan-their-trips-with-less-than-a-month-s-notice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee reveals birthday flash sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</guid><description>Shopee, a prominent mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is marking its first anniversary. To commemorate the occasion, they are holding hourly flash sales with discounts of up to 70% on December 12, 2016.
Two products will be discounted every hour on December 12th, from 12 pm to 7 pm.
Along with the hourly flash sales on December 12th, Shopee is running a lucky draw for users who take advantage of daily category vouchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DEAL.com.sg is celebrating its upcoming birthday by giving away S$5 million to customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 15:39:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</guid><description>The flash sale website, DEAL.com.sg, is thanking its loyal customers by offering them millions of dollars in discounts. This initiative, launched after the company&amp;rsquo;s start in May 2010, also aims to draw in new customers.
Patrick Linden, the CEO of DEAL.com.sg&amp;rsquo;s parent company, iBuy Group, expressed his gratitude, stating that the company is giving back $5 million to thank customers for their support over the past three and a half years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deal-com-sg-is-celebrating-its-upcoming-birthday-by-giving-away-s-5-million-to-customers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>