<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ham Radio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ham-radio/</link><description>Recent content in Ham Radio on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ham-radio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process.</description></item><item><title>Use Your Technical Savvy To Save Elephants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-your-technical-savvy-to-save-elephants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 23:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-your-technical-savvy-to-save-elephants/</guid><description>The African forest elephant, a critically endangered species, faces imminent extinction due to illegal poaching. Their value extends beyond ivory, making their preservation crucial for both nature and humanity.
While conservation efforts are crucial, you possess valuable skills that can contribute to their survival: technological expertise and innovative thinking.
The challenge lies in locating and monitoring the remaining elephants, a task made difficult by their dwindling numbers and remote habitat within dense forests.</description></item></channel></rss>