<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bent on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bent/</link><description>Recent content in Bent on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Brand New Hood Fatally Damaged Due to Bent Hood Hinges! - Straightening Hinges Out and Installation of Another Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-brand-new-hood-fatally-damaged-due-to-bent-hood-hinges-straightening-hinges-out-and-installation-of-another-hood/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) for a Florida-based client and installed a new dust cover purchased from beoparts-shop in Denmark. These dust covers are remarkable replicas, made with the same die-cast process as the originals, resulting in a seamless finish.
However, a problem arose with this particular dust cover. When closing it, there was slight friction on the hinge approximately halfway through its movement. While I initially dismissed it as an insignificant tolerance issue common in older manufacturing, the issue escalated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Carriage Position Switches and Fixing a Bent Output Switch Contact Tab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000, a process known as &amp;ldquo;switch day&amp;rdquo; involves cleaning the contacts of the many open switches. While some recommend desoldering the switches for thorough cleaning, it&amp;rsquo;s generally sufficient to clean the contact areas directly. This minimizes the risk of damaging the delicate contact tabs.
Effective switch functionality hinges on clean contact points, not the overall appearance of the switch. The contact tabs should be straight and have adequate spring to ensure proper contact.</description></item></channel></rss>