<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Natural on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/natural/</link><description>Recent content in Natural on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/natural/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves.</description></item><item><title>Dabur Herb'l Sensitive Toothpaste is designed to combat tooth demineralization in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Dabur International.
Dabur International has introduced its new Herb’l Sensitive Toothpaste to the Middle East market. This toothpaste uses natural ingredients, including cinnamon, mint, licorice root, and potassium ions to quickly and effectively alleviate tooth sensitivity.
The company states that using this toothpaste twice daily will not only reduce sensitivity but also lead to healthier gums. It does this by preventing plaque buildup, gum inflammation, and cavities, all while freshening breath.</description></item><item><title>Cachet Hotel Group unveils the fresh appearance of URBN Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</guid><description>The Cachet Hotel Group (CHG) has revamped its stylish URBN Hotel in Shanghai, a former warehouse. Led by CHG&amp;rsquo;s renowned fashion designer, Jay Godfrey, the updated interiors offer guests a modern, zen-like ambiance. The use of recycled and reclaimed wood materials adds a natural touch, further enhanced by the neutral color scheme.
Source: CHG. The Jay Godfrey Courtyard Suite.
Photo - http://photos.prnasia.com/prnh/20140911/0861406560
The URBN Shanghai boasts a unique Jay Godfrey-designed suite.</description></item></channel></rss>