<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carriers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carriers/</link><description>Recent content in Carriers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carriers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting in Clouds and Colos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 22:22:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</guid><description>There are many hosting choices available. Shared hosting is popular among individuals and small businesses due to its affordability and acceptable performance. However, as your needs grow, you face a decision: self-hosting or a managed solution.
While setting up a website previously required technical expertise in server management, Linux and Windows hosting have become increasingly user-friendly and widely accessible. Even large enterprises accustomed to managing their servers in-house are reconsidering colocation and cloud solutions, driven by cost and resource optimization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-in-clouds-and-colos/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>