<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Group on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/group/</link><description>Recent content in Group on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:05:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Madison Group introduces the Venini and Rimadesio collection to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 20:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</guid><description>The Madison Group, headquartered in Hong Kong, has expanded its Southeast Asian presence by introducing two Italian interior design brands to Singapore: Venini and Rimadesio.
Source: The Madison Group.
Rimadesio products.
Venini is renowned for its handcrafted Venetian mouth-blown glassware, while Rimadesio specializes in glass and aluminum furniture and accessories. The Madison Group holds exclusive distribution rights for both brands in Singapore. There are also plans to offer Venini glassware at select locations and retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-madison-group-introduces-the-venini-and-rimadesio-collection-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Pottinger Hong Kong is now open for business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 19:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</guid><description>Sino Group, a hospitality branch of Sino Land Company, manages various properties including hotels, a yacht club, serviced apartments, and residential dining establishments. They have recently introduced The Pottinger Hong Kong, a luxurious 68-room boutique hotel. Situated on Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s oldest paved street, the hotel holds a notable position on a site recognized as a Grade I historic place by the Antiquities Advisory Board of Hong Kong.
As per the Sino Group of Hotels, The Pottinger Hong Kong features 68 upscale guestrooms and suites, with sizes varying from 23 to 68 square meters...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pottinger-hong-kong-is-now-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Special discounts are available for group bookings for iftar and suhoor at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp; Hotel in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 11:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Source: Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is offering special group rates for iftar and suhoor.
The iftar buffet, which includes Ramadan juices, is priced at AED 180*, with a discounted rate of AED 170 per person for groups of 10 or more. Using the coupon system**, the price drops to AED 150 per person. The suhoor buffet, also with Ramadan juices, costs AED 90 per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-discounts-are-available-for-group-bookings-for-iftar-and-suhoor-at-the-armed-forces-officers-club-hotel-in-abu-dhabi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AFOCH invites businesses to gather for iftar during Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: AFOCH website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is hosting Iftar celebrations ideal for gatherings with business associates.
Peter Freeman, the Deputy Director General of the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, highlighted that the hotel&amp;rsquo;s leading chefs will once again prepare a grand Iftar buffet. The buffet will feature exquisite Arabic delicacies alongside international dishes.
&amp;ldquo;Here at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, we provide the most authentic Arabic cuisine, meticulously crafted with the freshest ingredients by our highly skilled culinary team,&amp;rdquo; Freeman stated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jebsen Group marks six decades of collaboration with Porsche by celebrating their 60th anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</guid><description>Source: Jebsen Group. Pictured from left: Grant Smith, General Manager of Porsche Centre Hong Kong and Macau; Franz Jung, President and CEO of Porsche China; Hans Joachim Stuck, two-time winner of the 24 Hours of Le Mans; Hans Michael Jebsen, Chairman of Jebsen Group; Helmuth Hennig, Group Managing Director of Jebsen Group; Earl Anderson Bamber, 2015 champion of the 24 Hours of Le Mans; and Joachim Eberlein, Managing Director of Jebsen Motors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>