<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Production on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/production/</link><description>Recent content in Production on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advanced Manufacturing Driving Faster WANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 09:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advanced-manufacturing-driving-faster-wans/</guid><description>The recent &amp;ldquo;Great Recession&amp;rdquo; stands out not just for its severity, but also for the uneven recovery that followed. While businesses have bounced back, job growth has lagged. This unusual trend has been attributed to unexpected gains in productivity, where output increases without a proportional rise in employment. But is this sustainable or merely a blip in the current economic climate?
The saying &amp;ldquo;everything old is new again&amp;rdquo; rings true. While new applications and technologies emerge, they often echo past advancements driven by innovation.</description></item><item><title>AdAsia Holdings introduces new video production services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</guid><description>Source: AdAsia website. Drones can give bird&amp;rsquo;s eye views of scenes.
AdAsia Holdings, an advertising company, has introduced AdAsia Video Production, a new service within its AdAsia Digital Platform that caters to video and animation production needs.
Clients can utilize this service for a range of video formats, from traditional productions to drone footage, 360-degree videos, and animations. Video quality options span from 140p to 2,160p. The produced materials can be featured on the AdAsia Video Network as well as other distribution channels.</description></item></channel></rss>