<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backhaul Upgrades For Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>A curious thing occurred on the path to widespread mobile broadband: we hit a bandwidth bottleneck. While the focus was on wireless channels as the potential constraint, it&amp;rsquo;s the insufficient backhaul capacity that&amp;rsquo;s now jeopardizing the expansion of wireless services. Fortunately, this issue is being acknowledged and addressed.
But what exactly is backhaul, and how does it impede mobile services? Backhaul, in its current usage, refers to the connection linking a wireless tower site back to the provider&amp;rsquo;s central office or mobile switching center...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-upgrades-for-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part V</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</guid><description>While wireless technology is a hot topic, the wired world is also seeing significant advancements. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the future of copper and fiber optic services over the next decade.
Fiber optic networks are rapidly expanding, driven in part by the American Reinvestment and Recovery Act&amp;rsquo;s $7.2 billion investment in nationwide broadband access. This initiative particularly targets underserved rural areas, enabling competitive carriers to expand their networks by leveraging funds allocated for middle-mile fiber optic cable installations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-v/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Is Making Obsolescence Obsolete</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</guid><description>Keeping up with technology is a constant struggle, similar to swimming against a strong current. Any pause or delay can cause you to fall behind competitors who are advancing rapidly.
Technology is constantly evolving, becoming outdated quickly. The longer you rely on existing technology, the more outdated it gets, eventually lacking support or functionality. While the physical hardware may remain functional, it struggles to utilize the latest resources and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>