<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shoe on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shoe/</link><description>Recent content in Shoe on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shoe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Adidas Originals is reintroducing the Superstar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</guid><description>Source: adidas.
This year, adidas Originals launches a campaign exploring the meaning of being a superstar, coinciding with the anniversary of the iconic Superstar shoe, first released in 1969.
A short film by adidas Originals, directed by Karim Huu Do, examines what it means to be a superstar in 2015. Footballer David Beckham states, &amp;ldquo;It’s not about trying to be the next big thing.&amp;rdquo; Entertainer Pharrell Williams believes &amp;ldquo;It’s not about the number of views, likes or shares...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-is-reintroducing-the-superstar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces its lightest-ever cushioning shoe for runners</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The DynaFlyte.
ASICS has released its lightest cushioned running shoe to date. The DynaFlyte combines lightness and cushioning with a full-length FlyteFoam midsole, utilizing the company&amp;rsquo;s patented midsole technology in its most basic form. According to ASICS, the shoe&amp;rsquo;s reduced weight minimizes energy loss during the stride, resulting in more efficient running and the potential for increased speed at any distance.
Balancing efficient cushioning with minimizing weight is a significant challenge in running shoe design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-its-lightest-ever-cushioning-shoe-for-runners/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces the Superstar 80s Pioneers Pack in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 06:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: adidas. Drawing on Superstar 80s by Gonz.
Adidas recently released the Superstar 80s Pioneers Pack, a collaboration with skateboarder Mark Gonzales, known as Gonz, and designer NIGO.
Gonz, a renowned innovator and rule-breaker, changed skateboarding for a whole generation. His drive to create inspired the Superstar 80s by Gonz. The shoe&amp;rsquo;s all-white leather upper serves as a blank slate, inviting wearers to personalize their sneakers using the included markers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-the-superstar-80s-pioneers-pack-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The YEEZY BOOST 350 will be released on August 22nd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</guid><description>On August 22, 2015, Kanye West and adidas Originals will launch a new all-black version of the YEEZY BOOST 350 sneaker in select stores worldwide. This release follows the successful June launch of the white YEEZY BOOST 350.
This is the third shoe model designed collaboratively by West and adidas. The low-top YEEZY BOOST 350 in black features a one-color upper made from adidas Primeknit, a material engineered to feel like a second skin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-yeezy-boost-350-will-be-released-on-august-22nd/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adidas introduces new Stan Smith designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:03:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</guid><description>This summer, the Stan Smith shoe gets a bold update with the Wrapped Animal Pack. Available in three color combinations, the pack keeps the Stan Smith&amp;rsquo;s famous shape while incorporating textured snake, alligator, and crocodile leather around the outsole.
Source: adidas.
Complementary heel tab accents in green, red, and black add a fashionable touch to this classic preppy sneaker. The Adidas Originals Stan Smith, originally a tennis shoe, has become a timeless classic thanks to its all-leather design and simple aesthetic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-introduces-new-stan-smith-designs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The last adidas Originals = PHARRELL WILLIAMS collection of 2014 will be released on November 28th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 08:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</guid><description>The last adidas Originals and Pharrell Williams collaboration of 2014 features a playful use of polka dots. More releases are planned for 2015. The bold and cheerful polka dot motif symbolizes energy and happiness.
Source: adidas Originals. The Polka Dot Pack includes Stan Smith sneakers.
Launching in Southeast Asia on November 28th, the Polka Dot Pack features leather Stan Smith sneakers. This collection embodies the profound joy of love. The youthful and optimistic designs aim for a relatable and authentic feel, representing the collaboration&amp;rsquo;s core value...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-last-adidas-originals-pharrell-williams-collection-of-2014-will-be-released-on-november-28th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASICS introduces the versatile fuzeX TR, an all-in-one fitness solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 08:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</guid><description>Source: ASICS. The fuzeX TR training shoe.
ASICS has introduced the fuzeX TR, a training shoe designed for greater workout efficiency with its lightweight cushioning and versatile design. This all-in-one shoe supports athletes of all backgrounds and experience levels, accommodating activities from high-intensity interval training (HIIT) and weightlifting to treadmill running.
The fuzeX TR launch is part of ASICS&amp;rsquo;s larger expansion into the training category, a market expected to exceed US$55 billion globally by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asics-introduces-the-versatile-fuzex-tr-an-all-in-one-fitness-solution/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>