<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Price on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/price/</link><description>Recent content in Price on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/price/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Less expensive smartphones are available for those in developing markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</guid><description>To prepare for future growth, smartphone manufacturers are looking beyond China to other emerging markets. Although China represented a third of global smartphone shipments in 2013, the International Data Corporation (IDC) indicates this market is reaching its saturation point.
IDC reports that smartphones constitute over 80% of China&amp;rsquo;s total phone sales. Consequently, they predict that India and Africa will be the primary sources of the next half billion smartphone customers.</description></item><item><title>Starting on January 26, 2015, AirAsia will no longer impose fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:27:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Starting January 26, 2015, AirAsia, along with its long-haul affiliates AirAsia X, Thai AirAsia X, and Indonesia AirAsia X, will eliminate fuel surcharges on all flights. This decision aligns with the current downward trend in global oil prices.
Source: AirAsia eDM.
This marks a return to AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s previous policy from 2008, where fuel surcharges were eliminated on all domestic and international flights. However, due to surging fuel prices, surcharges were reinstated in 2011.</description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide.</description></item></channel></rss>