<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HNWI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hnwi/</link><description>Recent content in HNWI on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hnwi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2018, Dubai drew in more than 1,000 residents with a net worth of over a million dollars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</guid><description>Hamdan bin Mohammed: &amp;ldquo;The UAE&amp;rsquo;s forward-looking leadership has made it a top global destination for living and business.&amp;rdquo;
Over 1,000 millionaires relocated to Dubai in 2018.
Crown Prince of Dubai, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, credits the UAE&amp;rsquo;s robust investment and economic landscape to its leadership&amp;rsquo;s visionary approach. He highlights their commitment to the well-being of residents, visitors, and investors, along with fostering innovation, as key factors in establishing the UAE as a premier lifestyle and business hub.</description></item><item><title>Best investment migration programmes for wealthy individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-investment-migration-programmes-for-wealthy-individuals/</guid><description>The increased global demand for residence and citizenship-by-investment programs, particularly among wealthy investors, highlights the desire to overcome limitations posed by single jurisdictions in the wake of COVID-19. Recognizing this, Deep Knowledge Analytics and Henley &amp;amp; Partners have collaborated to create the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
Source: Henley &amp;amp; Partners website. Illustration for the Investment Migration Programs Health Risk Assessment.
This digital publication provides a detailed analysis, interactive tools, and unique perspectives on the efficiency of countries offering these programs during the pandemic, and their potential as future havens for longevity.</description></item><item><title>Henley &amp; Partners has been selected as the worldwide concessionaire for the Thai residency program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/henley-partners-has-been-selected-as-the-worldwide-concessionaire-for-the-thai-residency-program/</guid><description>Henley &amp;amp; Partners, a global firm specializing in residence and citizenship advisory, has been chosen to promote Thailand&amp;rsquo;s residence visa program, Thailand Elite. This program allows foreigners to reside in Thailand for up to 20 years.
Thailand&amp;rsquo;s welcoming atmosphere has made it a desirable destination in Southeast Asia. Individuals and families from affluent nations are increasingly drawn to its climate, scenery, and recreational opportunities. The 2017 &amp;ldquo;Best Countries&amp;rdquo; report highlighted Thailand as a prime location for starting a business due to its affordability, efficient bureaucracy, and accessible capital.</description></item></channel></rss>