<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Q116 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q116/</link><description>Recent content in Q116 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q116/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices.</description></item></channel></rss>