<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plugs on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plugs/</link><description>Recent content in Plugs on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plugs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated DIN Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</guid><description>During the ongoing refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a corroded DIN5 plug was replaced after a new output relay had been installed. The original plug showed significant signs of wear.
A high-quality Rean DIN5 plug with gold-plated terminals was chosen as a replacement. Photos document the preparation of the cable and the installation process. The author notes the limited space inside the DIN5 plug, making it difficult to separate the signal and ground connections.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Corroded RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) currently under restoration was equipped with RCA plugs and a grounding wire instead of the typical DIN 5 connector. The plugs and grounding terminal were noticeably dirty and corroded.
The RCA plugs were switched out for all-metal gold-plated ones, and a new grounding terminal was installed.
These compact RCA plugs lack color coding, so 3D-printed inserts were created. These inserts enclose the back of the plugs and provide a visual distinction between the left and right channels.</description></item></channel></rss>