<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Space on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/space/</link><description>Recent content in Space on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound.</description></item><item><title>ERC has opened a co-working space in multiple cities across Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</guid><description>The University Mentorship program will connect lecturers with the BIG Work community to offer guidance. Users can utilize ERC&amp;rsquo;s expertise in various business areas and schedule consultations with program managers and resource advisors Guests at the BIG Hotel, catering to international and startup business travelers, will have early access to new hospitality-related products and services for research. Entrepreneur Resource Centre Holdings (ERC) has launched BIG Work, a new co-working space with locations in Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam.</description></item><item><title>Booqed offers a selection of workspaces available for rent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</guid><description>Booqed, an online marketplace for booking meeting rooms and workspaces, has introduced its mobile app on the Apple App Store. This app offers a convenient way to find and reserve available spaces in a city, allowing users to book instantly or in advance and make payments directly from their smartphones or tablets.
Businesses can also benefit from this service by monetizing their underutilized meeting or conference rooms. Booqed provides a platform for them to list and rent out these spaces.</description></item><item><title>INVADE aims to connect landlords and retailers in Singapore through matchmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 06:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/invade-aims-to-connect-landlords-and-retailers-in-singapore-through-matchmaking/</guid><description>INVADE, the first real-time retail space booking platform in Singapore, has officially launched. The platform allows businesses to instantly find and book retail spaces. Over 35,000 retail businesses, startups, and entrepreneurs have already become INVADE members.
The idea for INVADE came from Singaporeans Koh Cheng Guan and Kent Teo. Having experience working with major landlords, marketing pop-up and retail spaces, and organizing flea markets, they recognized the challenges entrepreneurs face in finding suitable retail spaces and the landlords&amp;rsquo; need to utilize vacant space.</description></item><item><title>Avanta India inaugurates a new office space in Gurgaon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</guid><description>Avanta Business Centre has established a new premium office space in Gurgaon, India, spanning 25,000 square feet. Conveniently situated near the HUDA City Centre Metro station, the Park Centra facility offers easy accessibility.
This marks Avanta&amp;rsquo;s second business center in Gurgaon. The Park Centra location provides a variety of office sizes, ranging from 77 square feet to approximately 20,000 square feet, to accommodate a diverse clientele. The space is ready for occupancy and features around 300 workstations, a communal area, a pantry, and four meeting rooms.</description></item></channel></rss>