<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>STEM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stem/</link><description>Recent content in STEM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stem/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dream Collective is empowering potential female leaders in Singapore with their first-ever bootcamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 22:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dream-collective-is-empowering-potential-female-leaders-in-singapore-with-their-first-ever-bootcamp/</guid><description>Source: The Dream Collective.
The Dream Collective, a global platform for training women in corporate leadership, has introduced the Emerging Leaders Bootcamp - Singapore Edition. This program offers a new approach to female empowerment and initiates a crucial conversation about developing female leadership talent in the corporate world. Modeled after MBA programs from top business schools, the program collaborates with major corporations to find, develop, and empower high-potential young women with leadership skills.</description></item><item><title>Today is International Women's Day: can you help create the future? #MakeWhatsNext</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-international-women-s-day-can-you-help-create-the-future-makewhatsnext/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft blog. Ada Lovelace was the world&amp;rsquo;s first computer programmer.
In honor of International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day, a global celebration of the achievements of women, Microsoft is encouraging girls around the world to pursue careers in STEM fields with their #MakeWhatsNext campaign.
According to the World Economic Forum, the gender gap won&amp;rsquo;t close until 2133. This gap is especially prominent in computer science and STEM fields. Dr. Daiana Beitler, Microsoft Philanthropies Lead for Asia, notes in a blog post that the Asian Development Bank found women in the region are 70% less likely to be employed than men.</description></item><item><title>Coding is an essential skill for future careers for the following four reasons</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coding-is-an-essential-skill-for-future-careers-for-the-following-four-reasons/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coding-is-an-essential-skill-for-future-careers-for-the-following-four-reasons/</guid><description>September 12th, the 256th day of the year, is a significant date for programmers because the number 256 represents all the values possible within an eight-bit byte. This day is celebrated as International Programmer’s Day.
Dr. Daiana Beitler, Philanthropies Lead at Microsoft Asia, emphasizes how much we rely on the work of programmers. Our ability to connect with loved ones and shop online is thanks to their efforts.
Microsoft highlights the importance of coding for several key reasons:</description></item></channel></rss>