<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Best on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/best/</link><description>Recent content in Best on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aon Hewitt announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers award in Thailand for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</guid><description>Leading employers in Thailand boast engagement scores that are 24 points higher than the average company. This trend is particularly noticeable among Gen Y employees (born between 1979 and 1990), who report engagement levels 22 points higher when working for a top employer. A striking 89% of employees at these leading companies would recommend their workplace to job seekers, significantly surpassing the 68% market average. Among the top performers, Advanced Info Services earned the distinguished title of &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Employers.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Dell EMC was recognized as one of the top companies to work for in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-dell-emc-was-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-companies-to-work-for-in-singapore/</guid><description>Dell EMC Singapore has been recognized as the 8th best company to work for in Singapore in 2016. This ranking comes from a comprehensive study conducted by the Great Place to Work Institute Singapore, which evaluates workplace culture.
The study utilizes 58 metrics from employee surveys and company audits to measure the factors that contribute to a positive and successful work environment. Only organizations where a majority of employees consider it a great place to work are eligible for inclusion.</description></item><item><title>Avoid using the following words on your resume: CareerBuilder</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-using-the-following-words-on-your-resume-careerbuilder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 02:06:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avoid-using-the-following-words-on-your-resume-careerbuilder/</guid><description>A CareerBuilder survey found that almost 70% of hiring managers spend less than two minutes looking at resumes, meaning word choice is critical for job seekers.
Rosemary Haefner, CareerBuilder&amp;rsquo;s VP of human resources, advises using strong action verbs that highlight specific experiences, skills, and achievements. She cautions against subjective terms and clichés because they fail to convey concrete information. For example, instead of claiming to be &amp;ldquo;results-driven,&amp;rdquo; demonstrate actual results.</description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil.</description></item><item><title>Avanade has been recognized as one of the top employers in Malaysia and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</guid><description>Avanade, a company specializing in Microsoft solutions, has received the 2023 Top Employer award in Malaysia and Singapore from the Top Employers Institute.
Source: Avanade. Kapoor.
The Top Employers Institute Programme grants certifications to companies based on their answers and performance on a survey evaluating their Human Resources (HR) practices. Avanade earned recognition for its exceptional practices in all areas reviewed, including People Strategy, Work Environment, Talent Acquisition, Learning, Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion, Wellbeing, and others.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia.</description></item></channel></rss>