<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Culture on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/culture/</link><description>Recent content in Culture on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Al Ain Cultural Programme for 2017/2018 is currently in full swing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:22:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-al-ain-cultural-programme-for-2017-2018-is-currently-in-full-swing/</guid><description>The Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi recently held three events showcasing Emirati culture and heritage as part of the annual Al Ain Cultural Programme.
On October 19th, Qasr Al Muwaiji (Al Muwaiji Palace) hosted the Bisht Workshop, which delved into the history of the traditional garment worn by UAE rulers and the unique patterns associated with each ruler. Attendees also participated in a hands-on workshop, learning to create their own bisht.</description></item><item><title>ARTWALK Little India combines elements of the past with modern influences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</guid><description>Source: ARTWALK Little India. Izzad Radzali Shah, Festival, ARTWALK Little India 2018, LASALLE College of the Arts, 2018. Photo: Ng Wu Gang. The multidisciplinary arts festival ARTWALK Little India is a collaboration between LASALLE College of the Arts (LASALLE) and the Singapore Tourism Board (STB), with support from the Little India Shopkeepers and Heritage Association. It returns for its fourth year in January 2018 as a featured event in Singapore Art Week.</description></item><item><title>Experience the hallyu wave with Viator tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-hallyu-wave-with-viator-tours/</guid><description>Viator, a popular tour booking platform, has noticed a surge in demand for tours featuring filming locations from the hit Korean drama &amp;ldquo;Descendants of the Sun.&amp;rdquo;
Besides tours to Greece, Viator offers the &amp;ldquo;Yongin MBC Dramia TV Set Tour&amp;rdquo; in Korea. This half-day tour takes fans behind the scenes at Yongin MBC TV studios, showcasing sets used in Korea&amp;rsquo;s most popular historical dramas.
For K-drama music enthusiasts, Viator has curated the &amp;ldquo;K Pop Tour&amp;rdquo; in Seoul.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural India-ASEAN Writers Festival premieres in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</guid><description>The High Commission of India in Singapore is hosting the first India-ASEAN Writers Festival in Singapore.
This festival is one of many events celebrating 25 years of friendship between India and ASEAN, coinciding with the ASEAN India Pravasi Bharatiya Divas (Overseas Indians Day). The events are scheduled for January 6-7 at the Marina Bay Sands.
The PBD Writers Festival, a key event organized by Singapore-based publishing house Kitaab International on behalf of the High Commission, aims to &amp;ldquo;celebrate the literary ties between India and the ASEAN nations,&amp;rdquo; said Zafar Anjum, Kitaab&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the history of Bukit Panjang, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</guid><description>Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global movement of free walking tours inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, continues to thrive in Singapore, with tours often fully booked within hours of being announced. This enthusiastic response highlights the movement&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect people with their communities and explore urban landscapes.
This year, on May 5th, a sold-out walk titled &amp;ldquo;At the Crossroads: Bukit Panjang&amp;rdquo; offered participants a unique opportunity to delve into the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s rich history.</description></item><item><title>The Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa introduces the Amara Heritage Trail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 18:58:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amara-sanctuary-resort-sentosa-introduces-the-amara-heritage-trail/</guid><description>Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is launching its first-ever Amara Heritage Trail. This tour allows guests to explore the resort&amp;rsquo;s hidden natural surroundings, conservation efforts, and historical significance.
Source: Amara Sanctury Resort Sentosa. The petai tree is one of 26 heritage trees in Sentosa protected by the Heritage Tree Scheme under Singapore’s National Parks Board. The seeds are edible.
The resort sits on ten acres of land that once housed British military barracks and air raid shelters built between 1897 and 1905 and later renovated in the 1920s.</description></item><item><title>Pesta Raya by Esplanade is back in July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</guid><description>The Esplanade – Theatres on the Bay’s 17th annual Pesta Raya – Malay Festival of Arts will take place from July 12th to 15th, 2018. The festival coincides with Hari Raya Aidilfitri, a celebration that lasts until mid-July.
This year, the festival focuses on the history of the Nusantara. Fezhah Maznan, a programmer with The Esplanade Company, stated that Pesta Raya has always celebrated the rich Malay heritage through arts and culture from the region.</description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>FUMI creates authentic Japanese dining experiences for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</guid><description>Source: FUMI Facebook page. FUMI sushi.
FUMI, a new Japanese eatery, seeks to share the finest Japanese cuisine in Hong Kong within a space adorned with Japanese art, furnishings, and tableware. They offer a range of dining experiences, from elaborate omakase and kaiseki dinners to individual dishes and set lunch options.
Situated in California Tower, FUMI sources the highest quality seasonal ingredients directly from Japan daily. Flown in and delivered straight to their kitchen, these ingredients are often prepared and served within hours of being harvested, guaranteeing freshness in their sushi, sashimi, omakase, and kaiseki preparations, as well as a variety of seasonal menus.</description></item><item><title>Suzhou is gaining more recognition in the MICE industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:42:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suzhou-is-gaining-more-recognition-in-the-mice-industry/</guid><description>The Suzhou Culture and Expo Centre Company (SCECC), which manages the Suzhou Culture and Arts Centre and the Suzhou International Expo Centre, claims that Suzhou is arguably the top Meetings, Incentives, Conferences and Exhibitions (MICE) destination in China.
SCECC highlights Suzhou&amp;rsquo;s success in hosting significant events, such as the 53rd World Table Tennis Championships earlier this year and Armani&amp;rsquo;s selection of the city&amp;rsquo;s Humble Administrator&amp;rsquo;s Garden as the venue for the global debut of its Pivoine Suzhou perfume.</description></item><item><title>The Emirates Literature Foundation introduces a new digital discussion series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-emirates-literature-foundation-introduces-a-new-digital-discussion-series/</guid><description>The Emirates Literature Foundation has launched a new project, Literary Conversations Across Borders. This digital initiative aims to promote global cultural understanding by connecting Emirati writers and thinkers with internationally recognized experts for live discussions on significant issues.
The series commences on May 30, 2020, with Indian politician and writer Shashi Tharoor and HE Zaki Nusseibeh, UAE Minister of State for the Office of Cultural Diplomacy. They will examine how the events of 2020 will shape the future, both positively and negatively.</description></item></channel></rss>