<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private Clouds on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-clouds/</link><description>Recent content in Private Clouds on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-clouds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud On The Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 00:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-on-the-cheap/</guid><description>Big corporations are shifting their data centers to the cloud for financial and logistical benefits, enabling work from anywhere. But what about smaller businesses? Can they enjoy similar advantages?
One cloud solution often overlooked due to its existence before the cloud trend is GoToMyPC. Although not typically associated with the cloud, it embodies the concept.
GoToMyPC enables remote login to your computer. But isn&amp;rsquo;t accessing your desktop from a restaurant, running office applications, conceptually similar to using a private cloud?</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Managed Cloud Solutions Are Your Business Edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-cloud-solutions-are-your-business-edge/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Technology is essential for modern businesses, but it comes with its own set of challenges. While technology enables businesses to function and thrive, it also demands significant capital investment, specialized expertise, and constant updates to stay ahead of obsolescence. This raises the question: can businesses leverage the power of technology without being burdened by its drawbacks?
Enter The Managed Cloud
The answer lies in the managed cloud. Instead of managing everything internally, businesses can now opt for cloud solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>