<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CTI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cti/</link><description>Recent content in CTI on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cti/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Replacement Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:31:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/</guid><description>Unhappy with your current VoIP provider? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing subpar customer service or your provider has gone out of business, our VoIP Service Finder can help you compare options and find a new provider. Businesses have additional alternatives worth exploring.
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, has rapidly gained popularity among residential, small business, and enterprise users. Its growth is largely driven by the potential for significant cost savings on phone services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-replacement-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Centers Move To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems are gaining popularity as a replacement for traditional phone systems. Businesses are recognizing the benefits of moving their phone systems to the cloud. So why aren&amp;rsquo;t call centers embracing this technology?
Actually, some call centers are already using cloud-based systems. Smaller and geographically dispersed call centers are more likely to transition from physical to cloud-based phone systems. Larger call centers face more challenges in adopting this technology because their needs extend beyond basic phone functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>