<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dyson on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dyson/</link><description>Recent content in Dyson on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 03:32:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dyson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dyson introduces the cordless Cyclone V10 vacuum cleaner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-introduces-the-cordless-cyclone-v10-vacuum-cleaner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 03:32:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-introduces-the-cordless-cyclone-v10-vacuum-cleaner/</guid><description>• The Dyson Cyclone V10, Dyson&amp;rsquo;s newest stick vacuum, is cordless.
• Although smaller and lighter, the Dyson digital motor V10 boasts a 20% increase in suction power compared to the Dyson V8 cord-free vacuum.
Dyson has introduced the Cyclone V10 cord-free vacuum cleaner, promising suction exceeding typical stick vacuums.
The key is the new Dyson digital motor V10, weighing almost half its predecessor, the Dyson digital motor V8. This is Dyson’s fastest and most power-dense digital vacuum motor, reaching speeds up to 125,000 rpm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-introduces-the-cordless-cyclone-v10-vacuum-cleaner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-introduces-the-cordless-cyclone-v10-vacuum-cleaner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dyson's latest Pure Cool fans also function as air purifiers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/</guid><description>Dyson has introduced the Dyson Pure Cool purifying fans, which leverage the company&amp;rsquo;s expertise in airflow, filtration, and electronics to address indoor air pollution and purify entire rooms.
Dyson first entered the purifying fan market in 2015, responding to the growing global concern of indoor air pollution. Dyson points out that we breathe mostly indoor air, which can contain invisible, microscopic particles. Urban pollution, particulate matter, and pollen can infiltrate indoor spaces like offices, mix with pollutants from sources like cleaning products, and become trapped...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dyson-s-latest-pure-cool-fans-also-function-as-air-purifiers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>