<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Entertainment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entertainment/</link><description>Recent content in Entertainment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entertainment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with TVB programming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</guid><description>Singtel TV is adding Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s TVB Jade and TVB Xing He channels to its lineup. From September 9th to October 8th, 2019, viewers can enjoy a free preview.
Singtel customers will have access to the same TVB Jade as Hong Kong viewers, featuring Cantonese dramas, variety shows, and infotainment programs.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CEO of Consumer Singapore, shared that the company is fulfilling customer requests by introducing these channels, broadening their comprehensive TV offerings and solidifying their position as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading pay-TV provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-tvb-programming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel increases its offering of free content as the circuit-breaker in Singapore is extended</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</guid><description>Singtel TV is expanding its free preview by adding 10 more channels while the circuit breaker period is extended. This is in addition to the 95,000 hours of programming already offered for free on Singtel TV and Singtel CAST, which was launched last month to help entertain people stuck at home.
From May 1st to 31st, Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO will offer a free preview with more entertainment, factual, news, and other programming from popular channels including National Geographic and FOX Family Movies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's 2022 Chinese New Year film features the Angs and the Huangs facing off on Sentosa with the addition of 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 23:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chinese New Year festive film for 2022.
To celebrate the Year of the Tiger and the values of family and community central to the holiday, Singtel has released its annual Chinese New Year short film. The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger is the third installment in a series of films by Singtel featuring the amusing rivalry between two families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hilton guests will enjoy Live Nation experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 20:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and Live Nation, a live entertainment company, have launched a new five-year marketing partnership. This collaboration will provide unique experiences, including artist connections and concerts, to Hilton HHonors members, guests, and employees across Hilton&amp;rsquo;s global network of over 4,250 hotels.
Source: Hilton Worldwide. Hilton
aims to motivate a new,
healthier way of thinking - urging
individuals to embrace the unfamiliar,
gain perspective, and learn from daily
life and travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-guests-will-enjoy-live-nation-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with the addition of HBO</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</guid><description>Singtel is adding HBO programming to its television offerings. The deal means Singtel TV and its Singtel TV GO app users will have access to HBO Asia’s six channels. To mark the occasion, Singtel is offering a free preview of all six channels until February 28, 2019.
Beginning March 15, subscribers can access HBO GO, HBO Asia’s streaming service, through CAST, Singtel’s video app for mobile and smart TV.
Yuen Kuan Moon, CEO, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, said the company is “thrilled” to welcome HBO to its roster...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals are using the popularity of Netflix and WhatsApp to distribute malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</guid><description>Source: Check Point Research. The Google Play page for the FlixOnline app.
Hackers are spreading Android malware disguised as an app to unlock Netflix content. Check Point Research (CPR) discovered that this malware automatically responds to incoming WhatsApp messages with malicious links.
The malware was initially concealed within an app called FlixOnline on Google Play. While promising users access to global Netflix content on their phones, it actually tracked victims’ WhatsApp notifications and automatically replied to messages using externally provided content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fans in Singapore of Song Seung Heon may have the opportunity to meet him</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for Saimdang featuring Song.
To kick off the new year, Singtel is bringing South Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon to Singapore on January 7, 2017. Song&amp;rsquo;s visit will promote the drama Saimdang (师任堂), which premieres on Singtel TV&amp;rsquo;s Oh!K channel (channel 525/611) on January 25, 2017, at 9 pm.
Singtel TV subscribers can enter to win 20 pairs of tickets to a meet-and-greet and autograph session with Song...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel Music is excited to announce the addition of TIDAL to its portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</guid><description>Singtel Music now offers its customers access to the global music and entertainment platform, TIDAL.
TIDAL differentiates itself as the sole music app providing high-fidelity, lossless audio quality and exclusive content from top global artists. Singtel Music users can enjoy both TIDAL Premium and TIDAL HIFI without impacting their data plans.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its music streaming options. Following the addition of Saavn in October, TIDAL further solidifies Singtel Music&amp;rsquo;s goal of providing the best music streaming experience with diverse content, attractive pricing, and no data charges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The video-on-demand service HOOQ has been launched in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: HOOQ. Bithos.
HOOQ, a leading premium video-on-demand service targeting the Asian market, has officially launched in Singapore. This expansion follows successful launches in the Philippines, Thailand, India, and Indonesia, bringing their reach to a potential audience exceeding 1.6 billion people.
Established in Singapore in 2015, HOOQ is a joint venture between Singtel, Sony Pictures Television, and Warner Brothers. This partnership represents a significant collaboration between major media companies to revolutionize entertainment consumption in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Traveloka will introduce awards based on audience participation for Asia's Got Talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</guid><description>Traveloka, a popular Southeast Asian travel app, is sponsoring the second season of AXN&amp;rsquo;s Asia&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent and introducing the Traveloka Awards.
The Traveloka Awards will recognize the contestant with the most compelling background, emphasizing unique talents and strong family and friend connections.
Premiering this October, Asia’s Got Talent on AXN will feature ten episodes, including auditions, semifinals, a finale, and a results show revealing the winner of a $100,000 prize from Traveloka...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ZEE5 is attracting viewers from Pakistan and Bangladesh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 01:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</guid><description>Source: Zee5. Images for the #ShareTheLove campaign.
Following its initial launch in over 190 countries, the digital entertainment platform ZEE5 is setting its sights on Pakistan and Bangladesh.
The company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;#ShareTheLove&amp;rdquo; campaign highlights the cultural and entertainment commonalities between ZEE5 and these two nations. ZEE5 aims to foster a sense of shared enjoyment by providing a diverse content library that resonates with Pakistani and Bangladeshi audiences, featuring Hindi and Bengali original series like &amp;ldquo;Rangbaaz,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Kaali,&amp;rdquo; and the upcoming &amp;ldquo;Sharate Aaj,&amp;rdquo; original films such as &amp;ldquo;Aranyadeb&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tigers,&amp;rdquo; and digital premieres of movies like &amp;ldquo;Namaste England&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Praktan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>