<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kaspersky on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kaspersky/</link><description>Recent content in Kaspersky on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:51:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/kaspersky/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Be cautious of malware with a Christmas theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:51:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-malware-with-a-christmas-theme/</guid><description>Christmas tree, Marina Bay Sands.
_&amp;quot;&amp;hellip;On the twelfth day of Christmas
my true love gave me:
Twelve pieces of malware
Eleven malfunctioning firewalls
Ten ransomware dangers
Nine account breaches
Eight adware websites
Seven deceitful emails
Six compromised PDFs
Five warning signs
Four spyware-infected games
Three junk text messages
Two Trojan horses
And a phishing email!&amp;quot;_
Holiday greetings can carry hidden cyber threats, even if sent from loved ones. Yeo Siang Tiong, Southeast Asia General Manager at Kaspersky Lab, emphasizes the importance of robust computer and mobile device protection before engaging in holiday activities like downloading festive content, sending emails, or online shopping.</description></item><item><title>Kaspersky Lab is providing security tips in preparation for the Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:54:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kaspersky-lab-is-providing-security-tips-in-preparation-for-the-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown is prominently featuring dog decorations in celebration of the new year.
As shoppers navigate the excitement and rush of Chinese New Year shopping, Kaspersky Lab cautions that they are more susceptible to making simple errors that could jeopardize their personal information.
Sylvia Ng, General Manager of Kaspersky Lab Southeast Asia, acknowledges that holiday shopping is a top priority for consumers. However, she emphasizes that it&amp;rsquo;s also an opportune time for cybercriminals.</description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods.</description></item></channel></rss>