<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>POS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pos/</link><description>Recent content in POS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs.</description></item><item><title>Small Business Merchant Accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:36:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-business-merchant-accounts/</guid><description>Could you be missing out on sales because you don&amp;rsquo;t accept credit cards? While setting up credit and debit card processing might seem expensive and complex, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. With the right processing partner, it can be a smooth and straightforward process.
Don&amp;rsquo;t mistake this for implying that credit card processing is simple. Behind the scenes, it involves a network of banks, credit card companies, merchant service providers, computer systems, and specialized equipment.</description></item><item><title>HP's ElitePOS is specifically designed for the retail industry 2.0</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elitepos-is-specifically-designed-for-the-retail-industry-2-0/</guid><description>HP Inc. is aiming to revolutionize the retail sector with its new HP ElitePOS system, a flexible all-in-one point-of-sale (POS) solution. The company&amp;rsquo;s goal is to enhance the in-store experience by providing a balanced technological approach that boosts sales and simplifies operations.
Research from HP highlights that 69% of customers are more inclined to make purchases in physical stores if they have access to digital self-service resources, such as interactive displays and kiosks.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless for Point of Sale Authorizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</guid><description>Credit card processing is essential for modern businesses, so having a fast and reliable authorization terminal is crucial. While dial-up terminals might have been sufficient in the past, their slow speed can frustrate customers and reflect poorly on your business. Upgrading to a broadband connection is a worthwhile investment.
T1 lines have become more affordable, making them a popular choice for businesses. However, they can still be expensive for smaller companies.</description></item><item><title>POS For Temporary Store Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 19:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pos-for-temporary-store-locations/</guid><description>A common sight during the holidays is the &amp;ldquo;pop-up shop.&amp;rdquo; These temporary stores occupy vacant spaces in malls and shopping centers, offering seasonal goods like decorations, costumes, and calendars. Once the season ends, so do their operations. Despite their temporary nature, these businesses require robust point-of-sale (POS) systems, even more so than traditional stores.
The need for efficient POS systems stems from the concentrated bursts of customer traffic these stores experience.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new mobile POS printer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 22:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-mobile-pos-printer/</guid><description>Epson, a company known for its printing and digital imaging solutions, has introduced the TM-m30 point of sale (POS) printer. Created specifically for tablet-based systems, the TM-m30 stands out as one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most compact desktop receipt printers, making it a perfect fit for retail and hospitality businesses aiming to transition to a POS system managed by smart devices.
Source: Epson Singapore. The Epson TM-m30 POS printer.
The TM-m30 is engineered for swift and effortless setup on iOS, Android, and Windows mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Includes Canada &amp; Puerto Rico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</guid><description>People often associate broadband with wired connections, like T1 lines commonly used by small to medium businesses, or the increasingly popular Ethernet option known for its speed and affordability. While satellite is vital for many chain stores, there&amp;rsquo;s another reliable broadband solution that avoids construction costs and high monthly fees: fixed wireless broadband, now available across the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Accel Networks, a leading provider of fixed wireless broadband, leverages existing 2.</description></item></channel></rss>