<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commercial Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commercial-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Commercial Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commercial-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>