<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Protection Directive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection-directive/</link><description>Recent content in Data Protection Directive on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection-directive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on the applicable law and jurisdiction for data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 04:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-applicable-law-and-jurisdiction-for-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently issued a decision in the Weltimmo case regarding the jurisdictional reach of data protection authorities. The court ruled that the authority of one Member State can exercise jurisdiction over entities primarily operating outside of that state’s borders. This ruling could impact two important issues being considered for the proposed data protection regulation: the regulation&amp;rsquo;s territorial scope and the authority of national data protection bodies.</description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in C-582/14 Breyer establishes IP addresses as personal data.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 12:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-c-582-14-breyer-establishes-ip-addresses-as-personal-data/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The opinions presented are solely those of the author and should not be interpreted as representing the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s official stance.
Background
The Breyer case saw the German Supreme Court (Bundesgerichtshof) request clarification from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on whether dynamic IP addresses constitute personal data under the EU Data Protection Directive and to what extent their storage and processing is permissible for maintaining website functionality.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens.</description></item><item><title>Could Data Protection be Returning Home? The CJEU's Ruling on Data Protection Law in Relation to Jehovah's Witnesses and Political Canvassing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re showering when the doorbell unexpectedly interrupts. Hoping it&amp;rsquo;s the anticipated Amazon delivery with a birthday gift for your daughter, you rush downstairs, only to find a pair of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witnesses.
After dismissing their pleas, you close the door, putting the encounter out of your mind. However, they haven&amp;rsquo;t forgotten you. To maintain their focus on potential converts, they keep records of visited homes, categorizing residents as &amp;ldquo;Believer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Unbeliever,&amp;rdquo; or perhaps even &amp;ldquo;Satanist,&amp;rdquo; depending on your towel situation.</description></item><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law.</description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails.</description></item><item><title>The Data Protection Bill and UK-EU Data Transfers: A Story of Brexit and Data Protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 13:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-protection-bill-and-uk-eu-data-transfers-a-story-of-brexit-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Elif Mendos Kuşkonmaz, PhD student at Queen Mary, University of London[*]
Introduction
A Bosnian folk song tells the story of a Pasha who died from a severe illness. When his wife heard about his passing, she died from grief. Similarly, now that the UK has chosen to leave the European Union, will the same fate befall data protection laws once the UK exits the EU?
The UK&amp;rsquo;s current data protection law, the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA), incorporates the EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 Data Protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>The impact of Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein v. Wirtschaftsakademie Schleswig-Holstein GmbH on Facebook fan pages and EU data protection regulations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
Case Summary
The Wirtschaftsakademie, a business using a Facebook fanpage, was ordered by the Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein (ULD), a German data protection authority, to deactivate their page. The ULD argued that the page failed to warn visitors about potential data collection by Facebook through cookies.
This case highlights the benefits and data implications associated with Facebook fanpages. Page administrators benefit from free, anonymous user statistics through &amp;ldquo;Facebook Insights,&amp;rdquo; while Facebook gathers data for targeted advertising.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union makes decisions regarding consent for cookies in accordance with data protection laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 19:09:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-makes-decisions-regarding-consent-for-cookies-in-accordance-with-data-protection-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A significant ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the use of cookies and the interpretation of consent under the e-Privacy Directive was issued last week in the Planet49 case. This ruling holds implications for comprehending cookie requirements under both the existing and forthcoming data protection regulations.
Judgment
At the heart of the matter was an online lottery requiring participants to provide their name and address.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's confusion on biometric data and data protection law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Growing concerns about the protection of biometric data have led the EU to propose a data protection regulation classifying such data as sensitive, thus providing it with a higher level of protection. However, until this proposal is enacted, existing EU regulations address this issue, although not always effectively, as demonstrated by the recent CJEU ruling in the Willems case, which falls short in its application of existing regulations to biometric data.</description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in Safe Interenvios addresses issues of money laundering, customer due diligence, and data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The views expressed are purely those of the author and may not in any circumstances be regarded as stating an official position of the European Commission
Background
This analysis examines a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment concerning a case, Safe Interenvios, which originated from a preliminary reference submitted by a Provincial Court in Barcelona. The Barcelona court requested the CJEU to clarify the interpretation of the third Anti-Money Laundering Directive (AML Directive) in relation to a dispute involving a financial institution, Safe Interenvios, and several banks.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v.</description></item></channel></rss>