<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brisbane on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brisbane/</link><description>Recent content in Brisbane on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brisbane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality introduces the new Sage Hotel brand, catering specifically to upscale business travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</guid><description>SilverNeedle Hospitality, headquartered in Singapore, has introduced a new upscale hotel brand, Sage Hotel, tailored for business travelers. The first Sage Hotel will be located in Brisbane, Australia.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated, &amp;ldquo;We recognize a significant group of business travelers seeking a consistent and straightforward experience while working in unfamiliar cities.&amp;rdquo; He added, &amp;ldquo;Sage Hotel is designed to meet their needs and complements our existing portfolio of six brands.</description></item></channel></rss>