<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Watch on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/watch/</link><description>Recent content in Watch on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/watch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple has revealed that the Apple Watch will be available in additional countries starting on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Apple has announced the availability of the Apple Watch in more countries, including Singapore, South Korea, and Taiwan, starting June 26th. The smartwatch will be sold through Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, and authorized retailers.
Select retailers such as BOONTHESHOP Cheongdam in Seoul and Malmaison by The Hour Glass in Singapore will offer a curated collection of Apple Watch models at launch. In the Asia Pacific region, the Apple Watch is already for sale in Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, and Japan.</description></item><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes.</description></item><item><title>CASIO introduces the G-SHOCK x ITZY SS2024 collection in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-the-g-shock-x-itzy-ss2024-collection-in-singapore/</guid><description>CASIO is promoting their new G-SHOCK shock-resistant watches for spring 2024 with the help of K-pop group ITZY, who have been G-SHOCK brand ambassadors since February 2023.
ITZY is shown wearing the new GMA-P2100SG-1A, GMA-P2100SG-4A, GMA-S120VA-7A, and GMA-S140VA-7A watches in a promotional image. Ryujin and Chaeryeong showcase the GMA-P2100SG-1A and GMA-P2100SG-4A, which are inspired by sunset hues on a beach. These watches are based on the GMA-P2100, a smaller version of the well-liked GMA-S2100 analog-digital combination watch.</description></item><item><title>Pre-orders for the Apple Watch will begin on April 10th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-orders-for-the-apple-watch-will-begin-on-april-10th/</guid><description>Source: Apple website. The Apple Watch Edition can cost up to US$17,000.
Apple has revealed the release dates for the Apple Watch, a device that combines the functions of a timepiece, communication tool, and health and fitness tracker. Starting on April 24th, it will be available in Australia, Canada, mainland China, France, Germany, Hong Kong, Japan, the UK, and the US.
What it does With the Apple Watch, users can send messages, check email, and answer calls received on their iPhone directly from their wrist.</description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones.</description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day.</description></item><item><title>CASIO introduces new watches to coincide with the 40th anniversary of G-SHOCK and the opening of its flagship store in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-new-watches-to-coincide-with-the-40th-anniversary-of-g-shock-and-the-opening-of-its-flagship-store-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 20:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casio-introduces-new-watches-to-coincide-with-the-40th-anniversary-of-g-shock-and-the-opening-of-its-flagship-store-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: CASIO. The new flagship store at ION Orchard mall in Singapore.
CASIO has established its latest flagship store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ION Orchard mall. This store showcases a distinctive sculpture by Singaporean artist Jahan Loh. This artwork features a metallic half-body bust that evokes a futuristic cyborg, with the face being a representation of Casio&amp;rsquo;s iconic watch and its signature rounded rectangular bezel.
Coinciding with the store launch, G-SHOCK, a Casio brand, has unveiled its most recent addition to the G-SQUAD sports series.</description></item><item><title>Singtel provides eSIMs for the Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</guid><description>Source: Samsung website. This Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch functions on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE network.
Singtel has launched the Samsung Gear S3 frontier (LTE) on its 4G LTE network. Equipped with an eSIM, this smartwatch offers independent 4G LTE connectivity. This allows users to make and receive calls, send text messages, and browse the internet without needing their smartphones.
Singtel customers will also experience 4G ClearVoice, also known as VoLTE.</description></item><item><title>Apple has released new Apple Watch options, including the addition of the Hermès collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The Apple Watch.
Apple has launched new Apple Watch cases and bands, updated its watch operating system, and introduced new gold and rose gold aluminum models for the Apple Watch Sport.
Available as a free update on September 16, the watchOS 2 operating system delivers new features and native third-party apps to Apple Watches. With watchOS 2, apps run faster. Users will also find new watch faces, third-party app information viewable on the watch face, and a &amp;ldquo;Time Travel&amp;rdquo; feature that provides chronological context.</description></item><item><title>The latest Apple watches have the capability to contact someone in case of a fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</guid><description>Apple has released the Apple Watch Series 4, a redesigned smartwatch focused on connectivity, activity tracking, and health management.
Maintaining its classic look, the fourth iteration boasts a 30% larger screen and a smaller, slimmer casing. This model introduces advanced fitness and communication features with watchOS 5, a new accelerometer and gyroscope for fall detection, and an electrical heart rate sensor that enables electrocardiograms (ECGs) through the new ECG app.</description></item><item><title>The TomTom Golfer 2 GPS Watch is created to assist golfers in enhancing their game</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</guid><description>TomTom has introduced the TomTom Golfer 2, a slim GPS watch designed for golfers. The watch uses automatic shot detection to provide detailed analysis after a round, aiming to improve users&amp;rsquo; games.
The TomTom Golfer 2 eliminates uncertainty on the course by measuring distances to greens and hazards. This automatic shot detection helps golfers understand their distance potential by displaying distances for drives and approach shots at a glance. After the game, golfers can analyze their strokes in detail using TomTom MySports.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player.</description></item><item><title>With Lavotre, you have the ability to create your own custom watch design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-lavotre-you-have-the-ability-to-create-your-own-custom-watch-design/</guid><description>Source: Lavotre. Bently
Anchor, an original design
from Lavotre.
Need a special corporate gift? Consider personalized watches.
Eugene Chow, Brand Manager at Lavotre, explained that their journey started with a simple question: &amp;ldquo;What if we could create our own watches?&amp;rdquo; They noticed a gap in the market for personalized watches without minimum order requirements or limited to generic &amp;ldquo;couple&amp;rdquo; designs. Partnering with Cheryl Tan, head of sales and operations, they established Lavotre to fill this void.</description></item><item><title>The LG Watch Urbane 2nd edition also functions as a phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG claims its Watch Urbane 2nd Edition is the first Android Wear smartwatch to offer cellular connectivity. The watch will launch globally this month, starting with the US and Korea, followed by other major markets in the coming months.
The LG Watch Urbane 2nd Edition works with both Android and iOS smartphones, giving users the freedom to answer calls and check messages without relying on their phones.</description></item><item><title>The Singtel NumberShare service is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 3, which comes with built-in cellular capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</guid><description>Singtel is the first in Singapore to offer Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS + Cellular), allowing users to stay connected without their iPhones. The watch has been available in Singapore since September 2017 and works with compatible plans.
Apple Watch Series 3 with cellular enables users to stay in touch, make calls, and send and receive texts without needing their iPhones nearby, as long as their carrier provides a compatible plan.</description></item></channel></rss>