<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Applications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-applications/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Applications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-applications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of a Wireless Business Continuity Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 01:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-a-wireless-business-continuity-plan/</guid><description>For businesses today, the difference between success and failure often comes down to a reliable internet connection. In the past, while important, telecom connections weren&amp;rsquo;t critical for daily operations. Now, with businesses relying on cloud-based applications and data storage, a lost connection can bring everything to a halt.
While wired connections are generally dependable, they aren&amp;rsquo;t perfect. Downtime, whether due to equipment malfunctions or accidental cable cuts, can lead to significant financial setbacks.</description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly.</description></item></channel></rss>