<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conference on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/conference/</link><description>Recent content in Conference on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region.</description></item><item><title>ACCA will be hosting a virtual conference called Accounting for the Future from September 15 to 18</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-will-be-hosting-a-virtual-conference-called-accounting-for-the-future-from-september-15-to-18/</guid><description>Source: ACCA website.
The sixth annual Accounting for the Future virtual conference, hosted by the Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA), will focus on important topics impacting the future of accounting. These topics include corporate culture, sustainability, and global business service models.
The conference, taking place from September 15th to 18th, 2014, will feature four days of live and on-demand video and audio webcasts covering various subjects related to the accounting profession.</description></item><item><title>The Startup Capitals conference will begin on May 20th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</guid><description>Source: Startup Capitals&amp;rsquo; website.
Startup Capitals, a leading-edge conference inspired by the recent book of the same name by Singapore-based author and journalist Zafar Anjum, will be held on May 20th in Singapore at The POD, NLB, 100 Victoria Street.
This one-day event, coinciding with the book&amp;rsquo;s official launch, will highlight the innovation and startup ecosystems of globally impactful cities. It will unite all facets of these ecosystems – entrepreneurs, business leaders, innovators, researchers, educators, government officials, and venture capitalists – under one roof.</description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival showcases performances by exceptionally talented artists with disabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 09:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-showcases-performances-by-exceptionally-talented-artists-with-disabilities/</guid><description>The True Colours Festival, showcasing talented performing artists with disabilities from the Asia Pacific region, will run from March 22nd to 25th, 2018 in Singapore.
The festival will feature up to 20 artist/troupe performances representing Japan, China, India, Korea, Malaysia, Cambodia, Kazakhstan, New Zealand, Australia, and Singapore. Guest artists from the UK and Canada will also be featured. Performances will take place at a multimedia concert experience inside the Singapore Indoor Stadium and at the nearby True Colours Festival Village.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra SPEAK 810 can detect and track people speaking from several meters away</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</guid><description>Fragment.in, a Swiss design interaction studio, created a computer orchestra controlled by gestures. Hand movements are recognized by a Kinect, which then controls audio from multiple computers. The sound is emitted through Jabra SPEAK 810 devices.
Jabra, a company specializing in audio and communications technology, has launched the SPEAK 810. This new conference speakerphone offers high-quality call experiences to enhance meeting collaboration.
Retailing at US$599, the Jabra SPEAK 810 addresses common obstacles to effective collaboration.</description></item><item><title>The 18th edition of All That Matters will take place from September 11th to 13th, 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</guid><description>All That Matters, a key event for professionals in Asia&amp;rsquo;s music, sports, gaming, digital, marketing, Web3, and entertainment sectors, is back for its 18th year. It will be held from September 11th to 13th at the Hilton Singapore Orchard.
Source: All That Matters organisers. Event poster.
The event combines a daytime conference with a nightly music festival. It offers attendees, including representatives from major labels, sports organizations, distributors, and publishers, a chance to connect with global brands.</description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join.</description></item><item><title>As Travel Becomes Costlier, Online Meetings Look Better</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/as-travel-becomes-costlier-online-meetings-look-better/</guid><description>During tough economic times, travel costs remain high, making it expensive and inconvenient to travel for work. While some in-person interaction is crucial, could more frequent collaboration without travel be beneficial?
Many companies find online meetings save money and increase productivity. GoToMeeting allows unlimited meetings for a low monthly fee, eliminating the need to coordinate with providers and making scheduling as simple as emailing.
GoToMeeting is easy to use. Start instant meetings with one click or schedule one-time or recurring meetings, allowing participants to join from anywhere using a Mac, PC, iPad, or iPhone, all for free.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the Healthy MICE Programme by SilverNeedle Hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-healthy-mice-programme-by-silverneedle-hospitality/</guid><description>To address the increasing demand for healthier options at conferences, SilverNeedle Hospitality is launching &amp;ldquo;Healthy Minds, Healthy Thinking,&amp;rdquo; a new MICE (Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions) program.
Watermelon salad
This program is being launched in response to a survey of 85 event organizers, in which 93% indicated that healthy food choices were a significant factor in their venue selection process.
&amp;ldquo;‘Our Healthy Minds, Healthy Thinking’ program came about because of a real need in the MICE sector,” explained Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Google is revealing how it plans to increase your productivity in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Google&amp;rsquo;s annual developer conference, I/O, brought a wave of announcements for Apps, Android, Chromebooks, and the Cloud Platform.
As highlighted on the official Google blog, Android now boasts a staggering one billion users who send an estimated 20 billion text messages and 93 million selfies daily. Key introductions include:
Android Wear
Expanding Android&amp;rsquo;s reach to wearable devices, Android Wear allows users to perform tasks or ask questions simply by saying &amp;ldquo;Ok Google.</description></item></channel></rss>