<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Free Movement of Workers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-workers/</link><description>Recent content in Free Movement of Workers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/free-movement-of-workers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive.</description></item><item><title>10 Questions &amp; Answers about EU Free Movement Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We shouldn&amp;rsquo;t create a misleading impression of the law.&amp;rdquo;
(Measure for Measure, 2.1.1)
Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School, University of York
Laurent Pech, Professor of European Law, Jean Monnet Chair of EU Public Law at Middlesex University London
This article clarifies common misunderstandings about EU free movement rules, often found in British media. We believe much criticism targets a distorted view of the actual system.
The UK shows a desire to restrict EU freedom of movement, yet misinterpretations about these rules persist.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for a 'fast-track' Treaty amendment on the free movement of workers with the Cameron express?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 10:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-a-fast-track-treaty-amendment-on-the-free-movement-of-workers-with-the-cameron-express/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Experts in EU law see Treaty amendments as a monumental event. After the Treaty of Lisbon, significant changes to the Treaty seemed improbable in the near future. However, this prospect is becoming more likely due to David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s push to renegotiate free movement regulations within the EU, a sentiment somewhat shared by the UK Labour party.
This brings us to the crucial question of what form such a Treaty amendment would take.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK's limitation on EU workers' eligibility for benefits lawful - and if not, should it be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK government recently established a new income requirement for EU citizens from other Member States to be classified as &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and access certain benefits. This raises the question of whether these rules align with EU law regarding the free movement of workers and if modifications are necessary.
Under these regulations, EU citizens must earn a minimum of £150 weekly for at least three months to be considered &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and qualify for benefits such as child benefit, child tax credit, job-seekers&amp;rsquo; allowance, and housing benefit.</description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on discrimination against EU citizen workers just a futile effort?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-discrimination-against-eu-citizen-workers-just-a-futile-effort/</guid><description>Despite public debate regarding EU citizens working in different Member States (&amp;ldquo;EU workers&amp;rdquo;), the Council and European Parliament have agreed on new legislation concerning this topic. Recently approved by the European Parliament, the new Directive focuses on enforcing existing rules against discrimination toward EU workers and will likely be adopted by the Council soon. Member States are given two years to implement this Directive.
The Directive itself doesn&amp;rsquo;t modify existing rights related to EU worker free movement, but instead, clarifies the enforcement and application of rights granted by Article 45 TFEU and Regulation 492/2011.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union rejects benefit tourism by EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-rejects-benefit-tourism-by-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant ruling in the case of Dano, which dealt with the ability of EU citizens to access social welfare benefits when they relocate to another Member State. The Court&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the laws in this case (and other rulings earlier this year involving EU citizens with criminal histories) suggests a stricter approach, possibly reflecting the ongoing political discussions regarding the free movement of EU citizens.</description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The future of the UK's free movement of people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
*The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe program. They thank their colleagues, Graeme Ross, Steve Peers, Jonathan Portes and Madelaine Sumption.
Introduction
A primary reason many voted to exit the European Union on June 23, 2016, was concern over immigration. Many felt the UK had &amp;ldquo;lost control&amp;rdquo; of its borders and that leaving the EU would allow the UK government to regain control.</description></item><item><title>The rights of pregnant workers and the free movement rights of EU citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rights-of-pregnant-workers-and-the-free-movement-rights-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Jessy Saint Prix, a young woman from France, relocated to Britain in 2006 to pursue a teaching career. Her experience led her to learn much more about EU law and the English legal system than she expected.
After working in the UK as a teaching assistant for a year, she began a teacher training program (PGCE). During the program, she became pregnant and decided to pause her studies to register with a teaching agency.</description></item><item><title>Is equal treatment possible in the fair movement of people? (Part Two)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-equal-treatment-possible-in-the-fair-movement-of-people-part-two/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme
Introduction
This blog post proposes a UK/EU migration policy based on &amp;ldquo;fair movement&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;free movement.&amp;rdquo; This system would require work permits for genuine employment or self-employment and a simplified registration process like the one used for Croatian migrants.
The authors suggest limiting the principle of equal treatment for work and benefits, using existing restrictions within the Citizens’ Rights Directive 2004/38 and the Brussels New Settlement Agreement.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union clarifies the access of EU citizens to benefits after leaving employment.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-clarifies-the-access-of-eu-citizens-to-benefits-after-leaving-employment/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the Alimanovic case provides further clarification on EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits in other Member States, a complex issue. Similar to last year&amp;rsquo;s Dano ruling, it takes a stricter stance than previous interpretations of EU law. However, like its predecessor, this judgment leaves some questions unanswered. This analysis will delve into the judgment itself, its implications for EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to benefits, and the UK government&amp;rsquo;s plans to renegotiate its EU membership.</description></item><item><title>Is Free Movement in Europe Unusual? The Recent Open Borders Policy in South America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 01:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-free-movement-in-europe-unusual-the-recent-open-borders-policy-in-south-america/</guid><description>Dr Diego Acosta Arcarazo, Lecturer in Law at the University of Bristol, and member of the research project Prospects for International Migration Governance (MIGPROSP)
While the freedom of movement within the European Union (EU) faces criticism and limitations from certain political and media outlets, other areas of the globe, such as South America, are embracing similar systems. This highlights that the EU model isn&amp;rsquo;t unusual, contrary to some opinions. Examining these different regional approaches offers valuable insights for refining existing legislation and policies.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on domestic violence and the free movement of EU citizens is disgraceful.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 17:59:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-domestic-violence-and-the-free-movement-of-eu-citizens-is-disgraceful/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU freedom of movement laws don&amp;rsquo;t directly apply to non-EU citizens. Instead, they gain rights through family ties with EU citizens. This poses a problem in domestic violence situations where the abuser is an EU citizen and the victim is not. Leaving the abuser could lead to expulsion, forcing victims to choose between their safety and remaining in the country, potentially separated from their children.
EU law attempts to mitigate this risk.</description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?</description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements.</description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's 'emergency brake' preserving or abolishing the free movement of people?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 03:21:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-emergency-brake-preserving-or-abolishing-the-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Steve Peers
If British pro-Europeans could travel back in time, their priority should be returning to 2004. They should focus all efforts on persuading the then-British government to reconsider granting immediate free movement of workers from new EU member states. While economically advantageous, this decision has severely damaged public support for EU membership in the UK, as well as for the UK Labour Party.
Today, the free movement of people is often framed as a fundamental flaw within the EU, prompting calls for the UK to either leave or renegotiate its terms.</description></item><item><title>Unemployed EU citizens may benefit from the CJEU's decision, potentially complicating David Cameron's renegotiation strategy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unemployed-eu-citizens-may-benefit-from-the-cjeu-s-decision-potentially-complicating-david-cameron-s-renegotiation-strategy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ability of EU citizens to move freely between Member States, often referred to as ‘immigration,’ has sparked significant political debate, particularly in the UK. Access to benefits for these individuals remains a point of contention. The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has an opportunity to provide clarity on key aspects of this issue in the upcoming case of Alimanovic. An Advocate-General recently issued a non-binding opinion on this case.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule.</description></item></channel></rss>