<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosted Exchange on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-exchange/</link><description>Recent content in Hosted Exchange on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-exchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Exchange Email Service Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 15:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-exchange-email-service-advantages/</guid><description>POP3 email, while widely used by both businesses and individuals, has limitations that might make you reconsider your email service. While convenient, its client-server model, where emails are downloaded to your device, poses risks such as data loss and limited accessibility.
What exactly is POP3? It stands for Post Office Protocol, an internet standard for retrieving emails from a server to a client, like Microsoft Outlook or Mac Mail, installed on your computer.</description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth.</description></item></channel></rss>