<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Upload on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/upload/</link><description>Recent content in Upload on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/upload/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>