<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Waste on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-waste/</link><description>Recent content in E-Waste on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:36:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-waste/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recycle Your Cell Phone To Save A Gorilla</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</guid><description>Recycling old cell phones is beneficial for many reasons, with one significant reason being the protection of the Eastern Lowland Mountain Gorilla in the Democratic Republic of Congo.
You might wonder how cell phone usage impacts gorillas in Africa. The answer lies in the interconnected nature of our ecosystem. Cell phones contain various electronic components, including tantalum capacitors. Tantalum, a scarce and valuable metal, enables the miniaturization of capacitors, making them suitable for slim cell phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There’s $$$ In E-Waste</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 06:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</guid><description>Imagine tossing a $100 bill in the trash. That&amp;rsquo;s essentially what&amp;rsquo;s happening when we discard old electronics, or e-waste. While it might not be actual cash, these devices hold significant monetary and material value that often gets overlooked.
E-waste isn&amp;rsquo;t a new issue. It&amp;rsquo;s been accumulating since the days of bulky radios and TVs. However, the sheer volume of discarded electronics has skyrocketed due to rapid technological advancements and shorter product lifecycles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-s-in-e-waste/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Don’t Be Part Of The Impending Worldwide E-Waste Crisis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common knowledge that discarding old electronics with regular trash is inappropriate. Many stores provide drop-off boxes for unwanted electronics like phones and batteries, and communities often organize special recycling events. Selling old electronics is also a viable option. Why then is the United Nations issuing warnings about an impending e-waste crisis?
This looming threat stems from the rapid development in nations like China, India, Africa, and Latin America, coupled with existing patterns in developed nations like the U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>