<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Antivirus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/antivirus/</link><description>Recent content in Antivirus on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/antivirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>INTERPOL warns against Simda, urges PC owners to conduct scans on their devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:41:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/</guid><description>A global operation based out of INTERPOL&amp;rsquo;s Global Complex for Innovation in Singapore recently disrupted the Simda botnet, which is estimated to have compromised over 770,000 computers globally. Cybercriminals used Simda to gain unauthorized access to computers, enabling them to steal sensitive data like banking credentials and spread additional malicious software.
Simda, active over several years, had become increasingly sophisticated. New, harder-to-detect versions were being created and disseminated every few hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/interpol-warns-against-simda-urges-pc-owners-to-conduct-scans-on-their-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The launch of ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9 has been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</guid><description>ESET, a global cybersecurity company, has launched ESET Smart Security 9 and ESET NOD32 Antivirus 9. These releases feature a redesigned user interface and enhanced security features.
Parvinder Walia, ESET&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific Sales and Marketing Director, highlighted the Asia-Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s rapid growth in internet and mobile usage, leading to increased adoption of online and mobile banking. He emphasized that the new banking and payment protection in ESET Smart Security 9 will allow customers to conduct secure financial transactions online...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-launch-of-eset-smart-security-9-and-eset-nod32-antivirus-9-has-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>