<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beocord on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beocord/</link><description>Recent content in Beocord on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beocord/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): Removing the Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-removing-the-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Note: This post documents an outdated method. There&amp;rsquo;s a simpler way to remove the drive that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve lifting the Pre-Amplifier board or disconnecting the solenoid linkage. See my later post for the updated procedure.
Following advice from &amp;lsquo;chartz&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;sonavor&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org (link to thread), I began replacing the belts in my Beocord 5000 (4716), which had become loose and stretched over time.
The first step is removing the drive mechanism.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Polishing the Plexiglass Cover</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-the-plexiglass-cover/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-the-plexiglass-cover/</guid><description>The refurbishment of my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) is nearly complete. I polished the plexiglass cover today, using the method described previously, and am pleased with the results. The attached photo shows the outcome, with the protective tape still in place on the back portion of the panel.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Slow Rewinding, Inconsistent Pause Function and Auto Stop</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-slow-rewinding-inconsistent-pause-function-and-auto-stop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-slow-rewinding-inconsistent-pause-function-and-auto-stop/</guid><description>After reinstalling the drive unit into the Beocord 5000 (4715), I began testing. Initial impressions were positive, with fast forward, rewind, play, and stop functions all working. However, the Auto Stop function would cease working after a few minutes. The tape would reach the end, but the drive mechanism would continue running, potentially harming the motor. The only solution was to turn off the deck for an hour to reset the function.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Installing Rebuilt Rubber Pinch Rollers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 03:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-installing-rebuilt-rubber-pinch-rollers/</guid><description>Thorough testing of the Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape deck revealed an occasional issue where the leading capstan would cease to move the tape forward. This occurred under specific conditions, particularly when humidity hovered around 60% and room temperature dipped below 65°F. As a result, the supply capstan would continue to push the tape forward, causing it to slip out of place between the erase head and the supply pinch roller. Fortunately, the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s auto-stop function activated quickly enough to prevent damage to the tape.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Extraction of Drive Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 12:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-extraction-of-drive-mechanism/</guid><description>Having restored a Beocord 5000 before, I&amp;rsquo;ve refined the process of removing the tape mechanism, simplifying the steps from my previous post and video.
I began by removing the plexiglass cover for polishing, which provided better access to the tape mechanism. To prepare for a full recap, I also lifted the preamplifier and radio amplifier boards. The photo shows the unit opened up:
&amp;lsquo;Chartz&amp;rsquo; from Beoworld.org suggested leaving the solenoid in place during removal, which led me to realize that even loosening the solenoid fixture is unnecessary.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Fader Fixed and Putting it Back Together</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-fader-fixed-and-putting-it-back-together/</guid><description>I examined the fader on my Beocord 5000 (4715) tape deck and discovered significant corrosion on the Fade In and Fade Out button contacts, preventing them from making a connection. Using DeoxIT D100 applied to a strip of paper, I cleaned the contact pads while pressing the buttons. This successfully removed the corrosion, evidenced by black streaks on the paper. I repeated this process on the remaining buttons, restoring the deck&amp;rsquo;s responsiveness to a like-new condition.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating Recording Current and Bias</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-recording-current-and-bias/</guid><description>Pleased with the seemingly functional Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) tape mechanism, an initial test recording was conducted using a waveform generator. Playback revealed a 3 dB channel imbalance on the Peak Program Meter (PPM), indicating a calibration issue. This was unsurprising given the deck&amp;rsquo;s age and highlighted the fortunate performance of a previously rebuilt Beocord 5000 in a Beolab 6000 setup, which operated well without calibration. To establish a solid calibration baseline, a reliable frequency response measurement was deemed essential.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): First Recordings!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-first-recordings-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-first-recordings-/</guid><description>I connected my Beocord 5000 tape deck to my Beomaster 6000 receiver for testing. Using a Beogram 4004 turntable, I recorded a track from a 1970s Miles Davis record onto a TDK SA 90 cassette. Everything worked perfectly! The Beocord performed flawlessly, recording and playing back the track with excellent quality. The sound was almost identical to the source material, with just a touch more background noise (even with Dolby noise reduction enabled).</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Replacing the Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-replacing-the-belts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 04:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-replacing-the-belts/</guid><description>I obtained replacement belts for my Beocord 5000 from &amp;lsquo;Dillen&amp;rsquo; on Beoworld.org, allowing me to resume my work on the unit. Replacing the belts is a straightforward process, but it demands patience because the drive mechanism requires significant disassembly. The service manual only explains how to access the top belts, not the bottom ones. However, a Beoworld.org thread provided valuable insights and cautions, including a story about a broken PCB #3 (&amp;ldquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rdquo;) resulting from improper belt installation.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Polishing of Plexiglass Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-of-plexiglass-panel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 01:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-polishing-of-plexiglass-panel/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring another Beocord 5000 (4715/4716) cassette deck, inspired by the resurgence of cassette tapes. It reminds me of the days when creating mixtapes was a way to express affection, unlike simply sharing Spotify playlists today.
I decided to practice polishing a spare Beocord 5000 panel before working on the one for my restoration project. I was concerned about the coating on these plexiglass panels, but it seems like it was only there to enhance shine without affecting the color.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Calibrating the Peak Program Meters (VU Meters)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 07:54:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-calibrating-the-peak-program-meters-vu-meters-/</guid><description>After reassembling and successfully testing a Beocord 5000 tape deck, I decided to calibrate its Peak Program Meters (PPMs) according to the service manual.
Instead of directly inputting a 300 Hz signal into the Dolby B ICs as the manual suggested, I opted to feed a 25 mV, 300 Hz signal into the Beocord&amp;rsquo;s inputs while in record mode (paused). Using a multimeter, I adjusted the recording levels to achieve the specified 740 mV RMS output at the Dolby B ICs (pin 7), allowing for the calibration of the PPMs&amp;rsquo; 0 dB level.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4716/4715): First Contact</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-first-contact/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 10:37:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47164715-first-contact/</guid><description>After a couple of evenings with the Beomaster 6000, my curiosity led me to the non-working Beocord 5000 (4716). The design is quite impressive, especially the electronic VU meters that use seven incandescent light bulbs each. This cutting-edge technology from the past is incredible! The attention to detail is remarkable.
Here are some pictures:
Plexiglass cover removed:
Notice the two red tabs above the level knobs, they display the recording level!</description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Exchanging the Belts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 12:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-exchanging-the-belts/</guid><description>After removing the tape mechanism from the Beocord 5000 (4715) for rebuilding, I replaced the old, worn-out belts. My process was largely based on the one shown in my YouTube video.
However, I made one key improvement. I learned that the eject lever&amp;rsquo;s alignment with the tape mechanism is vital for the eject key to function correctly after reassembly. Previously, I had only marked the position of part #256 (&amp;ldquo;lever&amp;rdquo;) with a pencil, leading to time-consuming readjustments.</description></item></channel></rss>