<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cellular Carriers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-carriers/</link><description>Recent content in Cellular Carriers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 01:06:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cellular-carriers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>So Many Free Phones Online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 01:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-free-phones-online/</guid><description>After a couple of years, your old phone probably looks outdated. Its functionality likely pales compared to the latest models, even if you&amp;rsquo;ve kept it in pristine condition. While you might be dreaming of upgrading, don&amp;rsquo;t assume those high-tech phones are out of your price range. You can get amazing deals, even free phones, from resources like Cell Phone Plan Finder.
A quick glance at the deals available through Cell Phone Plan Finder reveals a surprising number of top-tier phones are available for free with a new service plan.</description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part I</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-i/</guid><description>The recent collapse of the AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile merger, while seemingly a win for consumers against a potential monopoly, wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly about market control. Even if the merger succeeded, Verizon and Sprint would still offer competition. The real issue was bandwidth.
The evidence is clear: immediately after the deal failed, AT&amp;amp;T purchased $1.9 billion in spectrum from Qualcomm with FCC approval, while Verizon, after acquiring $3.6 billion worth of spectrum from Comcast and Time Warner Cable, also bought $315 million of spectrum from Cox.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2.</description></item><item><title>Is Mobility Killing Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mobility-killing-your-company/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 17:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mobility-killing-your-company/</guid><description>Initially, only a few executives used company cell phones, which made sense for accessibility. However, this practice expanded to various levels of management, ultimately leading to company-issued smartphones for everyone. While this enhanced communication and response time, it resulted in a complex network of individual contracts and bills due to a phased implementation. Consequently, managing numerous contracts and potentially unused devices became a challenge.
Instead of handling this burden, businesses can outsource wireless cost control to specialized companies.</description></item></channel></rss>