<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GigE Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in GigE Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Domination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</guid><description>In the near future, Ethernet may become the sole networking standard.
Previously, local networking involved choices like Token Bus or Token Ring. Today, almost every Network Interface Card (NIC) uses Ethernet, with speeds ranging from 10 to 1,000 Mbps, and 10 Gbps becoming increasingly affordable. Local Area Networks (LANs) predominantly use switched Ethernet over twisted pair copper wiring with RJ-45 connectors, although fiber optics is becoming a competitor.
Cost drives this standardization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why The WAN Lags The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 18:04:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</guid><description>Corporate networks are often set up to ensure smooth data flow within the organization (LAN), but the real bottleneck often lies in the connection to the outside world (WAN).
LANs typically use Ethernet standards with speeds of 10/100/1000 Mbps, while WAN connections like T1 or DS3 lines operate at much slower speeds (1.5 Mbps to 45 Mbps). This disparity in speed results in significant slowdowns when transferring files outside the organization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-wan-lags-the-lan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>