<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Workplace on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workplace/</link><description>Recent content in Workplace on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/workplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encouraging an open workplace culture: the role of leaders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</guid><description>Open communication and strong relationships are essential for a thriving workplace. UK-based sales and marketing firm Forrest Bell emphasizes that openness involves respectful and constructive dialogue about needs, opinions, and concerns. It also means actively listening to and considering new ideas, questions, and feedback.
Forrest Bell believes that a culture of openness fosters trust and facilitates collaboration on projects. It also promotes transparency and streamlines processes in dynamic business environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHH Healthcare, NUS, Otis, and PSA set new standards for leadership and workplace mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</guid><description>WorkWell Leaders (WWL), a Singapore-based non-profit focused on workplace wellbeing and mental health, has revealed the winners of the WorkWell Leaders Awards 2024. These awards acknowledge exemplary practices in promoting positive change within workplaces. WWL emphasized that these awards are unique in their recognition of specific elements of workplace wellbeing that drive business results, as well as leadership behaviors that foster cultural transformation within organizations.
Anthea Ong, Founder and Chairperson of WorkWell Leaders, stressed the importance of addressing mental health proactively in the workplace, stating, &amp;ldquo;With 70% of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s population employed and spending a significant portion of their day at work, workplaces must serve as catalysts to support employees and their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ERC has opened a co-working space in multiple cities across Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</guid><description>The University Mentorship program will connect lecturers with the BIG Work community to offer guidance. Users can utilize ERC&amp;rsquo;s expertise in various business areas and schedule consultations with program managers and resource advisors Guests at the BIG Hotel, catering to international and startup business travelers, will have early access to new hospitality-related products and services for research. Entrepreneur Resource Centre Holdings (ERC) has launched BIG Work, a new co-working space with locations in Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colliers presents the concept of the Internet of the Workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 18:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/</guid><description>Colliers International, a leading global real estate services firm, has published a new report titled &amp;ldquo;Flex, Core and the Cloud: A Blueprint for the Future Asia Pacific Workplace.&amp;rdquo; The report examines how businesses, particularly those in technology, financial services, and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG), are incorporating cloud technology into their operations and the effects this has on employee productivity and well-being.
The report highlights that cloud computing, driven by the Internet of Things (IoT), is creating new opportunities for businesses in the Asia Pacific region to change how and where their employees work...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colliers-presents-the-concept-of-the-internet-of-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Desk Just Moved To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 10:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The 20th century saw a significant shift in employment, moving from farm work to factory jobs and finally to office positions. Now, the 21st century is experiencing another major change as workplaces transition from offices to the cloud.
The Cloud is Here and Now
Contrary to the idea of the cloud being a distant concept, it has become an integral part of our present reality. Nearly everything we do has or will soon have a cloud connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra discusses the obstacles of maintaining productivity in a workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</guid><description>Source: Jabra research report.
According to audio and communications company Jabra, modern workplaces face difficulties in fostering productivity due to common hurdles employees experience daily. These include distractions, poorly structured meetings, and technology that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as intended.
Jabra&amp;rsquo;s 2015 research report, Productivity at the Office – Challenges, highlights that while companies invest in resources and tools to help office workers collaborate and focus, employees still encounter obstacles. These include constant distractions, unproductive meetings, and challenges utilizing technology meant to enhance their output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Childcare centers are emerging in Chinese workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</guid><description>Government policy changes are fueling the growth of the preschool or childcare market in China. Technavio forecasts a CAGR exceeding 6% for this market between 2016 and 2020. This growth is largely attributed to recent policy adjustments, notably the 2015 amendment to the one-child policy, now permitting couples to have two children. This shift aims to balance population development and, coupled with rising disposable incomes among middle-class families, is driving increased preschool enrollment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New e-book series examines generational disparities in the workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>The INSEAD Emerging Markets Institute collaborated with employer branding specialist Universum, Singapore-based think tank The HEAD Foundation, and MIT Leadership Centre to release Brave New Workplace, the first in a series of e-books called Generations Series.
As companies aim to create optimal work environments and policies for multigenerational workforces, they may find generational differences to be a significant factor, though this is not always the case. Brave New Workplace examines how Gen X, Gen Y, and Gen Z are transforming the nature of work and workplace culture by looking at their behaviors and attitudes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-e-book-series-examines-generational-disparities-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>