<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access to Environmental Information on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-environmental-information/</link><description>Recent content in Access to Environmental Information on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-environmental-information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War.</description></item></channel></rss>