<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hosted VoIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-voip/</link><description>Recent content in Hosted VoIP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hosted-voip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>The Ubiquitous Cloud of 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</guid><description>The year 2012 brings a shift in the business landscape, not towards a downturn, but rather a move towards cloud computing. This change benefits businesses facing uncertainty by offering flexibility and adaptability. Instead of struggling to predict the future, businesses can embrace the cloud and adjust their strategies as needed.
The current business environment is already in flux. While some businesses are stagnant, others experience constant change. This unpredictability leaves many longing for a more stable past.</description></item><item><title>Take a Conference, Save the Carbon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</guid><description>While conference calls have been a common business tool, they are often reserved for specific projects or occasional use. Similarly, web conferencing, its internet-based counterpart, allows for incorporating visuals like charts and graphs but remains irregularly utilized. So, when does integrating conferencing into daily operations become a more practical approach rather than just another tool?
Several factors suggest a potential shift. Firstly, technological advancements have made it possible. Computers and speakerphones are commonplace, with many conference rooms equipped with internet access and large display screens or projectors.</description></item><item><title>10x10 Mbps Ethernet Providers in Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:25:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10x10-mbps-ethernet-providers-in-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many believe that 10 Mbps Ethernet is replacing traditional T1 lines, and for good reason. This article will explore why that is, how this technology works, and the steps to upgrade.
Businesses have relied on T1 lines for decades due to their high reliability, guaranteed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps, and symmetrical upload and download speeds. Prices have also decreased over time, and availability is now widespread.
The main drawback of T1 lines is their limited bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Why NOT to Buy a New PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</guid><description>Traditionally, businesses dealing with outdated or inadequate phone systems have opted for a complete replacement, known as a “forklift upgrade.” While this provided enhanced performance and capacity, like a brand new car, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling alternative in today&amp;rsquo;s world: hosted PBX solutions.
Rather than investing heavily in another physical PBX system, consider a hosted PBX, also referred to as Hosted VoIP or PBX in the cloud. This service eliminates the need for a physical PBX on your premises.</description></item><item><title>A New Cloud In IT Managed Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:32:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-cloud-in-it-managed-services/</guid><description>Many businesses are seriously considering migrating their IT infrastructure to cloud-based managed solutions. The key question then becomes: which cloud platform is the right fit? One compelling option is the &amp;ldquo;new cloud.&amp;rdquo;
NewCloud Networks, a managed service provider established in 1988, offers comprehensive solutions ranging from voice and data services for small businesses to intricate national and international networking solutions.
NewCloud differentiates itself by providing bespoke solutions tailored to specific client needs, rather than forcing a one-size-fits-all approach.</description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs.</description></item><item><title>Call Center Contact Center Phone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-center-contact-center-phone-service/</guid><description>Call centers depend heavily on phone services, particularly long-distance and toll-free numbers. To determine the most effective and affordable options for your call center, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available choices.
Traditional phone systems rely on basic business phone lines, also known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service). Despite their age, analog phone lines remain reliable, offering clear audio without the delays common in digital systems.
While analog lines were initially designed for single-line phones, key systems allow multiple lines on a single phone, enabling users to select which line to answer.</description></item><item><title>What is Cloud Computing For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-cloud-computing-for-business/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is gaining popularity, but what does it mean for businesses beyond giants like Amazon and Google? Essentially, the cloud isn&amp;rsquo;t a new invention. It&amp;rsquo;s a way of structuring technology, similar to the public telephone system, where a central provider manages the complex infrastructure (&amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo;), and users access services through simple devices (&amp;ldquo;thin clients&amp;rdquo;).
This centralized system, known as multi-tenancy, allows numerous users to access resources seemingly simultaneously while remaining isolated.</description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner.</description></item></channel></rss>