<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Benefits on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benefits/</link><description>Recent content in Benefits on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/benefits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it possible to deport and prohibit unemployed EU citizens from returning?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 18:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Germany&amp;rsquo;s recent exploration of expelling unemployed EU citizens has sparked interest among critics of EU free movement in the UK. As this topic gains traction, it&amp;rsquo;s timely to clarify the circumstances under which EU citizens can be expelled.
While the EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Directive empowers Member States to expel citizens for reasons related to public policy, security, or health, it explicitly prohibits using these grounds for economic reasons. Consequently, the rules for expelling unemployed EU citizens lie elsewhere within the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-deport-and-prohibit-unemployed-eu-citizens-from-returning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the UK's limitation on EU workers' eligibility for benefits lawful - and if not, should it be?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK government recently established a new income requirement for EU citizens from other Member States to be classified as &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and access certain benefits. This raises the question of whether these rules align with EU law regarding the free movement of workers and if modifications are necessary.
Under these regulations, EU citizens must earn a minimum of £150 weekly for at least three months to be considered &amp;ldquo;workers&amp;rdquo; and qualify for benefits such as child benefit, child tax credit, job-seekers&amp;rsquo; allowance, and housing benefit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-limitation-on-eu-workers-eligibility-for-benefits-lawful-and-if-not-should-it-be/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Cameron's speech at Chatham House signaling a strong push for the renegotiation of the UK's EU membership?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 22:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</guid><description>Steve Peers
David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s recent speech at Chatham House provided more specifics about the UK&amp;rsquo;s demands for renegotiating its EU membership. These demands were summarized in a letter from Cameron to European Council President Donald Tusk.
Cameron also outlined two planned changes to UK law regarding the EU Charter of Rights and potentially the role of UK courts in reviewing EU court decisions. As these changes pertain to domestic law, they don&amp;rsquo;t require negotiation with other Member States unless they potentially violate EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-cameron-s-speech-at-chatham-house-signaling-a-strong-push-for-the-renegotiation-of-the-uk-s-eu-membership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Robert Half suggests diversifying incentives in order to retain talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 08:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</guid><description>A significant portion of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce prioritizes work-life balance over higher salaries, according to a recent study.
The Robert Half 2017 Salary Guide highlights that 69% of Singaporean employees are driven by more than just monetary compensation. The study reveals that nearly half (43%) would accept lower pay for flexible work hours, while over a third (37%) would choose the ability to work remotely over a pay raise.
Non-financial benefits are highly valued by Singaporean workers, with 28% willing to trade a portion of their salary for increased medical benefits and 20% favoring more vacation time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-half-suggests-diversifying-incentives-in-order-to-retain-talent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disregard the children! CJEU supports automatic exclusions from family benefits in Case C-308/14 Commission v UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</guid><description>Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School The Court of Justice is increasingly distancing itself from the social welfare systems of Member States. Although the Court once suggested that citizenship is paramount and forms the basis for financial solidarity, guaranteeing some support from a host state for EU citizens facing temporary hardship, this stance is changing.
With the Court moving away from the concept of citizenship, the idea of a reasonable burden may be disappearing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>