<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Remote Data Centers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-data-centers/</link><description>Recent content in Remote Data Centers on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/remote-data-centers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Earth to Cloud Network Security Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</guid><description>Information technology specialists understand the need for secure corporate networks, including enterprise-level security for cloud computing services in remote data centers. However, maintaining security across the entire network, especially when extending the LAN remotely, poses a significant challenge.
Level 3 Communications offers a solution with its “Earth to Cloud” comprehensive global security suite. This multi-layered protection strategy aims to secure every aspect of the network from potential threats.
A key factor in this approach is having a single provider for both connectivity and network security, a role Level 3 is well-equipped to fill.</description></item></channel></rss>