<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Association Agreeements on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/association-agreeements/</link><description>Recent content in Association Agreeements on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/association-agreeements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Union a cause worth sacrificing for? Contemplating the future of Ukraine and the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-union-a-cause-worth-sacrificing-for-contemplating-the-future-of-ukraine-and-the-eu/</guid><description>There were many reasons to criticize the Yanukovych government in Ukraine, but the protests that led to its downfall were sparked by Yanukovych&amp;rsquo;s refusal to sign an agreement with the European Union. This strong desire for EU membership among some Ukrainians raises important questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s future.
The first steps after the planned elections would be straightforward. A pro-European government would likely ratify the association agreement, which connects Ukraine to EU law more closely than previous agreements.</description></item><item><title>What impact will the Dutch referendum on the EU/Ukraine association agreement have?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-impact-will-the-dutch-referendum-on-the-eu-ukraine-association-agreement-have/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Brkan and Alexander Hoogenboom
On April 6, 2016, Dutch voters rejected the EU-Ukraine association agreement. The vote, with 61.1 percent voting against the agreement, was not unexpected based on recent polling. While voter turnout barely passed the 30 percent minimum, the outcome itself delivers a resounding &amp;ldquo;no.&amp;rdquo;
The EU has established numerous association agreements with countries like Algeria, Tunisia, Morocco, Israel, Egypt, Chile, Kosovo, and others. So why was a referendum held specifically for Ukraine?</description></item></channel></rss>