<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephony/</link><description>Recent content in Telephony on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls.</description></item><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website.</description></item><item><title>Buy Convergence By The Byte</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</guid><description>XO Communications is revolutionizing telecommunications by offering IP Network services priced by bandwidth usage instead of traditional lines or channels. This shift to an IP-based network and the use of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for telephone trunking are rendering traditional telephony services obsolete. By utilizing a packet-switched network and transmitting everything in packet protocol, voice, and data traffic can easily share a single circuit.
The concept of convergence, using one network for voice, video, and data, has gained traction with IT departments aiming to simplify network management and executives seeking cost reductions.</description></item><item><title>TalkSwitch Supports both VoIP and Legacy PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</guid><description>Choosing between a traditional phone system (analog or digital TDM PBX) and a newer VoIP system can be tough. TalkSwitch offers a solution by supporting both technologies.
For example, the TalkSwitch 244vs desktop PBX handles 2 incoming lines, 4 extensions for analog phones, and features like voicemail and music on hold. It also supports 10 remote extensions, allowing cell phones, home phones, and phones on other systems to connect by dialing a 3-digit extension.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades.</description></item><item><title>Managed IP Networks Enable Voice and Data Convergence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 04:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-networks-enable-voice-and-data-convergence/</guid><description>Businesses have been looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing service, and combining their computer and telephone networks into a single, multi-functional LAN that can connect to the public Internet and phone network seems like a good way to do it. Ideally, this means one network, one connection per desk, and one support team. However, the reality isn&amp;rsquo;t always so simple.
The reason for this is that computers and telephones use networks in very different ways.</description></item><item><title>Free International Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</guid><description>During tough economic times, everyone appreciates a good deal, especially free offers. Phone Power is offering free international calls through 2008 to promote its competitive business and residential VoIP services. This is a great opportunity for anyone who makes a lot of international calls. Even after the promotion ends, Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s rates remain very affordable.
This holiday season, you can call landlines in the following countries for free: United Kingdom (44), Spain (34), Ireland (353), Israel (972), Germany (49), Singapore (65), France (33), Denmark (45), Greece (30), Italy (39), and China (86).</description></item><item><title>Free Help On Your Telecom Needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 13:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/</guid><description>Want free, top-notch tech support for your phone and computer networks? No cost now or ever, even with today&amp;rsquo;s tight budgets.
Sounds too good to be true? It&amp;rsquo;s not. This is a telecom brokerage service with a team of experts in telephony, computer networking, international networks, wireless solutions, and more. They&amp;rsquo;re ready to help – just tell them what you need.
But how is this free? A third party – the service providers – foots the bill.</description></item><item><title>USA Digital Offers Comprehensive Call Center Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usa-digital-offers-comprehensive-call-center-services/</guid><description>Companies with call centers need reliable and affordable telecommunication services. USA Digital specializes in providing these services, offering high-performance options that won&amp;rsquo;t break the bank.
Established in 1991, USA Digital is a trusted provider with a proven track record of growth and customer satisfaction. Their success stems from a dedication to excellent customer service and a diverse range of voice and data solutions.
USA Digital understands the unique needs of call centers.</description></item><item><title>We're Looking For Successful IT Consultants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</guid><description>Are you an experienced IT professional looking to expand your consulting business? If you specialize in voice and data network design, implementation, and troubleshooting, and perhaps even hold certifications with equipment vendors, we have an opportunity for you.
We&amp;rsquo;re offering a chance to grow your business with minimal effort. Gain access to new clients in your area and expand your service offerings without any upfront costs or extensive training. This is a simple way to boost your existing business.</description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Telephone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-telephone-lines/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple phone lines might be leaving money on the table if they haven&amp;rsquo;t explored T-1 digital phone lines. Even businesses already using T1 service might be unaware of potential savings from newer options.
Digital telephony emerged in the 1950s as phone companies sought efficient ways to handle large call volumes. Analog phone lines carried a single conversation per wire pair. While analog multiplexing (carrier telephony) allowed multiple calls on a single wire pair, it suffered from quality issues over long distances.</description></item><item><title>Know the Lingo to Save Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 13:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/know-the-lingo-to-save-money/</guid><description>To succeed with technology, you need to understand the terminology. This is especially true for VoIP telephony, where &amp;ldquo;Lingo&amp;rdquo; can refer to both the industry jargon and a specific company.
Lingo, the company, offers broadband phone services for residential and business users. These services provide significant cost savings compared to traditional landlines, especially for international calls from the US.
Residential plans include options like Chatter Box, Global Gabber, and Lingo Link, each with unique features and pricing.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential.</description></item><item><title>IP Phones Are In Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 23:32:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-phones-are-in-demand/</guid><description>While business use of Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) is booming, residential use is lagging significantly, according to a recent study. This raises the question: are consumers less open to adopting new communication technologies than businesses, or is there another reason for this discrepancy?
IP networks have been steadily replacing traditional phone lines for years, driven by both technological advancements and cost savings. Consumers are primarily drawn to VoIP because it allows them to make calls through their existing broadband internet connection, saving them money compared to traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series.</description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong.</description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX Enables New Telephone Apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</guid><description>Just like apps revolutionized smartphones, they are now transforming desktop and laptop experiences, moving away from traditional software. And yes, this wave of innovation has reached phone systems too. AireSpring is leading the way with a suite of apps designed for their AirePBX cloud-hosted system.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the possibilities. CommPortal acts as your messaging hub, allowing you to manage voicemail, activate a one-number service for seamless device switching, prioritize callers, and utilize click-to-dial functionality.</description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>QT Talk is Both VoIP and Dial-Around</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</guid><description>Many people are interested in VoIP phone service because of its features and affordability, but they also want the freedom of mobile calling. QT Talk offers a solution that combines the advantages of VoIP with the flexibility of cellular service.
QT Talk provides a feature-rich VoIP service, including their popular North America Plus plan. For a low monthly fee, users enjoy unlimited calls to the U.S., Canada, and Puerto Rico, along with a reduced rate to select international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Business VoIP Solution Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about switching your business phone system from the traditional analog or PBX setup to VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), it&amp;rsquo;s wise to explore the various business VoIP options available before making a complete overhaul. The best choice for you depends on your specific needs and, by selecting wisely, you can maximize your telephony investment.
The main reasons to consider VoIP are cost savings, enhanced calling features, or a combination of both.</description></item><item><title>A Visual Guide To Enterprise VoIP Justification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</guid><description>Thank you to MegaPath Broadband Service Providers for this interesting infographic.
Is your company missing out on the advantages of enterprise VoIP technology, which can potentially reduce costs and increase productivity? A variety of on-site and hosted options are available to accommodate businesses of all sizes. Explore business VoIP solutions and pricing from MegaPath and other providers.</description></item></channel></rss>