<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RSBG4000UK on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rsbg4000uk/</link><description>Recent content in RSBG4000UK on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rsbg4000uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Neutrik Gold Plated DIN5 Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</guid><description>A common improvement for the Beogram 4000 is replacing the DIN5 plug with a gold-plated version. The older plugs, often corroded, benefit from the upgrade. This particular Beogram 4000 was no exception.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a comparison of the old plug and the new, gleaming Neutrik plug (Newark 27B4483):
The old plug was removed, and the cable was prepped for the new plug. Stripping the outer insulation to this length works well:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Arrives From UK! Solenoid Oscillates!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 13:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</guid><description>I recently acquired another Beogram 4000 from the UK. The unit is in fair shape; importantly, the MMC cartridge mount is undamaged and the sensor arm insert is present. The control panel for the cueing and tonearm lift detached during shipping, highlighting the wisdom of securing such parts. Thankfully, the seller had protected the turntable with a durable plastic sheet, preventing any damage. Reattaching the panel should be simple.
Internally, all parts appear to be present:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-arrives-from-uk-solenoid-oscillates-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Gap at the Carriage Servo Pulley Bearing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, significant longitudinal play was discovered in the threaded rod responsible for moving the carriage. This play resulted in a &amp;lsquo;clacking&amp;rsquo; noise whenever the carriage changed direction.
The issue was resolved by removing the servo pulley, damaged locking ring, and worn plastic washer. A new, thick 2-56 nylon washer, which fit snugly on the shaft, replaced the locking ring and washer. The locking ring became unnecessary as the pulley was secured with a setscrew...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-gap-at-the-carriage-servo-pulley-bearing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Platter, Cleaning the Panels and Installing a 3D Printed Guiding Washer for the Cabinet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:25:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</guid><description>I dedicated some time today to refining the appearance of the Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on. The first step involved adjusting the platter&amp;rsquo;s height and alignment within the aluminum panel. Achieving a centered and flush platter is crucial for the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s visual appeal. The platter was positioned too low upon arrival, even grazing the panel due to misalignment.
Therefore, I made adjustments to the main bearing and the chassis&amp;rsquo;s three suspension points to achieve the correct setup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-platter-cleaning-the-panels-and-installing-a-3d-printed-guiding-washer-for-the-cabinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of Hood Mounting Screw Springs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</guid><description>During my quest for the ideal Beogram 4000 turntable, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed that none of the early models possess the hood mounting screw springs found on the later Beogram 4002 and 4004. These springs make removing and attaching the hood significantly easier. After consulting the service manuals, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the Beogram 4000 was not designed with these springs. It seems B&amp;amp;O employed a continuous improvement approach, refining their designs over time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-hood-mounting-screw-springs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Tracking Sensor Incandescent Bulb with a Drop-In SMD LED Assembly and a Peek at the Opto-Resistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</guid><description>The tracking sensor bulb in my Beogram 4000 recently burned out. This was the fourth bulb to fail. I decided to use this opportunity to install my new SMD LED replacement assembly. This assembly uses efficient white LEDs at low power for longevity, likely exceeding 50 years. It also reduces the unit&amp;rsquo;s energy consumption by a few watts, lessening the load on the aging transformer. Details about the assembly and adjustments can be found in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-tracking-sensor-incandescent-bulb-with-a-drop-in-smd-led-assembly-and-a-peek-at-the-opto-resistors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Increasing Tonearm Lowering Delay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</guid><description>After installing a new hood on a Beogram 4000 turntable, the author noticed the tonearm descended too quickly. Adjusting the damper&amp;rsquo;s screw didn&amp;rsquo;t solve the problem, as the tonearm still dropped rapidly despite the damper slowing down.
Further inspection revealed the damper&amp;rsquo;s linkage was positioned very close to the damper plunger. This proximity meant the linkage moved immediately when the damper activated, even before the damper could build up enough vacuum to slow the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s descent effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-increasing-tonearm-lowering-delay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 01:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration involved replacing the motor phase capacitor and reservoir. I used a 3D-printed adapter I designed, which allows for secure mounting of modern, smaller capacitors in the original location using the factory bracket. This post provides a closer look at the replacement process and includes a comprehensive wiring diagram for the capacitors. This can be particularly helpful for those tackling this task for the first time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Aluminum Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all spring terminals in the switches, this Beogram 4000 received another upgrade: a replacement for the old, unstable plastic carriage pulley, now made from aluminum. The original pulley is shown below:
And here it is equipped with one of Nick&amp;rsquo;s well-crafted aluminum pulleys:
Contact me if you need a pulley for your Beogram; I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to connect you with Nick. These pulleys are compatible with the 4002 and 4004 models as well...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Grounding Switch That Allows to Connect System and Signal Grounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:15:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</guid><description>During my latest restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, I encountered a loud hum when playing records through my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s 4-channel phono input. The issue was resolved by connecting the signal and system grounds. Although the root cause of the hum remains unclear, I decided to install a switch to allow for easy toggling between the original separate grounding configuration and a direct connection between signal and system grounds at the turntable&amp;rsquo;s output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-that-allows-to-connect-system-and-signal-grounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of a Seized Solenoid to Tonearm Linkage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:07:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I got from the UK had a seized linkage connecting the solenoid mechanism and tonearm. To lubricate this linkage, I had to disassemble the sensor arm assembly and remove it. Further inspection showed that the linkage&amp;rsquo;s rotating pin was stuck and had detached from its press-fit socket within the sensor arm base. I&amp;rsquo;ve created a video illustrating the problem and the repair process:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Carriage Position Switches and Fixing a Bent Output Switch Contact Tab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000, a process known as &amp;ldquo;switch day&amp;rdquo; involves cleaning the contacts of the many open switches. While some recommend desoldering the switches for thorough cleaning, it&amp;rsquo;s generally sufficient to clean the contact areas directly. This minimizes the risk of damaging the delicate contact tabs.
Effective switch functionality hinges on clean contact points, not the overall appearance of the switch. The contact tabs should be straight and have adequate spring to ensure proper contact...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Zero Force Balancing and Tracking Force Calibration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:45:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring is almost ready for its initial test run. It&amp;rsquo;s time to fine-tune the zero force balance and set the appropriate tracking force. I documented this process in a video on my YouTube channel, featuring a Beogram 4002. You can find the video and my entire Beogram 4000 playlist through the provided links.
Let me share some observations from this specific Beogram 4000 restoration. The first stage involves achieving zero force balance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-zero-force-balancing-and-tracking-force-calibration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the AC Motor Voltage and Measuring the Voltage Differences Between the Phases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 19:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the AC motor requires precise adjustment. The service manual recommends setting the main phase voltage to 6V (RMS) and the frequency to 42.3 Hz for 33 RPM using an oscilloscope. To observe both motor phases, connect the oscilloscope probes across the phase capacitor.
Begin the adjustment by setting the 33 RPM trimmer on the control panel to its neutral position. This allows for fine-tuning the RPM offset potentiometer on the main PCB to achieve the target 42...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-ac-motor-voltage-and-measuring-the-voltage-differences-between-the-phases/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>