<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Browser on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/browser/</link><description>Recent content in Browser on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:24:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/browser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mozilla has launched Firefox Focus on Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</guid><description>Source: Mozilla. Mozilla launches Firefox Focus for Android.
Mozilla, a strong advocate for an open and accessible internet, has released Firefox Focus for Android devices. This launch caters to the increasing number of mobile users seeking enhanced online privacy.
Firefox Focus allows users to browse the internet without being tracked by advertisements, which are infamous for slowing down mobile browsing. This announcement comes six months after the successful iPhone and iPad launch in November.</description></item><item><title>WebRTC set to boost business productivity for browsers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/webrtc-set-to-boost-business-productivity-for-browsers/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably used a web browser like Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, or Safari on your phone or computer to visit websites.
Some companies believe browsers can be much more than tools for accessing websites; they think browsers can simplify our lives. Tata Communications suggests that incorporating the right features into browsers could significantly boost employee productivity.
&amp;ldquo;Despite some positive developments, most of us are still dealing with separate, disconnected communication platforms.</description></item></channel></rss>