<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resistance on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resistance/</link><description>Recent content in Resistance on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:19:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resistance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kinetika Xtreme is unveiling innovative workout technology designed to enhance fitness levels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</guid><description>Ghaneswaran Sukumaran holds a certification from Italy and is one of only two TechnoGym Master Trainers in Singapore. His wife, Santhi Haridass, is the other. As the owner of Kinetika Xtreme, a gym in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Turf City that specializes in movement-based functional training, Sukumaran expresses concern that many individuals join gyms without proper research and engage in exercises that may be detrimental in the long term.
&amp;ldquo;Many people equate weight loss with fat loss and believe that excessive jogging is the key to achieving a slim physique...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinetika-xtreme-is-unveiling-innovative-workout-technology-designed-to-enhance-fitness-levels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kérastase Résistance Thérapiste offers amazing results for hair that has been over-processed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
The Résistance line was launched by Kérastase in 1995 to provide women with superior hair care and repair solutions. Two decades later, the brand expanded with Résistance Thérapiste, specifically addressing the needs of over-processed hair.
Kérastase claims that this innovation, driven by a breakthrough discovery in hair structure, harnesses the power of an ancient plant and incorporates a novel sensory experience, allowing women to achieve complete renewal of damaged hair in just one use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/k-rastase-r-sistance-th-rapiste-offers-amazing-results-for-hair-that-has-been-over-processed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consuming a balanced amount of protein helps dieters maintain muscle mass at a slower rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</guid><description>Source: Nestlé.
Nestlé Research Center collaborated with global scientists and found that consistent protein intake throughout the day might reduce muscle loss during weight loss attempts.
Published in the American Journal of Physiology - Endocrinology and Metabolism, the study explored ways to promote weight loss in obese older men while preventing muscle loss. Muscle loss can hinder weight loss, decrease strength and functional capacity, and heighten the risk of disability and mortality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>