<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Huawei on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/huawei/</link><description>Recent content in Huawei on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 03:18:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/huawei/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore gets a sneak peek at the HUAWEI Mate 20 icon before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. The square icon at various malls in
Singapore.
People in Singapore were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through an unexpected display of an illuminated square icon projected onto buildings throughout the city over the weekend.
This symbolic imagery appeared on structures in various locations such as Raffles City, Bugis Junction, Bugis+, and Plaza Singapura.
This readily identifiable square represents the phone&amp;rsquo;s camera setup, which includes a Leica Triple Camera and flash seamlessly integrated into the back of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei assures users of phones and tablets that it will maintain support services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-assures-users-of-phones-and-tablets-that-it-will-maintain-support-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:10:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-assures-users-of-phones-and-tablets-that-it-will-maintain-support-services/</guid><description>A Reuters report revealed that Google is planning to cease business operations with Huawei concerning software, hardware, and services that are not open source. This decision stems from a US government order against Huawei. The impact of this decision is projected to affect only new Huawei phones, leaving existing phones unaffected.
Android confirmed via Twitter that Google Play and its associated security features will remain operational on current Huawei devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-assures-users-of-phones-and-tablets-that-it-will-maintain-support-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-assures-users-of-phones-and-tablets-that-it-will-maintain-support-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preorder the HUAWEI Matebook X Pro now in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</guid><description>Huawei Consumer Business Group is introducing the HUAWEI MateBook X Pro to its Singapore laptop collection. Until August 16, 2020, customers can take advantage of special gift packages worth S$250 to S$1,200 when they purchase select laptops.
The premium MateBook X Pro boasts a sleek, metallic design with a sandblasted finish. At just 14.6 mm thick and 1.33 kg, it prioritizes portability without sacrificing a truly immersive viewing experience.
Source: Huawei...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preorder-the-huawei-matebook-x-pro-now-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Huawei nova 2i is a mid-range phone with four cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</guid><description>Source: Huawei website. The nova 2i boasts a 5.9&amp;quot; FullView display.
Huawei has released the nova 2i, a 4G LTE mid-range phone designed for users who love taking selfies. This device stands out with its four cameras - two in the front and two on the back.
Clement Wong, Director of Global Product Marketing for the Huawei Consumer Business Group, highlighted that four cameras are uncommon in mid-range phones. He explained that Huawei aims to make its cutting-edge technology accessible to a wider customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Founders' Friday session in Singapore by Huawei will showcase Scott Bales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 00:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</guid><description>Source: Scott Bales website.
Huawei is launching a new networking series called Founders&amp;rsquo; Friday. The series aims to connect business leaders with professionals to exchange ideas, address difficulties, and develop innovative solutions for advancing the digital world.
The inaugural event, presented alongside the HUAWEI Mate 9, features prominent digital and innovation expert Scott Bales. He will discuss essential principles for fostering a culture of innovation within organizations. Bales, the Managing Director of Singapore-based Innovation Labs Asia, brings over a decade of global experience in innovation, thought leadership, implementation planning, and strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-founders-friday-session-in-singapore-by-huawei-will-showcase-scott-bales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI Mate 20 is receiving a warm welcome in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. Over one thousand people lined up at Causeway Point mall in Singapore for the HUAWEI Mate 20 series launch.
Huawei Consumer Business Group Singapore reported a queue of over a thousand people awaiting the launch of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series.
The first person in line, Kishore Lal, arrived at six in the morning and is a first-time Huawei user. He shared, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve read many positive reviews about Huawei smartphones and their camera quality, so I decided to try one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI Mate 10 Pro was first launched in Singapore, making it the first country in the world to introduce the device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</guid><description>Huawei recently launched its Mate 10 Series smartphones, including the Mate 10, Mate 10 Pro, and PORSCHE DESIGN Mate 10, in Singapore. The launch makes Singapore the first country globally to have the Mate 10 Pro available for purchase.
A key feature of these phones is the Kirin 970 AI chipset, which significantly boosts system response speed and ensures smoother performance. According to Cheng Jiangfei, Country Head of Huawei Singapore, Consumer Business Group, the company is committed to providing Singaporean customers with the latest and greatest technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei P9 and India Photo Project introduce Monochrome award in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</guid><description>Source: Instagram. Top Instagram posts for the contest hashtag #ipp_ma2016 at the time of writing.
Huawei, in partnership with the Instagram-based India Photo Project, has introduced the &amp;ldquo;Monochrome&amp;rdquo; award to commemorate World Photography Day on August 19th. This competition, running from August 20th to August 31st, aims to discover India&amp;rsquo;s top black and white Instagram photographer.
The judging panel comprises Sumit Dayal, recognized as CNN&amp;rsquo;s Indian Instagrammer of the Year in 2015, Tara Bedi, the first Instagram employee from India, Devika Daulet Singh, Director of PHOTOINK, a prominent photography gallery, and Neeraj Priyadarshini, the Photo Editor at the Indian Express...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei introduces new wireless speaker for audio playback</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-new-wireless-speaker-for-audio-playback/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 23:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-new-wireless-speaker-for-audio-playback/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group has introduced a range of new consumer products alongside their latest flagship P series smartphones, including a new wireless speaker, the HUAWEI Sound X.
Huawei claims their new HUAWEI Sound X, developed in partnership with Devialet, will revolutionize high-end audio. Devialet, known for its high-quality audio products, brings its expertise in delivering powerful and precise sound from a compact design. This partnership promises distortion-free audio even at high volumes and deep bass that resonates physically...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-new-wireless-speaker-for-audio-playback/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-new-wireless-speaker-for-audio-playback/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 Bluetooth earphones are now available in Singapore through Huawei's official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</guid><description>Huawei Singapore has introduced the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3, stereo Bluetooth earphones with a groundbreaking open-fit design that incorporates active noise cancellation.
Source: Huawei. Eager customers queue at SITEX to buy the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 on November 30, 2019.
As the new year approaches, Huawei is focused on creating a comprehensive product ecosystem in Singapore, allowing customers to experience seamless connectivity between their smartphones and other devices such as the new Huawei Watch GT 2 and Gentle Monster – Huawei Eyewear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei will be offering laptops for sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:43:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore customers can purchase the HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro starting May 30, 2019.
The HUAWEI P30 Pro in Amber Sunrise will be offered for models with 512 GB of storage.
The Huawei Consumer Business Group Singapore has revealed its plan to expand its product lineup in Singapore beyond smartphones and smartwatches to include laptops. This new laptop selection features the latest HUAWEI MateBook 13 and MateBook X Pro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-will-be-offering-laptops-for-sale-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Entries are now being accepted for the inaugural HUAWEI Film Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</guid><description>Filmmakers in the Asia Pacific region can win prizes for films made on Huawei smartphones.
The top prize includes $20,000 and a trip to Bangkok for the awards ceremony.
An event in Singapore on December 21 will showcase a film by local director Boris Boo.
Source: Huawei. Poster for the HFA.
Huawei has launched its first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), in the Asia Pacific region. The competition aims to encourage filmmakers and content creators to use Huawei smartphones to demonstrate their creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei introduces the cover shot-ready HUAWEI P10 and HUAWEI P10 PLUS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-the-cover-shot-ready-huawei-p10-and-huawei-p10-plus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 21:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-the-cover-shot-ready-huawei-p10-and-huawei-p10-plus/</guid><description>Huawei recently launched its P10 and P10 Plus smartphones in Singapore, emphasizing their advanced camera capabilities developed in partnership with Leica. The event showcased the phones&amp;rsquo; ability to &amp;ldquo;make every shot a cover shot,&amp;rdquo; highlighting features like the Leica dual-camera system and artistic portrait enhancements.
To illustrate the phones&amp;rsquo; capabilities, Huawei created an artistic studio atmosphere. Attendees could experience the phones firsthand and view a portrait gallery captured by renowned photographers using the P10 and P10 Plus...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-the-cover-shot-ready-huawei-p10-and-huawei-p10-plus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-introduces-the-cover-shot-ready-huawei-p10-and-huawei-p10-plus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have you ever witnessed the power of a Leica Triple Camera and a single flash?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</guid><description>On the evenings of October 19th and 20th, Singaporeans were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through a series of unannounced projections.
This recognizable design, featuring a square arrangement of three Leica cameras and a flash, was displayed on buildings throughout Singapore, including Tampines Mall, Bugis+, and Star Vista. This camera setup, found on the back of HUAWEI Mate 20 smartphones, uses a 12 MP main RGB lens, an 8 MP telephoto lens, and a 16 MP ultra-wide-angle lens, all from Leica, along with a flash...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Participate in the Singapore Mother's Day contest for a chance to win a Huawei P20 in Pink Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</guid><description>Source: Huawei Mobile Singapore
Facebook page. Watch the video
In Singapore, Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group is holding a contest in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day (May 13th), ending on May 24th.
To participate, Singaporean residents simply need to comment on the contest video found on the Huawei Mobile Singapore Facebook page. The comment should answer the question: &amp;ldquo;What lengths would your mother go to for you?&amp;rdquo; and include the hashtag #SeeMooore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI P30 completely sold out on its first day in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Huawei P30 Series launched in Singapore at VivoCity yesterday and quickly sold out, with the first people in line having arrived the night before to buy the newest model in Huawei&amp;rsquo;s photography-focused smartphone line.
The Huawei P30 Series has garnered attention since its global launch last week in France for its Leica Quad Camera, the first of its kind, which boasts cutting-edge zoom and low-light capabilities.
Yvelyn Tey, the first person in line, waited with her fiance to purchase the phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei joins Singaporeans in celebrating National Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 01:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/</guid><description>In honor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 55th birthday, Huawei collaborated with five local photographers: Bryan van der Beek, Don Lee, Junaidi Lim, Zipeng Lee, and Jovanne Amolat. These photographers used the HUAWEI P40 Series smartphones to capture the spirit of Singapore by showcasing unique perspectives on everyday scenes.
Fresh Perspectives of the Familiar
Through thoughtful composition and utilizing the depth of field capabilities of the HUAWEI P40 Series, these photos provide a fresh perspective on common sights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-joins-singaporeans-in-celebrating-national-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In February, the Pink Gold version of Huawei's Mate 10 Pro will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</guid><description>Huawei has added a new Pink Gold color option to its Mate 10 Pro lineup. However, it is a limited edition with only 1,000 sets available in Singapore.
The HUAWEI Mate 10 Pro features the world’s first AI chipset, the Kirin 970, and dual Leica SUMMILUX-H f1.6 lenses for exceptional image quality.
Here are some key features:
A 6-inch HUAWEI FullView OLED display. The intelligent Kirin 970 AI processor, capable of adapting and reacting to real-world scenarios instantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive outfits for My Omamori will be available to Huawei mobile gamers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. My Omamori offers perks for Huawei users.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s mobile services branch has teamed up with Original Workshop, the creators of the female-oriented game My Omamori, to give special prizes to mobile players.
Omamori means lucky charm in Japanese. In the game, an ancient warrior, Toki Mamoru, travels to the present to become the player’s guardian angel. Mamoru, who is voiced by Japanese voice actor Yuki Ono, was developed by Taiwanese novelist Deer Li...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei smartphones in Singapore are now receiving the EMUI 9.1 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 06:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group started releasing its newest software update, EMUI 9.1, in Singapore on June 27th. This version is based on Android 9.0 Pie.
The update will be available in stages, beginning with the Mate 20 Series in late June. Following that, the P20 Series and Nova 3 Series will get the update in July, and finally, models like the Mate RS, P10, and P10 Plus will receive it in August...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei is advancing while other smartphone vendors are trying to catch up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s consumer division introduces the Mate 20 smartphone series, emphasizing a blend of aesthetics and innovation. This lineup offers various sizes and models, including the Mate 20, Mate 20 Pro, Mate 20 X, and the Porsche Design Mate 20 RS. Richard Yu, CEO of Huawei Consumer Business Group, highlights the series&amp;rsquo; role as a digital companion, enhancing users&amp;rsquo; lives through advanced technology.
Design The Mate 20 series prioritizes comfortable one-hand use, with nature-inspired design elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei has released the schedule for the EMUI10 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</guid><description>Huawei has released the global update schedule for EMUI 10. This latest version features an updated interface, a &amp;ldquo;Dark Mode&amp;rdquo; setting, performance and security improvements, and &amp;ldquo;Multi-screen Collaboration&amp;rdquo; which allows Huawei PCs and Android devices to seamlessly connect.
Starting this month, users with the HUAWEI P30 Pro, HUAWEI P30, HUAWEI Mate 20 Pro, HUAWEI Mate 20, HUAWEI Mate 20 X (4G) and HUAWEI nova 5T will get push notifications to install the EMUI 10 update...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Honor Magic is redefining the limits of smartphone capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Honor. Honor Magic utilizes AI technology to anticipate user needs.
Honor, a Huawei Group brand targeting young, tech-savvy consumers, celebrated its third anniversary by introducing the innovative Honor Magic smartphone. This device incorporates artificial intelligence (AI) for a more interactive user experience.
The Honor Magic boasts a sleek and ergonomic design featuring a 3D curved glass body. Powered by a Kirin 950 processor, it offers a 5.09&amp;quot; 2K AMOLED curved screen, intelligent sensors, and advanced recognition technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improve your filmmaking abilities using a smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 05:07:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</guid><description>Boo (left) with Tan (right).
While using mobile phones for filmmaking only emerged around 2008, recent technological advancements have empowered many phone owners to become filmmakers.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), aim to raise awareness about this potential in the Asia Pacific region and cultivate local talent. Their latest phone, the HUAWEI Mate 30 Pro, boasts features like 4K video recording, ultra-wide angle lens, and ultra slow motion capabilities, making it a capable filmmaking tool...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-filmmaking-abilities-using-a-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Huawei P10 Plus has the potential to serve as a substitute for a digital SLR camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</guid><description>Fashion and beauty photographer Richard Chen, also a Leica Akademie Instructor, believes the Huawei P10 Plus offers the capabilities of a professional camera in a pocket-sized device.
During a Huawei P10 Plus Masterclass held in Singapore, Chen, a professional Leica photographer, shared his growing preference for the Huawei P10 Plus&amp;rsquo;s mobile camera over traditional cameras for personal photography. He appreciates the portability and convenience of the smartphone, noting, &amp;ldquo;If I&amp;rsquo;m exploring I actually don&amp;rsquo;t bring the (conventional digital) camera nowadays&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m starting to use it as the main camera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei has launched the HUAWEI nova 3i</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 06:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</guid><description>Singapore is among the first countries globally to introduce the HUAWEI nova 3i, a midrange smartphone equipped with AI-powered front-facing dual cameras.
Huawei aims to make high-end technology and value accessible to budget-conscious consumers, according to Cheng Jiangfei, Managing Director of Huawei Singapore Consumer Business Group. He emphasized that the HUAWEI nova 3i combines stylish design with advanced AI features, offering exceptional quality and functionality at an affordable price.
Notable features of the HUAWEI nova 3i include:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new Mate 10 from Huawei: a portable desktop experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 12:38:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</guid><description>The Huawei Mate 10, unveiled in 2017, builds upon the success of its predecessors like the Mate 7 and Mate 9, offering even more power and efficiency in a compact design. Distinguishing itself as a pocket desktop, the Mate 10 series, particularly the Mate 10 and Mate 10 Pro models, boasts a pioneering AI processor known as the Kirin 970. This processor integrates a neural-network processing unit (NPU), enabling functionalities like real-time computer vision and enhanced photography...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>