<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2014 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2014/</link><description>Recent content in 2014 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hong Kong government confirms the schedule for releasing statistics from March to May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 07:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</guid><description>Companies interested in monitoring the Hong Kong economy can stay informed through press release schedules published by the Hong Kong government. These releases provide insights into various economic indicators.
A schedule of upcoming releases for March to May 2014 is provided below, starting with March 3rd.
March 2014
3rd: January 2014 Retail Sales Statistics
7th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Statistics on Vessels, Port Cargo, and Containers
10th: Fourth Quarter 2013 Quarterly Business Receipts Indices for Service Industries..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-government-confirms-the-schedule-for-releasing-statistics-from-march-to-may/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>APEC-SMETC has sold out all 1,200 booths</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</guid><description>The APEC Small &amp;amp; Medium Enterprises Technology Conference and Fair (APEC-SMETC) will take place in Yiwu, China, a global hub for consumer goods, from June 19th to 22nd. This event aims to provide a platform for APEC members to display new technologies and products, encourage technological exchange, and foster economic cooperation among SMEs in the Asia-Pacific region, ultimately boosting their international success.
The 8th APEC-SMETC, themed &amp;ldquo;technology promotes the economy, cooperation creates the future&amp;rdquo;, will showcase innovative products and technologies from SMEs across the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apec-smetc-has-sold-out-all-1-200-booths/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unique guest experiences offered by the Peninsula Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</guid><description>The Peninsula Hotels recently announced their Peninsula Academy Summer programs for this year. The luxury hotel group offers exclusive experiences focused on food, fashion, and art, perfect for corporate events or special clients.
Source: Peninsula Hotels.
Each program includes unique touches like bespoke Peninsula transportation, ranging from private helicopters and chauffeured Rolls-Royces to MINI Cooper S Clubman vehicles.
Here are some highlights from their Asian properties:
The Peninsula Hong Kong presents &amp;ldquo;Caviar Connoisseurship,&amp;rdquo; providing an in-depth look into the world of sustainably-farmed caviars, exploring their distinct qualities and ideal enjoyment methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The IDA in Singapore has compiled a report on home computer usage in Singapore for the year 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</guid><description>A 2014 survey by the Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) of Singapore revealed a surge in smartphone, computer, and internet use among Singaporean seniors. The study, titled Annual Survey on Infocomm Usage in Households, found that 74% of Singaporean residents used a computer in the three months leading up to the survey. Senior citizens aged 50 and above showed the most significant increase in computer usage.
Between 2012 and 2014, computer use among seniors aged 50 to 59 grew by 14 percentage points, while those over 60 showed an 11 percentage-point increase...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ida-in-singapore-has-compiled-a-report-on-home-computer-usage-in-singapore-for-the-year-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC experienced a 12.3% increase in new company registrations in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</guid><description>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC), a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, demonstrated strong performance across all financial sectors in 2014. These sectors include banking, insurance, leasing, wealth management, and Islamic finance, with a 12.3% rise in new company registrations compared to the previous year.
The organization highlights that 70% of companies registered in Labuan IBFC come from Asia, with 57% from Southeast Asia, particularly Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CHKLC has announced the winners of the 2014 HK Corporate Governance Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</guid><description>The Chamber of Hong Kong Listed Companies (CHKLC) recently revealed the winners of the Hong Kong Corporate Governance Excellence Awards 2014. The CHKLC defines corporate governance as respecting shareholder rights and values, maintaining board and management integrity, and demonstrating transparency and accountability.
Dr. Eddy Fong, Judging Panel Chairman, highlighted that the awardees went beyond standard practices, tailoring their governance strategies to address industry-specific risks and challenges.
&amp;ldquo;Furthermore,&amp;rdquo; he stated, &amp;ldquo;winning companies view sustainability as inseparable from good corporate governance, crucial for long-term growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Top 25 Multinational Workplaces consist of widely recognized brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</guid><description>Great Place to Work, a global firm that assists organizations in developing positive workplace cultures, has announced its yearly ranking of the top 25 multinational workplaces worldwide. This list is derived from an extensive study of workplace environments and recognizes companies with exceptional work cultures.
To be eligible for this list, companies must meet specific requirements: placement on at least five national &amp;ldquo;Best Workplaces&amp;rdquo; lists, a minimum of 5,000 employees, and a workforce comprised of at least 40% employees based outside of the company&amp;rsquo;s home country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-25-multinational-workplaces-consist-of-widely-recognized-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three of the top 25 hotels in the world, as listed by TripAdvisor, are located in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</guid><description>TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Choice awards highlights 25 diverse hotels worldwide. Notably, three hotels from Asia secured spots within the top 10. Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s The Upper House claimed the second position, while India&amp;rsquo;s Oberoi Udaivilas and Oberoi Mumbai ranked fifth and ninth, respectively.
The Upper House, nestled in Pacific Place, holds the top spot among hotels in Hong Kong. One reviewer praised it as their &amp;ldquo;best hotel experience,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing its flawlessness. A remarkable 97% of the reviews for this hotel are positive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Holiday spending in Singapore is expected to exceed S$4 billion by the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: Adobe. A minimum of 10% of all online sales in Australia, mainland China, Singapore, Japan, New Zealand, Hong Kong, and Thailand occur during the year-end holiday season.
This holiday season, Singaporean shoppers are predicted to heavily utilize their mobile devices for online shopping, according to the latest Adobe Digital Index Holiday Shopping Prediction.
Tablets and smartphones are anticipated to be crucial to shoppers in Singapore, with purchases made on these devices projected to represent 17% of all online sales from now until Christmas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-spending-in-singapore-is-expected-to-exceed-s-4-billion-by-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year in the Philippines, the focus is on mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</guid><description>In the Philippines, technology is synonymous with mobile technology.
According to Jubert Alberto, Research Manager at IDC Philippines, &amp;ldquo;The younger generation is entering the workforce, and they have a strong desire to be connected, informed, and entertained. They also tend to have fewer dependents. These factors indicate a growing demand for all things mobile, including devices, services, and applications.&amp;rdquo; IDC predicts that the Philippines will experience a 22% rise in smartphone spending and a 40% increase in tablet expenditure in 2014, fueled by a positive economic outlook...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's Influential Brands are identified by Gen X</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Leading Brands Chosen by Generation X
A consumer-driven award program spearheaded by Brand Alliance has identified the top Influential Brands in Singapore, as determined by the upwardly mobile Generation X (Gen X) demographic.
Source: Brand Alliance. Brand Alliance presented the 2013 Influential Brands awards in November 2013. The 2014 Influential Brands conference is scheduled for November 10, 2014.
The survey highlighted over 100 prominent brands resonating with consumers in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Asian hotels are ranked in the top 25 of Expedia Insiders' Select 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</guid><description>Expedia unveiled its 2014 Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select list in early July. This list highlights the best hotels globally, as determined by almost two million verified customer reviews and Expedia&amp;rsquo;s own travel experts.
Source: Blue Karma Resort website.
Out of over 290,000 bookable properties on Expedia&amp;rsquo;s global websites, 650 hotels received the Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select designation in 2014.
Here are a few of the top 25 hotels from this year&amp;rsquo;s list:
2. Blue Karma Resort - Seminyak, Bali..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson reveals insights on video consumption habits of consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Looking for effective ways to invest your marketing budget? The recent Ericsson ConsumerLab TV &amp;amp; Media Report might offer some valuable insights.
Now in its fifth year, the study surveyed 1,000 individuals in Singapore for the first time. The results reveal that 80% of Singaporeans engage in streaming TV or video content at least once a week, while 72% continue to watch traditional broadcast programs. Globally, 75% of consumers stream content multiple times weekly, compared to 77% who watch scheduled broadcast TV programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-reveals-insights-on-video-consumption-habits-of-consumers-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region are allocating funds for security, infrastructure, and business intelligence applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</guid><description>When planning technology budgets for the year, remember to allocate resources for infrastructure software, business intelligence applications, and, most importantly, security. Research firm Forrester states that security software is now the fastest-growing software category in the Asia Pacific region, leading in projected software spending growth for 2014.
In a survey of 3,382 IT executives and technology decision-makers across Asia Pacific organizations, 55% indicated they would increase their security software budget by &amp;lsquo;5% to 10%, or more&amp;rsquo; in 2014 compared to 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-allocating-funds-for-security-infrastructure-and-business-intelligence-applications/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>