<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trunk Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trunk-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Trunk Lines on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trunk-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is MPLS The New Telephone Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</guid><description>The familiar telephone network we use today is built upon gradual enhancements to the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN). This infrastructure, composed of copper and fiber, switches circuits to connect analog, cellular, and digital calls between any two parties. Most business phone systems have relied on or replicated the PSTN&amp;rsquo;s architecture, even for internal calls. However, this is changing as new technologies emerge to connect phone calls.
This shift is not driven by wireless technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-mpls-the-new-telephone-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Hosted Voice Cut Your Phone Costs In Half?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</guid><description>In the past, businesses and individuals could save significantly by choosing alternative long-distance phone providers. This became possible with deregulation, breaking the monopoly of local phone companies. This shift was made simple for customers, requiring minimal effort on their part to experience reduced long-distance bills.
A similar shift is happening now with businesses transitioning from traditional, in-house phone systems to cloud-based phone services. This mirrors the changes in long-distance services years ago, using technology to lower costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-hosted-voice-cut-your-phone-costs-in-half/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>