<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Menu on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/menu/</link><description>Recent content in Menu on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/menu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches.</description></item><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay).</description></item><item><title>Strangers' Reunion cafe introduces new menu items</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:32:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strangers-reunion-cafe-introduces-new-menu-items/</guid><description>Source: Strangers&amp;rsquo; Reunion. Ocean Trout on Hash.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a new lunch spot, you might want to try Strangers’ Reunion, a cafe in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Kampong Bahru district that recently updated its menu. World Gourmet Summit-recognized chef Daniel Chin has crafted dishes with a minimum of five components to entice your taste buds.
The cafe is well-known for its coffee, which is chosen and curated by Ryan Tan, a three-time Singapore Barista Champion and Co-founder of Strangers’ Reunion.</description></item><item><title>Spice World Hot Pot enhances menu in honor of 1st anniversary celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spice-world-hot-pot-enhances-menu-in-honor-of-1st-anniversary-celebration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 06:39:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spice-world-hot-pot-enhances-menu-in-honor-of-1st-anniversary-celebration/</guid><description>Source: Spice World Hot Pot. Tender milk beef.
Spice World Hot Pot, a restaurant recognized for its creative food presentations, high-quality ingredients, and attentive service, is commemorating its first anniversary in Singapore with exciting new dishes at its spacious 200-seat location.
One standout offering is the &amp;ldquo;Bullish Day&amp;rdquo; platter (牛气冲天, S$36.90), which showcases various cuts of sliced beef, tripe, and tongue. Diners can also enjoy traditional handmade beef balls (牛肉丸, S$15.</description></item><item><title>Where could my Integration Manager be hiding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-could-my-integration-manager-be-hiding/</guid><description>A user encountering an issue in Microsoft Dynamics GP where the &amp;ldquo;Integration Manager&amp;rdquo; option under Tools &amp;gt; Integrate appears unresponsive, despite having proper security permissions and the application launching correctly from the Start menu, can resolve this problem with a simple fix.
The solution involves navigating to the Microsoft Dynamics GP program directory (typically located at C:\Program Files\Microsoft Dynamics\GP) and locating the &amp;ldquo;Dex.ini&amp;rdquo; file within the Data folder.
Open this file using Notepad and verify that the file paths specified for &amp;ldquo;IntegrationManagerExePath&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;IMWizard&amp;rdquo; are accurate, making any necessary corrections.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds.</description></item><item><title>First and business class customers on Emirates can now enjoy a new Japanese menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 01:36:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. A sample dish from the new Japanese menu.
Emirates now offers a specialized Japanese menu to its first and business class passengers traveling between Dubai and Haneda, Narita, and Kansai airports in Japan. The airline&amp;rsquo;s Dubai catering team partnered with a Japanese culinary provider to develop the dishes using the highest quality ingredients.
In addition to their international menu, first-class passengers can enjoy traditional kaiseki, a multi-course Japanese meal, while those in business class have the option of a bento box.</description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces.</description></item></channel></rss>