<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reassembly on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reassembly/</link><description>Recent content in Reassembly on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:35:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reassembly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Final Tasks, Adjustments &amp; Playing Records</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-final-tasks-adjustments-playing-records/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 00:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-final-tasks-adjustments-playing-records/</guid><description>The final steps of a Beogram 4002 Type 5513 restoration project involved addressing corrosion damage and replacing the 5-pin DIN phono plug. Using a helpful audio path diagram, continuity checks were performed from the cartridge connector to ensure proper signal flow.
The replacement phono plug, a REAN model with gold contact pins, was installed, though the tight fit of the rubber boot on the cable posed a minor challenge. As an improvement, a grounding switch was added to the output board, eliminating the need for an external grounding wire.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Cabinet Work Completion to First Record Play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</guid><description>I finally set up the Beogram 8002 turntable in a listening room to test its functionality.
While reassembly took a bit longer than expected due to a slight detour to repair chipped rosewood trim on the front panel.
Although fixing the trim wasn&amp;rsquo;t part of the initial restoration plan, I decided against leaving the front panel chipped.
Repairs involving glue, like this one, often take longer than expected due to the curing time.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #1 Reassembly for Testing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-reassembly-for-testing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 11:19:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-reassembly-for-testing/</guid><description>Following a slight weather-induced pause, it&amp;rsquo;s time to resume the Beomaster 1900 restoration.
The Beomaster has been functioning well in the workshop for over a week. It&amp;rsquo;s now safe to reassemble the casing and begin performance testing.
Before I can replace the touch button control and the tone/FM tuning panels, the three display masks for Bass, Treble, and Balance need to be reconnected.
Reinstalling the touch button control panel requires precision.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reassembly of the Floating Chassis and Some Initial Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reassembly-of-the-floating-chassis-and-some-initial-checks/</guid><description>After completing the tangential arm assembly checks and cleaning the Beogram 4002 cabinet, it was time to reinstall the floating chassis.
The reassembly began with cleaning and lubricating the three suspension lock down screws, then reinstalling them in the Beogram cabinet.
With all three suspension locks back in place, the platter motor and output board, which had been previously restored, were reinstalled.
The control panel, RPM indicator panel, and arm position scale were then put back in their respective places.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Changing out the tonearm phono cartridge connector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-changing-out-the-tonearm-phono-cartridge-connector/</guid><description>This Beogram 4002 restoration project was paused until a new batch of Beolover replacement parts for the Beogram 400x tonearm cartridge mounts became available. With the parts in hand, the installation process could begin.
One of the cartridge connector contacts on this particular Beogram 4002 was defective. Whether this was a factory issue or a result of wear and tear is unclear, but the owner&amp;rsquo;s prior problems with cartridge mounting made replacing the connector a necessary step.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #1 Power Restored</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-power-restored/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 09:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-power-restored/</guid><description>The first Beomaster 1900 unit is ready for testing after restoration. Testing always starts with powering it on and checking the voltages.
This Beomaster wasn&amp;rsquo;t powering on. Based on my previous observations, I suspected the +15 VDC fuse and the fuse holders. I also found a wire exposed on the main power switch.
I repaired the power switch wiring. The Beomaster 1900 has a secure yet easily accessible wire connection for the line voltage.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Wrap Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-wrap-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-wrap-up/</guid><description>The second Beomaster 1900 restoration project is finished.
After a night of playing music, the Beomaster 1900 was ready for the cabinet to be put back together.
The Bass, Treble, and Balance indicator masks were reattached to their slide controls.
The touch control panel was then placed onto the cabinet frame, carefully aligning the button actuators with the sensor posts.
All touch buttons were tested to ensure functionality before continuing the reassembly.</description></item><item><title> Beogram 4004 Type 5526: Platter Motor, Detector Arm Adjustment and Solenoid Repair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 09:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beogram-4004-type-5526-platter-motor-detector-arm-adjustment-and-solenoid-repair/</guid><description>During today&amp;rsquo;s work, I installed the Beogram 4004 platter motor, fine-tuned the position sensor&amp;rsquo;s voltage, calibrated the detector arm sensor, and addressed an issue with the arm lowering solenoid.
My previous checks indicated adjustments would be needed after installing new parts, which is typical.
I also observed that the Beogram 4004&amp;rsquo;s arm solenoid, responsible for lowering the tonearm, was not raising it correctly. There was a lag between the signal to raise the tonearm and the solenoid disengaging.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #2 Reassembly and Power Supply Checks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 02:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-2-reassembly-and-power-supply-checks/</guid><description>This Beomaster 1900 is almost ready for final testing after reassembly and initial power supply checks.
The power transistor heatsinks, crucial for cooling, have been reinstalled using Sil-Pad insulators for thermal protection. This process started with the power transistors in their original state before any capacitor replacements. After restoration and the addition of new thermal insulation, they were carefully mounted back onto the unit.
To prepare for the upcoming No-Load Current adjustments, test leads were soldered onto the board.</description></item><item><title>A Pair of Beomaster 1900 Receivers for Restoration: Unit #1 Reassembly for Testing and a Power Problem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-reassembly-for-testing-and-a-power-problem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 04:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-pair-of-beomaster-1900-receivers-for-restoration-unit-1-reassembly-for-testing-and-a-power-problem/</guid><description>Before testing the Beomaster 1900, I needed to reinstall its four output transistors, which are located on the rear heatsinks. I had previously removed the heatsinks and their old thermal paste. For this reassembly, I prefer using modern SIL-Pad thermal insulators. They are much cleaner to work with than thermal paste and provide excellent thermal transfer.
Here are the components prepped for reassembly.
Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen designed a clever mounting system for these transistors.</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Reassembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-reassembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 06:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-reassembly/</guid><description>After recapping, cleaning, and maintenance, today was the day to begin reassembling the Beocord. Starting with an empty shell, the process began. While this Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen model has some unique disassembly quirks, the internal components are readily accessible.
The reassembly process mirrored the disassembly: the last boards removed were the first ones back in.
A complete reassembly wasn&amp;rsquo;t done at this stage as the displays still needed work. Removing the transformer simplified moving and positioning the Beocord due to the reduced weight.</description></item></channel></rss>