<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Al Barsha on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/al-barsha/</link><description>Recent content in Al Barsha on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/al-barsha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha provides Iftar and suhoor meals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 12:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-provides-iftar-and-suhoor-meals/</guid><description>Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha is offering special meals for iftar and suhoor throughout Ramadan.
Source: Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha website. The Gem Garden.
George Sarkis, Director of Food and Beverage at the hotel, highlights the extensive iftar buffet, which combines Oriental and Continental cuisines with traditional Ramadan drinks.
Both iftar and suhoor are served at The Gem Garden, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s all-day dining venue. The iftar buffet, available from sunset to 10 pm, costs AED120* per person and includes live cooking stations.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian.</description></item></channel></rss>