<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content Delivery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery/</link><description>Recent content in Content Delivery on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency.</description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery.</description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance.</description></item></channel></rss>