<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sponsor on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sponsor/</link><description>Recent content in Sponsor on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sponsor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad Airways is the designated airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 09:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</guid><description>The image showcases young people at work, sourced from the WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017 website.
Etihad Airways is the official airline sponsor for WorldSkills Abu Dhabi 2017, a major international event focusing on vocational education and skills excellence. Taking place at the Abu Dhabi National Exhibition Centre (ADNEC) from October 14th to 17th, 2017, the event will host over 3,000 participants and experts representing approximately 75 countries.
WorldSkills encompasses a variety of industries, from construction and creative fields like arts and fashion to technology, manufacturing, engineering, social services, and transport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-is-the-designated-airline-sponsor-for-worldskills-abu-dhabi-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haenyeo Singapore visually captures the story of Jeju's female divers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 10:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. HAENYO SINGAPORE will be exhibited in Singapore until November 23rd.
Jose Jeuland, a French photographer based in Singapore, is presenting his debut photography exhibition. This exhibition, hosted at The Fullerton Hotel in Singapore, focuses on haenyo (해녀) - female divers from Jeju Island in South Korea. Epson Singapore, the official print sponsor for the exhibition, provided prints produced on one of their commercial and industrial photographic production printers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haenyeo-singapore-visually-captures-the-story-of-jeju-s-female-divers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Traveloka will introduce awards based on audience participation for Asia's Got Talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</guid><description>Traveloka, a popular Southeast Asian travel app, is sponsoring the second season of AXN&amp;rsquo;s Asia&amp;rsquo;s Got Talent and introducing the Traveloka Awards.
The Traveloka Awards will recognize the contestant with the most compelling background, emphasizing unique talents and strong family and friend connections.
Premiering this October, Asia’s Got Talent on AXN will feature ten episodes, including auditions, semifinals, a finale, and a results show revealing the winner of a $100,000 prize from Traveloka...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/traveloka-will-introduce-awards-based-on-audience-participation-for-asia-s-got-talent/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>