<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vitamin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vitamin/</link><description>Recent content in Vitamin on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vitamin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Herbalife introduces a new skincare line to the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Herbalife, a nutrition company, has expanded its product line with the launch of Herbalife SKIN, a new skincare collection available in Asia Pacific markets. This line complements Herbalife&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;outer nutrition&amp;rdquo; range, which focuses on achieving healthy, youthful skin through a blend of natural ingredients, botanicals, extracts, and scientific formulation.
[Image of Herbalife logo]
Herbalife SKIN products are designed to create softer, smoother, and more radiant skin while minimizing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vitamin D does not increase longevity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:34:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</guid><description>While some believe vitamin D is a miracle cure, new research from the University of Cambridge, which analyzed data from almost 100 studies, indicates that vitamin D supplementation alone doesn&amp;rsquo;t decrease mortality rates in older adults.
Past research connected low vitamin D levels with illnesses like multiple sclerosis, cancer, and cardiovascular disease. To clarify if vitamin D supplementation by itself (without calcium or other interventions) impacts death from various causes, researchers examined 73 observational cohort studies and 22 randomized trials on naturally occurring vitamin D and supplements (D2 or D3)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vitamin-d-does-not-increase-longevity/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>