<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4002/</link><description>Recent content in 4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>My work on restoring the 4002 continues, and today involved polishing the hood – a task that&amp;rsquo;s quite a workout! The plexiglass hood had some noticeable scratches:
I began by using 200 grit sandpaper to create a consistent surface:
Then I gradually polished it using Micromesh polishing cloths:
The final stage involved Micromesh Micro-Gloss:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Replacement of Carriage Position Sensor Photocell</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</guid><description>Over many years of working with the Beogram 400x, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a wide array of issues, but these turntables never cease to present new challenges. In this instance, a Beogram 4002 exhibited inconsistent behavior when attempting to locate the record&amp;rsquo;s setdown point after pressing start. This pointed to a potential fault in the carriage position sensor.
Initially, I suspected the IR LED, a common culprit in later models like this 5513 Type.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Final 3D Printed Part Added</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</guid><description>I have completed the final 3D printed component for my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control system. This piece fits into a 10mm opening on the remote control receiver board, allowing it to be secured using one of the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s screws. The image below shows the part with the screw in place:
Once the remote control board is in place, the original screw can be used to fasten it. The cylindrical portion is designed to prevent the remote board from pressing against the component pins on the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main PCB while ensuring a secure fit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a New Output Relay and a GND Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-new-output-relay-and-a-gnd-switch/</guid><description>During the testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513), I discovered an intermittent issue with the output relay. Occasionally, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t activate when the stylus made contact, blocking the audio signal from the amplifier. This was a fortunate problem since the relay is the same one used for RPM switching in the 4002 and 4000 models. I had previously designed a breakout board to replace the RPM relay in a Beogram 4000 with a modern, encapsulated SMD signal relay, and I was able to utilize this board in the 4002 repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Non-Working End Groove Detection - Repair of a Detached Carriage Position Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-non-working-end-groove-detection-repair-of-a-detached-carriage-position-sensor/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is nearly complete. One peculiar problem was a detached carriage position sensor, which is housed within a black light shield. This shield was hanging at an angle, but it needs to be positioned vertically. The sensor works by using black sections on a plexiglass strip attached to the carriage to interrupt light from an IR diode. If the sensor is misaligned, stray light can disrupt the carriage&amp;rsquo;s movement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Repair of an Intermittent Sensor Arm Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously restored in May 2022, recently came back to my workshop due to a malfunctioning sensor arm LED. This was concerning because I had implemented a redesigned LED assembly for this particular unit.
To my relief, the LED functioned correctly when I powered up the turntable in my workshop. This suggested an intermittent problem that resolved itself during transport.
I tried manipulating the plugs and cables, but the LED remained illuminated.</description></item><item><title>Bang &amp; Olufsen MMC Cartridge Protector: Dimensionally True Reproduction with Stereolithography</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 05:21:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bang-olufsen-mmc-cartridge-protector-dimensionally-true-reproduction-with-stereolithography/</guid><description>I recently decided to test out the clear resin (sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;maker juice&amp;rdquo;) on my Formlabs Form 1 printer. I chose to design a replica of a Multi Media Card (MMC) cartridge protector, as they always seem to go missing. While I own multiple MMC cartridges, I only had one remaining protector.
As you can see in the images, the finished product is pretty good! The term &amp;ldquo;transparent&amp;rdquo; might be subjective, as the 3D-printed clear material doesn&amp;rsquo;t quite match the real thing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-hood-restoration/</guid><description>I am currently restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) and focused on refurbishing its dust cover. As you can see in the first image, the cover had multiple scratches and abrasions common for its age.
My first step was to sand the cover using 220-grit sandpaper to smooth out the imperfections.
Following this, I used a Micro-Mesh polishing cloth to restore the cover&amp;rsquo;s clarity. The final result is a clear and revitalized dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Intermittent "17" Position Switch Causing Immediate Touchdown After Launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-intermittent-17-position-switch-causing-immediate-touchdown-after-launch/</guid><description>I thought I was finished with this Beogram 4000 turntable after refurbishing its dust cover. However, a new problem emerged. After playing a few records, the tonearm would drop next to the platter as soon as I pressed &amp;ldquo;ON.&amp;rdquo; Luckily, the stylus wasn&amp;rsquo;t damaged (thanks to proper arm height adjustment), but I clearly needed to examine the carriage mechanism&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;17&amp;rdquo; position switch. This particular switch is the most troublesome of the position switches because it&amp;rsquo;s the only &amp;ldquo;break switch.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: A New Day, a New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 14:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-a-new-day-a-new-hood-/</guid><description>I recently got a new dust cover for a Beogram turntable from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, so they have a seamless look, unlike older reproduction covers that were made by fusing together laser-cut pieces. The result is a cover that&amp;rsquo;s indistinguishable from the original.
This photo shows the new cover:
The hinge for the cover was missing the small plastic pieces that prevent the spring mechanism from rubbing against the hinge&amp;rsquo;s metal parts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Plexiglass Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-plexiglass-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>The restoration of my Beogram 4000 is nearly complete. The final cosmetic touch was adding a new, reproduction dust cover from Classic Audio in Denmark. They also supplied a matching aluminum trim piece for the back edge. Installing the dust cover was simple.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a look at the process:
This image showcases the original hinge being installed with new stainless steel screws:
The pre-drilled holes in the new cover aligned perfectly, and the screws went in just like the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a 3D Printed Installation Tray</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control upgrade, specifically the receiver board insulation. My previous solution, using plastic foil, wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal aesthetically.
To address this, I designed a plastic tray that safeguards the receiver board from the main circuit board&amp;rsquo;s solder points. The tray is designed to click into place without additional screws.
Here are some photos:
Tray and board before assembly:
The tray features three rectangular cutouts to provide clearance for the solder points.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 02:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>I finally decided to refurbish the dust cover of the Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway, a task that takes me around 3 hours. I had been putting it off because I was enjoying working on a custom transformer for a Beomaster 4000 receiver.
As is common with vintage turntables, the dust cover on this Beogram 4000 was showing its age. It had numerous scratches and blemishes, as you can see here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:20:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-hood/</guid><description>The final stage of my recent Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project involved reviving the dust cover. Like many Beograms of its era, the cover required attention, particularly the rubber bumpers which needed replacing. The extent of the damage is evident in this photo:
Fortunately, the scratches weren&amp;rsquo;t severe. A 320-grit sanding step effectively leveled the plexiglass, preparing it for polishing to regain its transparency:
After approximately ten stages of polishing, using progressively finer sandpaper and polishing cloths, the cover regained its shine:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Stuck RPM Relay with a Modern Encapsulated SMD Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-stuck-rpm-relay-with-a-modern-encapsulated-smd-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, the motor wouldn&amp;rsquo;t switch to 45 RPM. After changing the control panel lights, it became obvious that the 45 RPM button lit up the correct trimmer pot but the motor speed didn&amp;rsquo;t change. The issue was a faulty relay that was responsible for switching resistor networks within the Wien oscillator&amp;rsquo;s feedback loop to adjust the resonance frequency.
Finding a replacement relay for vintage electronics can be tricky.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Polishing and Exchange of the Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 19:33:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-polishing-and-exchange-of-the-hinge/</guid><description>My recent Beogram 4000 restoration project required a hood restoration. I had two hoods: one had a cracked corner, and the other had a good plexiglass body but a corroded hinge.
Corrosion is common on Beogram 4000 hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s fixable with sanding and repainting, but finding a good hinge is preferable. Luckily, the cracked hood had a usable hinge, so I decided to swap them.
Removing the hinge requires care to avoid damaging the aluminum strip on the back of the hood.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration - Exchange of Trim, Fixing Cracked Hinges, Spray Painting Corroded Metal Parts and Polishing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration-exchange-of-trim-fixing-cracked-hinges-spray-painting-corroded-metal-parts-and-polishing/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a damaged dust cover. It was scratched, the metal hinges were corroded, the plexiglass around the hinges was cracked, and it had the typical early-model plastic trim that imitated aluminum.
To start, I removed the plastic trim. It was attached with contact cement, so I warmed the dust cover in the oven at approximately 80 degrees Celsius (wrapped in aluminum foil to prevent hot spots) to soften the adhesive.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of Cracked Hood Hinge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 03:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-cracked-hood-hinge/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable had a broken hood hinge, a common problem caused by the design. The weight of the hood and the type of screws used put too much stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks.
The hinge was broken in one place, and the rest of it was still attached, but cracked. After carefully removing the old glue and aluminum strip, the broken piece was glued back on.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Awesome Refurbished Keypads in the House!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 06:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-awesome-refurbished-keypads-in-the-house-/</guid><description>I received two refurbished Beogram 4002 keypads from Denmark today. My friend, who did the repainting, said the weather conditions were perfect for the job, and he was right! The picture shows how fantastic they look.
He&amp;rsquo;s incredibly talented! The keypads look brand new, as if they were just made in 1975. He did a phenomenal job. I had sent him a worn-out keypad from a Beogram 4002 I recently restored, and he even found another one!</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of DC Motor Video Published - Check It Out!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:54:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-dc-motor-video-published-check-it-out-/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve finished my Beogram DC motor restoration video due to high demand! This video will show you how to disassemble the motor and revitalize the Oilite brass bearings by infusing oil under a vacuum. If your Beogram&amp;rsquo;s RPM is inconsistent, this video is for you! Have a look:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb with a LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-with-a-led/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a replacement was needed for the detector arm light bulb. The previous repair attempt had left the assembly in poor condition, with damaged wiring and a misaligned photo cell. To find a suitable replacement, a well-preserved Beogram 4004 was used for comparison.
Given the scarcity of original bulbs and the desire for a long-lasting solution, a 3mm LED was chosen as the replacement.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of a Brand New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 12:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood/</guid><description>Before returning the recently restored Beogram 4002 (5513) to its owner, one final detail needed attention: the original dust cover showed early signs of cracking around the hinges.
The owner opted for a brand new replacement dust cover from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These reproduction dust covers are made using the same injection molding process as the originals, resulting in a seamless look, unlike previous versions made by fusing laser-cut panels. The result is indistinguishable from the original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Restoration of the Carriage Position Sensor - Development of a New Beolover Part</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-restoration-of-the-carriage-position-sensor-development-of-a-new-beolover-part/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5503) being restored had a broken carriage position sensor photo resistor housing with damaged mounting tabs. After removing the housing and extracting the photo resistor, a replacement housing was designed and 3D printed.
The new housing consists of two parts. The photo resistor is placed on the insert part after straightening its leads. The main housing is then slid over the insert, sandwiching the photo resistor. This assembly is then inserted into the existing mounting cutouts and soldered to the PCB.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a Professionally Made PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</guid><description>I recently had a professionally made circuit board manufactured for the remote control receiver in my Beogram 4002 (5513). It was exciting to see the new board arrive and start assembling it.
The biggest changes in this design were simplifying the assembly by placing all the components on the top side and repositioning the ISP port to avoid interference with the aluminum top panel fixture. I also removed the reset button and made more space for the keypad connector.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Newly Adapted Beolover RIAA Pre-Amp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 13:17:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-newly-adapted-beolover-riaa-pre-amp/</guid><description>Following the recent redesign of the Beolover internal RIAA pre-amplifier for DC-motor Beogram 4002/4 turntables and its adaptation for the Beogram 4000, the final stage of the design process involved adjusting the circuit for the AC-motor Beogram 4002. The owner of a recently restored 4002 (5504) requested the RIAA installation, making his Beogram the first AC-motor 4002 to feature a Beolover RIAA.
The new board features an input jack that connects to a replicated Beogram-style plug through a multi-lead wiring harness.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Keyboard Repair - Detached Backstops</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 11:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</guid><description>Following the AC motor hood restoration on a Beogram 4002 (5503), the next cosmetic issue addressed was the loose keypad backstops. Some keys were protruding and functioned erratically, requiring multiple presses.
Upon removing the keypad and its PCB, it was discovered that several plastic backstops had detached. A previous attempt to reattach them using double-sided tape proved unsuccessful, causing an uneven keypad surface.
The remaining backstops were easily removed, but precisely reattaching them posed a challenge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Hood!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 02:02:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-/</guid><description>During a recent Beogram 4000 restoration, my customer opted for a brand new reproduction hood from Beoparts-shop in Denmark. These hoods mark a significant advancement in Beogram 400x restoration. Crafted through injection molding, they perfectly mirror the original hoods, eliminating the seams found in laser-cut and fused alternatives.
Simply put, these hoods are identical in appearance to the originals. Developed by Beoworld&amp;rsquo;s Dillen, their availability has greatly benefited Beogram 400x restorations.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Repair of a Cracked Plexiglass Hood With Laser Cut Patches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-repair-of-a-cracked-plexiglass-hood-with-laser-cut-patches/</guid><description>The hinge area is the most delicate part of plexiglass hoods found on Beogram turntables. It&amp;rsquo;s subject to significant stress when opened and closed, while the presence of screw holes for the metal hinge makes it structurally vulnerable. I recently worked on a Beogram 4000 with a cracked hood and a broken-off piece.
Inspired by a previous restoration of a Beogram 3000 hinge, I aimed to create a similar solution for the 4000/4002 models.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: New Aluminum Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-new-aluminum-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all spring terminals in the switches, this Beogram 4000 received another upgrade: a replacement for the old, unstable plastic carriage pulley, now made from aluminum. The original pulley is shown below:
And here it is equipped with one of Nick&amp;rsquo;s well-crafted aluminum pulleys:
Contact me if you need a pulley for your Beogram; I&amp;rsquo;d be happy to connect you with Nick. These pulleys are compatible with the 4002 and 4004 models as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of Upgrades - Internal RIAA Preamp, Commander Remote Control and a New Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 07:42:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-upgrades-internal-riaa-preamp-commander-remote-control-and-a-new-hood/</guid><description>Following the functional restoration of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) from Oklahoma, the next step was to add the customer&amp;rsquo;s desired upgrades. These included an internal Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier (designed for AC motor Beogram 4002s), a Beolover Commander remote control system, and a new hood for a pristine appearance.
The first upgrade was preparing the keypad for the Commander remote system. AC motor Beograms primarily use directly soldered wiring harnesses, so Commander installation isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;plug and play&amp;rdquo; like the DC motor version.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Conversion of the Tracking Sensor Light Bulb to an LED and Adjustment of the Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-conversion-of-the-tracking-sensor-light-bulb-to-an-led-and-adjustment-of-the-sensor/</guid><description>I began repairing a Beogram 4002 turntable that I purchased from Craigslist a year ago. I saw it as a good warm-up project before tackling the restoration of my prized Beogram 6000 4-Channel turntable.
When I plugged in the Beogram 4002, hoping for the best but prepared for potential issues, nothing happened except for the complete absence of tracking. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower, and there were signs of previous repair attempts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: RPM Performance Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-rpm-performance-test/</guid><description>I recently measured the RPM performance of my restored Beogram 4000 turntable. I was curious to see how the AC motor compared to the DC motors found in other models, like the Beogram 8000/8002 with their computer-controlled linear motors. After running the 4000 for 12 hours using my BeoloverRPM device, the results were interesting.
The AC motor demonstrated excellent stability, as evidenced by the graph. However, there was an initial period of drift as both the oscillator and motor warmed up.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Restoring the Plexiglass Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-restoring-the-plexiglass-hood/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5514) I recently restored had a very scratched dust cover.
[Image of scratched dust cover]
If I can feel the scratches with my fingernail, the first restoration step is sanding with 220 grit sandpaper. This creates a smooth surface for polishing. This is what the surface looks like after sanding:
[Image of dust cover after sanding]
It looks a bit like wood at this stage. After approximately 10 polishing steps using progressively finer sandpaper and then micro-mesh polishing cloths, the surface is restored:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of a Seized Solenoid to Tonearm Linkage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 11:07:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-a-seized-solenoid-to-tonearm-linkage/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I got from the UK had a seized linkage connecting the solenoid mechanism and tonearm. To lubricate this linkage, I had to disassemble the sensor arm assembly and remove it. Further inspection showed that the linkage&amp;rsquo;s rotating pin was stuck and had detached from its press-fit socket within the sensor arm base. I&amp;rsquo;ve created a video illustrating the problem and the repair process:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of a LED in the Sensor Arm and Adjustment of the Detection Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-a-led-in-the-sensor-arm-and-adjustment-of-the-detection-circuit/</guid><description>The last incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002 (5523) being restored was located in the sensor arm. The sensor compartment, with the original bulb, was removed from the arm.
A comparison of the original bulb and the replacement LED assembly is shown.
The flexible PCB design allows the LED board to be folded and fitted into the compartment.
The installed LED emits a warm white light, providing enough red photons to illuminate the red B&amp;amp;O logo on the arm&amp;rsquo;s front.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Apple Remote Controls All Functions of Turntable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</guid><description>After several weeks of testing, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my latest creation: a remote control receiver designed specifically for the Beogram 4002 (5513 model) turntable. This receiver seamlessly integrates with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s existing keypad connector without affecting its functionality.
The receiver board is compatible with the latest Apple TV remote, chosen for its sleek aluminum design that complements the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic. The remote&amp;rsquo;s minimalist button layout also aligns perfectly with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 Packaging for Shipping: An Update on How to Secure the Carriage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 16:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-packaging-for-shipping-an-update-on-how-to-secure-the-carriage/</guid><description>This article outlines a packaging update for the Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 turntables. Instead of taping the arm cover to the platter, the author now advises using an M3 screw to secure the carriage directly to the chassis.
This change is due to the risk of damaging the arm cover&amp;rsquo;s labeling with tape during shipping. While the author previously suggested using paper to protect the lettering, damage continued to occur.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Signal Path between DIN5 Plug and Cartridge, Plug Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 07:28:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-signal-path-between-din5-plug-and-cartridge-plug-replacement/</guid><description>I recently decided to update my Beogram 4002 turntable for the 21st century. While it was functional, the DIN 5 plug was noticeably worn and corroded. To address this, I swapped it out with a modern, high-quality Neutrik AG Rean NYS 322G plug featuring gold-plated pins, aiming for a reliable, long-lasting connection with my Beomaster 6000&amp;rsquo;s auxiliary input. The old plug was in rough shape, leaving me curious about its past.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The final step in restoring my Beogram 4000 involved replacing the damaged dust cover with one from a donor unit. While the replacement had some typical scratches, it was in good condition overall.
I began by sanding the surface with 320 grit sandpaper to remove the scratches. The next step was to polish it back to its original shine and clarity. Here&amp;rsquo;s the dust cover after polishing with 800 grit:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Installation of a Brand New Hood and Aluminum Trim</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 08:17:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-installation-of-a-brand-new-hood-and-aluminum-trim/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4002 hood hinge from Florida to use in the installation of a new hood. The first photo shows its condition upon arrival.
A closer look revealed the problem:
The mounting holes on the hood had developed a fracture. This is a common issue caused by the original design choices made by B&amp;amp;O. The use of flat head bolts placed lateral stress on the plexiglass, leading to cracks and eventual breakage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacing the Detector Arm Light Bulb, Discussion of the Circuit and Relevant Oscilloscope Traces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 06:23:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacing-the-detector-arm-light-bulb-discussion-of-the-circuit-and-relevant-oscilloscope-traces/</guid><description>A newly acquired Beogram 4002 turntable required a light bulb replacement in its detector arm. Despite the straightforward nature of the bulb replacement, positioning it correctly to ensure proper functionality can be challenging. A video documenting the process illustrates the installation steps, the adjustment of the bulb&amp;rsquo;s position, and relevant circuit components. Additionally, it showcases oscilloscope readings from a functioning detector setup.
High-resolution images provide further insights from the oscilloscope:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Polishing of the In- and Outside of the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-polishing-of-the-in-and-outside-of-the-hood/</guid><description>After installing a new remote control and internal pre-amplifier, the final touch on this Beogram 4002 (5523) was polishing its dust cover. While the outside showed typical scratches, the inside had an unusually large scratch as well.
Polishing the inside is more challenging because the polishing tool can hit the corners. However, because this scratch was situated away from the edges, it could be addressed. The technique involved gradually widening the polished area with each step.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of the Latest Version of the Beogram Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>While restoring my Beogram 4002 (5513), I decided to improve the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control I had previously designed. I added a &amp;ldquo;pairing&amp;rdquo; feature to prevent conflicts with Apple TVs and other devices that use Apple remotes. To completely eliminate the need to touch the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s delicate keypad, I also included remote switching between 33 and 45 RPM. A detailed video about the latest version explains the functions and demonstrates the remote and its pairing process:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Keypad with a Worn Through Start Button</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 keypad, showing signs of wear, was recently sent from New Zealand. The start button&amp;rsquo;s coating was entirely worn down:
This is a common problem for Beogram keypads. The combination of skin acids and friction wears away the coating.
Fortunately, this is fixable. Here is the keypad after being restored:
It looks great! The coating will be left to harden further before being returned to New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Polishing the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-polishing-the-hood/</guid><description>The final touch in restoring a Beogram turntable is typically polishing its plexiglass cover. This particular Beogram 4002 had noticeable scratches on its cover, including a branded logo above the platter&amp;rsquo;s center.
Deep scratches that can be felt by hand require an initial sanding with 220-grit sandpaper to level the surface, creating a temporarily rough appearance. If the scratches are less pronounced, starting with 320 or 400-grit sandpaper might suffice.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Plexiglass Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 18:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) I recently refurbished had a very scratched lid. Fortunately, the hinges were undamaged, and the inside of the lid was in good condition, with only a few minor cleaning marks. This made it worthwhile to try to restore the lid to an acceptable condition. The photo below shows the condition of the lid when I received the Beogram:
Because some scratches were deep enough to feel with a fingernail, I began by using 400-grit sandpaper to smooth the surface:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Replacement of Rusty RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 14:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-replacement-of-rusty-rca-plugs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration, I swapped out the old, worn-out RCA plugs. The originals were showing their age.
I chose robust, gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs as replacements. These are excellent for transmitting the low-voltage MMC signal to the amplifier. The metal housing provides superior shielding against electromagnetic interference, ensuring signal integrity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a look after soldering:
And here they are secured:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): RPM Stability Test and an Updated Display on the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 21:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rpm-stability-test-and-an-updated-display-on-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>I dedicated time to program the compact display integrated into my BeoloverRPM device. This enhancement enables precise RPM adjustments and long-term RPM stability analysis. The display now includes minimum and maximum values, along with the total measurement duration. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the display:
The display boasts high resolution and excellent contrast. However, those of us who are getting older might need reading glasses to decipher the small font. Is perfection ever attainable?</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beo4 Enabled Commander Remote Control: Seamless Integration of Beogram 4002 or 4004 with More Recent B&amp;O Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 04:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beo4-enabled-commander-remote-control-seamless-integration-of-beogram-4002-or-4004-with-more-recent-b-o-systems/</guid><description>Dirk, a Beolover from Berlin, recently reached out about controlling his Beogram 4004 turntable with a Beo4 remote. He wanted to seamlessly integrate the turntable with his existing Beosound 9000 system.
I found his idea intriguing and decided to modify the Beolover Commander remote to make it compatible. This involved adding a 455kHz IR receiver for Beo4 communication and deciphering the Beo4&amp;rsquo;s code system to rewrite the Commander&amp;rsquo;s firmware accordingly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Mass Production!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 02:04:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-mass-production-/</guid><description>More orders for the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control have been placed. The Commander is now compatible with a designated Apple TV remote, eliminating interference with other Apple devices in the same room. Designed specifically for later models of the 4002 turntable (types 551x and 552x) that feature the keypad connector on the main circuit board, the Commander offers a simple plug-and-play installation process. Today, five new units were assembled.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Random Stop Issue Fixed - Defective Photo Resistor in the Spindle RPM Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, previously restored, began experiencing a problem where the OFF function would randomly activate during playback as if the button was pressed.
Prior to delving into the solution, the circuit diagram is presented for reference.
Transistor TR17, within the &amp;lsquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rsquo; section, is responsible for initiating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s OFF function. When its base is grounded, the collector rises to approximately 18V, causing the arm to lift and return to its resting position.</description></item></channel></rss>