<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rewards on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rewards/</link><description>Recent content in Rewards on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/rewards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ADIB and Rotana have partnered to introduce the exclusive ADIB Rotana Rewards Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-and-rotana-have-partnered-to-introduce-the-exclusive-adib-rotana-rewards-card/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) and Rotana, a hotel management company, have teamed up to introduce the ADIB Rotana Rewards Exclusive Card. This card allows members to earn Rotana Rewards points and enjoy special benefits whenever they use it for purchases.
Source: ADIB. From left: Sarvesh Sarup, Global Head of Retail Banking, ADIB, and Omer Z. Kaddouri, President and CEO Rotana.
This card is the first of its kind in the Central Eastern Europe &amp;amp; Middle East and Africa (CEEMEA) region to be co-branded with a hospitality company and developed by a local issuer.</description></item><item><title>Dash, the mobile payment service by Singtel, introduces a new rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 22:32:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-the-mobile-payment-service-by-singtel-introduces-a-new-rewards-program/</guid><description>Singtel Dash users now have a new incentive to use the app – the Dash Rewards program. This program allows users to earn points for various transactions, including payments and overseas remittances. These points can then be redeemed for rewards such as Singtel mobile services, grocery vouchers, dining options, retail discounts, and lifestyle benefits.
Source: Singtel website. Dash Rewards incentivizes Dash users for making transactions.
Dash Rewards aims to provide more value to users by awarding points for every dollar spent.</description></item><item><title>Great Eastern has introduced additional rewards for online shopping in collaboration with RebateMango</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 02:32:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/</guid><description>Great Eastern&amp;rsquo;s rewards platform, UPGREAT, has partnered with RebateMango to provide users with an enhanced rewards experience. This collaboration aligns with the insurer&amp;rsquo;s strategy to increase online engagement with its customers across the region.
UPGREAT members can now enjoy a wider selection of rewards from over 500 retailers in Singapore, including popular names like Shopee, Agoda, AliExpress, Booking.com, and Lazada. This integration creates a seamless shopping experience where users can earn UPGREAT points easily.</description></item></channel></rss>