<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backup on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backup/</link><description>Recent content in Backup on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hitachi drives are endorsed with a vote of confidence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 02:48:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</guid><description>In a January 2014 blog post, cloud storage company Backblaze reported that Hitachi and Western Digital hard drives have been the most reliable in their data centers.
Backblaze engineer Brian Beach revealed that Seagate&amp;rsquo;s 1.5TB drives had an annual failure rate of about 14%, significantly higher than Hitachi&amp;rsquo;s 2TB drives at approximately 1% and Western Digital&amp;rsquo;s 1TB drives at 3%. For 3TB drives, Seagate again had the highest failure rate at around 9%, while Western Digital stood at about 3% and Hitachi at roughly 1%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hitachi-drives-are-endorsed-with-a-vote-of-confidence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2018 features AI technology that can detect ransomware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</guid><description>Acronis Integrates AI into True Image 2018 for Enhanced Data Protection Image: Beloussov introducing Acronis ahead of the launch of Acronis True Image 2018.
Beloussov speaking at the Acronis True Image 2018 launch event.
Acronis, a global leader in hybrid cloud data protection, is incorporating artificial intelligence (AI) into its entire product line. Serguei Beloussov, co-founder and CEO of Acronis, emphasized their commitment to AI integration across all products. This announcement was made during the launch of their flagship product, Acronis True Image 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2018-features-ai-technology-that-can-detect-ransomware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today is World Backup Day. Have you ensured the safety of your data?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</guid><description>A recent worldwide study funded by Acronis, a prominent name in hybrid cloud data protection, highlights a rising awareness of the importance of safeguarding personal data on computers, mobile phones, and tablets.
Almost half of the surveyed individuals possess more than four devices per household requiring protection, and 45% are most afraid of misplacing photos and videos. Security and privacy were identified as crucial factors in data backup.
Evolving Concerns in Personal Data Security The traditional worries of hardware malfunctions and accidental deletions are no longer the sole reasons for data loss apprehension...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-is-world-backup-day-have-you-ensured-the-safety-of-your-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drobo Mr. Storage Roboto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</guid><description>Hard drive space disappears faster than you can imagine, especially with large digital media files like photos and videos. Even large hard drives fill up quickly.
While upgrading or adding hard drives seems like a solution, it creates new problems like managing backups and worrying about data loss from hard drive failures. These tasks can be time-consuming, especially for professionals working with large files. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like you need a personal assistant to manage it all...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2017 is compatible with Facebook, wireless backups, and remote backups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:47:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</guid><description>Source: Acronis. Acronis True Image 2017.
Acronis, a major provider of hybrid cloud data protection, released Acronis True Image 2017, its newest personal backup software.
This iteration combines the existing full image local and cloud backup with new features such as wireless backup for mobile devices to either local Windows computers or the Acronis Cloud. It also allows for an unlimited number of mobile devices and provides complete Facebook account data backups...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2017-is-compatible-with-facebook-wireless-backups-and-remote-backups/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backup Your Gmail and Google Apps While You Can</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-your-gmail-and-google-apps-while-you-can/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-your-gmail-and-google-apps-while-you-can/</guid><description>A lot of us utilize Gmail and other Google services for work due to their ease of use and affordability. However, a major drawback is the lack of robust data recovery options in case of accidental deletions or other mishaps.
Imagine accidentally deleting crucial contact information from your Gmail account. Without a backup, that data would be lost forever. While Google doesn&amp;rsquo;t provide a native backup solution, third-party services like Backupify bridge the gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-your-gmail-and-google-apps-while-you-can/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-your-gmail-and-google-apps-while-you-can/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces the latest version of its software, Acronis True Image 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 19:42:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</guid><description>Acronis introduces the Acronis Survival Kit, a comprehensive system recovery solution.
New active disk cloning functionality for Mac enables data migration to other devices.
Acronis Active Protection, powered by AI, effectively combats ransomware threats.
Acronis Notary and ASign leverage blockchain technology to guarantee data integrity through notarization and e-signatures.
Enhanced backup solutions now extend protection to social media profiles.
Acronis, a leading provider of cyber protection and hybrid cloud solutions, has unveiled the 15th-anniversary edition of its renowned personal backup software, Acronis True Image 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-the-latest-version-of-its-software-acronis-true-image-2019/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is your method for backing up your HyperV virtual machines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-your-method-for-backing-up-your-hyperv-virtual-machines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-your-method-for-backing-up-your-hyperv-virtual-machines/</guid><description>Steve Endow, a Dynamics GP Certified Trainer and Certified Professional, outlines his simple and reliable method for backing up Hyper-V virtual machines (VMs), acknowledging that while more advanced solutions exist, he prioritizes simplicity and trust.
Endow uses traditional backup solutions for regular files but highlights the unique challenge of backing up large VM files, which consume significant time and storage space. He prefers manual backups using compression tools like 7-Zip over potentially complex VM backup solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-your-method-for-backing-up-your-hyperv-virtual-machines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-your-method-for-backing-up-your-hyperv-virtual-machines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2020 streamlines the 3-2-1 backup approach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company, has launched Acronis True Image 2020, a new personal cyber protection solution. This version allows users to automatically copy local backups to the cloud, making it the first personal solution to automate the 3-2-1 backup rule recommended by data protection experts.
This release supports Acronis&amp;rsquo;s vision of cyber protection, which combines traditional data protection and cybersecurity into one solution. As a result, Acronis True Image 2020 is the only personal solution to address all five vectors of cyber protection—safety, accessibility, privacy, authenticity, and security of data (SAPAS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2020-streamlines-the-3-2-1-backup-approach/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backup and Recovery For All Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</guid><description>Businesses are exposed to various risks, not just economic fluctuations or environmental factors. Your data, whether on your computer or in your data center, might be your biggest vulnerability. Without backup and recovery solutions, you&amp;rsquo;re one mishap away from major problems.
Your data is the most valuable asset at risk. While paper records were once the norm, with fire as a primary threat, today&amp;rsquo;s electronic records face risks like corruption and deletion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis introduces an improved True Image family and guarantees regular updates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</guid><description>Acronis, a leading provider of data protection solutions, recently launched its Acronis True Image Cloud and Acronis True Image 2016 products in Singapore.
During the launch event, Acronis Co-Founder and CEO, Serguei Beloussov, emphasized the increasing importance of data protection, stating that it will soon be as essential as basic necessities. He believes that data represents a comprehensive record of our lives and preserving it should be a top priority, with the goal of eventually retaining all data indefinitely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-introduces-an-improved-true-image-family-and-guarantees-regular-updates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropmysite has undergone a rebranding and is now known as Dropsuite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 21:29:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</guid><description>Dropmysite, a cloud-based backup provider for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), has been renamed Dropsuite. This rebranding reflects a new global vision, business strategy, and ambition focused on business continuity, data recovery, and protection.
Dropsuite now offers a comprehensive suite of backup, recovery, and archiving solutions, consolidating its previous standalone brands: Dropmysite (website and database backup), Dropmyemail (email backup), and Dropmymobile (mobile data backup).
Furthermore, Dropsuite has introduced DSE Server Backup, a new file-based server backup solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropmysite-has-undergone-a-rebranding-and-is-now-known-as-dropsuite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Acronis True Image 2021 provides a combination of cybersecurity and backup solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 02:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/</guid><description>Acronis, a global cyber protection company, has introduced Acronis True Image 2021. This new product combines robust cybersecurity features with personal backup, creating a comprehensive personal cyber protection solution for individuals, demanding home users, and small businesses with up to five users.
With the increase in remote work, securing home computers has become crucial. However, an Acronis survey revealed that nearly half (47%) of remote workers haven&amp;rsquo;t received clear guidance on cybersecurity while working from home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acronis-true-image-2021-provides-a-combination-of-cybersecurity-and-backup-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SMB Cloud Computing Portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</guid><description>While large companies have widely adopted cloud computing, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) may wonder about its relevance for them. Broadview Networks offers a range of cloud services ideal for such businesses. Already a prominent communications provider in the Northeastern and Mid-Atlantic US, Broadview provides various connectivity options, including T1 lines, Ethernet, fiber optic connections, and traditional phone lines.
What distinguishes Broadview is its ability to provide both cloud services and the reliable connectivity these services require, unlike many cloud providers that only offer the infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-cloud-computing-portfolio/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Veeam introduces a new free backup tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 06:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</guid><description>Source: Veeam video.
Veeam has introduced a cost-free solution for creating backups of Windows desktops and laptops that doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessitate any extra software or costs.
Users have the flexibility to select their backup locations, including options such as external hard drives, shared folders on the network, and more. This free software from Veeam also offers the capability to generate bootable recovery media, proving useful when addressing computer issues that hinder the operating system from starting properly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/veeam-introduces-a-new-free-backup-tool/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TelePacific Takes Business Continuity Seriously</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications, a telecommunications company serving California and Nevada, emphasizes a thorough approach to disaster preparedness and business continuity.
Their Business Continuity Services aim to keep your voice and data operational, even if a trunk line or your entire facility goes down. But how is this achieved?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with telephone service. Many businesses utilize digital trunk lines like T1 PRI and SIP Trunks, which offer cost savings compared to individual lines but pose a single point of failure risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-takes-business-continuity-seriously/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>