<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Connectivity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-connectivity/</link><description>Recent content in Business Connectivity on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-connectivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Choose An MPLS VPN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Businesses need secure communication between their different locations. While private networks offer the highest level of security, they are expensive to build and maintain. Using the public internet is cheaper but raises security concerns.
A fully private network, offering top-notch security and performance, requires significant investment. Building a central hub and connecting each location with dedicated lines like T1 or Ethernet can become very costly, especially with increasing bandwidth demands and staffing for maintenance.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Makes the Upgrades Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has always been a popular choice for businesses, particularly those requiring high-speed connections. The good news is that fiber optic service is becoming increasingly accessible to businesses. IT managers and executives now face a decision: stick with their existing copper wireline services or upgrade to fiber optics. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the factors that make fiber optics the preferred choice.
Fiber Optics: The Way of the Future</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Offers Lower Cost Carrier Grade Fiber Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 23:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-offers-lower-cost-carrier-grade-fiber-solutions/</guid><description>Large bandwidth consumers, including major corporations, healthcare systems, independent phone companies, video production companies, and internet service providers, now have an affordable alternative for obtaining the reliable bandwidth they require. This shift is thanks to Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet provides metropolitan and long-distance bandwidth services using Ethernet technology rather than conventional telephone company methods. This service is often called Metro Ethernet within a single metropolitan area. These services deliver professional-grade bandwidth solutions characterized by high reliability and dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Why Colo Bandwidth Pricing Is Lowest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</guid><description>Intrigued by the idea of significantly cheaper bandwidth? Take a look at the pricing for colocation bandwidth and see for yourself.
It&amp;rsquo;s tempting, right? The cost per Mbps at a colocation center is often much lower than standard bandwidth costs for your servers, even with a discounted rate from a telecom broker. While this might seem unfair, it&amp;rsquo;s simply a matter of economics.
Colocation facilities can offer these reduced costs for a couple of reasons.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading.</description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet and Colocation For Texas Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-and-colocation-for-texas-business/</guid><description>Texas is known for its expansive size, thriving businesses, massive data generation, and a critical need for extensive bandwidth. Alpheus, a Texas-based telecommunications company, is acutely aware of these needs and caters its services to businesses across various sectors including finance, energy, government, healthcare, IT, legal, and media.
Headquartered in Houston, Alpheus boasts a robust fiber optic network that interconnects major Texan cities like Dallas, Fort Worth, Waco, Bryan, Austin, San Antonio, Laredo, McAllen, Harlingen, Corpus Christi, Victoria, and Houston.</description></item><item><title>Instant Ethernet Fiber Network Quotes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 17:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/</guid><description>The need for fiber optic bandwidth has never been greater. Businesses are producing and sharing more video content, medical imaging has transitioned to digital platforms, and cloud-based IT relies heavily on bandwidth. However, finding available fiber services and their costs can be a tedious and time-consuming process.
Imagine getting instant online quotes for fiber optic services. It might seem too good to be true, but it&amp;rsquo;s now a reality. The Telarus GeoQuote bandwidth search engine has been enhanced to provide instant online quotes for Ethernet over Fiber, with bandwidth options ranging from 10 Mbps to 1 Gbps (GigE).</description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1.</description></item><item><title>3G Fixed Wireless For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-fixed-wireless-for-business/</guid><description>The same 3G technology that revolutionized mobile phones is also available as a fixed wireless service, offering a cost-effective solution for businesses in areas with limited internet options. Cellular networks have established a wide infrastructure of base stations, effectively blanketing the country with both voice and data coverage. These familiar cell towers transmit signals using microwave radio equipment.
Essentially, the 3G wireless broadband service functions as a network of interconnected Wi-Fi hotspots with a significantly larger coverage area.</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>Why Look For Fiber Lit Buildings?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-look-for-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:06:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-look-for-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Fiber lit building&amp;rdquo; refers to a building already equipped with fiber optic service. This is a significant advantage because it provides access to high-bandwidth internet without expensive installation costs.
To find these buildings, you can use the Ethernet Buildings Lit Building Locator. This online tool acts as a map to locate buildings with existing high-bandwidth infrastructure.
Fiber optic connections offer almost limitless bandwidth potential. While renting an office space won&amp;rsquo;t likely provide terabits per second, fiber connections can readily handle Gigabit Ethernet, 10 GigE, and even multiplexed connections for significantly higher capacity.</description></item></channel></rss>