<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Soft Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soft-law/</link><description>Recent content in Soft Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/soft-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>Is a Title Sufficient to Override Constitutional Rules and Fundamental Rule-of-Law Principles? A Paper on Enforcement Priorities for Article 102 TFEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</guid><description>Konstantinos Sidiropoulos
DPhil Candidate at University of Oxford – Prof Steve Weatherill
Foundation for Education and European culture scholar
Introduction
The best way to regulate abuse of dominance in the EU has been a subject of much discussion. In the early 2000s, aiming to address criticisms of its approach to unilateral conduct control, the European Commission started reviewing the relevant law, including how it was being applied (see the EAGCP Report and the Discussion Paper).</description></item></channel></rss>