<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EDGE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/edge/</link><description>Recent content in EDGE on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/edge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>Speedier Network For The iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</guid><description>While the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s popularity is a boon for AT&amp;amp;T, which holds the exclusive contract, the device&amp;rsquo;s data demands present a significant hurdle.
Historically, cellular towers primarily handled voice calls, with data as a secondary function. Early data speeds were adequate for text-based services, but the advent of camera phones, web browsers, and video streaming dramatically increased bandwidth requirements. Today&amp;rsquo;s users demand home and work-level speeds, typically between 3 to 10 Mbps, far exceeding the capabilities of older networks.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Plans With Aircards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 03:10:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-plans-with-aircards/</guid><description>Wireless modem aircards liberate you from the constraints of WiFi hotspots, transforming your laptop into a truly mobile computer. But how do they work, and what kind of service plans are necessary?
Essentially, an aircard functions as a specialized two-way radio, transmitting and receiving digital computer data instead of voice calls.
While they might resemble them, aircards don&amp;rsquo;t operate on cell phone networks. Currently, the majority adhere to either EVDO (Sprint and Verizon Wireless) or EDGE and HSPA (AT&amp;amp;T and T-Mobile) standards for cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G1 Google Android Phone Gets Vocal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</guid><description>Choosing your next smartphone can be tough. Touchscreen phones like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone, the BlackBerry Bold, and Samsung Delve are appealing, but some prefer a physical QWERTY keyboard. The BlackBerry Pearl&amp;rsquo;s trackball navigation is another option. Connectivity matters too, with 3G being desirable but not always accessible. WiFi capability for fast web browsing is also important.
The HTC-built G1 for T-Mobile might be the solution if you want it all. This &amp;ldquo;Android Phone,&amp;rdquo; marking Google&amp;rsquo;s entry into mobile wireless, operates on T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s network, offering quad-band service and various data features.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP).</description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T HSUPA Aircards Have the Edge Over EDGE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 21:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-hsupa-aircards-have-the-edge-over-edge/</guid><description>Major wireless carriers, including AT&amp;amp;T, are heavily invested in upgrading their cellular data capabilities to meet the increasing demand for broadband internet access. This demand stems from the desire for constant connectivity, enabling activities like web browsing and mobile video streaming. AT&amp;amp;T is eager to capitalize on this demand and provide the desired connectivity.
Those accustomed to traditional wired broadband connections and basic cell phones may not fully grasp the advancements in mobile broadband technology.</description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2.</description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi.</description></item><item><title>T-Mobile 3G Aircard For PC and Mac</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 08:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-3g-aircard-for-pc-and-mac/</guid><description>Want to connect your laptop to T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s 3G network and get free access to their HotSpots? The T-Mobile webConnect USB Laptop Stick can make that happen.
This device is a wireless modem with a USB connector that plugs into your PC or Mac. PCs require Windows XP or Vista, while Macs need OS X 10.3.9 or higher.
This aircard provides internet access virtually anywhere in the U.S. with T-Mobile cellular coverage.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone.</description></item></channel></rss>