<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5/</link><description>Recent content in 5 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen.</description></item><item><title>Sophos has simplified the process of securing corporate information on mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:35:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sophos-has-simplified-the-process-of-securing-corporate-information-on-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Source: Sophos website.
Sophos recently launched Sophos Mobile Control 5 (SMC 5), a software solution designed to differentiate personal and company data on devices to enhance corporate data security.
Managing devices like laptops, tablets, and smartphones often involves individual configuration, updates, and management. SMC 5 simplifies this process for IT administrators by allowing them to establish user-specific rules once to protect company data stored on the device or in personal cloud storage.</description></item></channel></rss>