<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Resort on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resort/</link><description>Recent content in Resort on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/resort/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Vines Resort &amp; Country Club introduces a new garden venue for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</guid><description>Source: The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club. The Pavilion.
The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club, located near Perth, Australia, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Pavilion.&amp;rdquo; This new event space is a specially designed garden structure situated at the front of the resort, offering scenic views of the golf course and surrounding gardens. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for events such as conference gatherings or product launches.
The open-air venue, capable of hosting 100 guests, has three sides open to the elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Katamama will be opening its doors to guests in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 03:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</guid><description>Source: Katamama. A rooftop suite at dusk.
Katamama, a 58-suite boutique hotel in Seminyak, Bali&amp;rsquo;s prime oceanfront area, is set to open in late March 2016.
The hotel emphasizes &amp;ldquo;handcrafted hospitality,&amp;rdquo; with every detail meticulously designed and executed by skilled Indonesian artisans. Katamama is a project by PTT Family, known for acclaimed restaurants, bars, and the Potato Head Beach Club in Bali. This 20-villa estate is famous for its innovative environmental design and a prominent contemporary Indonesian art gallery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/katamama-will-be-opening-its-doors-to-guests-in-april/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels establishes a high-end presence in the Maldives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>AccorHotels is entering the Maldives market with its first luxury resort there, the Dhevanafushi Maldives Luxury Resort. Located on the private island of Meradhoo, the resort will undergo improvements in late 2018 and subsequently become part of the prestigious Raffles brand.
Currently, the resort offers 21 island villas and 16 ocean villas, all with private pools. Guests can enjoy three restaurants and a variety of amenities and activities for relaxation and rejuvenation, such as a luxurious spa, an overwater fitness center, yoga classes, watersports, and private dining options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The first Nongsa Regatta took place in January 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:40:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</guid><description>Source: Nongsa Regatta Facebook page.
The first Nongsa Regatta will take place at Nongsa Point Marina &amp;amp; Resort in Batam, Indonesia, from January 27th to 31st, 2016. This period coincides with the strongest point of the northeast monsoon. The competition welcomes yachts, sporting boats, and racing multihulls. Additionally, there will be races for dinghies and traditional &amp;ldquo;kolek&amp;rdquo; boats.
Having hosted the Singapore Straits Regatta for almost two decades, the resort possesses extensive experience in regattas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-nongsa-regatta-took-place-in-january-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort introduces its new private villas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</guid><description>Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s InterContinental Phu Quoc Long Beach Resort has introduced new villas that provide enhanced privacy and luxury for guests. These villas overlook the Gulf of Thailand and the resort&amp;rsquo;s lotus lagoon. Their spaciousness makes them perfect for hosting private events, parties, or intimate gatherings, with amenities like a private chef, outdoor barbecues, and more.
Situated in a secluded part of the resort, the four three-bedroom and one four-bedroom villas offer direct access to the Club InterContinental Lounge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-phu-quoc-long-beach-resort-introduces-its-new-private-villas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Purify and detoxify on weekends in July and August at REVĪVŌ in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: REVĪVŌ. Throughout July and August, cleansing and detox retreats are offered every weekend.
The luxurious REVĪVŌ wellness resort in Bali, Indonesia, has introduced weekend-long cleansing and detox retreats for July and August.
Guests can choose to participate for one or two days. Kicking off at 10:00 am each Saturday, the program begins with a cold-pressed juice, followed by yoga, Pilates, or meditation. Afterward, attendees enjoy kombucha (a fermented tea beverage) and a detox lunch at the NŪTRIŌ restaurant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton introduces a new MICE venue in Hainan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 01:36:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide and its DoubleTree by Hilton brand have opened a new resort in China called the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hainan - Qixianling Hot Spring. Situated within the Qixianling Hot Spring National Rainforest Park, the 254-room hotel is conveniently located 50 km from Lingshui Railway Station and 90 km from Sanya Phoenix International Airport.
John Greenleaf, Global Head of DoubleTree by Hilton, emphasized the brand&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding guest expectations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-introduces-a-new-mice-venue-in-hainan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces the new Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. This hotel, the Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel, aims to create a beach resort atmosphere.
The recently opened Hotel Baraquda Pattaya MGallery by Sofitel is a 72-room boutique hotel located in the city center. Its convenient location provides guests with easy walking access to shopping, dining, and entertainment. Designed around a nautical theme, the hotel offers 60 Deluxe rooms, eight Baraquda Suites, and four Baraquda Grand Suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-the-new-hotel-baraquda-pattaya-mgallery-by-sofitel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Work together at a beach resort and form new relationships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</guid><description>While new coworking spaces and startup events are constantly emerging, forging meaningful connections with startups outside of one&amp;rsquo;s immediate location can still be challenging. Coworking Camp aims to bridge this gap with its upcoming six-week program. This program offers startups and digital nomads a chance to network and explore business opportunities with like-minded individuals in a relaxed and comfortable environment.
Source: Coworking Camp website.
Matthias Zeitler, Chief Coworker, highlights the program&amp;rsquo;s focus on fostering valuable connections and providing a space for rejuvenation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Group discounts are available for the iftar buffet at Coral Beach Resort Sharjah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 12:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</guid><description>Source: Coral Beach Resort Sharjah website.
The Coral Beach Resort Sharjah, having just finished a full update of its rooms and amenities, is offering an iftar buffet at its Al Bahar Restaurant. The buffet will feature a variety of traditional Arabic and international dishes, with options like mixed grills, shawarma, hot and cold mezze, stews and biryani, in addition to soups, salads, snacks, and customary Ramadan beverages.
Jean Pierre Simon, the Regional General Manager for Northern Emirates at Coral Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, highlighted Al Bahar restaurant as the perfect location for gatherings to break the fast, suggesting guests round off their dining experience with classic Ramadan sweets like the ever-popular umm Ali and mouhalabia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/group-discounts-are-available-for-the-iftar-buffet-at-coral-beach-resort-sharjah/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sunway's Resort Cafe provides a range of dining options from breakfast to dinner, perfect for business meetings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 05:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</guid><description>Source: Sunway.
The recently opened Resort Cafe, situated on the lobby level of the luxurious Sunway Resort Hotel and Spa, accommodates 362 guests and showcases the diverse culinary heritage of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Malay, Chinese, and Indian populations.
Spanning 17,588 square feet, the restaurant presents eight distinct culinary themes: the impressive Monumental Fruit and Salad Towers, Malay Archipelago (featuring dishes from Malaysia, Singapore, and Indonesia), Indo-Chine (showcasing cuisine from Thailand and Vietnam), Oriental Far East (highlighting dishes from Japan, Korea, and China), Spices of India, Mirage of the Gulf (offering dishes from the Middle East), Best from the West (featuring Western comfort food, grills, rotisserie, and churrasco), and a dedicated dessert section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sunway-s-resort-cafe-provides-a-range-of-dining-options-from-breakfast-to-dinner-perfect-for-business-meetings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>