<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Phuket on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phuket/</link><description>Recent content in Phuket on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phuket/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choose from a variety of MICE packages available in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Three travel companies — Chōsen, The Slate, and Samujana — have designed productivity programs for businesses and workgroups. These programs offer a variety of environments to help teams achieve their best results.
For adventure junkies Source: Chosen website. A view of Bali.
Chōsen provides experiences tailored for teams that thrive on new adventures and challenges:
Activities include cliff jumping, canyoning, surfing, and cooking classes. Accommodation is available at their estate in Bali and other locations, including New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-from-a-variety-of-mice-packages-available-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GrabTaxi introduces GrabCar service in Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a mobile application for on-demand transportation in Southeast Asia, has introduced a new service in Phuket, Thailand, called GrabCar. This premium service aims to simplify transportation for Phuket visitors by offering a personalized riding experience.
Tourists can use the app to book a GrabCar and be picked up directly from their location within minutes, allowing them to conveniently and securely explore Phuket with just a few taps on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grabtaxi-introduces-grabcar-service-in-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Khiri Travel reveals the hidden gems of Phuket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 21:27:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</guid><description>Hidden Gems of Phuket: A Local&amp;rsquo;s Guide Have some free time during your Phuket business trip? Gonzalo Gil Lavedra, manager of Khiri Travel Thailand&amp;rsquo;s Phuket branch, suggests exploring the island&amp;rsquo;s lesser-known attractions and authentic experiences.
&amp;ldquo;Discovering the quiet side of Phuket, away from the typical tourist spots, is what makes me appreciate calling this place home,&amp;rdquo; he shares.
One such gem is the Gibbon Rehabilitation Centre within the Khao Phra Taeo forest reserve...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/khiri-travel-reveals-the-hidden-gems-of-phuket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>