<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Television on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/television/</link><description>Recent content in Television on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lonliness of the Long Distance Landline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 10:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</guid><description>Recent data shows people are rapidly ditching landlines. If Alexander Graham Bell were alive today, he&amp;rsquo;d have trouble reaching anyone on his original invention. Instead, he&amp;rsquo;d have much better luck using a cell phone, just like everyone else.
It&amp;rsquo;s not surprising that most people own a cell phone, or even multiple old ones. People want to be constantly connected, even when they perhaps shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be. Observe drivers at a stoplight, and you&amp;rsquo;ll likely spot several talking on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lonliness-of-the-long-distance-landline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regulation of Audiovisual Media Services and the "Exception for Newspapers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 01:20:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Case C-347/14 New Media Online GmbH v. Bundeskommunikationssenat, 21 October 2015
Traditionally, broadcasting and newspapers have been regulated differently. Newspapers have enjoyed more lenient, often self-regulatory, oversight. EU law harmonized television broadcasting through the Television without Frontiers Directive. Newspapers, if subject to EU law, fell under general free movement and competition rules. As technology evolved and online information services emerged, the Television without Frontiers Directive underwent revisions, becoming the Audiovisual Media Services Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regulation-of-audiovisual-media-services-and-the-exception-for-newspapers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The proposal by the EU Commission regarding the regulation of media freedom.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:33:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Photo credit: Bin im Garten, via Wikimedia Commons
In the 2021 State of the Union address, EU Commission President von der Leyen underscored the importance of media independence, stating that Europe needs a law to protect it. The proposed Media Freedom Act (MFA) aims to address this, building upon existing regulations like the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and the Digital Services Act (DSA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Media Flos to Mobile TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 12:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</guid><description>Television is everywhere. While it started with over-the-air broadcasts, it quickly spread to cable, satellite, and the internet through platforms like YouTube and IPTV. Now, mobile devices like cell phones are the new frontier for watching TV on the go.
Early mobile video relied on downloadable clips using cellular broadband networks like EV-DO. However, these networks struggle with bandwidth limitations, making it difficult to deliver high-quality real-time video without overloading the system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/media-flos-to-mobile-tv/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>