<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Telecom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telecom/</link><description>Recent content in Business Telecom on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telecom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VoIP Without The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-without-the-internet/</guid><description>Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) emerged as an alternative telephone service that utilizes existing broadband connections for both internet and phone services. This allows providers to bypass fees associated with leasing traditional copper phone lines, leading to more attractive bundled packages for customers. Theoretically, the internet&amp;rsquo;s capacity should easily accommodate low-bandwidth voice data.
However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case in reality. Internet paths, much like highways, can become congested, leading to bandwidth constraints, transmission delays (latency), and dropped data packets, all of which disrupt real-time communication like phone calls.</description></item><item><title>XO Offering Ethernet to the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 05:36:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-offering-ethernet-to-the-world/</guid><description>Global telecommunications companies now have a unique opportunity: access to 4 million commercial buildings across the U.S. for offering Ethernet services. This is made possible by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; new Ethernet Hub service.
While this might seem irrelevant to businesses unless they&amp;rsquo;re looking to cut costs on voice and data services, the potential savings hidden within XO&amp;rsquo;s recent press release are significant.
XO Communications is a competitive carrier, meaning they weren&amp;rsquo;t part of the traditional Bell Telephone system.</description></item><item><title>Why Bandwidth is Cheap Downtown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</guid><description>Want to increase your business internet speed without breaking the bank? Head downtown! The city center offers more competition and cheaper prices than anywhere else. Can&amp;rsquo;t relocate for better bandwidth deals? There&amp;rsquo;s a comparable solution that works for many businesses.
Why is bandwidth cheaper downtown when real estate is so expensive? The answer is density. Imagine real estate as a pie: limited supply and high demand for the best slices drive up prices.</description></item><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation.</description></item><item><title>Yes, There IS Rural Broadband For Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-there-is-rural-broadband-for-businesses/</guid><description>Many people are excited about the economic stimulus plan&amp;rsquo;s promise of expanded rural broadband access. However, you might already be able to get the internet speeds your rural business needs.
Most major internet providers have overlooked rural areas, not because rural businesses are less important, but because the cost of installing infrastructure like coaxial cables or fiber optic cables is difficult to recoup when there are fewer customers. This is why cable and DSL internet services are less common in the countryside.</description></item><item><title>Five Years Of The Explainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</guid><description>T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer turned five this month, with more than 800 posts published since its 2004 launch. Our initial goal was to clarify complex telecommunications services and provide businesses with competitive options. Over time, we&amp;rsquo;ve broadened our scope to encompass a wide range of products, services, and topics relevant to our audience. As we approach our second decade, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the &amp;ldquo;aughts&amp;rdquo; and explore potential future trends.
This explainer blog, as the name suggests, was launched alongside T1Rex.</description></item></channel></rss>