<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Environment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environment/</link><description>Recent content in Environment on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/environment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa Eco Benefits promote sustainability in every transaction</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 02:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</guid><description>Visa, a digital payment company, has introduced Visa Eco Benefits in the Asia Pacific region. This suite of sustainability solutions aims to help Visa cardholders understand the environmental effects of their everyday spending. They can track their carbon footprint from Visa transactions and explore options for offsetting their impact through carbon offsets or charitable donations via their bank&amp;rsquo;s app or website.
Banks in the Asia Pacific region that adopt Eco Benefits can offer these solutions to their Visa cardholders, addressing the increasing demand for environmentally conscious financial services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-eco-benefits-promote-sustainability-in-every-transaction/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover the most environmentally friendly hotels worldwide with GreenHotelWorld</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</guid><description>Source: GreenHotelWorld website.
GreenHotelWorld, in collaboration with TripAdvisor, now boasts the largest selection of verified eco-friendly hotels on a single platform. This was achieved by incorporating hotels from TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s GreenLeaders Program.
With a global reach, GreenHotelWorld curates over 8,000 hotels recognized for their demonstrably sustainable practices. Their categorization process utilizes standards from the Global Sustainable Tourism Council (GSTC), a respected international body that sets benchmarks for sustainable tourism and accredits green hotel certifications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-environmentally-friendly-hotels-worldwide-with-greenhotelworld/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anticipate more sustainable and environmentally-friendly buildings in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Building and Construction Authority (BCA) announced new initiatives during the opening ceremony of Singapore Green Building Week (SGBW). These initiatives, stemming from a review of the third Green Building Masterplan, focus on improving occupant indoor environmental quality, promoting energy-efficient buildings, and incorporating green practices into existing structures.
Desmond Lee, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Social and Family Development and Second Minister for National Development, was the guest of honor at the ceremony...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anticipate-more-sustainable-and-environmentally-friendly-buildings-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHG will no longer provide mini toiletries as bathroom amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</guid><description>Source: IHG. A shower with sink showing miniatures as amenities.
The InterContinental Hotels Group (IHG) is transitioning from small, individual toiletry bottles to larger, bulk amenity dispensers in all 843,000 rooms across its portfolio of hotels. This change, to be fully implemented by 2021, is part of a larger sustainability initiative and establishes IHG as the first global hotel company to entirely eliminate miniature bathroom products in favor of bulk-sized options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihg-will-no-longer-provide-mini-toiletries-as-bathroom-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Essent ruling a new milestone in the legal precedent for the free movement of goods?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</guid><description>A Reassessment of Proportionality and Discrimination in Light of the Essent Case Filippo Fontanelli, Lecturer in International Economic Law, University of Edinburgh
Introduction
The September 11, 2014, Essent case (Joined Cases C-204 to C-208/12) judgment by the Court of Justice of the EU presents a nuanced analysis of proportionality, weighing factors such as promoting free energy trade, safeguarding the environment and human health, adhering to international emission reduction agreements, bolstering local employment, and encouraging energy self-sufficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</a></p></description></item><item><title>REPowerEU: Expanding Europe's financial capacity post-pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</guid><description>Rosalba Famà, PhD student in EU law, Bocconi University
Photo credit: ThibaultC, via wikicommons media
In response to the energy crisis stemming from the Russian invasion of Ukraine, the European Union is implementing REPowerEU. Presented in May 2022, the comprehensive REPowerEU strategy encompasses proposals to modify existing energy directives and an ambitious industrial policy program aimed at achieving energy independence. This analysis will focus on the latter, referred to as the REPowerEU plan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Green Your Cell Phone For St. Patrick's Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</guid><description>On this St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day, let&amp;rsquo;s think about being green in more ways than one! Before the festivities begin, take a few moments to consider how you can help the environment.
You might be surprised to learn that millions of old cell phones are discarded yearly. They contain valuable resources like gold – enough to create a significant treasure if they were all collected. Instead of letting these resources go to waste, retrieve that old phone you have lying around, and let&amp;rsquo;s discover how it can benefit you and the planet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commonwealth has adopted the Living Lands Charter and has launched the Blue Charter project incubator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</guid><description>Commonwealth leaders have formally agreed to the Living Lands Charter: A Commonwealth Call to action on Living Lands (CALL). This charter represents a commitment from all 54 member countries to protect global land resources and collaborate on climate change, biodiversity loss, and sustainable land management.
This non-binding agreement, announced at the close of the 2022 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in Kigali, Rwanda, is the result of almost two years of discussions and negotiations with member countries, United Nations Rio Conventions, and other involved parties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Anyone can begin eliminating plastic from their lives at any time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</guid><description>Douglas Yeo, pictured second from the right, is the Course Director at DIWA and a dedicated environmental advocate. Although widely recognized for his role as a diver in the 2018 Thai cave rescue and his nomination for Singaporean of the Year, Yeo is also the driving force behind a growing movement to eliminate plastic use.
Known as the PlasticFREE initiative, this DIWA-supported campaign encourages individuals to minimize plastic waste. Participants are invited to start with small changes in their own lives and then spread the message to friends and family...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/anyone-can-begin-eliminating-plastic-from-their-lives-at-any-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Commission's suggestions for environmentally-friendly finance and the efforts of financial regulators to promote sustainability.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</guid><description>Thomas Piticchio The rising popularity of green politics has led investors to demand more sustainable investment options and increased transparency regarding their money&amp;rsquo;s whereabouts and usage. Consequently, financial intermediaries are introducing &amp;ldquo;green&amp;rdquo; financial products. These products are undergoing regulatory development by the European Commission, aiming to direct capital towards sustainability and clarify what defines a sustainable investment.
In 2018, the European Commission tasked a group of specialists from social, financial, and academic fields to formulate a sustainable finance strategy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-commission-s-suggestions-for-environmentally-friendly-finance-and-the-efforts-of-financial-regulators-to-promote-sustainability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Blog Action Day For A Less Toasty Tomorrow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</guid><description>Is it hot in there, or is it just me? Hold on to your hats, folks, because global warming is here, and it&amp;rsquo;s not waiting for anyone. We&amp;rsquo;re already seeing the effects, despite what some people might believe. Forget those freezing Midwest winters; the Arctic Ocean is melting at an alarming rate, opening up shipping routes and sparking international interest in its resources. It seems like everywhere you look, there&amp;rsquo;s evidence of climate change, from California wildfires to polar bears struggling to stay afloat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU strengthens the EU's position as an external player.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) partnership agreements with non-EU countries must utilize EU powers related to development and trade, even when those agreements include provisions related to other areas like transportation, the environment, and readmission. This judgment, delivered in the Commission v Council case, broadens the EU&amp;rsquo;s development policy concept, potentially increasing the EU&amp;rsquo;s influence in achieving its foreign policy goals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-strengthens-the-eu-s-position-as-an-external-player/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards are now accepting submissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</guid><description>Source: GCSA organizers. GCSA winners for 2019 at the GCSF in 2019.
If your company demonstrates a strong dedication to sustainability, we encourage you to apply for the 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards (GCSA).
The Alliance for Sustainable Development Goals (A•SDGs) is hosting the 2020 GCSA in collaboration with the Taiwan Academy of Corporate Sustainability (TACS), the Taiwan Institute for Sustainable Energy (TAISE), and the Center for Corporate Sustainability (CCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Malaysia to identify energy-efficient government buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</guid><description>Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Energy Commission, under the Ministry of Energy, Science, Technology, Environment and Climate Change (MESTECC), has introduced the National Building Energy Intensity (BEI) Labelling for Government Buildings.
This program strives to enhance energy efficiency in government-owned buildings within Malaysia, encouraging building owners to prioritize and improve energy conservation. Buildings are assigned a star rating based on their energy efficiency, with a five-star rating indicating the highest level of efficiency.
The initial phase, concluding in late 2018, encompasses 100 buildings belonging to ministries, departments, and agencies under MESTECC and the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Department...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save the Cell Phone, Save the World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 23:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</guid><description>Cell phones are frequently overlooked as a source of environmental concern, valuable resources, and potential income. While seemingly harmless, these devices contain toxic materials and represent a significant waste problem due to their short lifespans and frequent replacement.
A cell phone&amp;rsquo;s small size and durable exterior might make it seem environmentally benign, but the internal components tell a different story. Lead, cadmium, arsenic, mercury, plastics, and glass are all found within these devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-the-cell-phone-save-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi is sponsoring customers to participate in the Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 22:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</guid><description>Source: Digi Telecommunications.
Digi Telecommunications is sponsoring 200 customers to join the WWF-Malaysia Earth Hour 2015 Night Walk in Penang and Sunway Pyramid. This event coincides with the Earth Hour 2015 celebration on March 28, 2015.
As the Night Walk@Sunway&amp;rsquo;s corporate sponsor, Digi has donated RM35,000 to support WWF-Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s environmental conservation efforts.
Digi is sponsoring 200 walk packs, costing RM60 each, for its customers. 100 packs are designated for Night Walk@Sunway and 100 for Night Walk@Penang...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-is-sponsoring-customers-to-participate-in-the-earth-hour-2015-night-walk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get a ride and offset your carbon emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:02:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</guid><description>Grab users will soon have the option to lessen the environmental impact of their trips by utilizing a new carbon offset feature integrated into the Grab app.
Source: Grab.
Explaining the carbon
offset feature.
A recent study across six Southeast Asian countries revealed that 82% of Grab users are concerned about climate change and are taking steps to minimize their environmental impact. However, 44% of those concerned but not actively addressing it cited a lack of knowledge on how to act, while 31% found it too challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-ride-and-offset-your-carbon-emissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eco Friendly Hosting $3.75/mo.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/</guid><description>As Earth Day approaches, you might feel uneasy about using a web host that relies on electricity from a coal-powered plant, further consuming energy for server cooling. This conflict is especially true if environmental responsibility aligns with your values.
Fortunately, eco-friendly hosting services are available for under $4 per month.
Dotster offers affordable domains and web hosting, including basic web hosting for $3.75 a month. Beyond affordability, Dotster is committed to environmental responsibility through its green hosting program...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eco-friendly-hosting-375mo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore SMEs are being advised to view sustainability as a key to achieving growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 01:51:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</guid><description>Ang explains why sustainability is important for Singapore SMEs.
Embracing sustainability provides a competitive edge for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). It aligns them with the practices of larger corporations, potentially opening doors to becoming their suppliers.
Wilson Ang, Executive Director of Global Compact Network Singapore (GCNS), highlighted this during Fuji Xerox DocuWorld in Singapore. He emphasized that sustainability attracts a more discerning investor base, prompting SMEs to adapt to remain competitive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-smes-are-being-advised-to-view-sustainability-as-a-key-to-achieving-growth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Implementing the European Green Deal and Making the EU Maritime Transport Sector "Fit for 55": Is Pain Necessary for Gain?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 11:07:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</guid><description>Killian O’Brien, DAAD Lecturer (Fachlektor), University College London
To achieve its European Green Deal objectives, the EU aims to cut greenhouse gas emissions by at least 55% of 1990 levels by 2030. As part of this goal, the European Commission introduced the “Fit for 55” legislative package on July 14, 2021. This collection of measures aims to rapidly decarbonize the EU economy by significantly altering the trajectory of emissions and aligning EU policies and legislation across 12 sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/implementing-the-european-green-deal-and-making-the-eu-maritime-transport-sector-fit-for-55-is-pain-necessary-for-gain/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The KPMG index assesses the capacity of 140 countries to adapt to change</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</guid><description>According to the 2019 KPMG Change Readiness Index (CRI), countries in the Asia Pacific region are generally showing improvement in their approaches to climate change. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose two spots to number 2, while Taiwan jumped 18 places.
Published twice a year, the CRI is now in its fourth year. It ranks 140 countries* based on their preparedness for and response to major change events. This edition focuses on the capabilities countries need to effectively combat climate change and minimize related risks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU Grand Chamber "Ilva" judgment: Balancing environmental law and human rights from a Kirchberg perspective.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 05:19:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</guid><description>Jacques Bellezit, University of Strasbourg (France)
Photo credit: mafe de baggis, via Wikimedia Commons
To understand the historical development of European construction, one must acknowledge the European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC). Established following the Schumann Declaration on May 9th, 1950, the ECSC marked the first attempt to create a common market for coal and steel, deemed strategic materials. This initiative aimed to not only bolster post-war reconstruction in Europe but also to curb rearmament efforts on both sides of the Rhine during the nascent Cold War...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-grand-chamber-ilva-judgment-balancing-environmental-law-and-human-rights-from-a-kirchberg-perspective/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protecting data and smart meters: GDPR and the EU clean energy law's 'winter package'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giulia Pizza, FratiniVergano, European Lawyers - a Brussels-based law firm specialising in European and international law
Introduction
In late 2016, the European Commission introduced the “Clean Energy for All Europeans” legislative package to modernize Europe&amp;rsquo;s electricity market and encourage cleaner energy solutions. This push for &amp;ldquo;decentralization&amp;rdquo; is seen as a way to drive innovation and shift the focus to a demand-driven energy policy. The goal is to give consumers the tools they need to actively participate in this change...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Submit your entries for the Zayed Sustainability Prize now!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</guid><description>The Zayed Sustainability Prize, a prominent global sustainability award based in the UAE, is calling for submissions for its 13th annual edition. Winners in each category will receive US$600,000 to further develop their sustainability solutions and create global impact.
Dr. Sultan Ahmed Al Jaber, UAE Minister of State and Director General of the Zayed Sustainability Prize, expressed confidence that the Prize will continue to draw in top innovators worldwide, tackling pressing global sustainability issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Universiti Putra Malaysia is leaving a significant impact on the academic world with its free MOOC platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</guid><description>Universiti Putra Malaysia (UPM) is providing a free online learning platform accessible to both Malaysians and a global audience. This platform covers a variety of subjects.
UPM highlighted that this new learning format aligns with the current National Higher Education Strategic Plan, which stresses lifelong learning, e-learning, internationalization, and knowledge sharing. PutraMOOC utilizes video lectures, interactive forums, chat features, quizzes, and e-assessments.
Students can enroll in Putra Massive Open Online Course (PutraMOOC) online and finish a course in approximately seven to eight weeks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/universiti-putra-malaysia-is-leaving-a-significant-impact-on-the-academic-world-with-its-free-mooc-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Drowning in a Sea of Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</guid><description>Current estimations show approximately three billion mobile phone users globally, with a billion new devices sold annually. Given that phones are typically replaced every two to three years, this equates to roughly one billion phones becoming obsolete yearly. The question then arises: where do these discarded devices end up?
Contrary to assumptions that they are forgotten in drawers, a recent study revealed that only 44% of old phones remain unused at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>