<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VPN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vpn/</link><description>Recent content in VPN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vpn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations.</description></item><item><title>Buy Convergence By The Byte</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</guid><description>XO Communications is revolutionizing telecommunications by offering IP Network services priced by bandwidth usage instead of traditional lines or channels. This shift to an IP-based network and the use of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for telephone trunking are rendering traditional telephony services obsolete. By utilizing a packet-switched network and transmitting everything in packet protocol, voice, and data traffic can easily share a single circuit.
The concept of convergence, using one network for voice, video, and data, has gained traction with IT departments aiming to simplify network management and executives seeking cost reductions.</description></item><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>VyprVPN from Golden Frog now includes a server in Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Golden Frog, a company dedicated to online privacy and internet accessibility, has expanded its services to India. This new server, located in Mumbai, marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 14th in Asia and aims to provide Indian internet users with a secure and unrestricted online experience through their VyprVPN service.
&amp;ldquo;India, with its vast population and rapidly growing tech sector, will benefit greatly from this new server location,&amp;rdquo; says Sunday Yokubaitis, President of Golden Frog.</description></item><item><title>Types of VPN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 04:49:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-vpn-connections/</guid><description>VPNs are widely used in business today; you&amp;rsquo;ve likely used one without realizing it. They&amp;rsquo;re not just an extra layer of protection anymore—they&amp;rsquo;re crucial for safeguarding data.
Let&amp;rsquo;s differentiate between private and virtually private networks. Your physical LAN is a private network, making it difficult for someone to tap into your wiring. Similarly, WANs using dedicated lines (like T1) offer a high level of security, as physically accessing the lines is challenging.</description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple.</description></item><item><title>Different Types of VPN Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</guid><description>You prioritize the privacy of your network, but what happens when you need to connect to the outside world? Do you let anyone and everyone in, or do you secure your network across the distance using a private or virtually private network?
Before Virtual Private Networks (VPNs), there were private networks, and they still exist. Some situations demand such high security that the only way to guarantee control and prevent intrusions is through dedicated, point-to-point private lines.</description></item><item><title>Secure Any Public WiFi Hotspot</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 09:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-any-public-wifi-hotspot/</guid><description>We all know the feeling: you&amp;rsquo;re away from your secure office network or home WiFi, relying on public WiFi that makes you uneasy. While convenient, unsecured WiFi hotspots present a security risk. How can you be sure someone isn&amp;rsquo;t monitoring your activity with malicious software when you send private emails or sensitive data?
](http://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-1726600-11129503)
It&amp;rsquo;s a valid concern. Cybercrime is rampant, and tools for intercepting data on public WiFi are readily available.</description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Shows How The Converged Business Network Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</guid><description>Larger organizations have been moving towards network convergence since IP became the standard network protocol. However, smaller companies, often lacking substantial IT departments, haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted this approach as readily. This is changing. Convergence is now a viable option for businesses of all sizes.
What&amp;rsquo;s driving this shift? The answer, as always, is cost savings. In today&amp;rsquo;s business climate, reducing expenses is crucial. The real game-changer is the availability of managed convergence services.</description></item><item><title>Managed Security Moves To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud services are expanding beyond the familiar Infrastructure, Platform, and Software as a Service to include Security as a Service. Integra, for example, now offers a suite of Cloud Security Services, including a Cloud Firewall Service.
Many companies find managed security appealing because it removes the need for dedicated IT staff or investments in security hardware. Traditionally, this involved a monthly service fee and an on-premises security device. Cloud-based security takes it further, eliminating the need for physical hardware altogether.</description></item><item><title>What Is MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</guid><description>MPLS networks are frequently mentioned as a way to connect multiple business locations. But what exactly is MPLS, and why is it superior to other network architectures?
MPLS, or Multi-Protocol Label Switching, is a technology distinct from traditional circuit-switched or packet-switched networks. While it allows IP traffic transmission, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on IP routing.
The advantage of MPLS networks lies in their ability to handle almost any protocol without requiring conversions to fit the network structure.</description></item><item><title>Advantage of Dedicated Cloud Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-dedicated-cloud-connections/</guid><description>Companies of all sizes are increasingly adopting cloud services due to their cost-effectiveness. However, the assumption that a basic internet connection is sufficient for accessing these services is proving to be inaccurate in many situations.
While the internet&amp;rsquo;s widespread availability and affordability make it appealing for WAN services, its security concerns led to the development of VPNs. These secure tunnels encrypt data, allowing remote workers and branch offices to connect securely to corporate networks and transfer sensitive information.</description></item><item><title>You Need a Black Cloud Software Defined Perimeter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 14:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-need-a-black-cloud-software-defined-perimeter/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Trust is a liability in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. The internet, despite its merits, harbors a range of malicious actors, from professional criminals to state-sponsored hackers, all seeking to exploit vulnerabilities. Traditional security measures like firewalls and VPNs may not be enough.
Virtual Private Networks: A False Sense of Security?
VPNs were designed to emulate the security of private networks over the public internet. They create encrypted &amp;ldquo;tunnels&amp;rdquo; for data transmission, shielding it from prying eyes.</description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office.</description></item><item><title>Branching Out With MPLS and VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/branching-out-with-mpls-and-vpn/</guid><description>Is secure communication between multiple locations critical for your business? As businesses increasingly rely on electronic forms and transactions, traditional methods like fax machines, overnight mail, and dial-up connections are no longer sufficient. To stay competitive, businesses need real-time access to sales and inventory data, rapid transfer of large files like medical images and CAD drawings, and instant delivery of important documents. A broadband connection linking all your key locations is essential.</description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative.</description></item><item><title>Point to Point With T1, VPN, MPLS, Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-with-t1-vpn-mpls-ethernet/</guid><description>Imagine you have two business locations, such as a main office and a branch, that you need to connect seamlessly. A crucial aspect of this connection is electronic communication, including voice, data, and potentially video. This is where a reliable solution comes in.
One established method for connecting locations is using T1 lines, particularly for telephone systems. These lines, often called tie lines, link PBX systems at each location.
More broadly, this is known as point-to-point T1 service, a dedicated connection between two points.</description></item><item><title>Why International MPLS Connections Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 14:08:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-international-mpls-connections-make-sense/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple branches, even those with only two, are realizing the benefits of MPLS network services for domestic and global connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS offers, particularly for international connections, and why it&amp;rsquo;s a practical solution even for single-link setups.
Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS) is a network technology designed to carry data for numerous users while maintaining security, service quality, and crucial network attributes such as bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss.</description></item><item><title>Two Routes to Virtual Private Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:26:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-routes-to-virtual-private-networking/</guid><description>VPNs have become the go-to solution for connecting multiple business locations due to their cost-effectiveness and ease of maintenance. Managed service providers allow businesses to enjoy secure multipoint communication without the burden of extensive staffing or high monthly line lease fees.
Virtual private networking is now cloud-based, but the choice of cloud type remains. You can opt for a VPN solution using the public internet or choose a completely private network for enhanced performance.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Private Network Definition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-private-network-definition/</guid><description>While everyone understands the concept of a network, the meaning of a virtual private network (VPN) can be a bit unclear. Essentially, a VPN is a real network that utilizes technology to make its privacy seem virtual. For instance, the internet is inherently public, but methods exist to enhance the privacy of online communications, making them &amp;ldquo;virtually&amp;rdquo; private.
A genuinely private network necessitates stringent access control. Only authorized individuals and devices should be granted access.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>Why The Smart WAN Beats A Dumb Pipe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) are traditionally built using &amp;ldquo;dumb pipes,&amp;rdquo; which are simple bandwidth connections between two points. These connections are efficient at their primary function: transferring data packets. However, as IT requirements become more complex, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing need for more intelligent solutions. This can be achieved by either enhancing your internal IT capabilities or outsourcing these needs as a service.
Level 3 Communications, a leading provider of fiber network services, recognizes this shift from basic to high-performance networking demands.</description></item><item><title>Tricks That T1 Lines Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 23:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tricks-that-t1-lines-do/</guid><description>Many people associate T1 lines with dedicated broadband internet connections, but they offer various business-enhancing applications beyond that.
While T1 lines are widely recognized for providing businesses with reliable, dedicated internet connectivity, outperforming consumer-grade options like DSL and cable, their capabilities extend further. T1 connections are governed by regulations, ensuring prioritized support in case of issues and often come with service level agreements for guaranteed performance. Their symmetrical upload and download speeds of 1.</description></item><item><title>Private Point to Point Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-point-to-point-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Secure and transparent data transfer is crucial. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some popular methods to achieve this.
What Are Dedicated Private Lines?
Imagine a dedicated private line as a secure connection between two points facilitated by a carrier. It&amp;rsquo;s like having your own wiring, but provided by a third party, spanning across cities or even globally.
T1 Dedicated Lines
T1 lines are the digital version of old-school &amp;ldquo;dry loops&amp;rdquo; used by radio stations and alarm systems.</description></item><item><title>VPLS Connects Your Many LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-connects-your-many-lans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-connects-your-many-lans/</guid><description>Do you have multiple offices in your company? It&amp;rsquo;s likely that each office has its own local network for computers and potentially even internet-based phone systems. The question then becomes, how do you link these separate networks together?
The solution, unfortunately, is often complex and costly.
However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to simplify this process and potentially save money compared to your current individual connections: VPLS, or Virtual Private LAN Service. This service is provided by companies like Layer2 Communications and other competitive network providers.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item><item><title>Telephone and Internet for Chain Stores</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 20:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-and-internet-for-chain-stores/</guid><description>Cost-conscious small businesses need reliable communication systems. They can&amp;rsquo;t risk losing customers due to failed credit card transactions or dropped calls. Businesses with multiple locations also need efficient ways to connect their operations. Integrated T1 offers a solution that addresses these needs while staying budget-friendly.
Integrated T1 merges voice and data services onto a single line, combining the reliability of T1 phone lines with the efficiency of T1 internet connections. This approach minimizes costs without sacrificing quality.</description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS).</description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations.</description></item><item><title>AboveNet Offers Gigabit Ethernet For Enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-offers-gigabit-ethernet-for-enterprises/</guid><description>Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is now the standard for local area networks (LANs) in most businesses. However, many organizations still struggle with slow wide area network (WAN) connections, creating a bottleneck. Today, using slower WAN technologies like DS3 or even OC3 fiber alongside a Gigabit LAN is comparable to connecting a small straw to a fire hose.
Historically, slower WAN speeds were sufficient, but today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands much faster connections. In the past, computer networks were primarily internal, with external connections raising concerns.</description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds.</description></item><item><title>WAN Topology Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-topology-options/</guid><description>Businesses have various choices for connecting their branch offices, franchisees, suppliers, customers, and remote employees. The ideal network structure depends on the specific goals, whether it&amp;rsquo;s basic off-site backups or creating a virtual company spanning multiple states. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some prevalent WAN topologies used today.
The most widespread WAN is the Internet, connecting almost everyone everywhere. It&amp;rsquo;s a massive mesh network with affordable connections available through various methods like wireline, wireless, and fiber optic.</description></item><item><title>Meshed MPLS Forms a Cloud of Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</guid><description>Modern MPLS networks are replacing outdated Frame Relay networks for connecting multiple business sites. Their ability to handle almost any protocol with high quality and reliability has driven their popularity. A long-standing desire has been the ability to use multiple carriers across locations seamlessly within a managed MPLS network. This desire has finally been fulfilled.
AireSpring, a rapidly growing and innovative carrier, now offers a &amp;ldquo;Meshed MPLS Network.&amp;rdquo; But what exactly does this entail and how does it differ from the inherent mesh capabilities of any MPLS network?</description></item></channel></rss>