<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Glue on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glue/</link><description>Recent content in Glue on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/glue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of Misaligned Plinth Corner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-misaligned-plinth-corner/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), a previously repaired corner of the plinth required attention. The corners of these plinths commonly separate due to glue deterioration. While it&amp;rsquo;s usually straightforward to repair them with wood glue, this particular corner hadn&amp;rsquo;t been aligned properly during a prior attempt.
Furthermore, noticeable glue residue on the veneer needed addressing. Fortunately, Mr. Clean Magic Eraser Pads effectively removed the residue without sanding.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula.</description></item></channel></rss>