<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telx on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telx/</link><description>Recent content in Telx on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation and Connectivity in Miami</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 01:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</guid><description>Miami, Florida, serves as a strategic location for businesses aiming to connect with South America, Central America, the Caribbean, and regions across the Atlantic. Telx, a prominent provider of colocation services, offers comprehensive solutions tailored to meet these connectivity needs.
Telx has established a strong reputation in the financial services sector by delivering ultra-low latency connections to electronic trading floors. Their extensive network encompasses 15 colocation facilities within the United States and global connectivity to over 800 carriers, ensuring comprehensive and reliable connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-and-connectivity-in-miami/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Service Providers Colocate With Customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 05:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</guid><description>A new trend is emerging, and it&amp;rsquo;s not just about companies moving their data to the cloud. Now, cloud service providers are moving into the same facilities as their customers.
Why is this happening? Companies are realizing that running applications on distant servers can&amp;rsquo;t match the speed of having them on-site. While this can be addressed by investing in high-bandwidth, low-latency connections, it&amp;rsquo;s often more cost-effective to simply be in the same location as your provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-service-providers-colocate-with-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GTT Expands Ethernet Footprint With PacketExchange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</guid><description>GTT, a global telecommunications company, is expanding its Ethernet services globally by acquiring PacketExchange, an Ethernet provider. PacketExchange, based in London, boasts a substantial 10 Gigabit fiber optic IP network spanning Europe, the United States, and Asia, largely acquired through its acquisition of MZIMA Networks in 2010. This combined infrastructure offers private line services, MPLS, VPLS networking, and peering capabilities.
This acquisition highlights the growing dominance of Carrier Ethernet in telecommunications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Booming For Telx Interconnection and Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</guid><description>Despite the current economic downturn, data center provider Telx is experiencing a surge in construction at their main Chicago facility. This might seem counterintuitive during a recession, but it makes sense considering the ongoing technological transformation in business and finance.
Companies have shifted from manual processes to computer-based systems, leading to a client-server model that boosted efficiency and productivity. Now, forward-thinking companies are seeking new strategies for a competitive edge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Makes High Frequency Trading Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</guid><description>Computerized trading, including high frequency trading, is now the norm in the stock market. As seen on CBS News, algorithms can automatically execute trades when specific conditions are met.
A key challenge of automated trading is ensuring fairness by synchronizing timing for all participants. The New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) addressed this by creating a data center that standardized access time to 65 microseconds for everyone. However, this only applies to trading within the NYSE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Exchange For Miami, Dallas and Los Angeles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet is emerging as a strong contender to replace the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), as evidenced by the increasing number of Ethernet Exchanges that facilitate traffic sharing among carriers. Telx, a prominent interconnection and colocation provider, recently expanded its Ethernet Exchange services to Miami, Dallas, and Los Angeles. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the significance of Ethernet Exchange and its impact on the future of international wide-area networking.
The PSTN&amp;rsquo;s global reach and interoperability have contributed to its longstanding success, enabling communication between any two phones worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>