<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Economy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-economy/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Economy on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experimenting with EU governance in the Telecoms sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</guid><description>Marta Cantero (Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Helsinki | FiDiPro Project)
Creating a unified digital market for telecommunications within Europe is a primary goal of the current European Commission. [i] However, achieving this single market remains a distant prospect. The current multi-tiered regulatory model for European telecommunications relies heavily on individual nations&amp;rsquo; regulatory bodies to implement the EU&amp;rsquo;s telecom framework. Furthermore, enforcing this framework falls upon the Member States themselves under their own national procedures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Legal Challenges of Implementing the Digital Euro by the Central Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 00:21:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</guid><description>Dr. (Annelieke) Anne Marieke Mooij, Tilburg University
The European Central Bank (ECB) is preparing to introduce a digital euro, a central bank digital currency (CBDC). The ECB has explored several design options, ranging from restricted access for financial institutions to broad accessibility for all consumers via national central banks. While a final design hasn&amp;rsquo;t been chosen, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s statements suggest a preference for broader accessibility. This blog post will examine the primary legal hurdles associated with each design option...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/legal-challenges-of-implementing-the-digital-euro-by-the-central-bank/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>