<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CO2 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/co2/</link><description>Recent content in CO2 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/co2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Blog Action Day For A Less Toasty Tomorrow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</guid><description>Is it hot in there, or is it just me? Hold on to your hats, folks, because global warming is here, and it&amp;rsquo;s not waiting for anyone. We&amp;rsquo;re already seeing the effects, despite what some people might believe. Forget those freezing Midwest winters; the Arctic Ocean is melting at an alarming rate, opening up shipping routes and sparking international interest in its resources. It seems like everywhere you look, there&amp;rsquo;s evidence of climate change, from California wildfires to polar bears struggling to stay afloat...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blog-action-day-for-a-less-toasty-tomorrow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Environmentally Friendly Hosting is Super Green</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/</guid><description>A growing number of website creators are seeking environmentally responsible technology solutions. Super Green hosting offers an eco-friendly approach.
Super Green Hosting prioritizes environmental responsibility, aiming to minimize their carbon footprint. Internet usage consumes electricity, often generated from non-renewable sources like coal, contributing to carbon emissions.
To mitigate this, they focus on reducing power consumption, utilizing renewable energy like wind power, and planting trees to offset remaining carbon emissions, achieving carbon neutrality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/environmentally-friendly-hosting-is-super-green/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>