<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipe on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recipe/</link><description>Recent content in Recipe on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:40:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/recipe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new packaging for its premium-quality coffee blends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</guid><description>Cafédirect, a UK beverage company, has launched its Smooth, Lively, and Intense Roast Coffees in redesigned packaging.
These coffees are expertly crafted by Cafédirect’s own Q-graders (coffee experts) to showcase the rich flavor of the beans and highlight specific notes. Q grading guarantees consistency in coffee evaluation, much like sommeliers do for wines.
“The exciting aspect of crafting these blends is our ability to select coffees that complement one another. Blending different varieties and regional beans not only allows Cafédirect to tailor the coffee to a particular taste profile but also provides you with a consistent cup of coffee,” explained Georgios Kokkalis, Q Grader and Production Manager at Cafédirect UK.</description></item><item><title>Allspice Institute develops recipes inspired by Cafédirect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allspice-institute-develops-recipes-inspired-by-caf-direct/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:57:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/allspice-institute-develops-recipes-inspired-by-caf-direct/</guid><description>Culinary experts from the Allspice Institute collaborated with Cafédirect to develop innovative recipes featuring their coffee blends.
Cafédirect, a UK beverage company, unveiled new packaging for its Smooth, Lively, and Intense Roast Coffees. The launch event showcased coffee-infused recipes created in partnership with the Allspice Institute, a renowned culinary school.
Chef Sakthivel Karuppiah, COO of Allspice, prepared coffee-smoked tandoori chicken using coffee in two unique ways. He marinated the chicken in coffee for tenderness and then smoked it using spent coffee grounds.</description></item></channel></rss>