<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Long Distance Phone Calls on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-phone-calls/</link><description>Recent content in Long Distance Phone Calls on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 04:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-phone-calls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Add International Capability To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 04:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-capability-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of wireless phones allows mobile professionals to stay connected consistently. However, international calls remain a challenge due to expensive rates. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: international dial-around services.
These services, such as TEL3Advantage, seamlessly integrate with existing cell phone plans. Essentially, they allow users to make international calls at significantly reduced rates by routing them through the dial-around service instead of their regular carrier.
For example, TEL3Advantage offers a rate of 1.</description></item><item><title>Where Competition Is Cutting Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-competition-is-cutting-telecom-costs/</guid><description>In this day and age, everyone is trying to save money. Your monthly telecom costs are a great place to start. Telecom expenses are often high and confusing, so it’s a good idea to take a close look at your bills and see if you can find ways to reduce costs or find a better deal. Keep in mind that pricing can vary significantly depending on your location.
We often assume that the cost of goods and services is relatively consistent regardless of location.</description></item></channel></rss>