<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Norton on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/norton/</link><description>Recent content in Norton on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/norton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The attitudes towards cybercrime and security in Singapore vary across different generations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attitudes-towards-cybercrime-and-security-in-singapore-vary-across-different-generations/</guid><description>This past week, I encountered WhatsApp spam shortly after a friend forwarded a McDonald&amp;rsquo;s discount coupon from Sniflr. Upon researching, I discovered Sniflr is a phishing scam that tricks people into sharing the coupon with 10 friends on WhatsApp, adding those numbers to a spam list.
Yesterday, a promoted tweet on my Twitter feed advertised a S$100 discount on a S$120 purchase at NTUC, a popular Singaporean supermarket chain. However, a Google search revealed a months-old news article warning about fake NTUC coupons on Facebook, a claim supported by NTUC&amp;rsquo;s official Twitter account.</description></item><item><title>Are you still using Windows XP? Norton and Qihoo 360 are here to assist you</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-still-using-windows-xp-norton-and-qihoo-360-are-here-to-assist-you/</guid><description>The AV-Test Institute, located in Germany, tested ten antivirus programs for Windows XP. Out of these, Qihoo 360 Internet Security 9 and Norton Internet Security 2014 proved most effective.
Source: Qihoo 360. AV-TEST Report: Exploit Protection on Windows XP
The institute designed 54 attack simulations using various methods and vulnerabilities to thoroughly test each program. The tested antivirus solutions included products from Qihoo 360, Avast, AVG, Avira, Bitdefender, Eset, Kaspersky, and Norton.</description></item></channel></rss>