<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Europe on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/europe/</link><description>Recent content in Europe on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/europe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU-ASEAN Business Council is pleased to receive the Joint Communication on the EU-ASEAN partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</guid><description>The European Union (EU) and the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) are strengthening their ties through a Joint Communication aimed at fostering a strategic partnership. This initiative seeks to bolster cooperation across various sectors.
The Joint Communication outlines several key proposals, including elevating trade relations between the two regions by pursuing an ambitious region-to-region free trade agreement. This builds upon existing bilateral agreements between the EU and individual ASEAN member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-is-pleased-to-receive-the-joint-communication-on-the-eu-asean-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China provides flights from Beijing to Vienna and Barcelona four days a week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 10:07:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</guid><description>As a prominent member of Star Alliance, the largest global airline network, Air China is actively expanding its flight schedule in Europe. The airline aims to bridge the gap in nonstop flights between East Asia and Barcelona and increase flight frequency between Beijing and Vienna.
Source: Air China
This new Beijing-Vienna-Barcelona route will be Air China&amp;rsquo;s 23rd European route, creating a direct link between East Asia and Central and Southern Europe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-provides-flights-from-beijing-to-vienna-and-barcelona-four-days-a-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>