<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LG on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lg/</link><description>Recent content in LG on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LG Stylus 2 will make its first appearance at MWC 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</guid><description>LG will introduce the LG Stylus 2 at the upcoming Mobile World Congress 2016 in Barcelona, Spain.
Source: LG. The LG Stylus 2.
The LG Stylus 2 is slimmer and lighter than its predecessor, measuring 7.4mm thick and weighing 145g. This follow-up to the G4 Stylus boasts a 5.7&amp;quot; HD display for an enhanced viewing experience.
Using the LG Stylus 2 mimics the experience of writing with a traditional pen and notepad.</description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>LG Electronics has introduced a new website dedicated to product security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</guid><description>LG Electronics has launched a dedicated website to address security concerns related to their mobile products. The website, managed by LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security Response Team (PSRT), will serve as a central hub for security announcements, updates, and a platform for reporting vulnerabilities.
LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security website will feature regular updates and bulletins on security matters concerning their mobile products, aiming to provide a secure and safe user experience. The website will prioritize vulnerabilities based on their severity, starting with the most critical ones, followed by high, moderate, and low-risk threats, including those identified by Google for the Android operating system.</description></item><item><title>LG introduces a new high-end beauty brand for the home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has introduced LG Pra.L, its high-end line of at-home beauty devices, in Singapore. The collection includes four devices: the Dual Cleanser, Galvanic Ion Booster, Total Lift Up Care, and Derma LED Mask, each designed to cleanse, nourish, lift, and firm the skin.
Inspired by the idea that beauty comes from within, LG Pra.L aims to elevate skincare routines for quicker, visible results. All four devices prioritize user convenience with features like silicone handles for grip, voice-guided instructions, USB-C charging, and long battery life for portability.</description></item><item><title>LG will be showcasing its newest Ultra monitors at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</guid><description>At CES, LG Electronics (LG) will showcase its newest Ultra monitors, featuring UltraWide models for productivity and UltraGear monitors designed for gaming.
2019 LG UltraWide Monitor
Source: LG. The new 49&amp;quot; UltraWide monitor.
Known for its innovation in the UltraWide monitor market, LG&amp;rsquo;s latest 49-inch model (49WL95) offers a 32:9 aspect ratio curved screen designed to enhance productivity. Its size is equivalent to two 27-inch Quad High Definition displays combined, with a resolution of 5,120 x 1,440 and 108 pixels per inch for clarity.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Flex2 provides a greater amount of curved excellence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the G Flex2, the newest iteration of its curved smartphone, at the 2015 International CES. The first G Flex received praise for its unique design and innovative approach. A year later, the G Flex2 improves upon its predecessor with an enhanced design, increased speed, and added user convenience.
The LG G Flex2 features a Qualcomm Snapdragon 810 processor for faster performance, making it the first smartphone to officially utilize this technology.</description></item><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen.</description></item><item><title>Free Cell Phones Galore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-cell-phones-galore/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m looking at 26 different cell phones offered by major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Sprint, T-Mobile, and Verizon. They vary in model and price, but they all have one key thing in common: they&amp;rsquo;re free.
You might think these are just outdated phones that no one wants, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case.
For example, there are several BlackBerry models available for free with a new AT&amp;amp;T wireless plan at standard rates. These include the BlackBerry Bold 9700 Black, BlackBerry Curve 8520 Black, and BlackBerry Curve 8900 Silver.</description></item><item><title>The B8S 4K OLED TV has been launched by LG Electronics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-b8s-4k-oled-tv-has-been-launched-by-lg-electronics/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s New B8S 4K OLED TV Offers High-End Features at an Accessible Price LG Electronics, a top OLED TV brand, is strengthening its market position with the new LG B8S 4K OLED TV. This Korean-made TV joins the 2018 4K OLED lineup, boasting impressive features like the α (Alpha) 7 processor, 4K Cinema HDR, and LG&amp;rsquo;s ThinQ Artificial Intelligence (AI).
The α7 processor delivers lifelike images characterized by rich colors, sharp details, and impressive depth, enhancing realism.</description></item><item><title>LG has released an updated version of the TONE INIFINIM around-the-neck wireless headset just in time for CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</guid><description>Source: LG. The TONE INFINIM HBS-910 headsets will debut at CES 2016.
LG Electronics (LG) will introduce its latest LG TONE INFINIM (HBS-910) headsets at CES 2016. The wireless neckband headset boasts a modernized design and exceptional audio quality.
As the next generation of the HBS-900, the new TONE INFINIM retains key features of its predecessor, like retractable earbuds and Harmon/Kardon audio. It also introduces upgraded Quad-Layer Speaker Technology for a top-tier audio experience with enhanced balance across the entire sound spectrum.</description></item><item><title>The V40ThinQ smartphone by LG has been revealed in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has launched the LG V40ThinQ, a new smartphone with five cameras. Designed for today&amp;rsquo;s multimedia storytellers, the device is marketed as a powerful tool for content creation.
Source: LG.
Staying true to the V series design, the LG V40ThinQ boasts an enhanced 6.4&amp;quot; FullVision OLED display with even slimmer bezels. It runs on the Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 Mobile Platform, coupled with 6 GB of RAM and 128 GB of internal storage, promising a superior smartphone camera experience.</description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities.</description></item><item><title>LG has introduced the G3 Beat, a mid-tier model of the G3, in Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the LG G3 Beat in Korea on July 18th. This mid-range version of their flagship G3 smartphone provides a comparable high-quality experience, incorporating the Floating Arc design and rapid Laser Auto Focus technology in a smaller form factor with a 5-inch thin-bezel display.
Dr. Jong-seok Park, President and CEO of LG Electronics Mobile Communications Company, emphasized the growing consumer demand for a balanced mix of aesthetics, functionality, performance, and affordability.</description></item><item><title>LG will be unveiling its 2020 laptops at CES 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 01:23:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-unveiling-its-2020-laptops-at-ces-2020/</guid><description>Source: LG. The LG gram 14T90N in action.
LG&amp;rsquo;s 2020 gram laptops maintain their focus on lightweight, compact design and long battery life, with the added benefit of improved performance. This refreshed lineup boasts a sleek, minimalist aesthetic and enhanced features.
Leading LG&amp;rsquo;s new gram series are the LG gram 17 (model 17Z90N), LG gram 15 (model 15Z90N), LG gram 14 (model 14Z90N), and the 14&amp;quot; LG gram 2-in-1 (model 14T90N).</description></item><item><title>If you ask LG ThinQ AI TVs, Google Assistant will respond</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-ask-lg-thinq-ai-tvs-google-assistant-will-respond/</guid><description>LG Electronics has integrated the recently launched Google Assistant into their OLED and SUPER UHD TVs.
This feature, available on all LG ThinQ AI TV models, enables users to search for information, check weather forecasts, and more using voice commands, all without interrupting their TV viewing.
Previously, voice commands were limited to basic functions like changing channels or adjusting volume. Now, users can search for specific content using the TV remote, for example, &amp;ldquo;show me romantic comedy movies on Netflix&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;show me yoga videos&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>The LG Watch Urbane 2nd edition also functions as a phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG claims its Watch Urbane 2nd Edition is the first Android Wear smartwatch to offer cellular connectivity. The watch will launch globally this month, starting with the US and Korea, followed by other major markets in the coming months.
The LG Watch Urbane 2nd Edition works with both Android and iOS smartphones, giving users the freedom to answer calls and check messages without relying on their phones.</description></item></channel></rss>