<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electrolytic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electrolytic/</link><description>Recent content in Electrolytic on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electrolytic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the Main PCB and Installation of a Biasing Trimmer for TR3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 07:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</guid><description>After getting the Beogram 4002 (5513) operational again, I focused on fully restoring the main PCB. This involved installing a trimmer to correctly calibrate TR3, the transistor responsible for amplifying the signal from the record detection sensor. The board&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown below:
The RPM relay and trimmers had already been replaced by the owner. I finished the restoration by replacing all electrolytic capacitors
and adding a trimmer to enable bias adjustment at the base of TR3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-main-pcb-and-installation-of-a-biasing-trimmer-for-tr3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Main and Power Supply PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 12:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the reservoir and motor capacitors on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to focus on the main and power supply PCBs. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to replace the RPM relay and trimmers alongside the electrolytic capacitors due to their susceptibility to corrosion.
The main PCB in its original state can be seen here:
A closer look at the outdated Siemens relay and RPM trimmers:
And the outcome after component replacement:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-main-and-power-supply-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, I focused on replacing components. Using a custom 3D-printed adapter, I substituted the large 4700/1000uF capacitor with modern, compact 105C-rated alternatives. The adapter ensured compatibility with the original mounting hardware.
Following this, I replaced all the tantalum and electrolytic capacitors on the main circuit board, refreshing its components for improved reliability and performance.
The only remaining capacitor, located on the output relay board, will be replaced when I disassemble the keypad to install a professionally refurbished replacement sourced from a Danish Beo expert...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Total Recap - Replacement of all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 10:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>This article revisits a complete restoration of a Beocord 9000 cassette deck, focusing on the replacement of electrolytic capacitors for improved long-term reliability. While not as crucial as with amplifiers due to lower operating temperatures, capacitor replacement is recommended for optimal performance.
The Beocord 9000, designed for serviceability, allows access to its numerous electrolytic capacitors. Unlike its predecessors, it offers easier access by removing the front and back panels instead of extracting the main circuit boards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-total-recap-replacement-of-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and RPM Adjustment Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 01:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</guid><description>Some time ago, I refurbished a Beogram 4002 DC platter motor for a client in California. However, even after the motor was reinstalled, the turntable still exhibited noticeable speed variations at 45 RPM. This often indicates a problem with the RPM relay, specifically oxidation. These relays tend to fail at 45 RPM first because most Beograms are typically used at 33 RPM, leaving the 45 RPM contacts unused and prone to oxide buildup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-rpm-adjustment-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Too Early Arm Lowering and RPM Change During START</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5524) turntables I&amp;rsquo;ve been repairing had a recurring issue: during the start-up sequence, the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t consistently lower at the 30 cm mark. Occasionally, the RPM would unexpectedly switch to 45 right after pressing start.
Troubleshooting was challenging because the problem was intermittent. I replaced all the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay, and trimmers, as detailed on my blog. To test, I installed the boards in my own Beogram 4002 (5513)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-too-early-arm-lowering-and-rpm-change-during-start/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs and the AC Platter Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on the Beogram 4000, the next stage was to substitute the electrolytic capacitors, the RPM control relay and trimmers, and the AC platter motor. The initial setup, including the original reservoir, motor capacitor, and AC platter motor, was documented before removal.
After removing the existing components, new capacitors were installed in a custom-designed 3D printed holder, designed to fit the original strap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-and-the-ac-platter-motor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): Rebuilding the Main and Output PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</guid><description>I recently got the main circuit board, output circuit board, and DC motor from a Beogram 4002 (5524) turntable. A customer in the UK sent them to me to fix because the platter&amp;rsquo;s RPM wasn&amp;rsquo;t consistent and the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower to the correct position when starting.
My usual process for these is to replace the electrolytic capacitors, install a new relay, and swap the single-turn RPM adjustment knobs with 25-turn ones for more precise control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-rebuilding-the-main-and-output-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Preamplifier and the Radio Amplifier Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 01:47:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s review the Beocord 5000! This model contains many tantalum capacitors that, due to their age (around 35 years), should be replaced. Tantalum capacitors pose a fire risk if they short circuit because of the intense heat released when tantalum reacts with oxygen. While tantalum capacitors were favored in the 1970s due to their smaller size compared to aluminum electrolytic capacitors, advancements in manufacturing have closed the size gap. Today, modern aluminum capacitors can be just as small as the older tantalum ones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-preamplifier-and-the-radio-amplifier-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Electrolytic Capacitors, the RPM Relay, and Adjusting the Motor Signal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 20:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</guid><description>My work on the Beogram 4000 turntable restoration continued with replacing all the electrolytic capacitors on the main board and power supply. I used high-quality, long-lasting Japanese components rated at 105C. Knowing that the RPM relays in these models can fail over time, I decided to swap out the old relay with a new one for improved long-term reliability. My objective is to restore these vintage turntables to like-new condition, both aesthetically and functionally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-electrolytic-capacitors-the-rpm-relay-and-adjusting-the-motor-signal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of New Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Using a 3D Printed Adapter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 15:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring a Beogram 4000 and it was time to replace the large capacitors. This is a process I enjoy, made easier with a 3D printed adapter I designed. This adapter allows for the use of smaller, modern capacitors while maintaining a neat and organized appearance. I have a previous post detailing the connections for anyone who might find it helpful, as there are several jumpers that require re-soldering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-new-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-using-a-3d-printed-adapter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 5000 (4715/4716): Recapping the Power Supply, Motor Control, Electronic Switch and Operational Control Boards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 05:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</guid><description>The restoration continues! Today, I replaced the remaining electrolytic capacitors on my Beocord 5000 (4715/4716). New electrolytics bring peace of mind!
The power supply board, including its reservoir and AC motor capacitors, along with the motor control, electronic switch, and operational control boards, were all addressed:
The Motor Control board, responsible for the take-up motor, had only one Tantalum capacitor that needed replacement:
Here it is after the replacement:
Next is the Electronic Switch board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-5000-47154716-recapping-the-power-supply-motor-control-electronic-switch-and-operational-control-boards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the carriage transport and arm lowering mechanisms, the electrolytic capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration project required attention. Replacing the original reservoir and motor capacitors in AC motor Beograms is always satisfying, and the 4000 boasts an impressive collection of large capacitors.
The initial step involved removing the outdated capacitors. A quick assessment using a BK LCR tester identified two faulty capacitors. One of the 2200uF capacitors registered a meager 7...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Reservoir and Motor Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:06:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the gold plating of all switch terminals on a Beogram 4000 restoration project, the next step involved addressing the electronics. The restoration typically begins by replacing outdated reservoir and motor capacitors, as they are frequently out of specification and nearing failure. The image provided showcases these original components.
To ensure proper fitment of the (smaller) modern replacement capacitors, a custom 3D-printed fixture was designed and utilized. This fixture secures the capacitors in the correct position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-reservoir-and-motor-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and Rebuilding of the Platter RPM Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 18:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</guid><description>During the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable, the electrolytic capacitors were replaced and new relays were installed to enhance RPM stability. The aging tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail catastrophically, were replaced as a precautionary measure. The main board was refurbished, replacing the electrolytic capacitors and installing new relays, including a custom-designed replacement for the Siemens relay that ensures precise RPM control.
The original reservoir capacitor, a dual-capacitor unit no longer in production, was replaced with a 3D-printed fixture housing two modern capacitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-rebuilding-of-the-platter-rpm-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the AC Motor and Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s printed circuit boards, attention shifted to the capacitors associated with the reservoir and motor, as well as the AC motor itself. The capacitor and motor section appeared as shown before any servicing.
Visual inspection revealed leakage from the larger capacitors, indicating a critical need for replacement. The extent of the capacitor bay&amp;rsquo;s condition was evident upon their removal.
The AC motor was extracted for servicing, taking advantage of its disconnected state from the capacitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Recapping the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:19:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</guid><description>During my Beogram 4000 restoration, I replaced all electrolytic capacitors as a preventative measure, opting for durable 105C types from reputable Japanese brands. Tantalum capacitors, particularly in older equipment, can fail dramatically, even catching fire.
On the power supply board, I discovered a missing screw and a loose one, potentially creating a dangerous short circuit scenario. Thankfully, no damage was evident. I replaced the tantalum capacitors and secured the board with a new stainless steel M3 screw...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-recapping-the-pcbs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs and Reservoir Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the refurbishment of the tonearm and drive carriage mechanisms on this Beogram 4002 (5513), attention turned to the electronics. The initial phase involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, RPM trimmers, and the relay to guarantee smooth operation for years to come.
The main PCB in its original state is shown here.
The same PCB is pictured here after component replacement.
This image provides a detailed view of the RPM control section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs-and-reservoir-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Reservoir and Motor Phase Capacitors Replacement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:25:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</guid><description>I recently provided a customer with replacement capacitors for his Beogram 4000 turntable, along with a 3D-printed adapter I designed.
He had been experiencing problems with the motor, as it was only displaying half waveforms. This suggested an issue with either the phase capacitor or the power supply reservoir capacitors. After installing the new components, the problem was completely resolved. You can find more details about this process in my original post here: link to my original post about this procedure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-reservoir-and-motor-phase-capacitors-replacement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, RPM Relay and Trimmers on the Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild on this Beogram 4002 (5513), the main PCB was addressed. All electrolytic capacitors were swapped with high-quality, Japanese-made, 105C-rated capacitors. The existing Tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail dramatically, were preemptively replaced with modern equivalents to avoid any potential issues. Images illustrate the original board and the sections targeted for capacitor replacement.
The author designed a replacement for the original Siemens relay using a modern, fully encapsulated SMD relay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs - New Capacitors, RPM Trimmers and RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the motor and reservoir capacitors in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step involved rebuilding the PCBs. This typically involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM trimmers, and the RPM relay. The main PCB, which is difficult to remove due to its hardwiring, was &amp;lsquo;flipped&amp;rsquo; for component replacement.
After replacing the components, the rebuilt board was ready for installation. A new relay was used, as the original Siemens relays often experience oxidation, hindering proper RPM switching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs-new-capacitors-rpm-trimmers-and-rpm-relay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board – a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of Main and Output Printed Circuit Boards, and a New Reservoir Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 05:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration continued with a focus on the PCBs after addressing the decayed transport lock bushings. The main PCB was first, as shown below:
In addition to replacing all electrolytic capacitors, the RPM relay and trimmers were targeted due to their susceptibility to corrosion and impact on RPM stability. The following image highlights the RPM section in its initial condition:
Modern, encapsulated 25-turn trimmers replaced the old ones, and a new relay was installed (interested enthusiasts can obtain a replacement relay by email or through the contact form)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-main-and-output-printed-circuit-boards-and-a-new-reservoir-capacitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Original Dual Main Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</guid><description>While restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513), I had the chance to improve my design for a replacement part for the reservoir capacitor. This part lets me use two modern, high-temperature Japanese capacitors in place of the original dual-capacitor unit, which is no longer available. My previous design worked, but this new version is more robust and easier to 3D print. I&amp;rsquo;m getting better at designing for 3D printing; for instance, I learned to minimize overhangs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, New Relays and New RPM Trimmers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 on my workbench needed its electrolytic capacitors replaced. Given their age, I also replaced the tantalum capacitors, which are prone to failure due to their highly reactive electrodes. The following photo shows the main board before the replacements, with the tantalum capacitors visible as blue and red dots:
As part of my standard restoration process, I replace the trimmers and relay in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s RPM control circuit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-new-relays-and-new-rpm-trimmers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>