<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hospitality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hospitality/</link><description>Recent content in Hospitality on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hospitality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Improve efficiency in the hospitality and retail industries with Epson solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 05:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</guid><description>Epson Singapore, a company that provides point-of-sale (POS) and labeling printers, presented its newest POS solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), a major trade show in Asia for food and hospitality products. Their aim was to demonstrate how these solutions could make operations smoother and more cost-effective for the food and hospitality sectors.
At FHA2016, Epson collaborated with system integrators Enterprise Advance System Intelligence (EASI) and POS Square to design their booth as a theme park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-efficiency-in-the-hospitality-and-retail-industries-with-epson-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian students are focusing on hospitality management programs at LHE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</guid><description>Asian students make up a significant portion of the student population at the four hospitality schools operated by Laureate Hospitality Education (LHE): Glion Institute of Higher Education, Les Roches International School of Hotel Management, Kendall College, and Blue Mountains International Hotel Management School.
Source: LHE. From left, Hou, Tatar, Williams Knight.
Judy Hou, CEO of Glion Institute of Higher Education, noted a growing demand for LHE&amp;rsquo;s programs (offered in Switzerland, the US, and their branch campuses) throughout the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-students-are-focusing-on-hospitality-management-programs-at-lhe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take a virtual tour of Emaar hotels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</guid><description>Source: Emaar. Using panoramic photography and videography, each virtual tour showcases the hotel&amp;rsquo;s features in detail.
Emaar Hospitality Group, the hospitality and leisure branch of Emaar Properties, has launched 360-degree virtual tours of its hotels in Dubai, UAE. These tours, created with high-definition photos and videos, allow potential guests to experience each hotel&amp;rsquo;s unique offerings, explore its various aspects, and make well-informed booking decisions.
The virtual tours encompass properties under the luxury Address Hotels + Resorts brand, the upscale lifestyle Vida Hotels and Resorts brand, and the new contemporary mid-scale Rove Hotels brand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-virtual-tour-of-emaar-hotels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jin Jiang International Hotels and Hanwha Hotels &amp; Resorts have officially merged their loyalty programs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</guid><description>Jin Jiang International Hotels from China and Hanwha Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts from Korea have joined their loyalty programs.
Starting September 1st, members of Jin Jiang&amp;rsquo;s J-Club and Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s THE PLUS will share membership benefits. This includes perks like discounts on rooms, food, and beverages, as well as late check-outs and room upgrades at both hotel groups. J-Club&amp;rsquo;s over 14 million members will also have access to Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s resorts and golf courses across Korea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Numerous innovations showcased at Food&amp;HotelAsia 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</guid><description>Display at the Suntec venue.
The Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) and ProWine Asia (PWA) trade shows are predicted to draw tens of thousands of attendees during their joint four-day run in Singapore, from April 24th to 27th.
This year marks the largest event yet. Visitors can explore exhibits from over 3,500 international food, beverage, and hospitality exhibitors throughout 120,000 sq m at FHA. In addition, PWA 2018 features 300 international wine and spirits exhibitors across 7,500 sq m...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langham Hospitality Group reintroduces MICE incentive program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 19:12:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</guid><description>Source: Langham Hospitality Group.
Langham Hospitality Group has reintroduced its Double the Extra Mile PLUS program. This initiative offers extra benefits to those who plan and organize events. Bookings are open from April 1st to June 30th, 2016, for events happening between July 1st and December 31st, 2016, at participating Langham and Langham Place hotels.
Planners and organizers can benefit from doubled hotel rewards or miles from 11 different frequent flyer/travel and lifestyle programs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langham-hospitality-group-reintroduces-mice-incentive-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Club Carlson celebrates reaching one million members in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Carlson Rezidor&amp;rsquo;s international hotel rewards program, Club Carlson, celebrated a milestone by awarding its one millionth member in the Asia Pacific region with one million Club Carlson Gold Points.
The lucky recipient, Rong Weiji, is a Sales and Marketing Division Manager at Santen Pharmaceutical. He became the millionth member upon checking in at the Radisson Blu Shanghai New World on August 22, 2014.
When asked about his hotel preferences, Mr. Weiji explained that he values brand recognition, quality, service, and location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/club-carlson-celebrates-reaching-one-million-members-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality is introducing an upgraded hotel sleep experience for travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality
SilverNeedle Hospitality, a company focused on hospitality investment, management, and development, is launching the SilverNeedle DreamWeave Sleep System to enhance the sleep quality of its guests. This system will be implemented in all new hotels joining their network across midscale to luxury categories and will be gradually introduced to existing properties in those segments over time.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality, emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving business travel by acknowledging the importance of sleep for their guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cristal Group has created a unique multilingual reservations tool that does not charge commissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 10:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</guid><description>Cristal Group is set to become the first hotel chain globally to introduce its own commission-free reservation platform, aiming to offer more affordable hotel bookings.
This month, a new multilingual website will be launched, powered by a proprietary booking engine. According to Kamal Fakhoury, Cristal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, this new platform will simplify the booking process for Cristal Hotels, featuring language options such as Arabic and Chinese, among others.
He stated, &amp;ldquo;With hotels in Abu Dhabi, Iraq, Lebanon, and upcoming properties in Saudi Arabia, we are building a global customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cristal-group-has-created-a-unique-multilingual-reservations-tool-that-does-not-charge-commissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A white paper providing solutions for talent management in the Chinese hospitality industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 13:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</guid><description>Florida International University&amp;rsquo;s Chaplin School of Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Management (CSHTM) and its Institute for Hospitality &amp;amp; Tourism Education &amp;amp; Research (IHTER) have published a new resource for HR professionals and hospitality businesses, particularly those working with Chinese markets. The white paper, titled &amp;ldquo;Managing Growing Pains of China’s Relentless Hotel Development Pipeline,&amp;rdquo; examines the significant lack of qualified talent within China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding hotel industry. The paper offers practical solutions such as professional development programs, conflict resolution strategies, and clearly defined career paths to attract and retain skilled employees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-white-paper-providing-solutions-for-talent-management-in-the-chinese-hospitality-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>