<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Red on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/red/</link><description>Recent content in Red on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/red/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Replacing the RPM Scale Illumination Bulbs with SMD LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 14:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-replacing-the-rpm-scale-illumination-bulbs-with-smd-leds/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the tracking sensor&amp;rsquo;s light source, the next stage in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5521) involved addressing the incandescent bulbs within the RPM trimmer panel. The 33 RPM bulb had burned out, prompting the decision to replace both bulbs with custom-designed SMD LED assemblies. Recognizing the importance of a red light component for illuminating the red RPM indicators, red-green LEDs were chosen. While amber LEDs offer an incandescent-like aesthetic, their narrow wavelength distribution hinders their ability to effectively illuminate red surfaces.</description></item><item><title>Add some festive flowers to the office to celebrate Chinese New Year and bring some brightness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</guid><description>Starting January 19, 2015, Viva La Fleur will debut a new collection of long-lasting bouquets and table arrangements. The color palette for this collection features predominantly red, orange, and yellow tones, symbolizing love, luck, and fortune, perfectly aligning with the festive season.
This arrangement, part of Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s new collection, showcases deep red roses, hydrangeas, and caspia accented with brown twigs. You can find this arrangement in Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s online shop here.</description></item></channel></rss>