<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Most on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/most/</link><description>Recent content in Most on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/most/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions.</description></item></channel></rss>