<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Privilege on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/privilege/</link><description>Recent content in Privilege on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/privilege/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jin Jiang International Hotels and Hanwha Hotels &amp; Resorts have officially merged their loyalty programs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jin-jiang-international-hotels-and-hanwha-hotels-resorts-have-officially-merged-their-loyalty-programs/</guid><description>Jin Jiang International Hotels from China and Hanwha Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts from Korea have joined their loyalty programs.
Starting September 1st, members of Jin Jiang&amp;rsquo;s J-Club and Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s THE PLUS will share membership benefits. This includes perks like discounts on rooms, food, and beverages, as well as late check-outs and room upgrades at both hotel groups. J-Club&amp;rsquo;s over 14 million members will also have access to Hanwha&amp;rsquo;s resorts and golf courses across Korea.</description></item><item><title>Subscribe to Grabz for exclusive insider privileges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</guid><description>Source: Grabz website.
Grabz is a subscription service that provides its members with exclusive benefits and special offers. Using location-based alerts and a wide range of affiliated businesses, the app connects its subscribers with exclusive deals and privileges in their city.
For a monthly fee of S$15.98, premium members enjoy invitations to events and promotions such as discounted business class airfare and exclusive access to limited-edition luxury watches.
Premium members also get access to the Grabz Concierge, a personalized booking service that assists members with securing reservations at clubs and getting on guest lists for exclusive parties in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>