<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Implementation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/implementation/</link><description>Recent content in Implementation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:55:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/implementation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arising from the Depths of the Curriculum Cave</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</guid><description>My apologies for being absent from this blog for the past six weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy updating training materials for the Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step 2010 release. My focus has been on the &amp;ldquo;Project Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations with Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step&amp;rdquo; course (80199), which utilizes a case study approach for collaborative learning. Participants work through a fictional company implementation, applying Sure Step tools, templates, and guidance. I&amp;rsquo;ve taught earlier versions of this course and witnessed how it transforms students&amp;rsquo; understanding of Sure Step, shifting from theoretical knowledge to practical application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The third instance of Implementation Trauma!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 16:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/</guid><description>Many people have been eagerly anticipating a post about common problems in software implementation. This post addresses the third consulting and customer pitfalls, as identified through personal experience and teaching. The goal is to share these insights to help others avoid similar mistakes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s revisit the list of common pitfalls:
Top 5 Consulting Mistakes:
Believing you are solely responsible for the project&amp;rsquo;s success or failure. Neglecting customer service, even during challenging implementation phases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-third-instance-of-implementation-trauma/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>