<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Preamplifier on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preamplifier/</link><description>Recent content in Preamplifier on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 13:50:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/preamplifier/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Audiophile Triad HS-3 Audio Transformer Auction for Elephants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 13:50:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audiophile-triad-hs-3-audio-transformer-auction-for-elephants/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As many know, I&amp;rsquo;m deeply passionate about protecting both captive and wild elephants globally. What people may not realize is that our generation might be the last to coexist with these magnificent creatures. In recent times, wild elephant populations have been decimated, their numbers plummeting from millions to mere thousands. This decline threatens their genetic diversity, jeopardizing the species&amp;rsquo; survival.
Each elephant is precious. One organization close to my heart is the Friends of the Asian Elephant hospital (FAE) in Thailand.</description></item><item><title> Beomaster 8000 - Workbench Unit - Testing a replacement device for the AD 10/278 Multiplex Switch on the preamplifier board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-workbench-unit-testing-a-replacement-device-for-the-ad-10278-multiplex-switch-on-the-preamplifier-board/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 11:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-beomaster-8000-workbench-unit-testing-a-replacement-device-for-the-ad-10278-multiplex-switch-on-the-preamplifier-board/</guid><description>My initial project using my new, dedicated Beomaster 8000 workshop unit is testing a replacement device I designed. This device replaces the Beomaster 8000 preamplifier board&amp;rsquo;s input source switching ICs, IC102 and IC202, which are obsolete AD 10/278 multiplexer devices.
The Beomaster 8000 preamplifier uses two types of analog switches for source selection. 3IC102 and 3IC202, the AD 10/278 devices, choose between FM, Phono, and Tape 2 for both left and right channels.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of Beolover RIAA Preamp and 4002 Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-beolover-riaa-preamp-and-4002-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>I recently refurbished a Beogram 4002 (5523), culminating in the installation of gold-plated RCA plugs. My customer opted to have my recently developed internal BeoloverRIAA preamplifier added, along with the 4002 Commander remote control system, which enables control of all functions via a paired Apple remote.
This marks the first 4002 to feature both the Commander and the RIAA preamp – a true fusion of past and present!
Pictures showcasing the installation process of the BeoloverRIAA board and the 4002 Commander are included.</description></item></channel></rss>