<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequencies on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frequencies/</link><description>Recent content in Frequencies on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frequencies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I'm Sorry, Dave. I Can't Let You Use That Channel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-sorry-dave-i-cant-let-you-use-that-channel/</guid><description>Despite the recent surge in spectrum auctions, leading to the perception that all available frequencies are allocated, opportunities for innovation remain. While unoccupied spectrum bands are scarce, similar to unclaimed land, existing communication channels often have unused capacity.
The challenge in maximizing spectrum utilization stems from the operational nature of transmitters and receivers. Simultaneous transmissions on the same channel create interference, rendering communication unintelligible. This interference is noticeable with walkie-talkies, overlapping radio stations, and even WiFi networks and wireless phones sharing the 2.</description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population.</description></item></channel></rss>