<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scalability on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scalability/</link><description>Recent content in Scalability on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scalability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>What is an Ethernet Connection?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-an-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>When we consider connecting to the wider world, traditional telecom services like POTS, PRI, T1, DS3, and OCx SONET often come to mind. However, Carrier Ethernet, a newer technology that extends Ethernet from the LAN to the WAN, is worth examining.
Extending an Ethernet connection from a building or campus to a distant location might seem strange considering traditional telecom&amp;rsquo;s long-standing dominance. However, the landscape is changing with new providers entering the market, unburdened by legacy telco standards.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions.</description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Ports In a Data Storm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</guid><description>Businesses are finding it increasingly challenging to forecast their WAN network needs, especially during uncertain economic times. The traditional long wait times for telecom upgrades add to this uncertainty. What&amp;rsquo;s needed is a solution that allows businesses to pay only for the bandwidth they currently use while retaining the ability to swiftly increase capacity as needed.
Ethernet service ports offer this flexibility. Service providers install these ports, often as RJ45 jacks or fiber optic connectors, on a managed router at the customer&amp;rsquo;s location.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Distance Sensitivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</guid><description>The arrival of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers businesses a range of bandwidth options previously unavailable without fiber optic connections. EoC surpasses the speed limits of traditional T1 lines, provides easy scalability, and often comes at a lower price point, making it an attractive option for businesses seeking robust internet solutions.
However, a few limitations hinder the widespread use of EoC. Firstly, it requires compatible equipment at the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office (CO), where your copper lines terminate.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Providers in Hot Competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 03:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-providers-in-hot-competition/</guid><description>While demand for bandwidth increases, budgets remain tight. Ethernet WAN connections offer a new solution to this problem. This technology has become a strong alternative to traditional T1 lines, leading to fierce competition among Ethernet providers vying for the best deals.
The buzz surrounding Ethernet, a protocol used in LANs for years, stems from its standardization as a carrier technology by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). This has propelled Ethernet services from LANs to MANs and WANs in just a few years, turning it from a niche product into the preferred transport service.</description></item><item><title>Why You Want A GigE Port</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</guid><description>Is it difficult to predict your future bandwidth requirements? You might be aware of your current traffic levels, but what about tomorrow, next week, or during peak seasons like holidays? How can you plan for the unknown?
Inaccurate bandwidth estimations can lead to overspending on unused capacity or, even worse, business losses due to insufficient bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to optimize your bandwidth allocation.
Traditional telecom services often come with lengthy installation and upgrade processes, making them inflexible.</description></item><item><title>1000 Mbps SONET or Gigabit Ethernet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1000-mbps-sonet-or-gigabit-ethernet-options/</guid><description>With growing bandwidth demands, businesses are turning to WAN network speeds that were once impractical. The competition within the bandwidth market has made 1,000 Mbps or Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) more affordable than one might expect. The cost per Mbps has dropped significantly in recent years, while availability has increased.
This is beneficial for businesses adopting cloud computing or those with substantial bandwidth requirements, such as medical facilities, content creators and distributors, and Internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Scalable Cloud Servers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/scalable-cloud-servers-free-trial/</guid><description>Considering a move to cloud servers but feeling apprehensive about the cost and complexity? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses desire the flexibility and cost-effectiveness of cloud computing without needing excessive processing power.
Scalable cloud servers are a great option for businesses of all sizes, offering pay-as-you-go pricing and easy scalability. Before committing to a major provider, explore options specifically designed for small to medium-sized businesses. These services often provide per-second billing, eliminating wasted expenses, along with free setup and no contractual obligations.</description></item><item><title>Secure Hosting In The Cloud For The US and Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 00:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-hosting-in-the-cloud-for-the-us-and-europe/</guid><description>While you&amp;rsquo;re exploring the advantages of cloud computing, cost and security might be concerns. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine what a reliable secure cloud hosting provider, particularly for companies in the US and Europe, should offer.
One provider, with high-security data centers in Phoenix, Dallas, London, and Amsterdam, connects these centers through a private network. They provide access via various Content Delivery Network (CDN) points in major cities across the US, Europe, and Asia.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance.</description></item><item><title>Cable, T1 and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 12:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-t1-and-eoc/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have three primary broadband options today: Cable, T1 lines, and Ethernet over Copper (EoC). While their costs are relatively similar, each offers distinct advantages. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore these options further.
T1 lines, a long-standing choice for SMBs, utilize half-century-old telephone industry technology. This technology transmits digital signals across standard copper telephone wiring. A T1 line consists of two copper pairs, one for uploads and the other for downloads, achieving a consistent speed of 1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office.</description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Ethernet Service To The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-ethernet-service-to-the-internet/</guid><description>The demand for internet access is constantly increasing due to factors like video content, big data, large websites, cloud services, and technological advancements. Internet speeds have evolved significantly, from less than 1 Kbps to 1 Gbps, and reaching 10 Gbps is only a matter of time. This article explores cost-effective ways for businesses to achieve Gbps bandwidth without breaking the bank.
Previously, obtaining hundreds or thousands of Mbps required SONET/SDH fiber optic service, with limited options like OC-12 (622 Mbps), OC-24 (1.</description></item><item><title>What’s to Become of Data Centers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 01:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-to-become-of-data-centers/</guid><description>The increasing costs and rapid technological advancements are putting pressure on both large colocation facilities and traditional in-house data centers. This infographic from David Vellante on Wikibon provides a concise overview of the current situation:
Exploring Data Center Alternatives
If you&amp;rsquo;re reconsidering the viability of investing in a new data center or maintaining your existing one, you have numerous options. These range from colocation services at large commercial data centers to cloud-based solutions.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits.</description></item><item><title>How To Deal With Sudden Massive Bandwidth Demands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 02:21:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-deal-with-sudden-massive-bandwidth-demands/</guid><description>For years, you experience consistent, though gradually increasing, network bandwidth needs. Then, unexpectedly, you&amp;rsquo;re hit with a demand to increase your WAN bandwidth by 10x or even 100x. How does this happen, and how can you handle such unpredictable situations?
It&amp;rsquo;s unlikely everyone in the company suddenly started downloading HD movies, right? While that would certainly max out your bandwidth, it&amp;rsquo;s not a realistic scenario. Bandwidth demands don&amp;rsquo;t surge without reason.</description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3.</description></item></channel></rss>