<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NFC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nfc/</link><description>Recent content in NFC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:47:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nfc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S III Supports Verizon 4G LTE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:47:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</guid><description>The Samsung Galaxy S III for Verizon Wireless is a top-of-the-line smartphone with cutting-edge technology for both features and speed. This model continues the Galaxy series&amp;rsquo; tradition of innovation.
This Android smartphone uses the Google Operating System 4.0 &amp;ldquo;Ice Cream Sandwich&amp;rdquo; and features a 4.8-inch HD Super AMOLED display. With 1280 x 720 pixels, the screen displays sharp, vibrant images and text. The curved design helps prevent scratches, even when the phone is face down...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain a prepaid virtual Visa account through Singtel Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one mobile payments app, Dash, now features Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first virtual Visa account. All Dash users, new and existing, will automatically receive a Dash Visa Virtual Account. This account can be used for mobile payments at over 50,000 merchant locations in Singapore.
To use the mobile payment feature, customers sign in to the Dash app, add funds to their Dash Visa accounts, and make purchases at Dash merchants and participating e-commerce websites like Qoo10, Zalora, and HungryGoWhere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>