<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ranking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ranking/</link><description>Recent content in Ranking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ranking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</description></item><item><title>Clarivate Analytics states that global innovation is shifting its focus from quantity to quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 07:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</guid><description>Source: Clarivate Analytics infographic.
Clarivate Analytics, previously known as the Intellectual Property &amp;amp; Science division of Thomson Reuters, has announced its 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators. Utilizing unique proprietary data analysis, the report recognizes the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative companies and institutions.
Now in its sixth year, the 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators report highlights a significant change in approach among leading global innovators, according to Clarivate Analytics. The report shows a decline in patent filings coupled with an increase in grant rates.</description></item><item><title>The flag-carrier airline of Dubai is the most popular brand among women in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. 2019 Women&amp;rsquo;s Choice Rankings, top 10 for the UAE.
For the third consecutive year, Emirates secured the top spot in the UAE YouGov BrandIndex Women&amp;rsquo;s Rankings. The airline achieved the highest positive &amp;ldquo;Impression&amp;rdquo; score, reaching +70.0 among women in the UAE. WhatsApp maintained its second-place position, while Carrefour climbed to third place, surpassing Apple, which descended to fourth.
These rankings were determined using data from YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex, a daily brand tracker.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>According to the Brand Finance Global 500 2016 report, Disney is recognized as the most influential brand in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 17:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-brand-finance-global-500-2016-report-disney-is-recognized-as-the-most-influential-brand-in-the-world/</guid><description>· Out of the top 10 fastest growing brands, four are Chinese.
· Disney is the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential brand due to the immense success of Star Wars.
· Despite experiencing a decline in sales, Apple&amp;rsquo;s brand value increased by 14% to US$145.9 billion, making it the most valuable brand globally.
· Volkswagen&amp;rsquo;s brand value experienced a decline of US$12 billion as a consequence of the emissions controversy.
· Leading brands are outperforming the S&amp;amp;P 500 average in terms of share performance.</description></item><item><title>Google is ranked first in the Brandindex Australia rankings for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</guid><description>Source: YouGov BrandIndex. Overall brand rankings for 2016 in Australia.
YouGov BrandIndex has released its 2016 rankings for Australia. Having monitored brands in Australia since mid-2015, BrandIndex currently tracks over 260 brands. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Google secured the top position, followed by YouTube, another Alphabet subsidiary, and then ALDI, the discount retailer.
Here are some other notable findings:
In the automotive sector, Toyota, Mazda, and Mercedes-Benz secured the top three spots.</description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10.</description></item><item><title>Business confidence in China continues to be weak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</guid><description>While overall business confidence in China showed a slight improvement, activity declined in December as large companies continued to face weak demand and an uncertain business climate. According to MNI Indicators, a provider of economic data and analysis, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t anticipate significant improvement in early 2016. This is reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator, which remains close to the previous month&amp;rsquo;s low point.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator, a measure of current business sentiment, rose 5.</description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year.</description></item><item><title>FMCG brands are well-regarded in the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 12:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fmcg-brands-are-well-regarded-in-the-philippines/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. Brandindex 2016 rankings for the Philippines are heavy on toiletry brands.
The YouGov BrandIndex rankings from 2016 show that personal care products are very popular in the Philippines. The top 10 includes Colgate dental care, Cream Silk hair products, Dove soaps and hair care, Safeguard soaps and washes, and Olay skin care. Bench, primarily a clothing retailer, also has a presence with their bath and body products.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia loves food and communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 18:12:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-loves-food-and-communication/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Top ranked-brands for KSA in 2016.
The YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016 illustrate the diverse brands consumers love. Rankings were determined by BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score, which asks respondents about their recent exposure to a brand through advertising, news, or word-of-mouth and whether their perception was positive or negative.
The Buzz Rankings chart highlights the brands that achieved the highest average Buzz scores from January to December 2016.</description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia has the highest number of brand advocates for Garuda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia, the national airline, has earned the highest level of brand advocacy among Indonesian consumers, according to a YouGov BrandIndex analysis.
With a score of 87.5, Garuda secured the top position, surpassing Singapore Airlines (77.2) and Bank Central Asia (76.5).
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s rankings utilize a net promoter score methodology to determine which brands have the highest percentage of current and former customers who would recommend them to family or friends. The top 10 list includes several automotive brands, with Toyota ranking 4th (75.</description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area.</description></item><item><title>Investors are increasingly optimistic about placing foreign direct investment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investors-are-increasingly-optimistic-about-placing-foreign-direct-investment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Singapore achieved a top-ten ranking in the 2016 AT Kearney Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) Confidence Index. The city-state climbed five positions, representing the most significant advancement in the rankings, securing the 10th spot.
This index provides a future-oriented assessment of how political, economic, and regulatory shifts are likely to influence FDI inflows into various countries in the coming years. Since its inception in 1998, the study has consistently identified the preferred global destinations for FDI, with the index rankings closely mirroring actual global FDI inflows.</description></item><item><title>According to BrandZ, Tencent is currently the most valuable brand in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:29:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-brandz-tencent-is-currently-the-most-valuable-brand-in-asia/</guid><description>Tencent, a Chinese company, has become the most valuable brand in Asia and the fastest growing brand globally, achieving a brand value of US$54 billion in the 2014 BrandZ Top 100 Most Valuable Global Brands ranking. This success propelled Tencent to the 14th spot globally, surpassing China Mobile.
Source: Millward Brown website.
Deepender Rana, Managing Director of Millward Brown Greater China, emphasized the significance of a market-driven Chinese brand like Tencent taking the lead over state-owned enterprises.</description></item><item><title>China has a strong presence in the new City Momentum Index by Jones Lang LaSalle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</guid><description>Five cities in Asia Pacific and the Middle East — Dubai, Wuhan, Shanghai, Hong Kong and Singapore — are among the top 10 in Jones Lang LaSalle&amp;rsquo;s new City Momentum Index (CMI). This index identifies cities worldwide with significant short-term socio-economic and commercial real estate momentum, as well as strong long-term growth potential.
Jeremy Kelly, Director of Global Research at Jones Lang LaSalle, explains that city momentum is not solely determined by GDP growth.</description></item><item><title>Singapore ranked among the top five in the 2016 WE Cities Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 17:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-ranked-among-the-top-five-in-the-2016-we-cities-index/</guid><description>Dell has identified the top 25 cities worldwide that cultivate high-potential women entrepreneurs (HPWE) for 2016 through their Women Entrepreneur Cities Index (WE Cities). This unique index assesses a city&amp;rsquo;s capacity to attract and promote the growth of women-led businesses. The study focused on cities rather than countries to highlight how local policies and initiatives impact women entrepreneurs, in addition to national legislation and norms.
The WE Cities findings will serve as a starting point for discussions at the seventh annual Dell Women’s Entrepreneur Network Summit (DWEN).</description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>Thailand is heavily involved in digital communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 05:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-heavily-involved-in-digital-communications/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. This data represents the Brandindex rankings for brands in Thailand in 2016.
According to the YouGov Brandindex rankings for 2016, digital brands were highly favored in Thailand. Facebook, Line, and 7-Eleven secured the top three spots, while YouTube and Google were among the top 10. Other notable tech brands included Apple iPhone and the e-commerce platform Lazada.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents whether their exposure to the brand, whether through advertising, news, or word of mouth, in the past two weeks has been positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines has been ranked as the airline with the highest positive buzz in Singapore, according to YouGov</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</guid><description>Source: Yougov.
YouGov, a market research firm, has identified the leading brands in Singapore across various sectors based on their &amp;ldquo;buzz.&amp;rdquo; These rankings, reflecting average &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo; scores from January to December 2015, offer insights into brands that garnered the most positive attention from the general public.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the top-ranking brands:
Ecommerce and mCommerce: Q0010 leads the pack, followed by Groupon and Carousell. Retail: Fashion: Uniqlo secures the top spot, with H&amp;amp;M and Robinsons trailing behind.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Computer Society reveals the top 10 tech companies to work for in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</guid><description>The Singapore Computer Society (SCS), the largest professional organization for infocomm and digital media professionals in the country, has revealed the winners of its &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Company to Work For Award&amp;rdquo;. The announcement took place at the SCS&amp;rsquo;s annual Tech3 Forum conference.
This award recognizes four organizations out of the ten &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Companies to Work For&amp;rdquo; as overall winners. These companies have developed innovative practices and demonstrated workplace excellence within the infocomm and digital media (ICM) industry.</description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50.</description></item><item><title>YouGov's ranking of the top brands in Hong Kong for the first half of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yougov-s-ranking-of-the-top-brands-in-hong-kong-for-the-first-half-of-2016/</guid><description>In the first half of 2016, Mannings was the most talked-about brand among Hong Kong respondents, according to YouGov&amp;rsquo;s 2016 Mid-Year Best Brand Ranking for Hong Kong. Nike and Adidas secured the second and third positions, respectively. This ranking, drawn from YouGov BrandIndex data, reflects the brands generating the most positive buzz.
The leading brands across various industries in Hong Kong are:
Source: YouGov. The top 10 brands by buzz.</description></item><item><title>India is making strides towards achieving global recognition for its universities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</guid><description>Indian educational institutions are increasingly recognizing the value of global university rankings, according to Quacquarelli Symonds (QS), the organization behind the recently released Asian Universities Ranking for 2014. This year&amp;rsquo;s list features 17 Indian universities, a significant increase from the 11 included in the previous year.
Source: QS website.
While the latest rankings show a slight dip in rankings for most of India&amp;rsquo;s top universities, the substantial increase in the number of represented institutions suggests a positive trajectory for the future.</description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations.</description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings.</description></item><item><title>Japanese consumers prefer domestic brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japanese-consumers-prefer-domestic-brands/</guid><description>Source: YouGov Brandindex. Brandindex rankings for 2016 for Japan.
YouGov Brandindex&amp;rsquo;s 2016 rankings reveal that Japanese brands are the most popular in Japan. Rakuten and Rakuten Card secured the top two spots, followed by clothing retailer Uniqlo in third place.
These brands were assessed using BrandIndex&amp;rsquo;s Buzz score. This score is determined by asking respondents if their exposure to the brand through advertising, news, or word of mouth in the past two weeks was positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>In 2016, Singapore welcomed technology and locally-made brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-singapore-welcomed-technology-and-locally-made-brands/</guid><description>Source: Yougov Brandindex. Brand rankings for 2016.
The 2016 YouGov Brandindex rankings show that Singaporeans have a strong preference for both local and digital brands. Singapore Airlines, DBS bank, The Straits Times newspaper, WhatsApp, and the Apple iPhone (in the top three) all made the list. Other popular tech brands included Facebook, Google, e-commerce platform Qoo10, and YouTube.
Brands were evaluated based on their BrandIndex Buzz score, which asks respondents whether their exposure to the brand in the previous two weeks, through advertising, news, or word of mouth, was positive or negative.</description></item><item><title>The APAC region is strongly featured in Warc's list of the top 100 marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 01:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-apac-region-is-strongly-featured-in-warc-s-list-of-the-top-100-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Warc, a provider of marketing intelligence, has introduced the Warc 100, a new ranking of the top marketing campaigns globally based on their effectiveness and strategic impact.
The Asia Pacific region contributed over 30 entries, including one from the UAE, with Australia having the second-highest representation after the US with 11 entries.
Among the top 10 campaigns from the Asia Pacific are: &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s More Fun in the Philippines&amp;rdquo; by the Philippines Department of Tourism and BBDO Guerrero (ranked 3rd), &amp;ldquo;Overstay Checkout&amp;rdquo; by Art Series Hotels and Naked Communications (5th), &amp;ldquo;Smoking Kid&amp;rdquo; by Thai Health Promotion Foundation and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (7th), &amp;ldquo;Old Parts for New&amp;rdquo; by ORBIS International and Ogilvy &amp;amp; Mather (8th), and &amp;ldquo;Car Creation&amp;rdquo; by NRMA Insurance and Whybin\TBWA (10th).</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines is the top-ranked brand in terms of recognition in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 02:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</guid><description>YouGov, a polling and research company, has released its mid-year rankings of the best brands in Singapore for 2015. Singapore Airlines secured the top spot, while Apple appeared twice on the list. Technology brands dominated the top 10, with WhatsApp, e-marketplace Qoo10, Facebook, and Google all making appearances.
Source: YouGov.
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex is a daily metric of public brand perception that monitors numerous brands across various sectors. The company compiles its data every six months and publishes the Best Brand Rankings globally.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is the third best city in APEC for living and conducting business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-the-third-best-city-in-apec-for-living-and-conducting-business/</guid><description>A new study presented at the APEC 2015 CEO Summit has positioned Singapore as the third most desirable city for living and conducting business within the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) region.
Conducted by PwC, the &amp;ldquo;Building Better Cities&amp;rdquo; study aims to provide city leaders with insights into their current standings and to encourage collaboration and knowledge sharing among APEC cities to tackle persistent challenges.
The study examines the role urban centers play in APEC&amp;rsquo;s economic and social progress, emphasizing their growing global influence.</description></item><item><title>The 2019 Passport Index reveals that smaller countries are experiencing larger increases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-passport-index-reveals-that-smaller-countries-are-experiencing-larger-increases/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:29:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-passport-index-reveals-that-smaller-countries-are-experiencing-larger-increases/</guid><description>The 2019 Passport Index Report highlights the significant progress made by smaller countries in terms of passport power.
Vanuatu, an island nation in the South Pacific, secured the 10th position on the &amp;ldquo;Top 10 Greatest Passports of the Decade&amp;rdquo; list. Its passport power increased by 70% over the decade, acquiring 53 new visa waivers. Timor Leste follows closely in 9th place, gaining 55 visa waivers and moving up from 86th to 48th in the global rankings.</description></item></channel></rss>