<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tunneling on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tunneling/</link><description>Recent content in Tunneling on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tunneling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Choose An MPLS VPN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</guid><description>Businesses need secure communication between their different locations. While private networks offer the highest level of security, they are expensive to build and maintain. Using the public internet is cheaper but raises security concerns.
A fully private network, offering top-notch security and performance, requires significant investment. Building a central hub and connecting each location with dedicated lines like T1 or Ethernet can become very costly, especially with increasing bandwidth demands and staffing for maintenance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-an-mpls-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Different Types of VPN Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</guid><description>You prioritize the privacy of your network, but what happens when you need to connect to the outside world? Do you let anyone and everyone in, or do you secure your network across the distance using a private or virtually private network?
Before Virtual Private Networks (VPNs), there were private networks, and they still exist. Some situations demand such high security that the only way to guarantee control and prevent intrusions is through dedicated, point-to-point private lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>