<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Voice Gateway on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice-gateway/</link><description>Recent content in Voice Gateway on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voice-gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How T1 Lines Support VoIP Telephony</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 19:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</guid><description>T1 lines have historically been the top choice for connecting traditional PBX business phone systems. But how do they support VoIP phone systems used by enterprises?
Many mid-size and large companies are integrating VoIP technology into their existing PBX systems. They&amp;rsquo;re installing new systems that combine voice and data, or even completely replacing outdated systems that are no longer cost-effective to maintain. This shift is driven by several well-known advantages: enhanced features that boost employee productivity, cost reductions from converging voice and data networks, and simplified system moves and upgrades...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-t1-lines-support-voip-telephony/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Voice Goes Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</guid><description>A significant shift is happening in the business world: companies are ditching their traditional PBX phone systems for cloud-based communication solutions like hosted PBX or hosted VoIP. This transition also incorporates mobile devices.
For example, Megapath&amp;rsquo;s Hosted Voice Mobile allows you to make and receive calls using a single number across multiple devices – desk phone, computer, and smartphone. Having one consistent number simplifies communication and avoids confusing clients with a business card full of numbers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voice-goes-mobile/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>