<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Talent Management on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/talent-management/</link><description>Recent content in Talent Management on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/talent-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Project management is expected to face challenges in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</guid><description>ESI International, a company that provides project management training, believes that in the coming year, project managers (PMs) will experience several changes. These include dealing with combined in-person and remote work environments, needing stronger talent management skills, and aligning project results with company goals.
Raed Haddad, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at ESI International, noted that strategy and execution are often discussed separately. He anticipates a stronger emphasis on connecting these two aspects, as more companies start seeing strategic execution as a crucial skill.</description></item><item><title>The IBM Kenexa Talent Suite leverages big data to benefit HR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 21:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibm-kenexa-talent-suite-leverages-big-data-to-benefit-hr/</guid><description>IBM has introduced a new software-as-a-service (SaaS) product designed to provide Chief Human Resources Officers (CHROs) and other executives with valuable insights from employee data.
The cloud-based IBM Kenexa Talent Suite helps organizations enhance the efficiency and accuracy of their hiring processes, boost workforce productivity, and foster employee connections in ways that positively influence business outcomes.
This software empowers HR teams to analyze extensive employee data, encompassing work history, social interactions, skills development, and individual interests.</description></item><item><title>Various approaches to talent management in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: ECN.
Attracting and retaining skilled managers in Asia has become increasingly crucial for business leaders.
A recent survey by the Economist Corporate Network (ECN) of 550 member companies in Asia revealed that 95% of CEOs actively engage in talent management practices. However, their level and type of involvement differ significantly.
The report, Aligned for Success? Strategy, talent management and the role of the CEO in Asia, indicates that CEOs primarily focus on the strategic aspects of human capital, such as forecasting future workforce needs and organizational design.</description></item></channel></rss>