<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Photocell on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/photocell/</link><description>Recent content in Photocell on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/photocell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Replacement of Carriage Position Sensor Photocell</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 08:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</guid><description>Over many years of working with the Beogram 400x, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a wide array of issues, but these turntables never cease to present new challenges. In this instance, a Beogram 4002 exhibited inconsistent behavior when attempting to locate the record&amp;rsquo;s setdown point after pressing start. This pointed to a potential fault in the carriage position sensor.
Initially, I suspected the IR LED, a common culprit in later models like this 5513 Type...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-replacement-of-carriage-position-sensor-photocell/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000 (type 5215): replacing sensor arm photo cell with modern one</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</guid><description>I recently had two Beogram turntables (a BG4000 and a BG4002) in my workshop with malfunctioning photocells in the detector arm. Usually, these photocells have a long lifespan, but the light bulbs can experience broken wires. While a pre-existing LED replacement for these bulbs exists (see sensor arm light bulb replacement), in this instance, the photocells themselves had broken wires and even a fractured cell, rendering repair impossible. Finding replacements proved futile as well...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-type-5215-replacing-sensor-arm-photo-cell-with-modern-one/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Repair of a Broken Sensor Arm Photocell with Three SMD Photodiodes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 15:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, a broken photocell presented a challenge. This component, crucial for record detection, was no longer available. While a previous solution involved using a modern phototransistor with circuit modifications, a simpler approach was considered.
Recognizing the functional similarity between photovoltaic cells and the original photocell, a test was conducted using readily available photodiodes. Initial results with a single photodiode proved insufficient, but connecting three in parallel yielded a promising voltage output...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-repair-of-a-broken-sensor-arm-photocell-with-three-smd-photodiodes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration and Exploration of Photocell Function in Sensor Arm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 17:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is going well, but it appears someone attempted repairs before. The sensor arm insert, containing the light bulb and photocell for record detection, was in disarray.
Upon inspection, a photocell wire was disconnected, another was damaged from being forced back into the aluminum profile, and the lens insert had heat damage, likely from improper soldering. Thankfully, the lenses were unharmed.
After reconnecting the wire, replacing the non-standard light bulb with a Beolover LED insert, and adjusting the TR14 bias to 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-and-exploration-of-photocell-function-in-sensor-arm/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>