<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frequent Flyer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frequent-flyer/</link><description>Recent content in Frequent Flyer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frequent-flyer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Miramar Hotel Group offer now available with Asia Miles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 20:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/miramar-hotel-group-offer-now-available-with-asia-miles/</guid><description>Source: Miramar Hotel Taipei website.
Miramar Hotel Group is now part of the Asia Miles rewards program. This means members can earn 250 Asia Miles for every qualifying stay at either the Miramar Garden Taipei or Miramar Hotel Hsinchu.
To earn miles, members should provide their membership number during booking and show their card upon arrival. Note that this offer applies to deluxe room reservations.
For reference, the Miramar Garden Taipei first opened its doors in 2006, followed by the Miramar Hotel Hsinchu in 2013.</description></item><item><title>United has made changes to the MileagePlus rules</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/united-has-made-changes-to-the-mileageplus-rules/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 02:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/united-has-made-changes-to-the-mileageplus-rules/</guid><description>Starting March 1, 2015, United Airlines will transition its MileagePlus program to a revenue-based model. Instead of earning miles based on flight distance, members will earn miles based on ticket price and MileagePlus status.
[Image of the United Airlines logo]
The new system calculates earned miles using the base fare, carrier-imposed surcharges, and the member&amp;rsquo;s MileagePlus status. Standard members will earn five miles per dollar spent. MileagePlus Premier members will earn based on the following structure:</description></item></channel></rss>