<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stability on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stability/</link><description>Recent content in Stability on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/stability/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): DC Motor Restoration and Yet Another Exciting Aspect of Achieving RPM Stability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 22:43:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-dc-motor-restoration-and-yet-another-exciting-aspect-of-achieving-rpm-stability/</guid><description>To restore the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 (5513) DC motor, several upgrades are necessary. These include installing modern multi-turn RPM trimmers, a new RPM relay, replacing the RPM trimmer backlights with LEDs, and refreshing the motor bearings with oil. Testing the RPM stability after each step reveals their individual impact on performance.
This particular Beogram 4002 had already undergone most of these improvements, with the exception of the motor restoration.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Assembly - Gold Plated Switch Terminals and Light Bulbs Replaced with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the repair of the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking systems, the next step was to focus on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control center: the keypad assembly. This unit houses an early digital control system that manages inputs from the keypad&amp;rsquo;s keys. The mechanical switches connected to these keys are a common source of problems and should be gold-plated to ensure reliable, long-term operation after restoration.
The keypad cluster was removed from the Beogram and opened, revealing a missing light bulb in the position indicator scale.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:</description></item></channel></rss>