<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>India on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/india/</link><description>Recent content in India on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/india/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India and Bangladesh have initiated connectivity projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</guid><description>The Prime Ministers of India and Bangladesh, Narendra Modi and Sheikh Hasina, respectively, along with West Bengal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Minister, Mamata Banerjee, inaugurated multiple connectivity initiatives between the two nations.
These projects include the inauguration of the second Bhairab and Titas Railway Bridges, situated on the 320-km Dhaka-Chittagong railway line in Bangladesh. Additionally, the International Rail Passenger Terminus in Kolkata, India, was also inaugurated.
The dignitaries also launched the first run of the Bandhan Express, connecting Kolkata to Khulna in southwest Bangladesh, covering a distance of over 150km...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carlson Rezidor has revealed plans for new hotel developments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</guid><description>The Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group has announced new deals and hotel openings in strategic locations within India, further solidifying its position as a leading international hotel group in the country.
Thorsten Kirschke, President for Asia Pacific at Carlson Rezidor Hotel Group, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s accomplishments, stating that building upon a successful 2013, the first four months of this year have shown strong results in India and Thailand. He added that with 95 hotels currently operational, they anticipate exceeding 100 operating hotels in the Asia Pacific region by year-end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carlson-rezidor-has-revealed-plans-for-new-hotel-developments-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Country Holidays is introducing new Signature Departures for the year 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 05:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</guid><description>Luxury travel agency Country Holidays has launched new &amp;ldquo;Signature Departures&amp;rdquo; trips for discerning travelers based in Singapore. Established in 2011, Signature Departures offers a fresh approach to group travel, steering clear of crowded buses, generic hotels, large-scale dining, and tourist traps.
Theng Hwee Chang, Managing Director of Country Holidays, explains: &amp;ldquo;We created Signature Departures four years ago to address the increasing demand for more enriching group travel experiences that go beyond the ordinary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/country-holidays-is-introducing-new-signature-departures-for-the-year-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Worli is the trendy spot in Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/worli-is-the-trendy-spot-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 05:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/worli-is-the-trendy-spot-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Worli, situated at the entrance of South Mumbai, is gaining popularity as Mumbai&amp;rsquo;s top luxury neighborhood. The Park, a property development located in this central area, generated over ₹250 crore in a single weekend, according to developer Lodha Group.
Source: Lodha Group. Mrs. Aishwarya Rai Bachchan, prospective President and Brand Ambassador for The Park, a 17-acre residential project by the Lodha Group.
Lodha states that Worli has transformed into a business center with numerous offices and corporations headquartered there...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/worli-is-the-trendy-spot-in-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/worli-is-the-trendy-spot-in-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Chennai City Centre is now open under AccorHotels management</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 06:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels.
AccorHotels, a leading global hotel company, has expanded its presence in Chennai with the launch of the ibis Chennai City Centre, its third establishment in the city. Joining the ibis Chennai SIPCOT and Novotel Chennai SIPCOT, which debuted in 2014, this new hotel offers 155 rooms and enjoys a prime location on the historic Mount Road. Its convenient position places it within a short distance of Chennai airport and in proximity to various shopping and entertainment destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-chennai-city-centre-is-now-open-under-accorhotels-management/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VyprVPN from Golden Frog now includes a server in Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</guid><description>Golden Frog, a company dedicated to online privacy and internet accessibility, has expanded its services to India. This new server, located in Mumbai, marks the company&amp;rsquo;s 14th in Asia and aims to provide Indian internet users with a secure and unrestricted online experience through their VyprVPN service.
&amp;ldquo;India, with its vast population and rapidly growing tech sector, will benefit greatly from this new server location,&amp;rdquo; says Sunday Yokubaitis, President of Golden Frog...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyprvpn-from-golden-frog-now-includes-a-server-in-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ARTWALK Little India combines elements of the past with modern influences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</guid><description>Source: ARTWALK Little India. Izzad Radzali Shah, Festival, ARTWALK Little India 2018, LASALLE College of the Arts, 2018. Photo: Ng Wu Gang. The multidisciplinary arts festival ARTWALK Little India is a collaboration between LASALLE College of the Arts (LASALLE) and the Singapore Tourism Board (STB), with support from the Little India Shopkeepers and Heritage Association. It returns for its fourth year in January 2018 as a featured event in Singapore Art Week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting today, Singtel will be accepting preorders for the Google Pixel 2 XL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 17:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</guid><description>Singtel announced a partnership with Google to become the official telecommunications provider for the highly anticipated Google Pixel 2 XL in Singapore. Starting November 15th, Singtel customers will have the exclusive opportunity to be the first in Southeast Asia to purchase this new device.
Yuen Kuan Moon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chief Executive Officer for Consumer Singapore, expressed excitement about bringing the Pixel 2 XL to Singapore, highlighting its innovative features that have been eagerly awaited by Android fans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-singtel-will-be-accepting-preorders-for-the-google-pixel-2-xl/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IndianMoney.com is creating additional financial education content</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 10:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</guid><description>IndianMoney.com, a leading financial education company in India, partnered with Kannada news channel Suddi TV to create Money Maathu (Money Talk), an educational series about personal finance. The series features short episodes, typically eight to ten minutes long, that cover a wide range of financial topics. With 35 episodes already released, the goal is to empower viewers with the knowledge to make informed financial choices.
CS Sudheer, founder and CEO of IndianMoney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indianmoney-com-is-creating-additional-financial-education-content/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DebtorsWatch compiles data on delinquent payments in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</guid><description>DebtorsWatch is the first online platform in India designed for reporting trade defaults. The interactive website allows businesses to report overdue payments and defaults, conduct credit checks, and monitor customer creditworthiness. Registered members can also utilize the data for due diligence.
Deepanjan Periwal, Chartered Accountant and founder of DebtorsWatch, highlights the lack of transparency in India&amp;rsquo;s credit system compared to countries like the US, UK, and Australia, where credit tracking is standard practice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debtorswatch-compiles-data-on-delinquent-payments-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is your company using mobile for recruiting?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</guid><description>Mobile interaction is crucial for successful recruitment in India. In 2014-15, almost half of companies surveyed by TimesJobs reported receiving 10-20% of job applications via mobile phones, significantly up from the previous year.
With mobile phones widespread, 65% of organizations in India now have mobile recruitment strategies, a 10% increase from the previous year, according to a TimesJobs.com survey.
Jobseeker behavior has shifted dramatically, with 85% of online job searching now done on smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural India-ASEAN Writers Festival premieres in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</guid><description>The High Commission of India in Singapore is hosting the first India-ASEAN Writers Festival in Singapore.
This festival is one of many events celebrating 25 years of friendship between India and ASEAN, coinciding with the ASEAN India Pravasi Bharatiya Divas (Overseas Indians Day). The events are scheduled for January 6-7 at the Marina Bay Sands.
The PBD Writers Festival, a key event organized by Singapore-based publishing house Kitaab International on behalf of the High Commission, aims to &amp;ldquo;celebrate the literary ties between India and the ASEAN nations,&amp;rdquo; said Zafar Anjum, Kitaab&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India has implemented measures to prepare for Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</guid><description>India is actively monitoring the situation to prevent the Ebola virus disease (EVD) from entering the country. Three dedicated helplines (2306 3205, 2306 1469, and 2306 1302) were set up at the Health Ministry on August 9th to address public inquiries.
While India has no confirmed or suspected Ebola cases, the World Health Organization (WHO) alerted the government about an Indian passenger who shared a flight with an Ebola patient traveling from Monrovia (Liberia) to Lagos (Nigeria), both experiencing outbreaks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces the first mobile-only bank in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</guid><description>Source: DBS. From left: Sachin Tendulkar, Cricketer, digor
the digibank mascot, DBS CEO Piyush Gupta.
Introducing a pioneering Virtual Assistant powered by artificial intelligence. Account creation utilizes Aadhaar, the largest biometric identification system globally. DBS Bank, headquartered in Singapore and a prominent financial institution in Asia, has introduced digibank, India&amp;rsquo;s inaugural mobile-centric bank. This innovative banking platform harnesses advanced technologies, including biometrics and artificial intelligence (AI), to offer customers a novel banking experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Idealo has developed a flight price comparison portal for India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</guid><description>Source: idealo India website.
Idealo, a company specializing in price comparison, has expanded its services to India. With fourteen successful price comparison websites globally, idealo already helps numerous travelers find the best flight deals. The company proudly launched its fifteenth website, flights.idealo.in, in 2015.
Indian customers can now compare prices on thousands of flights from various online travel agencies and airlines, all without any cost. Idealo&amp;rsquo;s platform features offers from both budget-friendly and high-end airlines, encompassing one-way and round-trip journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is enhancing its intellectual property infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</guid><description>The Indian government has decided to continue its efforts to improve its intellectual property (IP) offices. This initiative, part of the 12th Plan (2012-2017), will cost Rs309.6 crore, with Rs258 crore allocated for the 12th Plan and Rs51.6 crore for the 13th Plan.
This decision recognizes the increasing importance of IP in a globalized economy, India&amp;rsquo;s recent membership in the Madrid Protocol (April 2013), and the Controller General of Patents, Designs, and Trademarks (CGPDTM) office&amp;rsquo;s new role as an International Searching and Preliminary Examining Authority (ISA/IPEA) under the Patent Cooperation Treaty (starting October 2013)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Letv reaches one million Facebook likes within two months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</guid><description>Source: Socialbakers.
Letv, a company that has yet to formally debut in India, has already amassed a following of one million on Facebook in just 60 days. According to Socialbakers, Letv is currently the top and fastest-growing phone brand page in India. In contrast, it took Xiaomi India more than 400 days to achieve the same milestone*.
Over the past month, Letv has consistently ranked high in Facebook popularity, rivaling established brands like HTC, Motorola, Lava, Vivo, and Xiaomi in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei P9 and India Photo Project introduce Monochrome award in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 22:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</guid><description>Source: Instagram. Top Instagram posts for the contest hashtag #ipp_ma2016 at the time of writing.
Huawei, in partnership with the Instagram-based India Photo Project, has introduced the &amp;ldquo;Monochrome&amp;rdquo; award to commemorate World Photography Day on August 19th. This competition, running from August 20th to August 31st, aims to discover India&amp;rsquo;s top black and white Instagram photographer.
The judging panel comprises Sumit Dayal, recognized as CNN&amp;rsquo;s Indian Instagrammer of the Year in 2015, Tara Bedi, the first Instagram employee from India, Devika Daulet Singh, Director of PHOTOINK, a prominent photography gallery, and Neeraj Priyadarshini, the Photo Editor at the Indian Express...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-p9-and-india-photo-project-introduce-monochrome-award-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ASUS EeeBook X205 is now available for purchase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</guid><description>ASUS has introduced the EeeBook X205 to the Indian market. This 11.6-inch ultraportable laptop is designed to offer a user experience similar to a smartphone and is well-suited for young professionals.
The EeeBook X205 features &amp;ldquo;connected standby technology,&amp;rdquo; allowing for near-instantaneous wake-up from sleep mode and continuous social connectivity, even in standby. Equipped with a quad-core Intel Atom processor, the laptop comes with Windows 8.1 with Bing and is offered in four colors: dark blue, white, gold, and red...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asus-eeebook-x205-is-now-available-for-purchase-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is in a position to lead the way in the 21st century</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</guid><description>A new IBM study suggests that the 21st century has the potential to be known as the &amp;ldquo;Indian century&amp;rdquo; as India prepares to take a leading role on the global stage. Over half of the executives surveyed believe that better governance and reduced regulation are key to sustained economic growth. Building robust social infrastructure was identified as the second most important factor for economic productivity. Over 40% also highlighted the significance of quality physical infrastructure and a skilled workforce for driving growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-in-a-position-to-lead-the-way-in-the-21st-century/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel collaborates with Airtel to launch hi!India plans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:05:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</guid><description>Singtel and Airtel have partnered to provide Singtel prepaid mobile customers with access to high-quality calls to India through the Airtel Talk app. This service was previously only available to credit card holders.
Now, Singtel prepaid customers can utilize Airtel Talk by purchasing hi!India plans using their prepaid credits. Calls made through Airtel Talk are transmitted via standard IDD lines, resulting in enhanced call clarity.
Hi!India plans start at S$5 for 100 minutes (S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-collaborates-with-airtel-to-launch-hi-india-plans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India will receive the India Inclusive Innovation Fund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</guid><description>The Indian Cabinet has approved a proposal from the Ministry of Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSME) to establish a dedicated fund. This fund will focus on promoting grassroots innovations that generate social benefits alongside reasonable economic returns. Union Minister Shri Kalraj Mishra shared this information in a written response to a question in Lok Sabha.
The fund, named &amp;ldquo;India Inclusive Innovation Fund,&amp;rdquo; aims to support businesses developing solutions for citizens at the lower end of India&amp;rsquo;s economic spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smartphone manufacturers are experimenting with various marketing strategies to stand out in the competitive Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</guid><description>Source: Zinnov website.
As the Indian smartphone market becomes more competitive, vendors are shifting their go-to-market approaches, according to management consultancy Zinnov. In their report &amp;ldquo;India Smartphone Market: Witnessing Exponential Growth,&amp;rdquo; Zinnov highlights the intense pressure local vendors face from Chinese competitors. Xiaomi, for example, recently took the lead in 4G LTE smartphone sales, and Micromax is challenging Samsung&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
To stand out, smartphone vendors are exploring different strategies. These include online-only retail partnerships (like Motorola&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Flipkart), establishing physical experience centers to enhance customer interaction (such as Xiaomi&amp;rsquo;s plan for 100 centers in India), and investing in traditional brick-and-mortar retail models (like Gionee&amp;rsquo;s plan for 250 stores)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has launched the Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp; Residences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</guid><description>Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences, the largest five-star hotel in Kolkata, is now open in the city’s New Town precinct.
Source: Accor Hotels. The Novotel Kolkata Hotel &amp;amp; Residences. The hotel has 347 guest rooms and suites. It is located near the airport and offers the city&amp;rsquo;s first serviced apartments. Guests can enjoy amenities such as a flat-screen LED TV, coffee and tea maker, in-room safe, refreshment center, and complimentary internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-launched-the-novotel-kolkata-hotel-residences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Teabox shortens tea supply chain to deliver fresher teas to the market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:25:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</guid><description>Kaushal Dugar, CEO of Teabox, which launched in 2012, comes from a family with over 70 years in the tea industry. He started the company to revolutionize the tea trade.
Source: Teabox. Dugar.
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been passionate about entrepreneurship,&amp;rdquo; Dugar shared, noting that the tea industry, valued at US$90 billion, uses outdated practices. He pointed out that while India is a top tea producer, its tea isn&amp;rsquo;t as renowned as tea from Japan or China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teabox-shortens-tea-supply-chain-to-deliver-fresher-teas-to-the-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels introduces a new combined Pullman &amp; Novotel hotel in New Delhi Aerocity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Lobby, Novotel New Delhi Aerocity.
AccorHotels has recently launched a new project: a combined Pullman &amp;amp; Novotel in New Delhi Aerocity, adding 670 internationally-standard rooms near the Indian capital. This opening marks the 100th Pullman hotel worldwide. Guests staying at either hotel can enjoy the shared dining and leisure facilities.
The complex centers around a garden and heated outdoor pool, housing two of AccorHotels&amp;rsquo; most well-known brands. The Pullman New Delhi offers diverse dining options, including: &amp;ldquo;Pluck,&amp;rdquo; a farm-to-table restaurant with a seasonal menu; a delicatessen café serving a variety of teas, coffees, beverages, and freshly baked goods; and &amp;ldquo;Honk,&amp;rdquo; their signature restaurant, specializing in upscale Asian street food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-introduces-a-new-combined-pullman-novotel-hotel-in-new-delhi-aerocity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India no longer accepts high denomination notes in the current series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Reserve Bank (RBI) has decided to discontinue the use of 500 and 1,000 rupee notes. These notes ceased to be legal tender as of November 9, 2016. Consequently, ATMs and other cash transaction machines were shut down on November 9 and 10. However, bank branches and government treasuries remained open on November 10.
This move was prompted by the difficulty in differentiating real banknotes from counterfeit ones. The surge in fake currency was negatively impacting the Indian economy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Handbags will be the focus in India and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</guid><description>A new report from Technavio predicts the handbag market in Brazil, Russia, India, and China will experience significant growth between 2014 and 2019. This growth is projected to be over 7.41% in revenue and 7.02% in volume.
Technavio attributes this anticipated growth to the increasing association of handbags with social status among consumers. The introduction of stylish and functional designs, along with attractive colors, finishes, and textures, are making handbags more desirable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports a decrease in luxury demand in China and an increase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, predicts the global luxury goods industry will experience a 19% growth, reaching $405 billion by 2019.
Fflur Roberts, the Head of Luxury Goods Research at Euromonitor, pointed out China&amp;rsquo;s significant luxury market growth of $9.6 billion over the past five years. She noted that this growth, while impressive, slowed at the end of 2013, prompting luxury brands to reassess their strategies in China and other emerging markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Automotive industry continues to export to China as its third-largest destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</guid><description>The Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) recently released data revealing that Britain is exporting more cars than ever. The number of British-built cars shipped globally increased by 10.3%, reaching a new record of 1,354,216 units. This marks the second year in a row that this record has been broken.
China, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest car market, maintained its position as the UK&amp;rsquo;s third largest trading partner, after the EU and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IBM has raised concerns about the skills gap in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</guid><description>Source: IBM. Cover for the Upskilling India report.
IBM has released a study conducted by the IBM Institute for Business Value (IBV), in partnership with the Economist Intelligence Unit. This study assesses India&amp;rsquo;s increasing skills gap and offers suggestions to address the issue.
The study surveyed Indian executives, and most believe that the Indian workforce&amp;rsquo;s skills are on par with or better than those of other nations. However, only 40% reported that new employees possess the necessary skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibm-has-raised-concerns-about-the-skills-gap-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>16% of the top 100 MBAs from the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 01:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Business schools in Asia may be overlooking the potential of online MBAs. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s first ever Online MBA Rankings for 2014, which came out in March, contained no Asian business schools in its list of the top 15 programs.
However, the region performs better in the traditional MBA format. The Financial Times&amp;rsquo;s Global MBA Rankings for 2014, published in January 2014, features a number of Asian schools within its top 50...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/16-of-the-top-100-mbas-from-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoTripy Car Rentals is now available in 11 cities across India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</guid><description>Source: GoTripy Car Rentals&amp;rsquo; website.
GoTripy Car Rentals currently operates in 11 cities across India. Their updated website makes online booking easier than ever before.
GoTripy offers a variety of budget-friendly and luxury vehicles, along with professional drivers, in cities like Mumbai, Pune, Nashik, Ahmednagar, Aurangabad, Shirdi, Kolhapur, Delhi, Gurgaon, Bangalore, and Ahmedabad. Their car rental services cater to diverse needs such as local transportation, day trips within a city, sightseeing excursions, airport and railway station transfers, inter-city travel, weekend getaways, business trips, and multi-city journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vistara, a new airline, launches in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</guid><description>Tata SIA Airlines Limited (TSAL) revealed &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; as the name for its new airline on August 11th. This announcement follows a September 2013 agreement between Tata Sons and Singapore Airlines to create a new Indian airline, aiming to further boost air travel demand.
Source: Twitter. The Vistara logo was unveiled on Twitter and Facebook.
The name &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; originates from the Sanskrit word &amp;ldquo;vistaar,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;limitless expanse,&amp;rdquo; symbolizing the boundless sky, the airline&amp;rsquo;s domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In India, Swarn Amrit produces sweets made with edible gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</guid><description>Swarn Amrit, a high-end confectionery brand, has introduced a first-of-its-kind product line in India: sweets made with real 24-karat gold. The company believes that gold symbolizes purity, prosperity, and good fortune, and even suggests it may promote longevity.
Swarn Kalash
The new collection features a variety of sweets with names like kalash, mukhi, madhu, yukti, and katak, representing both Indian and international flavors. For example, Swarn Mukhi layers cashews, almonds, pistachios, and gold, while Swarn Madhu combines Belgian chocolate with gold, and Swarn Katak adds a touch of gold to Turkish delight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trunk Calls Soothe Lonely Elephants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trunk-calls-soothe-lonely-elephants/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 12:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trunk-calls-soothe-lonely-elephants/</guid><description>The rapid development of smartphone apps, particularly after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release, has provided solutions for almost every need. But could technology address something as unique as an elephant&amp;rsquo;s loneliness? Interestingly, a simple cell phone offered a solution for two elephants, Devi and Rahul, at the Okinawa Zoo.
When these Bengal elephants were relocated from India, they became despondent and difficult to manage without their familiar trainers, known as mahouts. To address this, the zookeepers devised a heartwarming solution: they used cell phones to allow the elephants to hear the voices of their mahouts back in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trunk-calls-soothe-lonely-elephants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trunk-calls-soothe-lonely-elephants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dabur Herb'l Sensitive Toothpaste is designed to combat tooth demineralization in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 07:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Source: Dabur International.
Dabur International has introduced its new Herb’l Sensitive Toothpaste to the Middle East market. This toothpaste uses natural ingredients, including cinnamon, mint, licorice root, and potassium ions to quickly and effectively alleviate tooth sensitivity.
The company states that using this toothpaste twice daily will not only reduce sensitivity but also lead to healthier gums. It does this by preventing plaque buildup, gum inflammation, and cavities, all while freshening breath...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dabur-herb-l-sensitive-toothpaste-is-designed-to-combat-tooth-demineralization-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is making strides towards achieving global recognition for its universities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</guid><description>Indian educational institutions are increasingly recognizing the value of global university rankings, according to Quacquarelli Symonds (QS), the organization behind the recently released Asian Universities Ranking for 2014. This year&amp;rsquo;s list features 17 Indian universities, a significant increase from the 11 included in the previous year.
Source: QS website.
While the latest rankings show a slight dip in rankings for most of India&amp;rsquo;s top universities, the substantial increase in the number of represented institutions suggests a positive trajectory for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Haldiram's is promoting mithai in India that is free from adulteration at SwaadMarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 04:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</guid><description>Source: SwaadMarket.com website.
Haldiram&amp;rsquo;s, a leading brand in the Indian sweets market, is now available on SwaadMarket.com. SwaadMarket is an Indian online marketplace that guarantees authentic, hygienic, and pure sweets and other food products. Giving Indian sweets (mithai) as gifts is a long-standing tradition, but recently the mithai market has declined due to a lack of new ideas and concerns about hygiene and purity. This trend inspired both companies to start promoting unadulterated sweets within India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP introduces two phablets in the Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 05:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</guid><description>HP has introduced two new mobile devices to their collection: the 6-inch HP Slate6 VoiceTab and the 7-inch HP Slate7 VoiceTab. These &amp;ldquo;voice tablets&amp;rdquo; will be released in India this February*.
These devices combine the functions of a phone and a tablet into one portable design. “The voice tablet market is growing because consumers want to combine their phones and tablets into one device,” said Ron Coughlin, Senior VP of HP&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Personal Systems Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-two-phablets-in-the-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi is working to increase the popularity of taxis in India and other countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</guid><description>A new free taxi booking app called TaxiPixi is gaining popularity in India. Available on Android, iOS, and online, this less-than-a-year-old service offers reliable options for booking cabs, motorcycles, or auto-rickshaws for point-to-point trips or hourly packages.
TaxiPixi&amp;rsquo;s online home page
Co-founder and CEO Kajal Dubey believes that the biggest obstacles to increased taxi use are the uncertainty of finding a ride and the perception that taxis are much more expensive than driving...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-is-working-to-increase-the-popularity-of-taxis-in-india-and-other-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Citadines OMR serviced apartments are now available in Chennai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 18:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</guid><description>The Ascott Limited, a fully owned subsidiary of CapitaLand specializing in serviced residences, has expanded its presence in India with the opening of Citadines OMR in Chennai. This 269-unit property marks Ascott&amp;rsquo;s second serviced residence in India, further solidifying its position as a leading international serviced residence operator in the country.
With this addition, Ascott&amp;rsquo;s portfolio in India now encompasses over 1,600 units across nine properties, including those currently operational and under development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/citadines-omr-serviced-apartments-are-now-available-in-chennai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Users of Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola can now utilize their apps in different countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 12:50:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</guid><description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;roaming&amp;rdquo; has evolved from phone services to ATM cash withdrawals. Now, a partnership similar to the airline industry&amp;rsquo;s Star Alliance is bringing global roaming to ride-hailing apps that were once limited to specific regions.
Didi Kuaidi, GrabTaxi, Lyft, and Ola have expanded their initial ride-sharing agreement, first established between Lyft and Didi Kuaidi in September. This expanded partnership now encompasses a significant portion of the world&amp;rsquo;s population, covering nearly all of Southeast Asia, India, China, and the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/users-of-didi-kuaidi-grabtaxi-lyft-and-ola-can-now-utilize-their-apps-in-different-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A study conducted by Abbott reveals concerning patterns among diabetics in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 22:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</guid><description>Special thosai set.
A recent study, the Abbott Food, Spikes and Diabetes Survey, suggests that 70% of individuals managing diabetes in urban India may not be carefully managing their food intake. This survey, conducted by Ipsos India on behalf of Abbott, involved over 4,100 participants aged 36 to 65 with Type 2 diabetes (diagnosed for over 18 months) from various socioeconomic backgrounds across eight major cities. The study aimed to understand their eating habits, the impact of meals on blood sugar fluctuations, and its effect on diabetes management...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Selecting the appropriate tea for the workplace break room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find pre-mixed tea sachets or teabags in office pantries. While these are convenient and widely available, Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, suggests there might be downsides to these options.
Source: Teabox website.
Teabox CEO, Kaushal Dugar, explains that tea dust, a byproduct of tea production, lacks the full flavor, taste, and aroma of whole tea leaves. This tea dust is often what ends up in teabags, resulting in a less flavorful and potentially less nutritious cup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BrandZ reports that the value of Indian brands has increased by 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 03:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</guid><description>The combined value of India&amp;rsquo;s top brands has seen a significant increase of 33% over the past year, as reported by the second yearly BrandZ Top 50 Most Valuable Indian Brands ranking from WPP and Millward Brown. This growth rate is the most substantial among all BrandZ rankings in the past decade, surpassing the Global Top 100, China, Latin America, and Indonesia.
The current total worth of India&amp;rsquo;s Top 50 brands is US$92...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brandz-reports-that-the-value-of-indian-brands-has-increased-by-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ZEE5 is attracting viewers from Pakistan and Bangladesh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 01:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</guid><description>Source: Zee5. Images for the #ShareTheLove campaign.
Following its initial launch in over 190 countries, the digital entertainment platform ZEE5 is setting its sights on Pakistan and Bangladesh.
The company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;#ShareTheLove&amp;rdquo; campaign highlights the cultural and entertainment commonalities between ZEE5 and these two nations. ZEE5 aims to foster a sense of shared enjoyment by providing a diverse content library that resonates with Pakistani and Bangladeshi audiences, featuring Hindi and Bengali original series like &amp;ldquo;Rangbaaz,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Kaali,&amp;rdquo; and the upcoming &amp;ldquo;Sharate Aaj,&amp;rdquo; original films such as &amp;ldquo;Aranyadeb&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tigers,&amp;rdquo; and digital premieres of movies like &amp;ldquo;Namaste England&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Praktan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avanta India inaugurates a new office space in Gurgaon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</guid><description>Avanta Business Centre has established a new premium office space in Gurgaon, India, spanning 25,000 square feet. Conveniently situated near the HUDA City Centre Metro station, the Park Centra facility offers easy accessibility.
This marks Avanta&amp;rsquo;s second business center in Gurgaon. The Park Centra location provides a variety of office sizes, ranging from 77 square feet to approximately 20,000 square feet, to accommodate a diverse clientele. The space is ready for occupancy and features around 300 workstations, a communal area, a pantry, and four meeting rooms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in October, Air China will offer nonstop flights from Beijing to Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</guid><description>Air China will commence nonstop flights between Beijing and Mumbai starting October 25, 2015. This decision comes as a response to the growing travel demand between these two BRICS nations, driven by strengthening political and economic ties.
Source: Air China.
The route will operate four times a week, with flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays, and Sundays. The seven-hour journey departs Beijing at 7:40 PM local time and arrives in Mumbai at 1 AM the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India will be implementing GST and has announced additional training and business initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Shri Arun Jaitley, announced in his Budget speech that a comprehensive goods and services tax (GST) system will be implemented by April 1, 2016. Additionally, corporate tax rates are expected to be reduced from 30% to 25% gradually over the next four years. These proposals were presented alongside initiatives aimed at enhancing human resource capabilities and fostering innovation nationwide.
Training and Development The Finance Minister stressed the importance of structured skills training, revealing the government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce a National Skills Mission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ADIB introduces the Spice credit card specifically for Non-Resident Indians and Non-Resident Pakistanis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 09:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</guid><description>Source: ADIB. The new Spice Card offers a range of cashbacks if the owner hits a minimum spend.
Abu Dhabi Islamic Bank (ADIB) has introduced the Spice Card, a new product designed specifically for non-resident Indians (NRIs) and non-resident Pakistanis (NRPs) living in the UAE.
The ADIB Spice Card provides NRIs and NRPs with opportunities to save money through a variety of competitive offers and discounts. These include cashback rewards of 9% on dining, 7% on supermarket purchases, 4% on fuel, and 1% on utility bills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adib-introduces-the-spice-credit-card-specifically-for-non-resident-indians-and-non-resident-pakistanis/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>