<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Level 3 Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level-3-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Level 3 Communications on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/level-3-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly.</description></item><item><title>Can You Save 50% With Unified Communications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-save-50-with-unified-communications/</guid><description>As your company expands, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely seen a simultaneous increase in your telephone costs. While it&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume this is simply due to having more employees making calls, the reality is that not all phone expenses are unavoidable.
Unified communications technology can help you significantly reduce unnecessary costs. This approach combines your voice, data, and video networks into a single, unified system, leading to cost savings for businesses of all sizes, even those with just one location.</description></item><item><title>Transforming the WAN Into The Smart WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transforming-the-wan-into-the-smart-wan/</guid><description>People tend to think of WAN connections as basic channels for data, similar to how Senator Ted Stevens once described the internet. However, with the shift from on-site data centers to cloud-based systems, VoIP, and video streaming, our needs have outgrown this simple model. This is where the concept of a Smart WAN comes into play.
Instead of treating all data equally, a Smart WAN prioritizes different types of data through a system called Class of Service (CoS).</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous.</description></item><item><title>Better Network Connectivity Into France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</guid><description>Globalization is increasingly common, and even companies without a multinational presence often conduct business internationally. The European Union, with its vast pool of consumers and producers, is a significant market, and France stands out as a key destination within the EU.
Level 3 Communications, a major telecommunications provider, recently enhanced its resources, infrastructure, and services for French enterprise customers. The company expanded its network reach with additional Points of Presence (POPs) in Paris and its surrounding areas, along with core network extensions in Lille, Lyon, and Toulouse.</description></item><item><title>Why Colocate To An Omaha Data Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</guid><description>While major corporations might associate colocation data centers with locations like 60 Hudson St in New York City or One Wilshire in Los Angeles, Omaha, Nebraska, presents a compelling alternative.
Beyond being home to Warren Buffett and Berkshire Hathaway, Omaha boasts a robust business environment, earning recognition from Forbes magazine as the nation&amp;rsquo;s top &amp;ldquo;Best-Bang-For-The-Buck City.&amp;rdquo; Crucially, Omaha houses the Scott Data Center complex.
The Scott Data Center offers over 110,000 square feet of data storage, boasting continuous operation since 2006.</description></item><item><title>Why The Smart WAN Beats A Dumb Pipe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) are traditionally built using &amp;ldquo;dumb pipes,&amp;rdquo; which are simple bandwidth connections between two points. These connections are efficient at their primary function: transferring data packets. However, as IT requirements become more complex, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing need for more intelligent solutions. This can be achieved by either enhancing your internal IT capabilities or outsourcing these needs as a service.
Level 3 Communications, a leading provider of fiber network services, recognizes this shift from basic to high-performance networking demands.</description></item><item><title>Earth to Cloud Network Security Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 18:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earth-to-cloud-network-security-solutions/</guid><description>Information technology specialists understand the need for secure corporate networks, including enterprise-level security for cloud computing services in remote data centers. However, maintaining security across the entire network, especially when extending the LAN remotely, poses a significant challenge.
Level 3 Communications offers a solution with its “Earth to Cloud” comprehensive global security suite. This multi-layered protection strategy aims to secure every aspect of the network from potential threats.
A key factor in this approach is having a single provider for both connectivity and network security, a role Level 3 is well-equipped to fill.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item></channel></rss>