<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trends on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trends/</link><description>Recent content in Trends on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals.</description></item><item><title>In 2017, the Brunei freight and logistics market had a value of US$157.25 million</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-the-brunei-freight-and-logistics-market-had-a-value-of-us-157-25-million/</guid><description>A new report by Mordor Intelligence, titled &amp;ldquo;Brunei Freight &amp;amp; Logistics Market Study - Market Trends, Analysis &amp;amp; Forecasts to 2023,&amp;rdquo; has been added to ResearchAndMarkets.com&amp;rsquo;s collection.
The Brunei freight and logistics market, valued at US$157.25 million in 2017, sees its biggest opportunity in the multi-trillion dollar halal industry. Mordor Intelligence highlights Brunei&amp;rsquo;s positive image within the Islamic world, where it is regarded as a hub of Islamic culture.
Brunei&amp;rsquo;s strategic location for China, along with its alignment with the Belt and Road project, presents significant opportunities for its halal certification industry.</description></item></channel></rss>