<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Assessment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/assessment/</link><description>Recent content in Assessment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/assessment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Massachusetts - First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:14:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from a Massachusetts customer for a complete restoration. Thankfully, it was properly packaged and arrived without damage.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s dust cover shows typical signs of use, but it will be replaced with a new one. The aluminum surfaces are in good shape overall.
However, there are some minor flaws. The keypad has a corner ding, suggesting it might have come loose during past transportation. Additionally, there are small scratches on the aluminum, possibly from the keypad moving around.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A new Arrival from Nebraska</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-nebraska/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-nebraska/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from Nebraska arrived for a complete restoration. It was securely shipped in a Beolover container. This is my first look at the unit.
Upon unboxing and bench inspection:
The turntable is in relatively good cosmetic condition. The dust cover is in good shape, though it would benefit from polishing.
The aluminum surfaces show only minor imperfections:
The base has one slightly worn corner on the right side:</description></item><item><title>Discover your leadership potential with a revolutionary tool from Hogan Assessment Systems and Sirota</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 15:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-your-leadership-potential-with-a-revolutionary-tool-from-hogan-assessment-systems-and-sirota/</guid><description>On July 30th at the Oasia Hotel Singapore, Dr. Tomas Chamorro-Premuzic, CEO of Hogan Assessment Systems, a leader in personality profiling and psychometric testing, along with Lewis Garrad, Managing Director Asia Pacific at Sirota, a performance consulting firm, will preview a new employee assessment model they jointly developed.
Launching in the Asia Pacific market in October 2015, the Engaging Leader tool will help companies and brands better identify and develop leadership potential.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Massachusetts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-massachusetts/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s always wonderful to see a returning customer! Earlier this year, I restored a Beogram 4000 for a client in Massachusetts. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to work on another Beogram 4000 he&amp;rsquo;s sent my way. It seems one can never have too many Beograms!
The Beogram 4000 arrived safely, shipped securely in a Beolover box. It was accompanied by a thoughtful gift for Beolover, for which I am incredibly grateful.
This beautiful reissue of &amp;ldquo;Waltz for Debby&amp;rdquo; by the Bill Evans Trio, a legendary jazz record, is a 180g pressing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Montana</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-montana/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-montana/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable from a customer in Montana who purchased it in the 1970s. He wants a complete restoration. This post provides an initial assessment, and a follow-up will detail the work done.
The turntable arrived safely in a protective Beolover shipping container. Upon opening it, the turntable appeared to be in good overall condition, with the aluminum surfaces and plinth corners looking particularly well-preserved.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival From California - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 08:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 Type 5513 from California, which needs a complete technical overhaul.
This post will provide an initial evaluation of the unit. It was delivered in excellent shape thanks to the customer&amp;rsquo;s careful packaging in a Beolover-provided shipping container. I was relieved because this device is in fantastic cosmetic shape. In the past, Beolover had a lot of &amp;ldquo;heartbreaking&amp;rdquo; experiences with units that arrived damaged because of inadequate packaging despite initially seeming pristine.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-australia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-australia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Australia recently arrived and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my initial assessment. Despite the packaging using incredibly small packing peanuts (resulting in a big mess!), the turntable arrived in great shape.
The attached image showcases the turntable as I unpacked it:
This Beogram 4000 has a nice dust cover with minimal scratching, good aluminum trim, and intact plexiglass hinges. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely worth keeping and polishing.
Under the dust cover, things are looking good as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look at a New Arrival from Berlin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look-at-a-new-arrival-from-berlin/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look-at-a-new-arrival-from-berlin/</guid><description>My first project in Germany this year is a Beogram 4000 turntable. While the packaging from Berlin was good, the dust cover was cracked in one corner, likely due to inadequate protection by the seller. Thankfully, the turntable itself is in decent cosmetic condition.
The aluminum surfaces are mostly unscathed, with some minor scratches from the tonearm assembly, probably because the transport lock wasn&amp;rsquo;t engaged. The wooden base is also in good shape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival from Florida</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 18:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida/</guid><description>A customer from Florida recently sent me a DC-motor Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable in its original packaging. After unboxing and setting it up, I observed the aluminum surfaces were in good shape, but the keypad showed typical wear. A refurbished keypad could address this issue. The plinth itself is in excellent condition with sharp corners.
Internally, the turntable appears largely original except for signs of work done on the motor.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival From Oklahoma - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 11:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-oklahoma-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in good condition.
While the dust cover is intact, it does have some scratches and might need polishing or replacement. The turntable itself is in good shape, with only minor blemishes on the aluminum surfaces and minimal wear on the keypad. Using a soft cloth to operate the keypad or installing a remote control module would help preserve its condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): A New Arrival from Australia with a Very Creative Way to Send the Cartridge Along!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-a-new-arrival-from-australia-with-a-very-creative-way-to-send-the-cartridge-along-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:51:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-a-new-arrival-from-australia-with-a-very-creative-way-to-send-the-cartridge-along-/</guid><description>The same Australian who owned the Beogram 4000 I recently restored also sent me a Beogram 4002 (a Type 5504) for refurbishment. Like the first turntable, it arrived safely in good condition thanks to its double boxing.
This unit came equipped with an MMC20E cartridge, secured in a uniquely inventive manner. Upon inspection at my workbench, I was greeted with this:
Removing the styrofoam revealed the following:
This novel approach, while unusual, seemed surprisingly effective for transporting a cartridge in the absence of a proper container.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival from Florida - First Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida-first-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 01:09:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-florida-first-assessment/</guid><description>A local customer brought me a Beogram 4002 (5513) for restoration last year, opting for the safety of personal delivery. The unit is in decent condition, as seen upon arrival.
[Image]
The dust cover is nearly flawless, with one common hinge crack just starting to form.
[Image]
This makes it a perfect candidate for Beolover hinge patches to reinforce the area, especially since the crack hasn&amp;rsquo;t fully developed. Of course, new hoods are an option now as well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Tennessee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-tennessee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-tennessee/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable arrived from a Tennessee customer for a complete restoration. The turntable was shipped safely in a Beolover container. This post focuses on the turntable&amp;rsquo;s initial condition upon arrival.
The first photo shows the turntable as it was unpacked.
The dust cover has numerous scratches and a spot that appears to be chemical damage. Replacing the existing cover with a new one from Beoparts-shop in Denmark is recommended, along with a new reproduction of the aluminum strip.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival From New Jersey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-new-jersey/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 02:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-new-jersey/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503) turntable from a collector in New Jersey who was downsizing their collection. This particular model will be restored for a customer who specifically requested a Beogram 4002 with an AC motor.
The turntable arrived securely packaged and in good cosmetic condition, although the dust cover had numerous scratches. I&amp;rsquo;m considering polishing the cover or replacing it with a newly available reproduction.
Upon removing the cover, I noticed the aluminum surfaces were well-maintained, but the keypad had delaminated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5524): A New Arrival from Texas - A Wrong Hood and Some Blown Fuses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-a-new-arrival-from-texas-a-wrong-hood-and-some-blown-fuses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 16:54:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5524-a-new-arrival-from-texas-a-wrong-hood-and-some-blown-fuses/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5524) turntable from Texas. This particular model features a universal voltage DC motor and a power switch located beneath the unit.
The turntable arrived securely packaged in a specialized container, ensuring it was free from any shipping damage. Here&amp;rsquo;s a photo of the turntable as I received it:
B&amp;amp;O enthusiasts might immediately notice something peculiar about this image. The hood&amp;rsquo;s color seems to suggest it belongs to a Beogram 4000, not a 4002.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): A New Arrival from California - First Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-assessment/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 09:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-a-new-arrival-from-california-first-assessment/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 turntable (model 5513) from a California customer. The turntable was shipped in a container provided by Beolover, ensuring a smooth transit process. This article details my initial assessment of the unit.
Upon unboxing, the turntable appeared to be in fair cosmetic condition. However, there were noticeable fingerprints on the keypad and a few minor scratches on the aluminum panel. The plinth corners, on the other hand, were well-preserved.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Kentucky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from Kentucky arrived safely thanks to its secure packaging. The turntable was in excellent cosmetic condition, with minimal scratching on the dust cover and un-cracked hinges.
Upon removing the cover, the aluminum surfaces appeared nearly flawless, showing only minor signs of wear. The keypad was also well-preserved, exhibiting only slight deterioration on the START key and a few insignificant marks. The pristine condition of the keypad made it an ideal candidate for the Beolover Commander remote control system, which protects such keypads from further wear.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-texas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 08:02:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-texas/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from a Texas customer. It was shipped securely in a Beolover container. This post will provide an initial assessment of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s condition. A follow-up post will detail the restoration process to bring it back to like-new performance.
Upon unboxing and inspecting the unit:
The dust cover shows typical signs of wear:
The hinges are intact, suggesting either polishing for extended use or replacement with a new reproduction from the Beoparts-store in Denmark.</description></item></channel></rss>