<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real Estate on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real-estate/</link><description>Recent content in Real Estate on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Keppel Land enhances marketing strategy with virtual show suites</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</guid><description>Keppel Land is the first developer in Singapore to utilize Oculus Rift technology to create 360-degree immersive virtual reality (VR) show suites for its Highline Residences property. These two digitally rendered suites complement the three existing physical show suites at the Highline Residences showroom in Singapore.
The new VR platform, a collaboration between Keppel Land and visualisation firm VMW Group, features virtual tours of these new unit layouts. It also allows for a virtual exploration of key landmarks in the trendy Tiong Bahru neighborhood where Highline Residences is located...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/keppel-land-enhances-marketing-strategy-with-virtual-show-suites/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>