<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Parallels on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/parallels/</link><description>Recent content in Parallels on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/parallels/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website.</description></item><item><title>Pi Day is on July 22nd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pi-day-is-on-july-22nd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 01:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pi-day-is-on-july-22nd/</guid><description>Pi Day is observed twice a year. The date March 14 (3/14) reflects the constant&amp;rsquo;s value. It&amp;rsquo;s also celebrated on July 22, referencing the common fractional representation of Pi, 22/7.
To mark the occasion, Parallels has designed an infographic with fascinating information about Pi and suggestions for celebrating.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in Singapore are increasingly transitioning to cloud services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-singapore-are-increasingly-transitioning-to-cloud-services/</guid><description>Parallels, a company specializing in hosting and cloud services, has released an updated report on the Singaporean cloud market for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), called Parallels SMB Cloud Insights. This 2014 report predicts significant growth for the SMB cloud services market in Singapore, projecting it to reach S$916 million by 2017. This represents a strong three-year compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 21%.
Source: Parallels. Zanni.
John Zanni, Chief Marketing Officer for Service Providers at Parallels, observed that the Asia Pacific region is poised to outpace the rest of the world in cloud adoption due to its later start.</description></item><item><title>Simplify your computing experience with Parallels Toolbox 3.5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simplify-your-computing-experience-with-parallels-toolbox-3-5/</guid><description>Parallels has released Parallels Toolbox 3.5 for Windows and Mac. This suite of over 30 tools is designed to make using PCs and Macs easier.
“We&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to PC and Mac users who want new tools that can simplify their lives,” said Nick Dobrovolskiy, Senior VP of Engineering and Support at Parallels.
“We&amp;rsquo;ve added Break Time, Energy Saver, Hide Menu Icons, Clipboard History, and Sleep Timer to the dozens of other one-click solutions already available.</description></item><item><title>Access PC or Mac applications from iOS and Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</guid><description>Source: Parallels website.
Parallels has launched an updated version of its Parallels Access app for iOS and Android. The app allows for remote access to both PCs and Macs, letting users access files and run applications while on the move.
With Parallels Access, mobile devices can remotely utilize applications, edit documents, and search through files on a connected computer. Users can connect to any computer through a web browser without needing additional plugins or extensions.</description></item></channel></rss>