<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HDTV on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hdtv/</link><description>Recent content in HDTV on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:18:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hdtv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1.5 and 3.0 Gbps Uncompressed HD Video Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</guid><description>Analog television with its standard-definition video signals is a thing of the past. While older 4:3 aspect ratio televisions still exist, they are sustained by cable and satellite receivers. However, high-definition (HD) channels are becoming more prevalent, and standard-definition channels are being phased out as viewers switch to flat-screen HD TVs. The future of television is internet protocol television (IPTV) in high definition, with 3D technology on the horizon.
For broadcasters, distributors, and content providers, traditional video transport methods are no longer adequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Samsung Epic 4G offers Epic Performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 17:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</guid><description>Imagine a smartphone so powerful it surpasses a netbook. Picture yourself declining WiFi because your cellular connection is faster. That&amp;rsquo;s the kind of speed the Samsung Epic 4G offers with its impressive 10+ Mbps download speeds, thanks to the Sprint WiMAX 4G network. You can even share your connection as a mobile hotspot for your other devices.
Beyond speed, the Epic boasts a stunning Super AMOLED touchscreen display with near-HD quality and unmatched contrast...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Time to Move to HD Video Cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/</guid><description>The familiar sound of &amp;ldquo;Taps&amp;rdquo; softly playing from your TV symbolizes the end of an era: analog television. From its start with Herbert Hoover to its abrupt conclusion, marked by TV stations switching off their analog transmitters, this technology has reached its end. The outdated 4:3 video format should disappear alongside it, but strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s still present.
Observe TV broadcasts throughout the day, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find many programs, including network shows and local news, still framed by black bars on the sides...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Video is Moving to H.264</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</guid><description>Digital video is gaining immense popularity and rapidly consuming internet bandwidth. It&amp;rsquo;s revolutionizing television, expanding its presence on the internet, and being adopted by businesses for cost reduction, productivity gains, and environmental benefits. However, its major drawback is its heavy bandwidth consumption.
H.264, a video coding standard, addresses this issue by offering high-quality video at lower bandwidths through compression. While uncompressed high-quality video demands significant bandwidth, unsuitable for most businesses and consumers, H...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-video-is-moving-to-h264/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>