<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EPPO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eppo/</link><description>Recent content in EPPO on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eppo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Evolution of EU Criminal Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 06:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2014 was significant for the European Union, marked by events such as European Parliament elections, the establishment of a new European Commission, and notable legislative and case-law developments. This post, the first in a series, reviews key developments in specific EU law areas.
The most substantial change in EU criminal law occurred on December 1st, ending the five-year transition period for EU criminal law measures enacted before the Lisbon Treaty came into effect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-evolution-of-eu-criminal-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Public Prosecutor’s Office and Fundamental Rights: A Disquieting Lack of Discussion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</guid><description>Michiel Luchtman, Jannemieke Ouwerkerk, Marloes van Noorloos, Pim Geelhoed, Jorrit Rijpma, and Louis Middelkoop are affiliated with the Meijers Committee (www.commissie-meijers.nl/en).
The EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed European Public Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office (EPPO) has sparked significant debate among Member States. The EPPO&amp;rsquo;s role would be to investigate and prosecute fraudulent use of EU funds, with discussions already underway to expand its jurisdiction to include terrorism and other serious crimes. Current political dialogue centers around the necessity of this supranational entity and the potential impact on national sovereignty, particularly within the sensitive realm of criminal justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>