<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Navigation System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/navigation-system/</link><description>Recent content in Navigation System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:28:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/navigation-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Wants A Computer In Their Car?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-wants-a-computer-in-their-car/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:28:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-wants-a-computer-in-their-car/</guid><description>Ford is considering adding in-dash computers to their work trucks and vans, which begs the question: could passenger cars be next? This technology would replace laptops that contractors currently rely on, offering features like digital forms, planning documents, and even invoice printing.
While this is helpful for construction workers, an in-dash computer could benefit others, too. Salespeople, consultants, and anyone who conducts business on-the-go could manage messages, documents, orders, receipts, and faxes directly from their vehicles.</description></item><item><title>Can iPhone 3G S Be The Universal Gadget?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 17:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-iphone-3g-s-be-the-universal-gadget/</guid><description>People love electronics but hate carrying a lot of them around. A single, universal gadget would be ideal – one that combines the functions of a cell phone, TV, camera, computer, and more.
Such a device would need to be a phone, TV, DVR, high-quality camera, camcorder, audio recorder, navigation system, gaming console, computer, messaging system, productivity tool, radio, eBook reader, music player, stock trading platform, watch, alarm clock, weather tracker, and shopping service.</description></item></channel></rss>