<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Headphone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headphone/</link><description>Recent content in Headphone on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bose's Bluetooth speakers and headphones simplify the process of making connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bose-s-bluetooth-speakers-and-headphones-simplify-the-process-of-making-connections/</guid><description>Bose has expanded its SoundLink mobile audio lineup with two new products: the SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker, their most budget-friendly SoundLink speaker yet, and the SoundLink Bluetooth on-ear headphones, Bose&amp;rsquo;s first foray into on-ear Bluetooth headphones.
The SoundLink Color Bluetooth speaker features a brand new design. Weighing in at 1.25 pounds (567g), it measures 5 inches wide, 2.1 inches deep, and 5.3 inches high. Bose has engineered the speaker with dual-opposing passive radiators and two high-efficiency transducers to deliver powerful, full-range sound, including impressive bass performance.</description></item><item><title>Introducing the new BioSport In-Ear headphones, now in stock</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 07:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-new-biosport-in-ear-headphones-now-in-stock/</guid><description>Source: Intel.
The BioSport In-Ear headphones are now available, developed through a partnership between SMS Audio and Intel. These headphones provide high-quality audio while simultaneously tracking fitness progress.
The headphones monitor heart rate through integrated biometric sensors, allowing users to monitor their fitness journey and strive for peak performance.
BioSport headphones take in-ear technology to the next level. Their ear-wing design fits securely in the ear canal for constant heart rate monitoring in real time.</description></item><item><title>JVC introduces new sports in-ear headphones that are waterproof and washable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 03:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jvc-introduces-new-sports-in-ear-headphones-that-are-waterproof-and-washable/</guid><description>Source: JVC.
JVC introduces four new sports headphone options designed to stay securely in place during physical activity, with some models offering waterproof and washable features.
The lineup includes two models in both the JVC Gumy Sport and Extreme Fitness series. The Gumy Sport headphones, HA-EN10 and HA-ENR15, utilize a Nozzle Fit earpiece constructed from soft silicone. This unique shape ensures a secure and comfortable fit, preventing the headphones from falling out during workouts.</description></item><item><title>The Beats Decade Collection features the Defiant Black-Red colorway for Beats by Dr. Dre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 21:28:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beats-decade-collection-features-the-defiant-black-red-colorway-for-beats-by-dr-dre/</guid><description>Source: Beats. The Beats Decade Collection.
To commemorate its 10th anniversary, Beats by Dr Dre has unveiled the Beats Decade Collection, a special edition line of products in a striking black and red colorway. This bold design choice pays homage to the brand&amp;rsquo;s origins and the intense emotions evoked by music.
The Defiant Black-Red color scheme is showcased in these models:
Source: Beats. The Beats Studio3 wireless headphones, in folded mode.</description></item></channel></rss>