<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brief on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brief/</link><description>Recent content in Brief on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/brief/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Fun Evening with a Prematurely Activating Solenoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 06:48:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-fun-evening-with-a-prematurely-activating-solenoid/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration is progressing well. Rebuilding the deck led to a successful initial power-up where the carriage moved to the correct position, but the arm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t lower. A visual inspection showed a disconnected thin grey wire from the SK3054 NPN power transistor (0TR4).
Tracing the wiring and consulting the schematic revealed that the grey wire connected to the transistor&amp;rsquo;s emitter, responsible for bypassing a current-limiting resistor (7R1) during the arm&amp;rsquo;s initial descent.</description></item><item><title>Brief Lab introduces new online certification program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 09:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brief-lab-introduces-new-online-certification-program/</guid><description>The Brief Lab, an organization that trains professionals to be concise communicators, is marking its one-year anniversary with a redesigned website and the introduction of its first online certification program, Brief Practitioner.
Source: The Brief Lab website.
The Brief Practitioner program is geared towards professionals who want to embrace conciseness and become certified in a structured approach to lean communication. The online course is designed for those who aim to champion these methodologies within their organizations.</description></item></channel></rss>