<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Q1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q1/</link><description>Recent content in Q1 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/q1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smaato has analyzed the effectiveness of mobile video ads in the first quarter of 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</guid><description>Source: Smaato website.
Smaato, a global platform connecting mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q1 2016 Global Trends in Mobile Advertising report. The report leverages Smaato&amp;rsquo;s analysis of billions of mobile ad impressions that ran on its exchange platform in the first quarter of 2016.
The findings highlight significant growth in mobile video advertising, which generated 11 times higher effective cost per thousand impressions (eCPMs) for publishers than other ad formats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-has-analyzed-the-effectiveness-of-mobile-video-ads-in-the-first-quarter-of-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Passenger figures for Dubai taxis in the first quarter of 2017 have been released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</guid><description>Source: RTA. A taxi on Dubai roads.
During the first quarter of 2017, taxis in Dubai, UAE provided 25,795,251 rides, serving a total of 44,883,737 passengers. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s taxi franchises collectively operate 10,038 vehicles. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown by company:
Dubai Taxi: 12,981,104 trips, serving 21,050,701 passengers. Arabia Taxi: 2,536,705 trips, serving 4,413,867 passengers. Cars Taxi: 5,311,065 trips, serving 9,241,253 passengers. Metro Taxi: 1,995,090 trips, serving 3,471,457 passengers. National Taxi: 3,755,367 trips, serving 6,534,339 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passenger-figures-for-dubai-taxis-in-the-first-quarter-of-2017-have-been-released/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>