<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>O2O on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/o2o/</link><description>Recent content in O2O on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/o2o/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MatahariMall.com in Indonesia is growing its O2O network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</guid><description>Source: MatahariMall.com website.
The online shopping platform MatahariMall has broadened its Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD and eLocker services through a partnership with PT Pos Indonesia in Jakarta. This collaboration uses an online-to-offline approach, enabling customers to receive, return, and pay for their online purchases at physical locations.
This partnership introduces more Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD points at designated post offices. Additionally, MatahariMall will install eLockers at strategic post office locations across Jakarta, Bogor, Depok, Tangerang, Bekasi, and Bandung...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive outfits for My Omamori will be available to Huawei mobile gamers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. My Omamori offers perks for Huawei users.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s mobile services branch has teamed up with Original Workshop, the creators of the female-oriented game My Omamori, to give special prizes to mobile players.
Omamori means lucky charm in Japanese. In the game, an ancient warrior, Toki Mamoru, travels to the present to become the player’s guardian angel. Mamoru, who is voiced by Japanese voice actor Yuki Ono, was developed by Taiwanese novelist Deer Li...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The latest digital tools that lead to business success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 01:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</guid><description>Ebenezer Heng, Principal Consultant at Top Advertising, emphasizes that businesses must understand and leverage the connection between online and offline marketing to thrive. Speaking at the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld Conference, he argued that traditional success factors like &amp;ldquo;gut feel&amp;rdquo; are no longer enough in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape.
He illustrated this with the example of choosing a business location. Simply observing foot traffic isn&amp;rsquo;t sufficient; online sentiment analysis, which gauges public opinion about a location, can reveal a different picture of popularity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-digital-tools-that-lead-to-business-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Utilize online brand ambassadors to add a personal touch to your online presence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</guid><description>Source: Oomph! Lee.
Oomph!, a Singapore-based staffing agency, has introduced ENGAGE, a new online platform and service for brand ambassadors. This platform aims to replicate the personalized customer service of physical stores in the digital world.
ENGAGE connects businesses with trained online brand ambassadors who can interact with customers through a chat box, including video chat options. These ambassadors can help customers find suitable products, answer their questions, and even book in-person store visits for a more traditional shopping experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>