<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tower on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tower/</link><description>Recent content in Tower on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tower/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP creates servers specifically for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced new ProLiant Gen9 Tower servers to its Compute portfolio. These servers are designed to give small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) a cost-effective solution with a good mix of performance, efficiency, and manageability.
These servers are designed to handle a variety of general-purpose workloads and critical applications, including IT infrastructure, collaboration, web, and business applications. This support is intended to meet both current and future business needs.
“Small businesses must not only address immediate business challenges but also establish a foundation for rapid business expansion,” stated Peter Schrady, VP and GM of Rack and Tower Servers at HP...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-creates-servers-specifically-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>