<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>3D on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d/</link><description>Recent content in 3D on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:08:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/3d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fuji Xerox provides an introduction to 3D printing in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuji-xerox-provides-an-introduction-to-3d-printing-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fuji-xerox-provides-an-introduction-to-3d-printing-in-singapore/</guid><description>Eugene Ying inquired about the audience&amp;rsquo;s understanding of additive manufacturing.
Singapore offers ample resources for those interested in 3D printing, according to Eugene Ying, 3D Sales Manager for Fuji Xerox Asia Pacific. He made this statement during the Fuji Xerox DocuWorld event in Singapore.
Ying emphasized the rapid commercialization of 3D printing, citing Airbus as a prime example. As of September 2017, Airbus incorporated a 3D-printed titanium bracket into the production of their A350 XWB aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is on recording directly from your phone to the computer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 14:36:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-on-recording-directly-from-your-phone-to-the-computer/</guid><description>Recap S2, a compact device designed to connect to smartphones for saving calls to external devices like computers or voice recorders, is seeking funding on Kickstarter.
Source: Kickstarter website
Inventor Igor Ramos highlights the device&amp;rsquo;s user-friendliness, stating its compatibility with any device equipped with a combo port for input and a standard stereo microphone port for output.
Ramos assures users that Recap recordings maintain the original call quality.
A video demonstration is available here.</description></item><item><title>Golden Village Multiplex is the first in Singapore to introduce Auro 11.1 audio technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-village-multiplex-is-the-first-in-singapore-to-introduce-auro-11-1-audio-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-village-multiplex-is-the-first-in-singapore-to-introduce-auro-11-1-audio-technology/</guid><description>Golden Village Multiplex is the first cinema chain in Singapore to offer Auro 11.1 by Barco, an immersive 3D sound technology.
Long, Long Time Ago portrays Singapore approximately 50 years in the past.
Audiences can experience Auro 11.1 at Golden Village Suntec City in Singapore with the debut of Jack Neo&amp;rsquo;s newest Chinese New Year film, Long, Long Time Ago (我们的故事), premiering February 4th. To fully utilize this immersive audio technology, the film was mixed at Galaxy Studios Belgium specifically for Auro 11.</description></item><item><title>Your Windows device will soon enhance your creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-windows-device-will-soon-enhance-your-creativity/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The possibilities of Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, sketched on a Microsoft Surface by Michael Mindflyer.
Microsoft has launched the latest version of its operating system, the Windows 10 Fall Creators Update, offering it as a free upgrade to current Windows 10 users globally. This update, the fourth major one for Windows 10, prioritizes creativity. It aims to make mixed reality and 3D design accessible to Windows users, leading to improvements in gaming, audiovisual content, and mixed reality experiences.</description></item><item><title>Tinkr provides custom calligraphy necklaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 19:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</guid><description>Source: Tinkr website.
The company Tinkr is offering custom-made pendants. These pendants are unique corporate gifts because they are designed using a person&amp;rsquo;s actual handwriting.
Starting at S$78, the company will craft a pendant featuring up to two words written in the handwriting provided. For those who prefer professional calligraphy, Tinkr offers this service starting at S$98. Veronica Halim, Tinkr&amp;rsquo;s in-house calligrapher, would design the calligraphy.
Source: Tinkr newsletter.</description></item><item><title>ItSeez3D has released an updated version of its 3D scanner app for iPad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/itseez3d-has-released-an-updated-version-of-its-3d-scanner-app-for-ipad/</guid><description>Source: itSeez3D page on the App Store.
itSeez3D, a company that develops 3D scanning software, has released an updated version of their mobile scanning app, also named itSeez3D. This app, designed for use with the Occipital Structure Sensor 3D device, now allows iPads to generate lifelike, full-body 3D models.
This updated app serves as a valuable tool for 3D printing, enabling the scanning of a full-color figurine in under two minutes.</description></item></channel></rss>