<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jabra on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jabra/</link><description>Recent content in Jabra on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jabra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Halo Smart is designed to enhance both your calling and music experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</guid><description>Jabra Halo Smart headphones are designed for users who prioritize call quality but also enjoy listening to music. Research indicates that 79% of consumers desire headphones suitable for both calls and music, yet find most music headphones lacking in call performance.
These headphones prioritize calls with features like high-quality microphones, wind-noise reduction, and a dedicated button for Google Now or Siri. At the same time, they offer great audio quality for music with 10mm speakers.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra SPEAK 810 can detect and track people speaking from several meters away</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-speak-810-can-detect-and-track-people-speaking-from-several-meters-away/</guid><description>Fragment.in, a Swiss design interaction studio, created a computer orchestra controlled by gestures. Hand movements are recognized by a Kinect, which then controls audio from multiple computers. The sound is emitted through Jabra SPEAK 810 devices.
Jabra, a company specializing in audio and communications technology, has launched the SPEAK 810. This new conference speakerphone offers high-quality call experiences to enhance meeting collaboration.
Retailing at US$599, the Jabra SPEAK 810 addresses common obstacles to effective collaboration.</description></item><item><title>Jabra is unveiling three new additions to its Elite series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</guid><description>Jabra introduces the Elite Active 65t (right), Elite 65e (left), and Elite 45e (middle) to the Singapore market.
Jabra is releasing three new products: the Elite Active 65t, Elite 65e, and Elite 45e in Singapore. These devices belong to the Elite family of headphones and earbuds, known for superior music quality and excellent voice capabilities.
The Elite family encompasses various styles like true wireless, headband, neckband, and soft neckband. The suffix &amp;ldquo;e&amp;rdquo; signifies an earbud design, while &amp;ldquo;t&amp;rdquo; indicates true wireless.</description></item><item><title>Jabra discusses the obstacles of maintaining productivity in a workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</guid><description>Source: Jabra research report.
According to audio and communications company Jabra, modern workplaces face difficulties in fostering productivity due to common hurdles employees experience daily. These include distractions, poorly structured meetings, and technology that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as intended.
Jabra&amp;rsquo;s 2015 research report, Productivity at the Office – Challenges, highlights that while companies invest in resources and tools to help office workers collaborate and focus, employees still encounter obstacles. These include constant distractions, unproductive meetings, and challenges utilizing technology meant to enhance their output.</description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around.</description></item><item><title>Jabra emphasizes the importance of educating and incentivizing employees to guarantee the success of UC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 14:49:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-emphasizes-the-importance-of-educating-and-incentivizing-employees-to-guarantee-the-success-of-uc/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that makes audio solutions, believes the tech industry needs to rethink its definition of success for unified communications (UC) deployments.
Source: Jabra website.
Currently, only 10% of companies use UC. This is because employees don&amp;rsquo;t want to give up their current tools and ways of working. Companies are spending a lot of money on UC, but employees don&amp;rsquo;t see how it can help them be more productive.</description></item></channel></rss>