<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Call Routing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-routing/</link><description>Recent content in Call Routing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/call-routing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2.</description></item><item><title>How AI is Helping to Improve Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 22:16:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-ai-is-helping-to-improve-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Customer service calls are increasingly frustrating due to rising costs and labor shortages, negatively impacting both customers and companies. Tech expert David Pogue, in a CBS News report, suggests a blend of human agents and AI as a solution.
One such AI, called Grace, can handle customer interactions independently. However, AI like Grace can falter in complex situations, necessitating a transfer to human agents. While some of the best agents are located internationally and may have accents, this can be a hurdle for some US customers.</description></item></channel></rss>