<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TTG on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ttg/</link><description>Recent content in TTG on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 19:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ttg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Singapore Gifts Show will be running until July 11th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 19:21:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show 2014 (SGS), now in its ninth year, will focus on showcasing products designed in Singapore and local businesses.
The show, supported by the DesignSingapore Council, will feature many Singapore-made gifts, including a new gift and souvenir line called Now &amp;amp; Then. Celcem, led by designer and Singaporean entrepreneur Edwin Low, owner of the local retail boutique Supermama, spearheads this new label. Low, the recipient of the President’s Design Award in 2013, runs Supermama, the studio responsible for the President’s Design Award’s ‘Singapore Icons’ souvenir collection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-gifts-show-will-be-running-until-july-11th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Come to Singapore Gifts Show 2015 for a wide selection of corporate gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</guid><description>The upcoming Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015 is the ideal event to discover this year&amp;rsquo;s corporate gift trends. Taking place from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, Halls 401 to 403, this international trade event offers free admission. It showcases innovative gifts, premiums, and lifestyle products and services, catering to trade buyers and corporate attendees.
Celebrating its 10th anniversary, SGS 2015 will host 160 booths featuring exhibitors from the Philippines, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>