<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access to Justice on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-justice/</link><description>Recent content in Access to Justice on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:31:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-justice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The EU has restricted access to evidence through secretive means, pushing the boundaries of justice and cooperation within the European judicial system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi &amp;amp; Christina Eckes*
*Assistant professor of European law, Maastricht University and professor of European law, University of Amsterdam, respectively.
Beyond a &amp;lsquo;Procedural&amp;rsquo; Adjustment
The European Union has encountered substantial political and economic turmoil in recent years. For the first time in its 60-year existence, it faces a Member State seeking to withdraw, confronts hostility and trade conflicts with its former transatlantic partner, and grapples with rising populist movements across Europe that challenge the EU&amp;rsquo;s core principles, such as the rule of law.</description></item><item><title>New discoveries in the "Mellifera" case shed light on access to environmental justice under the Aarhus Regulation, but the underlying issues remain unchanged.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 01:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-discoveries-in-the-mellifera-case-shed-light-on-access-to-environmental-justice-under-the-aarhus-regulation-but-the-underlying-issues-remain-unchanged/</guid><description>Mario Pagano, PhD candidate in EU environmental law, European University Institute
Background
The Aarhus Convention is a crucial piece of international law concerning environmental democracy rights. Established in 1998, this UN Convention lays out three procedural rights directly connected to environmental protection: the right to environmental information, the right to participate in environmental decision-making, and the right to legal recourse on environmental issues (the three Aarhus &amp;ldquo;pillars&amp;rdquo;).
The Aarhus Convention Compliance Committee (ACCC), formed in Geneva in 2002, ensures that the legislation of the Convention&amp;rsquo;s Parties aligns with the Convention itself.</description></item><item><title>A missed chance to enhance access to justice in environmental issues: the CJEU's ruling on the applicability of the Aarhus Convention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 15:14:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-missed-chance-to-enhance-access-to-justice-in-environmental-issues-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-applicability-of-the-aarhus-convention/</guid><description>**
**
Dr. Apolline J. C. Roger, Senior Teaching Fellow in EU environmental law, University of Edinburgh Law School.
The right to access justice is a crucial safeguard for environmental NGOs and citizens, allowing them to contest public authorities&amp;rsquo; decisions that impact the environment and public health. By joining the Aarhus Convention in 2005, the EU acknowledged this right as a pillar of good governance and a key element of the human right to a healthy environment.</description></item></channel></rss>