<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Sales on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-sales/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Sales on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>Telarus, the New Face of Telecom Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a massive transformation thanks to disruptive technology. Wireless technology is shaking up the century-old wireline business, VoIP is changing the landscape of the digital voice trunking business, competitive fiber optic carriers are challenging the dominance of established phone companies, and Ethernet and IP networks are blurring the lines between local and wide area networks.
Despite these technological advancements, the sales and marketing processes for business telecommunications services have remained largely unchanged.</description></item><item><title>Supplement Your Income</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplement-your-income/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 16:12:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplement-your-income/</guid><description>The economy is strained, jobs are scarce, and even secure positions might not be safe in the future. Instead of panicking, consider building an additional income source. This could boost your savings, cover rising expenses or investment losses, and provide a safety net if you lose your job.
Those with technical or business expertise are well-suited to generate supplementary income through what&amp;rsquo;s traditionally known as a &amp;ldquo;side business.&amp;rdquo; This could involve freelance work, a hobby that generates income, or a start-up, all operating alongside your primary job.</description></item></channel></rss>