<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cultural on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cultural/</link><description>Recent content in Cultural on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cultural/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes.</description></item><item><title>The intangible cultural heritage of North Korea includes the tradition of making kimchi and the rituals surrounding Arabic coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-north-korea-includes-the-tradition-of-making-kimchi-and-the-rituals-surrounding-arabic-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 08:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-north-korea-includes-the-tradition-of-making-kimchi-and-the-rituals-surrounding-arabic-coffee/</guid><description>The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) committee dedicated to safeguarding intangible cultural heritage convened in Namibia and added 20 new elements to the prestigious Representative List of the Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity. This list showcases diverse forms of expression that embody intangible heritage and promotes broader awareness of their significance. Concluding this year&amp;rsquo;s nomination review, the committee inscribed 23 out of 35 proposed elements.
On December 2nd, the following entries from the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions were formally included on the list:</description></item></channel></rss>