<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wireless Backhaul on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-backhaul/</link><description>Recent content in Wireless Backhaul on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wireless-backhaul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Many T1 Lines Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</guid><description>For small businesses dissatisfied with DSL or Cable broadband, a professional T1 line might seem like the ideal solution. The superior reliability and dedicated bandwidth make T1 lines the popular choice for business voice and data services. However, as your business expands, you might encounter the bandwidth limitations of your once-sufficient T1 line. What then?
Similarly, high-tech businesses, such as Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) or video production companies, might find the 1.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper Rivals Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-ethernet-over-copper-rivals-fiber/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper is quickly replacing T1 lines for low to medium bandwidth needs. While copper lines can reach speeds of 20 to 50 Mbps, Paetec now offers 100 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, eliminating the need for fiber optic service in many situations.
For over a century, copper wires have connected central offices to telephones. While designed for low-frequency audio signals, clever engineering enables these existing copper lines to carry high-frequency digital signals.</description></item><item><title>Backhaul is Backing Things Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backhaul-is-backing-things-up/</guid><description>While it may seem like the world operates solely on wireless connections, especially if you rely on cell phones and mobile internet, this is only true for the link between your device and the nearest cell tower or access point. Beyond that point lies the backhaul, a crucial but often overlooked component that bridges the wireless and wired worlds. As wireless connections become faster, the limitations of traditional backhaul solutions are becoming increasingly apparent.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Network Expansion Underway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</guid><description>Our society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to bandwidth is evident with the recent launch of a massive dark fiber network project by Allied Fiber. This project will encircle the US with 548 dark fibers and 300 tower sites.
Fiber optic communication is experiencing a resurgence and this time it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. Unlike the failed attempt in the 1990s, the unused fiber optic cables laid then are likely to be utilized soon due to the resurfacing of the telecommunication revolution.</description></item></channel></rss>