<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MetroE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metroe/</link><description>Recent content in MetroE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metroe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>150 Mbps Ethernet vs OC3 Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 08:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</guid><description>If your current DS3 bandwidth of 45 Mbps is no longer sufficient, it might be time to consider faster options like OC3 at 155 Mbps or Ethernet services. Comparing these choices could prove beneficial.
When you require higher bandwidth, fiber optic delivery usually becomes necessary. While options like Ethernet over Copper or fixed wireless microwave service exceeding 100 Mbps exist, they are limited to locations very close to the provider with clear line of sight for microwave...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/150-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc3-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Growing Companies Buy Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/</guid><description>As businesses recover and grow, they&amp;rsquo;ll need more resources. But with economic uncertainty, it&amp;rsquo;s wise to expand cautiously. Is that even possible with bandwidth?
Yes, it is. Traditional telecom contracts lock you into a service level for 1 to 3 years. For example, a T1 line provides a fixed 1.5 Mbps bandwidth for a monthly fee. Doubling bandwidth means another T1 line. These lines can be &amp;lsquo;bonded&amp;rsquo; for combined bandwidth, either by the provider or using devices like Mushroom Networks&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Truffle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-growing-companies-buy-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Stunning Truth About Metro Ethernet Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 09:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/</guid><description>In recent years, a new type of network connection called Metro Ethernet (MetroE) has emerged, offering significantly more bandwidth at lower costs compared to traditional options.
This cost-effectiveness is driven by two main factors: technological advancements and the rise of competitive service providers. This combination provides businesses, especially in challenging economic times, an opportunity to enhance their network capabilities without increasing expenses or even reduce costs while maintaining the same bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stunning-truth-about-metro-ethernet-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fast MEN Available Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 23:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</guid><description>When you need to transfer a lot of data quickly, you need a robust solution to get it from its origin to its destination. If your current method is slow and inefficient, you need a powerful alternative to get things moving. If the cost of your current telecommunications connection is too high, you need a solution that is both fast and affordable.
This might sound like a case for a superhero, but the answer to your telecommunications problems could be MEN - Metropolitan Ethernet Networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fast-men-available-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Flavors of Fast Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Don&amp;rsquo;t let bandwidth restrictions hinder your business growth. There are two budget-friendly ways to obtain 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service, which is typically sufficient for small to medium-sized businesses. We&amp;rsquo;ll discuss upgrading to Gigabit Ethernet later.
Fast Ethernet over Fiber
The leading business bandwidth solution has transitioned from traditional T1 lines to fiber optic service. We&amp;rsquo;re not referring to the outdated and expensive SONET telco fiber known as OC-3, OC-12, or OC-48, but rather the contemporary Carrier Ethernet standard called Ethernet over Fiber, or Metro Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-flavors-of-fast-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>