<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coworking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coworking/</link><description>Recent content in Coworking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/coworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Collective Works and CapitaLand are teaming up to launch a new coworking space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</guid><description>Artist&amp;rsquo;s impression of the new coworking space at Capital Tower, Singapore.
A new high-end coworking space will be launched on the 12th floor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Capital Tower. This joint venture between two companies will occupy 22,000 square feet and support 250 businesses. The space is adaptable and caters to a variety of businesses, from new startups to large corporations. Technological features include secure server hosting, video conferencing, internet phone services, and fiber optic broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>Work together at a beach resort and form new relationships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:32:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/work-together-at-a-beach-resort-and-form-new-relationships/</guid><description>While new coworking spaces and startup events are constantly emerging, forging meaningful connections with startups outside of one&amp;rsquo;s immediate location can still be challenging. Coworking Camp aims to bridge this gap with its upcoming six-week program. This program offers startups and digital nomads a chance to network and explore business opportunities with like-minded individuals in a relaxed and comfortable environment.
Source: Coworking Camp website.
Matthias Zeitler, Chief Coworker, highlights the program&amp;rsquo;s focus on fostering valuable connections and providing a space for rejuvenation.</description></item><item><title>OUE has chosen The Work Project as its official coworking space partner at the Downtown Gallery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oue-has-chosen-the-work-project-as-its-official-coworking-space-partner-at-the-downtown-gallery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 05:13:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oue-has-chosen-the-work-project-as-its-official-coworking-space-partner-at-the-downtown-gallery/</guid><description>Source: OUE Limited. Concept workspace at The Work Project.
OUE Limited has selected The Work Project as its official coworking space provider for the new Downtown Gallery located in OUE Downtown, Singapore. Downtown Gallery, envisioned as a &amp;ldquo;Future Mall for the Future Self,&amp;rdquo; will feature The Work Project&amp;rsquo;s innovative workspaces designed for the modern workforce.
Every detail of The Work Project, from the layout to the sensory environment and membership options, has been thoughtfully chosen to create a comprehensive and modern office setting.</description></item></channel></rss>