<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electricity on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electricity/</link><description>Recent content in Electricity on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electricity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Your Next Battery Is a Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</guid><description>Benjamin Franklin&amp;rsquo;s experiment with capturing electricity in Leyden Jars, glass jars with foil conductors that store electric charge, laid the groundwork for modern battery technology.
Today, researchers have developed ultracapacitors, like the Graphene Ultracapacitor from the University of Texas at Austin, which are essentially very small but powerful capacitors. These ultracapacitors use nanometer-thin dielectrics instead of bulky glass jars, allowing them to achieve farad-level capacitance, much higher than the picofarad capacity of a Leyden Jar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Protecting data and smart meters: GDPR and the EU clean energy law's 'winter package'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giulia Pizza, FratiniVergano, European Lawyers - a Brussels-based law firm specialising in European and international law
Introduction
In late 2016, the European Commission introduced the “Clean Energy for All Europeans” legislative package to modernize Europe&amp;rsquo;s electricity market and encourage cleaner energy solutions. This push for &amp;ldquo;decentralization&amp;rdquo; is seen as a way to drive innovation and shift the focus to a demand-driven energy policy. The goal is to give consumers the tools they need to actively participate in this change...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Holy Guacamole, It's Green Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:11:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</guid><description>The internet&amp;rsquo;s days of excessive energy consumption might be ending. Websites and online businesses contribute to environmental issues, but we can&amp;rsquo;t just abandon the technology we rely on. We need a more sustainable solution: eco-friendly hosting.
The demand for electricity is increasing while clean energy sources are limited. Traditional power sources like coal are harmful, and even with reduced emissions, they still contribute to climate change. Renewable energy is becoming a viable solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holy-guacamole-its-green-hosting/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>