<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Auckland on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/auckland/</link><description>Recent content in Auckland on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/auckland/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service.</description></item></channel></rss>