<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tbps on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tbps/</link><description>Recent content in Tbps on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tbps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly.</description></item><item><title>XO Communications Nears Tbps National Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 01:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-nears-tbps-national-network/</guid><description>Any lingering doubts about the supposed overabundance of bandwidth in the late &amp;rsquo;90s telecom boom should be dispelled by XO Communications&amp;rsquo; recent announcement. Despite upgrading their national backbone just last year, XO is increasing its capacity again. This upgrade will boost major coast-to-coast network routes from 400 Gbps to a staggering 800 Gbps, putting them within reach of terabit-per-second speeds.
This massive capacity increase is driven by a fivefold surge in demand for high-capacity inter-city network services over the past year, according to XO.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item></channel></rss>