<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Car on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/car/</link><description>Recent content in Car on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/car/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dawn Black Badge provides luxurious open-top driving in a striking black color</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</guid><description>Source: Rolls-Royce Motor Cars. The Rolls-Royce Dawn Black Badge.
Rolls-Royce Motor Cars has introduced the Dawn Black Badge, a new addition to their lineup.
This model joins the Wraith Black Badge and Ghost Black Badge, offering a luxurious and bold take on open-top driving with a darker and more sensual aesthetic. The Dawn Black Badge was revealed in a strikingly deep black shade, achieved through a meticulous painting and polishing process that is the most extensive ever employed by Rolls-Royce for a solid paint color...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Official images of the Sportage exterior have been shared by Kia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/official-images-of-the-sportage-exterior-have-been-shared-by-kia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 07:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/official-images-of-the-sportage-exterior-have-been-shared-by-kia/</guid><description>Source: Kia Motors. The Sportage.
Kia Motors has released the first official pictures of the exterior of the newest Kia Sportage. Its worldwide debut will take place at the Frankfurt International Motor Show on September 15, 2015.
Now in its fourth generation, the completely redesigned Kia Sportage takes inspiration from modern fighter jets, incorporating a blend of smooth and angular elements for a sportier, more streamlined appearance. The most noticeable change is to the front end...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/official-images-of-the-sportage-exterior-have-been-shared-by-kia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/official-images-of-the-sportage-exterior-have-been-shared-by-kia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom introduces assistance for speed cameras and traffic congestion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</guid><description>The image displayed is a screenshot from the Android Play store showcasing the TomTom Speed Cameras app. This app provides information about mobile speed cameras.
TomTom has recently launched a new feature called TomTom Jam Ahead Warnings for their free Android app, TomTom Speed Cameras.
This feature utilizes visual and audio cues to notify drivers of sudden slowdowns or stopped traffic ahead on highways. This allows drivers time to brake safely and efficiently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-introduces-assistance-for-speed-cameras-and-traffic-congestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Volvo is offering special deals on their cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. The Volvo XC60.
Trading Enterprises – Volvo, the sole distributor of Volvo cars in the UAE and a member of the Al-Futtaim Group, has revealed its Ramadan promotional offers for several popular models.
The Volvo XC90 and XC60, both luxury SUVs, come with a 20% dealer contribution towards the down payment through the Volvo Selection program. This offer also includes a two-year buyback guarantee and monthly payments starting at AED 2,999 for the XC90 and AED 1,999 for the XC60...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avis inaugurates a new branch in Malacca, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 05:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</guid><description>Avis Car Rental has expanded its presence in Malaysia by opening its eighth branch at the Holiday Inn Melaka on Jalan Syed Abdul Aziz, Malacca.
The new location offers a range of recent car models, including the economical Toyota Passo, the compact Honda City, the full-size Toyota Camry, and the Nissan X-Trail SUV. In addition to vehicles, Avis provides renters with options for GPS navigation, child safety seats, and fuel services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avis-inaugurates-a-new-branch-in-malacca-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyundai introduces the Grand i10 in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 22:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Hyundai Motor Company.
Hyundai Motor Company has introduced the Grand i10 to the GCC market. Targeting young adults in their 20s and 30s seeking comfort, practicality, and safety, the car is offered in both hatchback and sedan styles. Two trim levels, GL and GLS, are available, with a starting price of US$10,000.
Hyundai reports strong early sales figures for the Grand i10, with over 5,400 units sold within the first six months following its April 2014 launch in Lebanon...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyundai-introduces-the-grand-i10-in-the-gcc-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carly users now have the ability to post on Carousell as well</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</guid><description>Carousell, a popular online classifieds platform, has acquired Caarly, a Singapore-based startup, as part of its strategy to dominate the classifieds market.
Caarly is a mobile-first tool designed to simplify inventory management for used car dealerships. Since launching in Singapore in 2014, Caarly has partnered with over 200 car dealerships, representing a large portion of the market in Singapore. Existing Caarly partners can continue managing their inventory on the Caarly platform and seamlessly cross-post their listings to the cars category on Carousell with just one click...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cathay Pacific has chosen Hertz as its sole car rental service provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</guid><description>Hertz Global is now the sole car rental provider for Cathay Pacific, an international airline based in Hong Kong. To streamline the rental process, Hertz created a dedicated website for Cathay Pacific travelers, offering a wide array of vehicles and deals at approximately 10,000 global locations. Furthermore, Cathay Pacific passengers will automatically receive a 5% discount on Hertz car rentals worldwide.
This agreement expands on the existing partnership between Hertz and Asia Miles, Cathay Pacific&amp;rsquo;s frequent flyer program...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enhance car safety with 360-degree hands-free device viewing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</guid><description>Sprint-Cass, the sole distributor of Taiwanese brand Digidock in Singapore, is introducing a new line of Digidock mobile device holders for vehicles at IT Show 2015, happening from March 19th to 22nd at the Suntec Convention Centre. These holders are designed for cars, motorcycles, and bicycles.
Every Digidock holder features a 360-degree swivel joint, allowing users to securely position their smartphones or tablets at any desired angle. Engineered for simple attachment and removal, the holders come with interchangeable cradles and universal mounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enhance-car-safety-with-360-degree-hands-free-device-viewing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Lexus LC performance coupe has been introduced in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:34:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/</guid><description>The 2018 Lexus LC, a flagship performance coupe now available from Al-Futtaim Motors, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s exclusive Lexus distributor, seamlessly blends striking aesthetics, exhilarating performance, long-distance comfort, and superior craftsmanship.
This production coupe embodies the essence of the handcrafted Lexus LFA supercar and visually echoes the Lexus LF-LC concept. Christopher Buxton, Managing Director of Lexus at Al-Futtaim Motors, highlights the brand&amp;rsquo;s strong presence in the UAE, particularly its leadership in luxury hybrid vehicles over the past seven years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lexus-lc-performance-coupe-has-been-introduced-in-the-uae/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bosch is advocating for an increase in the number of vehicles in Southeast Asia to be equipped with safety features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</guid><description> Road traffic deaths in ASEAN countries are estimated at 117,000 annually, with over half involving motorcycles.
 An increasing number of countries and territories, including Japan, Taiwan, and India, are making motorcycle antilock braking systems (ABS) mandatory for new motorcycles.
 Malaysia is the first and only ASEAN nation to require all new cars to have electronic stability control (ESC) as of 2018.
Bosch believes Southeast Asia can do more to enhance road safety...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Garmin introduces complimentary live services for 2017 Garmin Drive models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</guid><description>Garmin International has refreshed its Garmin Drive portable navigation device (PND) lineup with free live services* for the most up-to-date content and driver alerts to improve safety. These upgrades to the Garmin Drive, Garmin DriveSmart, Garmin DriveAssist, and Garmin DriveLuxe models show the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving PNDs.
The base model Garmin Drive 51/61 includes helpful driver alerts. The Garmin DriveSmart 51/61 adds smart features. The camera-equipped Garmin DriveAssist 51 is for recording drives, while the premium Garmin DriveLuxe 51 has an elegant metal design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garmin-introduces-complimentary-live-services-for-2017-garmin-drive-models/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ValueChampion warns that driving in Singapore is more perilous than you might realize</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 21:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</guid><description>While Singapore boasts one of the world&amp;rsquo;s lowest road fatality rates per person, ValueChampion suggests that driving in Singapore might be riskier than in other developed nations. Anastassia Evlanova, a Senior Research Analyst at ValueChampion Singapore, highlights in a recent blog post (which builds on research from 2017) that Singapore recorded 12.13 deaths per 100,000 vehicles in 2019, surpassing rates in Japan and Australia.
She explains, &amp;ldquo;Looking at road safety solely based on deaths per capita creates a deceptive view of driving safety in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/valuechampion-warns-that-driving-in-singapore-is-more-perilous-than-you-might-realize/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport introduces a new reward for the Be a Changi Millionaire campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. This year&amp;rsquo;s Be a Changi Millionaire competition offers a chance to win a Volvo sedan as well.
Changi Airport has enhanced its well-known *Be a Changi Millionaire*_ retail promotion this year by adding a new prize: a Volvo S90 T5 luxury sedan. This is in addition to the existing S$1 million cash prize. According to Changi Airport, this is the largest retail promotion at any airport globally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Obtain Apple CarPlay in Malaysia with Pioneer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:46:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</guid><description>Pioneer Electronics AsiaCentre, the Asian headquarters for Pioneer Corporation, has announced that Apple CarPlay is now available in Malaysia.
Drivers can now upgrade their vehicles with Apple CarPlay through three of Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s aftermarket in-dash car multimedia receivers: the AVH-X8850BT, AVH-X8750BT, and AVH-X8650BT. This offers a safer and more convenient way for drivers to use their iPhones in their vehicles.
Using Pioneer&amp;rsquo;s large LCD displays, iPhone 5 (or newer) users with the latest iOS version can utilize Siri voice control with Apple CarPlay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-apple-carplay-in-malaysia-with-pioneer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK Automotive industry continues to export to China as its third-largest destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</guid><description>The Society of Motor Manufacturers and Traders (SMMT) recently released data revealing that Britain is exporting more cars than ever. The number of British-built cars shipped globally increased by 10.3%, reaching a new record of 1,354,216 units. This marks the second year in a row that this record has been broken.
China, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest car market, maintained its position as the UK&amp;rsquo;s third largest trading partner, after the EU and the US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-automotive-industry-continues-to-export-to-china-as-its-third-largest-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoTripy Car Rentals is now available in 11 cities across India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</guid><description>Source: GoTripy Car Rentals&amp;rsquo; website.
GoTripy Car Rentals currently operates in 11 cities across India. Their updated website makes online booking easier than ever before.
GoTripy offers a variety of budget-friendly and luxury vehicles, along with professional drivers, in cities like Mumbai, Pune, Nashik, Ahmednagar, Aurangabad, Shirdi, Kolhapur, Delhi, Gurgaon, Bangalore, and Ahmedabad. Their car rental services cater to diverse needs such as local transportation, day trips within a city, sightseeing excursions, airport and railway station transfers, inter-city travel, weekend getaways, business trips, and multi-city journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has seen the launch of four new BMW models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is launching four new car models simultaneously for the first time in Singapore.
The First-Ever BMW i8 Roadster The BMW i8 Roadster features upward-opening doors.
This groundbreaking convertible plug-in hybrid, dubbed a &amp;ldquo;gentleman&amp;rsquo;s racer,&amp;rdquo; can accelerate from 0 to 100 km/h in 4.6 seconds. CS Liew, a director at an agricultural science company, owns the first edition in Singapore, which is already on the road. Initially preferring hardtop convertibles, Liew was captivated by the i8 Roadster&amp;rsquo;s design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has relaxed its requirements for car loans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 08:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced adjustments to loan regulations for motor vehicles. The maximum loan-to-value (LTV) ratios and allowable loan durations will be relaxed, but some limitations will remain indefinitely.
These changes come after three years of sustained moderation in Certificate of Entitlement (COE) premiums and related inflationary pressures.
Financial institutions&amp;rsquo; motor vehicle loan restrictions were implemented in 2013 to control car and COE demand and reduce inflationary pressures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big discounts on Honda vehicles in the UAE during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Honda cars are on Ramadan offer in the UAE.
This Ramadan, Al-Futtaim Honda, the exclusive distributor of Honda vehicles, motorcycles, marine engines, and power products in the UAE, is offering reduced starting prices and complimentary service and warranty coverage across their car lineup. Ramadan is typically a popular time for purchasing new vehicles in the GCC region, and various brands offer promotions during this period.
Honda Civic..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Uber has expanded its services to Seremban, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 08:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Uber. UberX is arriving in Seremban in December
Uber is expanding its services to Seremban, the eighth city in Malaysia to have Uber. Starting December 1, 2016, residents of Seremban can hail a ride via the UberX service. This launch comes after the successful introduction of UberX in Melaka on October 27, 2016.
Uber also presents earning opportunities for driver-partners using their own vehicles. Drivers have the flexibility to set their own schedules and determine their earnings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uber-has-expanded-its-services-to-seremban-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lexus has launched the new NX luxury crossover, accompanied by video advertisements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</guid><description>Source: Lexus. The Lexus NX.
Lexus has launched the NX, a luxury crossover. The 2015 NX marketing campaign highlights how the vehicle surpasses typical SUVs to provide urban drivers with a stylish option that suits their dynamic lifestyles.
“This is Lexus&amp;rsquo; first venture into the entry luxury crossover market. The NX is a dynamic vehicle that combines high-end design with practicality,” said Brian Smith, Lexus&amp;rsquo; VP of marketing. “This campaign showcases the fun driving experience and adventurous spirit of this vehicle, which boasts a bold, angular design and a powerful turbocharged engine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Al-Futtaim Automall at Dubai Festival City is offering a selection of used cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 15:51:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Used cars on offer at the Al-Futtaim Automall at Dubai Festival City.
A new destination for used car shoppers in the UAE is coming soon with the launch of the country&amp;rsquo;s largest site at Dubai Festival City (DFC).
Al-Futtaim Automall, the leading pre-owned vehicle retailer in the UAE, will inaugurate a spacious 12,000 sq m facility in June 2017. Situated opposite IKEA and adjacent to ACE, this new location will feature an inventory of over 400 vehicles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/al-futtaim-automall-at-dubai-festival-city-is-offering-a-selection-of-used-cars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jebsen Group marks six decades of collaboration with Porsche by celebrating their 60th anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</guid><description>Source: Jebsen Group. Pictured from left: Grant Smith, General Manager of Porsche Centre Hong Kong and Macau; Franz Jung, President and CEO of Porsche China; Hans Joachim Stuck, two-time winner of the 24 Hours of Le Mans; Hans Michael Jebsen, Chairman of Jebsen Group; Helmuth Hennig, Group Managing Director of Jebsen Group; Earl Anderson Bamber, 2015 champion of the 24 Hours of Le Mans; and Joachim Eberlein, Managing Director of Jebsen Motors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jebsen-group-marks-six-decades-of-collaboration-with-porsche-by-celebrating-their-60th-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The T.50 from Gordon Murray Automotive revolutionizes the supercar industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-t-50-from-gordon-murray-automotive-revolutionizes-the-supercar-industry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 01:45:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-t-50-from-gordon-murray-automotive-revolutionizes-the-supercar-industry/</guid><description>Designed with the driver in mind, this supercar prioritizes the driving experience above all else.
Both the interior and exterior designs emphasize purity and meticulous attention to detail.
The car boasts a remarkable 3.9-liter V12 engine, the world&amp;rsquo;s lightest, highest-revving, and most power-dense naturally aspirated engine designed for road cars.
Gordon Murray Automotive has taken the wraps off its £2.36 million T.50 supercar. This global debut gave the world a first look at the completed exterior and interior design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-t-50-from-gordon-murray-automotive-revolutionizes-the-supercar-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-t-50-from-gordon-murray-automotive-revolutionizes-the-supercar-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China Telecom is conducting a trial of a connected car concept in partnership with Gemalto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</guid><description>Gemalto, a digital security company, and China Telecom, a major Chinese mobile operator, are collaborating on a connected car project. They are using Gemalto&amp;rsquo;s LinqUs On-Demand Connectivity (ODC) subscription management solution.
The companies recently demonstrated at Mobile World Congress Shanghai how remote provisioning can securely connect mobile devices. They plan to apply this ODC solution to vehicles. This would allow China Telecom&amp;rsquo;s automotive clients to provide their customers with instant in-car connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-telecom-is-conducting-a-trial-of-a-connected-car-concept-in-partnership-with-gemalto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UMW Toyota Motor has expanded its Special Service Campaign to include almost 30,000 cars in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:57:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Toyota Motor Corporation (TMC) issued global recalls related to airbag inflators in some vehicle models on April 11, 2013, and May 13, 2015, and expanded the recall on June 25, 2015.
Responding to this, UMW Toyota Motor is expanding its Special Service Campaign in Malaysia. UMW Toyota Motor has confirmed with TMC that this campaign affects 29,985 Toyota Vios, Corolla Altis, and Yaris models manufactured between April 2007, and December 2008...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/umw-toyota-motor-has-expanded-its-special-service-campaign-to-include-almost-30-000-cars-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Fuel &amp; Trip Calculator from Bayswater Car Rentals eliminates the need for guessing petrol budgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</guid><description>To help people budget for fuel costs and travel time, Bayswater Car Rentals (BCR) has introduced the Fuel &amp;amp; Trip Calculator. This online tool is available to everyone, not just BCR customers.
Arnold Kluck, CEO of BCR, explained that the company was founded to provide budget-friendly car rentals. He noted that customers frequently underestimate petrol costs at the end of their rental period, as it’s easy to overlook this expense during travel planning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>