<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1/</link><description>Recent content in T1 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS1 Telephone Service Lowers Business Phone Bills</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</guid><description>DS1, more commonly known as T1, is a digital telecommunications standard that can potentially save businesses substantial amounts of money on their phone bills. Despite its benefits, many people are unfamiliar with it.
Although the terms are often used interchangeably, there&amp;rsquo;s a slight distinction between DS1 and T1. DS1 (Digital Signal 1) refers to the format of the digital signal transmitted over the line, while T1 describes the physical four-wire copper connection itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, DS3, EoC or Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</guid><description>When you require over a Gigabit of bandwidth, fiber is the only option. But what about less demanding situations, needing between 1 Mbps and 100 Mbps? In this range, twisted pair copper, coaxial cable, and fiber optics all become possibilities. So what is the optimal choice today?
The Importance of Bandwidth Choice
Choosing the right bandwidth connection might seem crucial, but relax. When you opt for dedicated Internet access or point-to-point private lines, performance between options is fairly similar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-ds3-eoc-or-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increase Your Bandwidth Beyond T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 03:46:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your trusty T1 line has served you well for years, maybe even decades. You appreciate its reliability, consistent bandwidth, minimal lag, and decreasing contract prices. However, the bandwidth is becoming a constraint. While 1.5 Mbps was sufficient a decade ago, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer enough. Can you maintain T1&amp;rsquo;s performance with faster speeds? Absolutely!
What Makes a Good T1 Replacement You had good reasons for choosing T1 when you signed your first contract...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-bandwidth-beyond-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet vs SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</guid><description>The increasing use of video and cloud services is pushing business bandwidth requirements to gigabit-per-second speeds, necessitating a shift from copper to fiber optic connections. However, there are two primary types of fiber optic bandwidth: SONET and Gigabit Ethernet.
Developed by telephone companies, SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) was initially designed for transmitting numerous simultaneous phone calls between switching centers, both domestically and internationally. SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) is its international counterpart, often referenced together as SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-vs-sonet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>50 Mbps Ethernet Takes on DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</guid><description>For businesses that have outgrown their T1 lines, DS3 connections have been the typical upgrade option. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a new service offering greater bandwidth at a lower cost than DS3, along with a straightforward upgrade path: 50 Mbps Ethernet.
Let&amp;rsquo;s examine why DS3 became a popular bandwidth service and why Carrier Ethernet will likely replace it. A DS3, sometimes called a T3 line, offers 28 times the bandwidth of a T1, not simply three times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/50-mbps-ethernet-takes-on-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speed of Metro Ethernet Zooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</guid><description>Forget Superman, when it comes to speed and affordability, Metro Ethernet is the real superhero of business bandwidth solutions. It surpasses conventional options like T1 and DS3, offering significantly faster speeds at a lower cost.
Metro Ethernet is in high demand, rapidly becoming the go-to choice for businesses. Its speed can be significantly higher than what you&amp;rsquo;re currently using, and it&amp;rsquo;s generally more cost-effective per Mbps compared to other options, including T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Bandwidth Dissimilar Line Bonding From Mushroom Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 18:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</guid><description>Want to create your own high-bandwidth internet connection without the exorbitant cost of dedicated services like SONET OC3? Combining consumer-grade options like DSL, cable, or wireless might seem appealing, but achieving a reliable, high-speed connection this way is practically impossible with standard routers.
Instead of another router, consider the Truffles appliance from Mushroom Networks. This innovative device combines multiple internet connections, regardless of type, into a single, high-bandwidth connection.
While traditional &amp;ldquo;T1 bonding&amp;rdquo; offered by carriers has limitations in terms of speed and requiring identical lines from a single provider, Truffles takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-bandwidth-dissimilar-line-bonding-from-mushroom-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connectivity For Multi-Business Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:12:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</guid><description>Instead of constructing their own offices, many businesses rent space in large buildings like office complexes, shopping centers, or strip malls. This shared situation offers a unique opportunity to secure better bandwidth at lower costs by joining forces with other tenants in the building.
There are a few approaches to leverage the collective bandwidth requirements of multiple businesses. One method is for the building owner to become an ISP, providing bandwidth to all tenants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-multi-business-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why You Need Dedicated Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s easy to assume all high-speed internet connections are equal, but this isn&amp;rsquo;t true. Unfortunately, businesses may only discover this reality after missing out on sales and losing valuable customers.
While the core of the internet is quite reliable, with issues like packet loss, latency, and bandwidth rarely impacting crucial applications, the most significant difference between internet services lies in the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection – the link between your router and the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-need-dedicated-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Asymmetrical Bandwidth Works Just Fine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 04:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</guid><description>Businesses have often dismissed asymmetrical bandwidth in favor of symmetrical options, sometimes leading to unnecessary expenses or frustratingly slow speeds. How do these symmetries work?
Symmetrical bandwidth offers identical upload and download speeds, often labeled as 3 x 3 Mbps Ethernet or 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet. A classic example is the T1 line, with a fixed 1.5 Mbps for both uploading and downloading.
T1, DS3, and SONET exemplify symmetrical bandwidth services, a legacy of their development by telephone companies for bulk voice calls, requiring equal bandwidth in both directions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-asymmetrical-bandwidth-works-just-fine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Holiday Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</guid><description>The holiday season is approaching quickly, bringing with it a surge in shopping activity. Both physical stores and online retailers experience their highest sales volumes during this period. Businesses need to ensure their systems can handle this increased demand to avoid losing customers to competitors.
While increasing server capacity is important, businesses often overlook the importance of sufficient bandwidth. A congested Wide Area Network (WAN) connection can lead to delays and disconnections, impacting order processing and customer service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Audio Interview With Adam Edwards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</guid><description>Telarus, Inc. is considered a leading innovator in telecommunications marketing since the major telecom expansion of the 1990s. The company has transformed how businesses purchase services like T1, Ethernet, and other high-speed internet options.
I recently spoke with Adam Edwards, Telarus&amp;rsquo;s president, to understand the company&amp;rsquo;s success as a top master agency. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share an MP3 recording of our conversation so you can hear directly from Adam instead of reading a transcript...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fonality Call Center in a Box</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</guid><description>Thinking about starting a call center but worried about the initial expenses and complex setup? While a large-scale call center requires significant investment, there are solutions for businesses looking to add call center capabilities or start small and gradually expand. Fonality offers a &amp;ldquo;call center in a box&amp;rdquo; solution, providing a simplified yet robust system.
This solution utilizes an off-the-shelf PC tower functioning as a Linux server, with the option to upgrade to a rack-mount server for increased capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Will Light Your Building</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</guid><description>Ethernet has become the preferred option for WAN (Wide Area Networking), moving beyond its established role in LAN networks. It makes sense to extend your LAN using the same standards both internally and for connecting to remote locations or the internet.
A key advantage is cost-effectiveness as bandwidth needs grow. While a 1.54 Mbps T1 line might cost around $450 per month ($292.20 per Mbps), a 45 Mbps DS3 connection could cost $5,000 per month ($111...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-will-light-your-building/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find The Ethernet Internet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</guid><description>Looking for increased bandwidth for your business without the high price tag? An Ethernet Internet connection might be the solution you need.
Ethernet Internet connections are a newer offering. While we’ve utilized Ethernet in our local area networks for years and the internet itself aligns with LAN Ethernet, connecting the two has involved specialized telecom services.
You likely currently have T1 or DS3 service, which require specific equipment and software for protocol conversion and signal interfacing with standard network Ethernet ports...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Connectivity Options For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</guid><description>Most medium to large businesses, and even some smaller ones with high bandwidth needs, can now afford fiber optic bandwidth. This is due to lower prices and a wider range of options, which is great news for those who need a lot of bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these options that you may not be aware of.
Fiber optic bandwidth services generally fall into two categories: traditional time division multiplexed technology, originating from telephone company research, and newer IP-centric networks offered by both competitive service providers and traditional telecom carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Ethernet Providers Expand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 17:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</guid><description>A significant development in network connectivity over the past few years has been the nationwide rise of Carrier Ethernet services, and this trend is gaining momentum. Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider it for more affordable metropolitan, long-distance, and last-mile connections using the Ethernet protocol.
You might be wondering about the buzz surrounding Carrier Ethernet, especially since bonded T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services have been available for years and their prices have been steadily declining...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-ethernet-providers-expand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunks vs EoC vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</guid><description>Not long ago, businesses seeking a dedicated, symmetrical bandwidth line had only one option: T1. However, the landscape has changed with the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) and SIP Trunks. While options like DSL, Cable, satellite, and 3G wireless offer shared and asymmetrical bandwidth, and DS3, SONET, and Ethernet over Fiber provide higher bandwidths at higher costs, they fall outside the scope of this comparison.
Similar to their copper-based counterparts, Ethernet over Fiber, DS3, and SONET are higher bandwidth alternatives to EoC, T1, and SIP Trunks, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunks-vs-eoc-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Data Center Services For You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</guid><description>Smaller companies often admire the data centers of larger organizations, but they may not realize that similar services are within their reach.
The key is to only own assets crucial to your business and lease the rest, including data center services. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a massive, secure facility with 24/7 staff, backup generators, and unlimited bandwidth. These services are available on a pay-as-you-go basis.
Two types of data centers are eager to accommodate your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The DS1 DS3 Relationship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</guid><description>The terms DS1 and DS3 are frequently used in business telecommunications networking. DS, which stands for Digital Signal level, indicates the capacity of a digital line within the T-carrier system. Essentially, DS1 is associated with T1 service, while DS3 corresponds with T3.
The origins of the T-carrier system can be traced back to the 1950s when Bell Labs recognized the benefits of transitioning from an entirely analog telephone system to digital connections between telephone company offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ds1-ds3-relationship/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>