<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CET on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cet/</link><description>Recent content in CET on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:08:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Centre for Excellence in Taxation has been launched by Singapore Management University</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-centre-for-excellence-in-taxation-has-been-launched-by-singapore-management-university/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-centre-for-excellence-in-taxation-has-been-launched-by-singapore-management-university/</guid><description>Singapore Management University (SMU) has partnered with the Tax Academy of Singapore and the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore to establish the SMU-TA Centre for Excellence in Taxation (SMU-TA CET). This groundbreaking research center is the first of its kind in Singapore.
The SMU-TA CET signifies a substantial step towards investigating international and regional tax matters and policies. Its primary goal is to generate comprehensive research in these areas to inform policy development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-centre-for-excellence-in-taxation-has-been-launched-by-singapore-management-university/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-centre-for-excellence-in-taxation-has-been-launched-by-singapore-management-university/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ethernet Connection To The World</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</guid><description>To connect your business locations across the globe, you need a reliable way to communicate with everyone, everywhere. While several protocols exist, Carrier Ethernet service is gaining popularity. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Carrier Ethernet builds upon the standard Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs). Although LAN Ethernet networks have distance limitations, especially those using Cat 5e/6 copper wiring, Ethernet can now span cities, countries, and even continents.
The Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an alliance of over 175 organizations invested in Carrier Ethernet, deserves credit for establishing standards that enable long-distance Ethernet connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ethernet-connection-to-the-world/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>