<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>External Relations on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-relations/</link><description>Recent content in External Relations on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/external-relations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>Cracks in the unity of EU representation are evident in the Global Compact for Migration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</guid><description>Pauline Melin, PhD, Lecturer in European Law (Maastricht University) and Researcher at the Institute for European Law (KULeuven)
The UN Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration is scheduled for approval at a conference in Marrakesh, aiming for adoption as a UN General Assembly Resolution in New York on December 19th, 2018. However, the political climate surrounding the Compact&amp;rsquo;s adoption has become contentious. Since Austria, an active participant in the negotiations, withdrew its support in late October 2018, multiple EU Member States have followed suit, publicly questioning or withdrawing their support every week.</description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Claimants of benefits who are not part of the European Union and the impact on the European Union's relationship with Switzerland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely to grab sensationalist headlines, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling on social security rules for Swiss citizens raises important questions about extending such rules to non-EU countries and the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Switzerland.
Background
This ruling marks the second instance where the UK has challenged the legal basis of Council Decisions concerning the extension of revised EU social security coordination rules to specific non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of the UK government's proposals for cross-border civil litigation post-Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-uk-government-s-proposals-for-cross-border-civil-litigation-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you&amp;rsquo;re a well-known UK politician who spends most of their time speaking on British radio or working in the US, only occasionally attending their primary job in France or Belgium. Imagine this politician is divorcing their German spouse. Which court and legal system would handle the divorce and child custody matters?
This scenario falls under the larger subject of international civil litigation, also known as private international law, which is the focus of the UK government&amp;rsquo;s most recent position paper on Brexit negotiations.</description></item><item><title>What is the appropriate response from the EU to the unlawful blocking of the Lachin corridor?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-appropriate-response-from-the-eu-to-the-unlawful-blocking-of-the-lachin-corridor/</guid><description>Nariné Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in International and European Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Alexander Naumov, via Wikimedia Commons
The 2020 Nagorno-Karabakh war ceasefire agreement, brokered by Russia, was seen with skepticism by close observers of the region. By mid-2021, attacks on Armenian territory made it evident that the ceasefire was unstable. This prompted the EU to take a leading role in peace negotiations between Armenia and Azerbaijan. This leadership involved high-profile mediation by European Council President Charles Michel, focusing on prisoner exchanges, discreet diplomatic initiatives, and a series of high-level trilateral meetings throughout 2021 and 2022.</description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations.</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention).</description></item><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim.</description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling in Case C-632/20 P Spain v Commission (Kosovo) on Third Parties, Nations, and Other Entities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
Photo credit: Aljabakphoto, via Wikimedia commons - Šar Mountains National Park in Dragaš, Kosovo
On January 17th, 2023, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in Case C-632/20 P, Spain v Commission (Kosovo), deciding that Kosovo can participate in the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications (BEREC). This decision, reached despite the EU&amp;rsquo;s non-recognition of Kosovo as a state, clarifies that &amp;ldquo;third country&amp;rdquo; status, as defined by the EU, can include territories not recognized as sovereign states and that these entities are eligible for participation in EU agencies.</description></item><item><title>Continuing the saga of EU/Armenia relations with Case C-180/20 Commission v Council (CEPA) and the 'centre of gravity' test in the CFSP.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/continuing-the-saga-of-eu-armenia-relations-with-case-c-180-20-commission-v-council-cepa-and-the-centre-of-gravity-test-in-the-cfsp/</guid><description>Narine Ghazaryan, Assistant Professor in EU and International Law, Radboud University Nijmegen
Photo credit: Jesper Ahlin Marceta via Wikicommons
Introduction
The recent ruling in Case C-180/20 (the CEPA case) marks a new chapter in the ongoing debate about the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) and its boundaries. This case saw the Commission challenge the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to deviate from a proposed Council Decision concerning the EU-Armenian Comprehensive and Enhanced Partnership Agreement (CEPA).</description></item><item><title>Opinion of Advocate General Szpunar on the compatibility of the Energy Charter Treaty with the Treaties and the jurisdiction of the CJEU in Case C-741/19.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, an Assistant Professor in Law at Aarhus University, examines a September 24, 2019 request by the French Cour d’appel de Paris. The court asked the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) to interpret &amp;ldquo;investment&amp;rdquo; as used in Article 1.6 of the Energy Charter Treaty (ECT). The intersection of the ECT and EU law, especially following the Achmea judgment against investor-state dispute settlement (ISDS) provisions in bilateral investment treaties (BITs) between EU Member States, has drawn scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to effectively help in the prohibition of forced labor by the ILO?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 03:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-effectively-help-in-the-prohibition-of-forced-labor-by-the-ilo/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although often used lightly, the term &amp;ldquo;wage slaves&amp;rdquo; reflects a harsh reality for millions trapped in forced labor globally, a modern form of slavery. This exploitation represents a significant aspect of human trafficking, alongside sexual exploitation.
Key international entities like the United Nations and the Council of Europe have been at the forefront of combating human trafficking. However, the International Labour Organisation (ILO) brings long-standing expertise, particularly concerning labor exploitation.</description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period.</description></item><item><title>Resolving conflicts and the agreement for the UK's exit from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A key point of contention in the Brexit withdrawal agreement is how disputes will be settled. Specifically, there&amp;rsquo;s debate about whether the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) maintains authority over the UK. This post provides an overview of this issue and a detailed analysis of the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s provisions concerning dispute resolution and the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s role.
This post is the third in a series examining the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations.</description></item><item><title>The relationship between the EU and Morocco and the issue of the Western Sahara: the European Court of Justice and the principles of international law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</guid><description>Markus W. Gehring: University Lecturer, University of Cambridge; J.S.D. (Yale), LL.M. (Yale), Dr jur. (Hamburg), MA (Cantab); Deputy Director, Economic Law at CIGI
On December 21, 2016, the Court of Justice issued its appeals decision in the case of Council v. Front Polisario. This Grand Chamber judgment, reached under an expedited procedure, overturned the prior decision made by the EU General Court in Front Polisario v Council roughly a year before.</description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI.</description></item><item><title>It is time for the EU to address the origins of informal agreements in EU migration law when cooperating on migration with third countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</guid><description>Dr Céline Hocquet, Teaching Fellow, Birmingham Law School, University of Birmingham
Photo credit: Issam Barhoumi, via Wikimedia Commons
As the EU proposes yet another collaboration with a non-EU nation to manage migration beyond its borders, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to critically examine the EU&amp;rsquo;s externalization policy and its use of informal cooperation. This analysis should consider the historical, legal, and political context of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external migration and asylum policy.
From the EU-Turkey to the EU-Tunisia deal?</description></item><item><title>A Global Court? The European Court of Justice's Ruling in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-global-court-the-european-court-of-justice-s-ruling-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti* and Alina Carrozzini**
*Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
**MPhil/PhD Candidate, Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London. Email: alina.carrozzini@kcl.ac.uk
A June 22, 2021, ruling by the Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice determined that Venezuela can legally challenge a set of European Union restrictive measures if it meets the remaining conditions outlined in Article 263 (4) TFEU. (Previous analyses of this judgment can be found here and here).</description></item><item><title>Is there a connection between readmission and development?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 22:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-connection-between-readmission-and-development/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Union has been establishing Partnership and Cooperation Agreements (PCAs) with several Asian nations. These agreements supersede earlier development policy agreements and incorporate more comprehensive cooperation, encompassing additional areas.
This broadened scope raises questions about the legal basis for these treaties. Should they be founded solely on trade and development, as with previous agreements, or are additional legal grounds required? The Commission favors the former stance, while the Council advocates for the latter.</description></item></channel></rss>