<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cabinet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cabinet/</link><description>Recent content in Cabinet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cabinet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some Cabinet Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>Over the weekend, I made progress reassembling the Beogram 4002, focusing on the cabinet trim and deck cover. To prevent damage, I had previously removed the rosewood trim.
The trim is attached to a metal frame that slides in and out to lock and unlock the cabinet. This frame relies on five guide washers, which are commonly broken in Beogram 4002 units. This one was no different. These washers have a unique design, as detailed in a past Beolover blog post.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Cabinet Work Completion to First Record Play</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 04:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-cabinet-work-completion-to-first-record-play/</guid><description>I finally set up the Beogram 8002 turntable in a listening room to test its functionality.
While reassembly took a bit longer than expected due to a slight detour to repair chipped rosewood trim on the front panel.
Although fixing the trim wasn&amp;rsquo;t part of the initial restoration plan, I decided against leaving the front panel chipped.
Repairs involving glue, like this one, often take longer than expected due to the curing time.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Fit and Finish Rework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 03:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-fit-and-finish-rework/</guid><description>Restoring Beogram 4002 turntables is a fulfilling endeavor, though it often necessitates revisiting steps multiple times. Despite getting this particular Beogram functioning properly, I was dissatisfied with the fit of some components.
The tonearm cover wasn&amp;rsquo;t sitting flush, as evidenced by its crooked appearance in the photo, with the center divider visibly off-center between the fixed arm and tonearm.
A head-on perspective further highlights this issue, along with the misaligned deck trim, showing an undesirably wide gap between the panels.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings with 3D Printed Replacement Parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 08:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-with-3d-printed-replacement-parts/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5523) arm lowering mechanism, I removed the circuit boards for refurbishment. This presented an ideal opportunity to swap the deteriorated transport lock bushings with 3D-printed replacements. The old bushings tend to break down, scattering fragments within the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s casing, often lodging beneath the floating chassis. These fragments can obstruct the chassis&amp;rsquo;s movement, hindering its ability to isolate the turntable and tonearm from the enclosure.</description></item><item><title>Bay Area Beogram 8002: Some cabinet work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-some-cabinet-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:22:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-area-beogram-8002-some-cabinet-work/</guid><description>The Beogram 8002&amp;rsquo;s internal components are ready to be placed back into the cabinet, but the cabinet needs some attention first.
While this Beogram&amp;rsquo;s cabinet is in good condition overall, there are a few things that need to be fixed, as mentioned in the initial assessment (linked in the original text).
The first step was to remove the aluminum deck lid. The previous re-attachment used overly thick double-sided tape that created too much space.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): New Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-new-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to adjusting the platter and sub-chassis of the Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable currently being restored, it was necessary to replace the deteriorated transport lock bushings. As this model used the orange type, their disintegration was expected.
Due to the widespread fragments, the sub-chassis was removed to ensure no remnants remained underneath. Stray fragments can be problematic as the sub-chassis hovers near the enclosure&amp;rsquo;s base. Any lodged splinters would hinder its free movement, negatively affecting the turntable mechanism&amp;rsquo;s vibration isolation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Brand New Beautiful Solid Oak Plinth! - Very Beolovely!!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-brand-new-beautiful-solid-oak-plinth-very-beolovely-/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s another great day for a Beogram enthusiast like myself! I recently received two new Beogram plinths from Matt Spangler of Vintage HiFi Nut in Oregon. He&amp;rsquo;s an expert in restoring and replacing vintage HiFi wood cabinets.
I had sent him a Beogram 4000 and a Beogram 4002 plinth a while back. Both had been damaged in transit because of inadequate packaging, a frequent problem as people often don&amp;rsquo;t realize how rough shipping can be.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Transport Lock Bushings and cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 07:24:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>Many Beogram 4002 (5513) turntables, including the one I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring, require replacement of the transport lock bushings and cabinet guidance washers. These components are crucial for proper platter and arm alignment. Without them, alignment is unreliable and won&amp;rsquo;t hold during transport.
This image shows the front transport lock missing its bushing:
Here&amp;rsquo;s the disassembled mechanism with the lower part of the new bushings installed:
The top part of the bushing is added next:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Re-Attaching Keypad Segments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-re-attaching-keypad-segments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-re-attaching-keypad-segments/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is moving along, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently focusing on aesthetics. The last step was to reattach two keypad sections that had become unglued. The image illustrates the problem:
I used a small amount of superglue gel and clamped the pads down with vise grips:
It&amp;rsquo;s important to use minimal glue to avoid damaging the delicate paint on the pad&amp;rsquo;s surface. Start with a small amount and add more if needed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchanging the Plinth Panels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 11:49:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchanging-the-plinth-panels/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 being restored arrived with a damaged plinth corner. As replacements are scarce, panels from a 4002 or 4004 model are often substituted, necessitating a swap of the metal fixtures due to variations in keypad design.
The restoration begins by detaching the plinth from the metal casing. Heating the plinth in a warm oven (around 80°C) for 30-45 minutes softens the adhesive, allowing for the removal of the metal fixtures with a spatula.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): New Cabinet Guiding Washers and Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 09:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-new-cabinet-guiding-washers-and-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>To finalize the mechanical repairs on this Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable, new transport lock bushings were necessary. These bushings ensure the sub-chassis is properly aligned within the upper and lower lock positions. This particular Beogram was missing these bushings, with no indication they were ever there. This photo shows the left transport lock disassembled:
The bushing should be located in the opening on the sub-chassis arm on the right.
The first step of the replacement bushing installation is shown here:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Cabinet Repair and Guiding Washers Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:52:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-cabinet-repair-and-guiding-washers-installation/</guid><description>While waiting for audio cables from Sounds Heavenly, I decided to fix up the wooden case of my Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable. Both corners were cracked, and the plastic washers that guide the sliding mechanism were gone. The first picture shows one of the damaged corners.
[Image of a cracked turntable cabinet]
Repairing the cracks was simple. Since the case is held together with metal bands, I glued the wood pieces and clamped them until the glue dried.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Glueing a Delaminated Platter Back Together and Installation of New Cabined Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-glueing-a-delaminated-platter-back-together-and-installation-of-new-cabined-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on was unfortunately damaged during shipping due to inadequate packaging by the seller. Because the platter wasn&amp;rsquo;t secured, it moved around and ultimately split into two pieces. The images show the separated top and bottom sections of the platter.
Examining the platter&amp;rsquo;s interior reveals interesting details about its construction. The heavier bottom section of each platter was individually balanced, much like car tires. This involved drilling away small amounts of material from the heavier side, as evidenced by the red pen marks near the drill holes.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Adjusting the Tracking Force and Replacing the Strange Original Front Center Cabinet Guiding Washer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:22:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-adjusting-the-tracking-force-and-replacing-the-strange-original-front-center-cabinet-guiding-washer/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration is complete, and it&amp;rsquo;s playing beautifully. As I write this, I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying &amp;ldquo;Song for My Father&amp;rdquo; by Horace Silver on a reissue, as original pressings are unfortunately outside my budget these days.
One of the final tasks was refining the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s mechanics. I calibrated the tonearm weight and limits and replaced the guiding washer, which ensures the plinth moves smoothly. The original washer, pictured below, has a design flaw that was later corrected in the Beogram 400x series.</description></item></channel></rss>