<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Convention on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convention/</link><description>Recent content in Convention on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convention/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor will assume management of the Star Convention Centre in Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</guid><description>In 2020, Accor will assume management of the 571-room Star Convention Centre in Thailand, rebranding it as the Novotel Rayong Star Convention Centre. The hotel, situated in Rayong province&amp;rsquo;s city center, will undergo a significant two-year renovation. The initial phase will focus on revamping public spaces, dining establishments, and 235 guest rooms. Subsequently, the remaining 336 guest rooms will be renovated in the second phase.
Patrick Basset, COO of Accor for Upper Southeast &amp;amp; Northeast Asia and the Maldives, expressed enthusiasm about the hotel joining Accor&amp;rsquo;s network and expanding their presence in Rayong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-will-assume-management-of-the-star-convention-centre-in-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thailand is gaining traction as a top choice for hosting business events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</guid><description>Source: TCEB.
Thailand, with the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB) at the helm, is establishing itself as a prime location for business events. As the Thai government&amp;rsquo;s primary representative for this sector, TCEB plays a vital role in solidifying Thailand&amp;rsquo;s leading position in the Asian business events industry and Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a top-tier destination for international business events.
The Thai business events sector is projected to experience robust growth in 2015, anticipating over a million visitors and generating approximately US$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thailand-is-gaining-traction-as-a-top-choice-for-hosting-business-events/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>