<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Check Point on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/check-point/</link><description>Recent content in Check Point on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:01:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/check-point/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Check Point has discovered a vulnerability in a preinstalled app on Xiaomi devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</guid><description>Slava Makkaveev, a researcher from cybersecurity firm Check Point Software, recently discovered a concerning security flaw in Xiaomi phones.
This vulnerability was found within the pre-installed &amp;ldquo;Guard Provider&amp;rdquo; app (com.miui.guardprovider), designed to identify malware. Ironically, this app could allow attackers on the same Wi-Fi network to perform a man-in-the-middle (MiTM) attack. This type of attack enables the interception and copying of data transmitted between the phone and online services.
Furthermore, by exploiting a third-party software development kit (SDK) update mechanism, attackers could potentially disable malware protection and inject malicious code...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-has-discovered-a-vulnerability-in-a-preinstalled-app-on-xiaomi-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are there any consequences to the WhatsApp hacking?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/</guid><description>Even though WhatsApp claims to use encryption for secure communications, the platform has experienced a security breach. Such attacks on widely used software have the potential to impact vast numbers of users, and while this specific vulnerability has been addressed, it highlights the possibility that everyday software might not be as secure as users believe.
Nabil Hannan, a Managing Principal specializing in Financial Services at Synopsys&amp;rsquo; Software Integrity Group, explained that this incident poses a risk because, theoretically, any WhatsApp user could be targeted using their phone number...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-there-any-consequences-to-the-whatsapp-hacking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel will provide ZoneAlarm Mobile Security protection from Check Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</guid><description>Singtel has partnered with Check Point Software Technologies to launch ZoneAlarm Mobile Security. This mobile security app offers extensive protection against digital threats like malware, hacking attempts, and Wi-Fi attacks.
ZoneAlarm, available for both iOS and Android devices, conducts thorough risk evaluations. It scans installed applications, identifies unsafe Wi-Fi networks, and suggests the safest Wi-Fi hotspot choices. Additionally, it alerts users of any questionable processes running on their phones and safeguards their operating systems from attacks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-will-provide-zonealarm-mobile-security-protection-from-check-point/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>