<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reception Conditions on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reception-conditions/</link><description>Recent content in Reception Conditions on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/reception-conditions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months.</description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections.</description></item><item><title>Europe's Immigration Detention: Uncovering the Truth - A Recent Study by the European Migration Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 02:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/europe-s-immigration-detention-uncovering-the-truth-a-recent-study-by-the-european-migration-network/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, Associate Researcher at Global Detention Project and PhD candidate in International Law at the Graduate Institute of International and Development Studies is Geneva.
In November, the European Migration Network (EMN) published a Focused Study entitled “The use of detention and alternatives to detention in the context of immigration policies.” The study is a synthesis report drawn from national reports from 26 countries, compiled by the EMN National Contact Points (NCPs).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU upholds the right of asylum seekers to family housing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 18:41:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-upholds-the-right-of-asylum-seekers-to-family-housing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This piece examines the housing obligations of EU Member States toward asylum-seeking families. The European Court of Justice (CJEU) recently clarified the minimum standards required of Member States in its ruling on the Saciri case. The judgment is a positive development, confirming that regardless of the challenges Member States face in providing reception services for asylum-seekers, families cannot be left homeless or in extremely poor living conditions by denying them financial aid for housing.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on the detention of asylum-seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-the-detention-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The detention of migrants is a contentious issue in immigration and asylum law. This involves detaining individuals who haven&amp;rsquo;t committed crimes other than potential immigration violations. They are held during their asylum application process or while awaiting deportation. The EU has established regulations on detaining irregular migrants through the Returns Directive. For insight into the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of these regulations, refer to the journal article on humane treatment versus efficient removal.</description></item><item><title>Is it permissible for Member States to confiscate the assets of asylum-seekers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-permissible-for-member-states-to-confiscate-the-assets-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk (Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen) and Steve Peers
Recently, several countries within and outside the EU have made headlines for seizing assets from asylum-seekers upon entry. This raises the question of whether this practice aligns with EU law. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine national practices, the development of relevant EU regulations, and finally, draw our conclusions.
Denmark
In November 2015, the Danish government put forward 34 measures aimed at deterring asylum seekers.</description></item><item><title>A blueprint for safeguarding human rights amidst the 'refugee crisis'? Recent ECtHR Grand Chamber decision on immigration detention and migrant expulsion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 23:46:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-blueprint-for-safeguarding-human-rights-amidst-the-refugee-crisis-recent-ecthr-grand-chamber-decision-on-immigration-detention-and-migrant-expulsion/</guid><description>Stefano Zirulia, Lecturer, University of Milano* (main text on ECHR) and Professor Steve Peers (Annex on EU law aspects)
* Stefano Zirulia was involved in the proceedings before the ECHR as counsel for the applicants.
Introduction
On December 15th, 2016, the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber delivered its judgment in the case of Khlaifia and Others v. Italy, partially overturning a previous Chamber ruling from September 1st, 2015.</description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR.</description></item><item><title>Is the ultimate goal of the Provisional Agreement on the recast Reception Conditions Directive to prevent 'Asylum Shopping' and 'Secondary Movements'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-ultimate-goal-of-the-provisional-agreement-on-the-recast-reception-conditions-directive-to-prevent-asylum-shopping-and-secondary-movements/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 13:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-ultimate-goal-of-the-provisional-agreement-on-the-recast-reception-conditions-directive-to-prevent-asylum-shopping-and-secondary-movements/</guid><description>Vasiliki Apatzidou, legal practitioner specializing in EU Asylum Law and PhD Student at Queen Mary University of London.
Photo credit: Rebecca Harms, via wikicommons
The Common European Asylum System (CEAS) and its current instruments, including the recast Reception Conditions Directive, have been in effect for almost a decade since 2013. However, the large influx of asylum seekers in 2015 highlighted significant shortcomings, inconsistencies, and gaps in EU asylum legislation. This response to the refugee &amp;lsquo;crisis&amp;rsquo; diminished the relevance of the harmonization goals.</description></item></channel></rss>