<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VAR Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/var-network/</link><description>Recent content in VAR Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/var-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goose Your Technical Service Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goose-your-technical-service-business/</guid><description>Are you seeing a decline in business lately? You might have just as many inquiries, but customers seem hesitant to commit. This is likely due to the current economic climate, not anything you&amp;rsquo;re doing wrong. However, there are ways to stimulate your business and potentially even increase your income.
While these ideas apply to many businesses, we&amp;rsquo;ll focus on those offering telephone or computer networking technical services. If this describes your business, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck!</description></item><item><title>Tell Me You're Not PAYING For Equipment Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tell-me-youre-not-paying-for-equipment-leads/</guid><description>Stop wasting money on expensive equipment leads that often lead nowhere.
There&amp;rsquo;s a smarter way to generate sales and marketing leads for your telephone systems and IT networking equipment: commission-based leads. This means you receive qualified leads from serious businesses in your area as they emerge, completely free of charge. You then select the leads you want to pursue and focus your efforts on closing the deal. Only after a successful sale and payment from the customer do you share a small percentage with the agency that provided the lead.</description></item><item><title>Attention: Telephone System Dealers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</guid><description>For businesses selling, installing, or servicing business telephone systems, a new business model called the VAR Network is gaining popularity nationwide. This model helps generate more business without requiring upfront expenses.
The VAR Network is an online database system showcasing business profiles of numerous telephone and computer networking dealers. This fully automated platform connects potential customers seeking telecom assistance with qualified dealers in their area. Dealers are notified of potential matches and can choose to pursue these opportunities.</description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price.</description></item><item><title>T1 Sales Support Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in earning money by selling business voice and data services, there&amp;rsquo;s a brokerage service that can simplify the process.
The VAR Network, managed by Telarus, Inc., connects telecom providers with VARs (Value Added Resellers). VARs typically represent manufacturers of business phone systems, network equipment, video conferencing tools, and similar products. They often handle both sales and service, providing clients with complete solutions and ongoing support.
Many VARs, focused on hardware and software, haven&amp;rsquo;t ventured into selling telephone lines or WAN services, which are crucial for a comprehensive business solution.</description></item><item><title>What Becomes Of The Broken Hardware?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-becomes-of-the-broken-hardware/</guid><description>_While troubleshooting a LAN for faulty wiring, I&amp;rsquo;m haunted by thoughts of server failures. The concept of uptime seems like a cruel joke, and I&amp;rsquo;m desperate for a solution.
What happens to malfunctioning equipment that dies prematurely? I need to determine the root cause of this outage.
The list of underlying issues is extensive, and the network is collapsing. The pressure mounts daily, becoming unbearable.
I examine server logs, looking for answers while facing the frustrated stares of the staff who demand updates.</description></item><item><title>Telarus, the New Face of Telecom Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a massive transformation thanks to disruptive technology. Wireless technology is shaking up the century-old wireline business, VoIP is changing the landscape of the digital voice trunking business, competitive fiber optic carriers are challenging the dominance of established phone companies, and Ethernet and IP networks are blurring the lines between local and wide area networks.
Despite these technological advancements, the sales and marketing processes for business telecommunications services have remained largely unchanged.</description></item></channel></rss>