<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authentication on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/authentication/</link><description>Recent content in Authentication on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/authentication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SingPass has simplified the 2FA verification process before the July deadline</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 02:59:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Infocomm Development Authority (IDA) announced that users of the national digital identity system, SingPass, can now enable two-factor authentication (2FA) more easily. This security feature is mandatory for accessing certain online services.
Without activating 2FA, users will lose access to important government e-services like tax filing with the Inland Revenue Authority of Singapore (IRAS) and viewing Central Provident Fund (CPF) statements.
Starting July 5, 2016, over 100 government e-services will require 2FA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpass-has-simplified-the-2fa-verification-process-before-the-july-deadline/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantages of SSL VPN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 20:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</guid><description>Cybersecurity is a significant concern for all internet users. With frequent news of hacking, data breaches, identity theft, and malicious bots, it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that people are anxious about the security of their sensitive information, especially with the move towards cloud-based storage. This has led to a surge in interest in virtual private networks (VPNs).
Why would one choose a virtual private network over a traditional one?
The answer lies in our need for widespread connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-ssl-vpn/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET advocates for the use of two-factor authentication to enhance security for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a cybersecurity company, cautions that small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) are frequently targeted by cybercriminals due to the vulnerability of their data. Javelin Strategy &amp;amp; Research&amp;rsquo;s study reveals that stolen personal data fuels a multi-billion dollar industry.
Lukas Raska, COO of ESET Asia, emphasizes the evolution of cybercrime from viruses to the current threat of identity theft, highlighting its potential to cripple businesses and compromise customer trust.
Parvinder Walia, Director at ESET APAC, explains that SMBs are attractive targets because they often lack the robust cybersecurity budgets and dedicated personnel of larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-advocates-for-the-use-of-two-factor-authentication-to-enhance-security-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>