<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hate Crime on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hate-crime/</link><description>Recent content in Hate Crime on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hate-crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Story of Two Institutions: Regulation of Hate Speech in Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</guid><description>Clotilde Pégorier, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The regulation of hate speech has recently resurfaced as a crucial legal and political topic in Europe. While the complexity of this issue and the varying views on balancing legislation with rights protection are well-known, the contrasting approaches of the EU and the Council of Europe, two closely linked entities, is notable. This difference raises questions about its underlying reasons and broader legislative ramifications in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Is Delfi restricting freedom of expression online in Estonia?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 21:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-delfi-restricting-freedom-of-expression-online-in-estonia/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Media Law, University of Essex
Under what circumstances can online freedom of expression be restricted? The recent decision from the European Court of Human Rights Grand Chamber in the case of Delfi v. Estonia tackles this question, focusing on comments made in response to a news article. This ruling presents thought-provoking issues concerning both human rights and EU law, which will be examined in this analysis.</description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013.</description></item></channel></rss>