<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dinner on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dinner/</link><description>Recent content in Dinner on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dinner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Buffets for Iftar are available at 21 on Rajah</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</guid><description>Source: 21 on Rajah.
The buffet.
If you&amp;rsquo;re searching for a venue to hold a corporate Iftar gathering in Singapore during Ramadan, consider the halal-certified 21 On Rajah. Situated within Days Hotel Singapore at Zhongshan Park, this all-day dining restaurant is presenting a selection of Mediterranean and Asian Iftar buffets each evening.
Chef de Cuisine Faustino Picardo Ines Jr and his culinary team have crafted diverse menus throughout the week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buffets-for-iftar-are-available-at-21-on-rajah/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Saturdays at InterContinental Bali Resort feature The Spirit of Bali cultural buffet dinner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Bali Resort website. The Taman Gita Terrace in the daytime.
Every Saturday night, the InterContinental Bali Resort hosts The Spirit of Bali cultural dinner, featuring traditional Balinese food and performances of Okokan, Tektekan, and Calonarang dances. This event reflects the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to promoting Balinese culture and supporting local artists.
The buffet dinner, served every Saturday at 7 pm on the resort&amp;rsquo;s Taman Gita Terrace, showcases classic hot and cold Balinese dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saturdays-at-intercontinental-bali-resort-feature-the-spirit-of-bali-cultural-buffet-dinner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway will be celebrating their first birthday on March 31st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Jen Orchardgateway website.
Hotel Jen, a new brand from the Shangri-La Group, is turning one year old on March 31, 2016. To mark this milestone, the two Singapore locations, Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway, are joining their sister hotels across nine Asian-Pacific cities for a grand birthday celebration. Each location will host unique events reflecting their city&amp;rsquo;s character, from a Mad Hatter&amp;rsquo;s tea party in Beijing to street art-inspired menus in Brisbane and a pool party in the Maldives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rajah revitalizes themed buffets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 19:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</guid><description>Starting April 4th, the all-day restaurant 21 On Rajah will introduce new lunch and dinner buffets inspired by Mediterranean and Asian cuisine.
Rijsttafel Weekday Lunch Buffet
Source: 21 on Rajah. A selection of dishes from the Rijsttafel weekday lunch buffet.
Inspired by the Dutch &amp;ldquo;rijsttafel&amp;rdquo; – meaning &amp;ldquo;rice table&amp;rdquo; – this lunch buffet presents a diverse array of side dishes served with rice, similar to the local nasi Padang. Chef de Cuisine Faustino Jr and his team have crafted a menu designed to energize diners for the rest of the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rajah-revitalizes-themed-buffets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CulinaryOn Singapore is offering Lunar New Year dinner experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Culinaryon Singapore. Yusheng with salmon sashimi.
For this Lunar New Year, CulinaryOn Singapore is offering special dinners starting on December 26th, 2017. These dinners feature premium six-to-eight course meals and include a taste of their cooking classes with a noodle-making activity. Guests can also choose to create their own desserts.
The eight-course premium menu features dishes such as yusheng with salmon sashimi, shiitake mushrooms with broccoli, crayfish braised longevity noodles, golden shrimp with honeydew mayo, and mango ice cream with pomelo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iftar gatherings at AquaMarine, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 03:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</guid><description>Originally from the Marina Mandarin Singapore website, this photo displays the Bakar Station&amp;rsquo;s offerings of chicken, oxtail, prawns, and sea bass cooked in banana leaves.
AquaMarine, a Halal-certified buffet restaurant, has recently renovated its Terrace@AquaMarine space. Now fully air-conditioned, it&amp;rsquo;s an ideal location for larger gatherings.
The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s current iftar menu, available until July 17th, features dishes like dates, slow-roasted baby lamb seasoned with Moroccan spices, bulgur wheat with raita, and a traditional Indonesian oxtail soup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During this Ramadan, the Corp Amman will offer Iftar dining and entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Corp Amman Hotel website.
The 4-star Corp Amman Hotel has put together a special offering for iftar and suhoor during Ramadan, showcasing traditional Jordanian hospitality. Guests can enjoy evenings filled with food and music for JD18 per person, not including services and taxes.
The celebration starts with an iftar menu at the Boulevard Restaurant &amp;amp; Poolside Terrace, available all day. The menu features Ramadan favorites such as juices, dried fruits, Arabic breads, soups, salads, pickles, and mezze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>