<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Retail Sales on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retail-sales/</link><description>Recent content in Retail Sales on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 03:59:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retail-sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bandwidth For Holiday Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 03:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</guid><description>The holiday season is approaching quickly, bringing with it a surge in shopping activity. Both physical stores and online retailers experience their highest sales volumes during this period. Businesses need to ensure their systems can handle this increased demand to avoid losing customers to competitors.
While increasing server capacity is important, businesses often overlook the importance of sufficient bandwidth. A congested Wide Area Network (WAN) connection can lead to delays and disconnections, impacting order processing and customer service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-holiday-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Includes Canada &amp; Puerto Rico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</guid><description>People often associate broadband with wired connections, like T1 lines commonly used by small to medium businesses, or the increasingly popular Ethernet option known for its speed and affordability. While satellite is vital for many chain stores, there&amp;rsquo;s another reliable broadband solution that avoids construction costs and high monthly fees: fixed wireless broadband, now available across the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Accel Networks, a leading provider of fixed wireless broadband, leverages existing 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>