<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Printing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/printing/</link><description>Recent content in Printing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/printing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Epson printer has assisted an Indonesian entrepreneur in expanding and diversifying their business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 16:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-epson-printer-has-assisted-an-indonesian-entrepreneur-in-expanding-and-diversifying-their-business/</guid><description>Source: Epson. A variety of print results from the printer.
Budi Santoso, an Indonesian entrepreneur specializing in digital textiles, established his first business, Moshaict, in 2008. Moshaict is a Jakarta-based clothing store offering fashion for Muslim women. In 2011, he decided to start printing his own products to sell in his store instead of depending on outside printers.
Santoso researched the Epson SureColor SC-F7070 online and compared it to similar machines.</description></item><item><title>You're Not Paying For Business Cards?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/youre-not-paying-for-business-cards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/youre-not-paying-for-business-cards/</guid><description>Business cards are essential for sharing contact information and promoting your business. While elaborate designs can be expensive, affordable options are widely available.
Don&amp;rsquo;t order thousands of cards unless necessary. Career changes and relocation make large quantities wasteful. Smaller businesses and individuals have cost-effective alternatives to company-issued cards.
Consider purchasing blank business card stock from office supply stores. These are compatible with printers and copiers. You can create your designs using graphic design software, word processors, or pre-designed templates.</description></item><item><title>Tinkr provides custom calligraphy necklaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 19:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tinkr-provides-custom-calligraphy-necklaces/</guid><description>Source: Tinkr website.
The company Tinkr is offering custom-made pendants. These pendants are unique corporate gifts because they are designed using a person&amp;rsquo;s actual handwriting.
Starting at S$78, the company will craft a pendant featuring up to two words written in the handwriting provided. For those who prefer professional calligraphy, Tinkr offers this service starting at S$98. Veronica Halim, Tinkr&amp;rsquo;s in-house calligrapher, would design the calligraphy.
Source: Tinkr newsletter.</description></item><item><title>Beijing Tiertime Technology introduces the UP BOX desktop 3D printer priced at less than $2,000</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 06:23:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beijing-tiertime-technology-introduces-the-up-box-desktop-3d-printer-priced-at-less-than-2-000/</guid><description>Tiertime, a company specializing in 3D printing technology, has introduced the UP BOX, the newest addition to their UP Series of desktop 3D printers.
Source: Tiertime.
The UP BOX draws upon the strengths of its predecessors, the UP Plus 2 and UP mini. It boasts a larger build volume of 255mm x 205mm x 205mm while achieving a higher print resolution of 0.1mm. Additionally, it surpasses the UP Plus 2 in printing speed by up to 30%.</description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials.</description></item></channel></rss>