<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Video Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is 1 Tbps The Next Optical Network Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</guid><description>While everyday users are getting used to 100 Mbps speeds, network providers are already looking ahead to Terabit per second speeds, debating whether 400 Gbps or 1 Tbps will be the next standard.
This push for higher speeds is a natural progression, similar to the advancement from Kbps to Mbps and Gbps. Just like previous upgrades, the proposed standards represent a tenfold increase.
This speed increase mirrors Moore&amp;rsquo;s Law, which predicted the doubling of transistors on integrated circuits yearly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-1-tbps-the-next-optical-network-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AT&amp;T Sees the Video Tsunami Coming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</guid><description>Video streaming is predicted to consume massive amounts of bandwidth, pushing the limits of what&amp;rsquo;s available. Even the concept of &amp;ldquo;unlimited&amp;rdquo; bandwidth offered by providers today comes with hidden caps due to network strain.
AT&amp;amp;T is one company actively addressing this challenge, not just by increasing general internet capacity but by adding 400 Gbps to its Content Delivery Network (CDN).
Think of a CDN as a dedicated express lane running parallel to the public internet highway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-t-sees-the-video-tsunami-coming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Your Network Capacity Drying Up?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 14:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network congestion can occur unexpectedly. While a network might be operating without issue one day, the next day, it could be bogged down. This begs the questions: what causes this, and more importantly, what can be done to fix it?
Network capacity, particularly for MAN and WAN networks, can become depleted rapidly as applications place greater demands on it. Video, in particular, consumes a significant amount of bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-network-capacity-drying-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Taming The Video Bandwidth Monster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 01:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</guid><description>Cisco forecasts that video will represent over half of all internet traffic by the close of next year, reaching 62% by 2015&amp;rsquo;s end. This surge in video consumption, driven by streaming and downloads, necessitates that both providers and consumers adapt to the escalating demand for bandwidth.
Netflix&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a cable and satellite TV competitor is accelerating the dominance of video data on the internet. Consumers are experiencing a transformation in how they consume &amp;ldquo;TV,&amp;rdquo; now utilizing computers, tablets, and smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taming-the-video-bandwidth-monster/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>