<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Spectrum on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spectrum/</link><description>Recent content in Spectrum on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/spectrum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Clever D Block Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</guid><description>During the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction, a small frequency band known as D Block went unsold because it didn&amp;rsquo;t reach its reserve price. This is unfortunate because D Block was supposed to play a crucial role in establishing a nationwide public service network. This plan, which could serve as a model for other initiatives, deserves further consideration, especially in challenging economic times.
The idea for D Block originated after the September 11, 2001, attacks, when communication breakdowns hampered rescue efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>