<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BFSI on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bfsi/</link><description>Recent content in BFSI on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:39:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bfsi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customers of Credit Suisse in Hong Kong now have access to a new digital private banking app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse e-brochure.
Credit Suisse has introduced its digital private banking platform in Hong Kong, launching an improved Private Banking Asia Pacific app.
This digital platform offers a new way to serve clients, blending digital and in-person experiences. Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s first digital private banking platform debuted in Singapore in March 2015. After analyzing client usage and conducting usability tests for over a year, the bank has introduced an enhanced app in Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-credit-suisse-in-hong-kong-now-have-access-to-a-new-digital-private-banking-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Simpanan Nasional has launched virtual teller machines in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Bank Simpanan Nasional (BSN) is the first bank in Malaysia to introduce virtual teller machines (VTMs). These machines allow bank tellers to assist customers in different locations throughout Malaysia remotely, through a live virtual banking system.
BSN&amp;rsquo;s adoption of VTMs was inspired by kiosk banking already in place in other countries, including those in Europe, China, Canada, and the US. The project is a collaboration between BSN and Vastcomp to develop a specialized system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Investing in corporate bonds will be made more accessible for Singaporean investors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) has launched two new regulations aimed at making it easier for retail investors – individuals who purchase securities for personal investment purposes – to participate in corporate bond offerings. These changes are part of MAS&amp;rsquo;s broader strategy to expand retail investors&amp;rsquo; investment choices by providing access to simpler, lower-risk investment products.
Corporate issuers typically rely on the wholesale bond market for funding due to the higher expenses associated with reaching retail investors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/investing-in-corporate-bonds-will-be-made-more-accessible-for-singaporean-investors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bankers in the APAC region predict a decrease in M&amp;A activity under President Trump's administration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</guid><description>A recent survey of 300 Asia Pacific mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) professionals conducted by Intralinks, a secure platform used by dealmakers for content sharing, found that 75% of respondents believe a potential presidency under Donald Trump would negatively impact M&amp;amp;A activity in the region. This mirrors the global sentiment revealed by Intralinks&amp;rsquo; survey of 1,500 M&amp;amp;A professionals worldwide.
Intralinks&amp;rsquo; Global M&amp;amp;A Sentiment Survey shows 75% of Asian dealmakers consider Trump the most detrimental presidential candidate for M&amp;amp;A activity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB discusses its regional strategies for participating in the ASEAN Economic Community</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. Chairman of CIMB Group, YBhg Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Nazir Razak (right) and Director, Southeast Asia of The Economist Intelligence Unit Justin Wood showcasing the special report Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia.
CIMB partnered with the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) to publish a report titled Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia. This independent management brief, co-sponsored by CIMB and Baker McKenzie, aims to equip companies for the upcoming launch of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) on December 31, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If you have digital or tech skills, chances are your salary is above average</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:11:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</guid><description>Source: Willis Towers Watson. Report cover.
The financial sector, particularly in digital roles, is experiencing salary stability due to a high demand for tech professionals. This trend persists despite overall economic weakness in other industries, including banking, according to the global advisory firm Willis Towers Watson.
Businesses across all sectors are becoming progressively reliant on data and technology, and the banking industry is no exception. This shift has resulted in a talent competition where technological expertise is more valuable than financial background...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-you-have-digital-or-tech-skills-chances-are-your-salary-is-above-average/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS introduces the first mobile-only bank in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</guid><description>Source: DBS. From left: Sachin Tendulkar, Cricketer, digor
the digibank mascot, DBS CEO Piyush Gupta.
Introducing a pioneering Virtual Assistant powered by artificial intelligence. Account creation utilizes Aadhaar, the largest biometric identification system globally. DBS Bank, headquartered in Singapore and a prominent financial institution in Asia, has introduced digibank, India&amp;rsquo;s inaugural mobile-centric bank. This innovative banking platform harnesses advanced technologies, including biometrics and artificial intelligence (AI), to offer customers a novel banking experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) reveals initiatives to promote innovation in the industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) outlined its plans to support the digitalization recommendations put forth by the Committee on the Future Economy (CFE) to help prepare the financial sector for the future.
MAS will facilitate infrastructure projects aimed at driving innovation, enhancing market efficiency, improving customer service, and strengthening Singapore’s regional connectivity. Key projects include:
Electronic Marketplace for Trade Finance Assets
An electronic trade finance platform will allow participating banks to distribute trade finance assets globally, free up capital for new trade finance loans, and increase the availability of trade finance within the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Financial services companies are placing a greater emphasis on developing a strong risk culture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</guid><description>A recent study by Mercer focusing on executive compensation in the global financial services industry found that a majority of firms are prioritizing the development of robust risk cultures within their organizations. Sixty-two percent of surveyed firms reported significant efforts to penalize misconduct and non-compliance, while 60% demonstrated clear leadership commitment to ethical behavior. Furthermore, 58% have established and communicated unambiguous objectives related to risk culture.
Vicki Elliott, Senior Partner and Financial Services Talent Leader at Mercer, highlighted the importance of senior leaders setting a positive example when it comes to risk management and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Maybank customers in Malaysia can now access Western Union remittances digitally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</guid><description>Maybank and Western Union have partnered to introduce the first digital remittance service in Malaysia. This service, accessible through the Maybank2u (M2u) mobile app and website, allows Maybank customers to send money to over 500,000 Western Union agent locations in more than 200 countries and territories. Available 24/7, the service facilitates transfers up to RM10,000 daily, with recipients typically receiving funds faster than traditional methods.
Datuk Lim Hong Tat, Maybank&amp;rsquo;s Group Head of Community Financial Services, highlighted that this launch strengthens Maybank&amp;rsquo;s online presence and promotes digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/maybank-customers-in-malaysia-can-now-access-western-union-remittances-digitally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xero collaborates with UOB to assist small businesses in handling their cash flow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 07:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</guid><description>Xero announced today that its platform will now integrate with UOB. This partnership will allow small businesses in Singapore who bank with UOB to connect their bank accounts to their Xero subscription.
Both Xero and UOB are dedicated to helping small businesses in Singapore succeed. This integration is a significant step toward solving a major challenge these businesses face: managing cash flow.
Small business customers banking with UOB can now opt to have their transactions sent directly from UOB to Xero daily through a secure connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-collaborates-with-uob-to-assist-small-businesses-in-handling-their-cash-flow/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UnionPay is expanding its presence in Turkey through partnerships with ZIRAAT BANK and Garanti Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</guid><description>Ziraat Bank in Turkey has partnered with UnionPay International to enable UnionPay card acceptance across all its ATMs and POS terminals within the year. This initiative aims to broaden the reach of UnionPay cards within Turkey and enhance the experience for visiting UnionPay cardholders.
UnionPay anticipates that this collaboration will increase the acceptance rate of UnionPay cards at Turkish ATMs from 50% to nearly 70% by year-end. Similarly, POS terminal acceptance is projected to rise from 80% to almost 90%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IMDA collaborates with telecommunications companies and financial institutions to assist small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:21:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Seven partnerships between the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA), telecommunications companies, and financial institutions aim to accelerate the adoption of digital technologies by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs). These partnerships will focus on providing SMEs with access to pre-approved, secure, and interoperable solutions in cybersecurity and data analytics.
Launched in 2017, the SMEs Go Digital program helps SMEs adopt appropriate digital technologies at each stage of their growth. SMEs are a significant part of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy, contributing to roughly 50% of its gross domestic product and employing two-thirds of its workforce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imda-collaborates-with-telecommunications-companies-and-financial-institutions-to-assist-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The bank in Beirut provides live video conferencing services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 15:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</guid><description>Bank Audi has established a new flagship branch called &amp;ldquo;Novo&amp;rdquo; in Beirut Central District&amp;rsquo;s Palladium Building. This branch is open every day of the year from 10 am to 10 pm and provides customers with interactive banking services.
In addition to smart ATMs offering services like cash withdrawals, cash and check deposits, and credit card payments, the branch introduces a first-of-its-kind feature in Lebanon: Interactive Teller Machines (ITMs). These ITMs enable customers to connect with personal tellers through live video conferencing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bank-in-beirut-provides-live-video-conferencing-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank celebrates reaching 100,000 Facebook Likes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</guid><description>Alizz Islamic Bank has achieved a significant milestone by reaching 100,000 likes on Facebook. This achievement places them among the top two banks in Oman to attain this level of popularity on the platform.
Over the past year, Alizz Islamic Bank has significantly bolstered its social media presence, driven by a strong belief in its ability to enhance customer service. In addition to their Facebook success, they have also surpassed 30,000 followers on Instagram...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-celebrates-reaching-100-000-facebook-likes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alizz Islamic Bank has enhanced its mobile application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 14:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</guid><description>Source: Alizz Islamic Bank. The app.
Alizz Islamic Bank has introduced a redesigned mobile banking app and online platform to solidify its position as a customer experience frontrunner in Oman.
The dual-language app, compatible with both Android and iOS devices, boasts high-level security features and a self-registration option. Users can conveniently manage web banking logins, money transfers, bill payments, and other transactions using QR codes. The app is compatible with 3D Touch technology and is the first of its kind in Oman to provide in-app alerts for new transactions and payment reminders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alizz-islamic-bank-has-enhanced-its-mobile-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mobile app-driven ATMs without screens could be the future of banking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</guid><description>EyeLock, a company that provides iris-based identity authentication solutions, has partnered with Diebold, a global provider of self-service technology, to create a screenless, compact ATM concept. A prototype called Irving is currently being tested by Citibank in the US.
This innovative ATM design eliminates the need for a PIN pad, card reader, or screen. Instead, users conduct transactions through a mobile app on their smartphone. The system utilizes near field communication (NFC), quick response (QR) code technology, and EyeLock&amp;rsquo;s iris scanning to verify the customer&amp;rsquo;s identity at the ATM...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mobile-app-driven-atms-without-screens-could-be-the-future-of-banking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an abundance of travel rewards with the NBK Miles World Mastercard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 08:09:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</guid><description>Source: NBK. The NBK Miles World Mastercard.
People who travel frequently from Kuwait can accumulate points and enjoy airport lounge access with the NBK Miles World Mastercard.
These NBK Miles Points can be used to reserve flights from over 800 airlines, book accommodations at more than 150,000 hotels, and rent vehicles from well-known agencies worldwide. Cardholders can redeem their miles for any destination, airline, origin point, and time of year, without blackout dates or seat restrictions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-abundance-of-travel-rewards-with-the-nbk-miles-world-mastercard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Sohar introduces a new relationship banking service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 04:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/</guid><description>Bank Sohar has introduced &amp;ldquo;Al Khaas,&amp;rdquo; a premium banking service designed to provide a personalized experience. This service includes dedicated relationship managers, wealth advisors, exclusive banking centers, a dedicated call center, and a range of benefits such as prize draws, rewards, and more.
Al Khaas aims to meet the needs of high-net-worth individuals (HNI) by providing a superior banking experience across all of its 31 branches in Oman. Dedicated Al Khaas service centers will also be available in select major branches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-sohar-introduces-a-new-relationship-banking-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Harmoney proudly displays impressive first-year results</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 12:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</guid><description>The remarkable first-year performance of Harmoney, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s sole peer-to-peer (P2P) lending platform, highlights a substantial unmet need for crowdfunded microloans.
Established on September 10, 2014, with NZ$100 million in committed capital from prominent institutions like Blue Elephant Capital Management and Heartland Bank, Harmoney has facilitated NZ$100 million in personal loans within its inaugural year. The company&amp;rsquo;s rapid expansion has resulted in the creation of 65 new jobs across New Zealand, Australia, and Fiji, with plans underway for an Australian launch...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harmoney-proudly-displays-impressive-first-year-results/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>