<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>France on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/france/</link><description>Recent content in France on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prisoner voting is now a legal issue under EU legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 05:28:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Jo Shaw, Salvesen Chair of European Institutions
Article 39(2) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights states:
‘European Parliament members shall be chosen through direct, universal suffrage in a free and secret ballot.’
The Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice, in a concise and understated judgment in Delvigne (Case C-650/13; ECLI:EU:C:2015:648) delivered on October 6, 2015, provided further definition to this provision. It found that national policies determining voter eligibility in European Parliament elections fall under EU law&amp;rsquo;s purview, as they implement EU law according to Article 51(1) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Which Member State bears responsibility for the Calais crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Thousands of migrants residing in subpar conditions near Calais are creating a difficult situation, as many aim to reach the UK. Their efforts to traverse the Eurotunnel are causing significant travel delays at the border. This raises the question: is the UK or France responsible for these individuals?
Initially, it&amp;rsquo;s important to acknowledge the conflict between two forms of movement within the EU. The EU actively promotes the free movement of goods, people, and transport services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/which-member-state-bears-responsibility-for-the-calais-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions of the Attorney General on recent CJEU cases regarding national data retention laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
Advocate General Campos Sanchez-Bordana has presented his opinions on three cases concerning data retention: SpaceNet and Telekom Deutschland, GD v Commissioner of the Garda Síochána, and VD and SR. These opinions are the latest development in a series of legal challenges related to data retention that began with an Irish challenge to the Data Retention Directive.
The Data Retention Directive, which allowed for the retention of communications data under certain exceptions to privacy principles, was invalidated in the Digital Rights Ireland case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines is now offering flights from China to France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</guid><description>Hainan Airlines has introduced a fifth European route to its network, joining existing services to Moscow, Saint Petersburg, Brussels, and Berlin. The inaugural flight, HU7907, departed Hangzhou International Airport on September 3rd, with a stopover at Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport before continuing to Paris&amp;rsquo; Roissy-Charles de Gaulle Airport.
Source: Hainan Airlines. The ribbon-cutting ceremony for the first flight on September 3.
This new service aims to enhance political, economic, and cultural ties between China and France, especially as 2014 marks the 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between the two nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Better Network Connectivity Into France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</guid><description>Globalization is increasingly common, and even companies without a multinational presence often conduct business internationally. The European Union, with its vast pool of consumers and producers, is a significant market, and France stands out as a key destination within the EU.
Level 3 Communications, a major telecommunications provider, recently enhanced its resources, infrastructure, and services for French enterprise customers. The company expanded its network reach with additional Points of Presence (POPs) in Paris and its surrounding areas, along with core network extensions in Lille, Lyon, and Toulouse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/better-network-connectivity-into-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's finally here - the CJEU has confirmed that UK citizens have officially lost their EU citizenship.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 15:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has affirmed that UK citizens lost EU citizenship due to Brexit, as per a recent judgment. This aligns with the earlier Advocate-General’s opinion. While other similar cases exist, the CJEU is unlikely to deviate from this decision.
This judgment is notable for its dismissal of arguments advocating for the retention of EU citizenship for British citizens, marking a significant shift...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-s-finally-here-the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-uk-citizens-have-officially-lost-their-eu-citizenship/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>