<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hyatt on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hyatt/</link><description>Recent content in Hyatt on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hyatt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong is the inaugural Hyatt Place in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 13:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-place-phuket-patong-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-place-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Hyatt and Boutique Corporation have announced the launch of the Hyatt Place Phuket, Patong in Phuket, Thailand. This 161-room beachfront property is the first Hyatt Place hotel in Southeast Asia. It embodies the Hyatt Place brand&amp;rsquo;s relaxed style and offers convenient amenities like complimentary Wi-Fi and 24/7 dining options.
&amp;ldquo;Thailand remains a crucial market for Hyatt, and Phuket is a top tourist spot in Southeast Asia with rising demand from both leisure and business travelers,&amp;rdquo; said David Udell, Group President – Asia Pacific, Hyatt Hotels Corporation.</description></item><item><title>Guests staying at the Hyatt hotel can enjoy complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels Corporation is demonstrating its commitment to enhancing the guest experience by providing free Wi-Fi at all of its hotels globally starting in February 2015. This initiative aims to provide guests with convenient connectivity regardless of how they booked their stay or their loyalty program status.
Guests will have access to complimentary Wi-Fi on an unlimited number of devices, including laptops and mobile phones, in both guest rooms and common areas of Hyatt-branded hotels.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Regency is back in Sydney and is now focusing on positioning the hotel for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels announced that a hotel situated at 161 Sussex Street, previously operating under the Four Points by Sheraton brand, will transition to Hyatt Regency Sydney starting November 30, 2016. This change signifies the return of the Hyatt Regency brand to Sydney. The company is strategically positioning the Hyatt Regency Sydney as a prime location for conferences.
The introduction of Hyatt Regency Sydney aligns with the growing demand for business, meetings, incentives, conferences and exhibitions (MICE), as well as leisure travel within the Australian market.</description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream.</description></item></channel></rss>