<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ir/</link><description>Recent content in IR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Final 3D Printed Part Added</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 01:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-final-3d-printed-part-added/</guid><description>I have completed the final 3D printed component for my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control system. This piece fits into a 10mm opening on the remote control receiver board, allowing it to be secured using one of the main PCB&amp;rsquo;s screws. The image below shows the part with the screw in place:
Once the remote control board is in place, the original screw can be used to fasten it. The cylindrical portion is designed to prevent the remote board from pressing against the component pins on the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s main PCB while ensuring a secure fit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a 3D Printed Installation Tray</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-3d-printed-installation-tray/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about my Beogram 4002 (5513) remote control upgrade, specifically the receiver board insulation. My previous solution, using plastic foil, wasn&amp;rsquo;t ideal aesthetically.
To address this, I designed a plastic tray that safeguards the receiver board from the main circuit board&amp;rsquo;s solder points. The tray is designed to click into place without additional screws.
Here are some photos:
Tray and board before assembly:
The tray features three rectangular cutouts to provide clearance for the solder points.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5504): Installation of Commander Remote Control Module</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:24:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5504-installation-of-commander-remote-control-module/</guid><description>This article details the installation of a Beolover Commander Remote Control Module into a Beogram 4002 (Type 5504) turntable. This particular unit was restored for a customer in Australia and also features an internal Beolover RIAA phono pre-amplifier.
The Commander Module, seen here before installation, allows for remote control of the turntable:
The module includes an IR receiver (black wire at the bottom), an adapter board (narrow board on the right), a wiring harness (white wires), and an auto-repeat indicator (red wire at the top).</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander Remote Control: Installation Video</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-remote-control-installation-video/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 &amp;ldquo;Commander&amp;rdquo; remote control system has recently seen a surge in popularity, with multiple orders coming in over a short time. This could be linked to the Commander&amp;rsquo;s new compatibility with a specific Apple TV remote, allowing it to integrate with Apple devices in the same space. Designed for later models of the 4002 turntable with the keypad connector on the main circuit board (types 551x and 552x), I recently built three receivers over the weekend and shipped them out today, each packaged with a compatible Apple remote:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513) Remote Control: Now With a Professionally Made PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-remote-control-now-with-a-professionally-made-pcb/</guid><description>I recently had a professionally made circuit board manufactured for the remote control receiver in my Beogram 4002 (5513). It was exciting to see the new board arrive and start assembling it.
The biggest changes in this design were simplifying the assembly by placing all the components on the top side and repositioning the ISP port to avoid interference with the aluminum top panel fixture. I also removed the reset button and made more space for the keypad connector.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Apple Remote Controls All Functions of Turntable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 14:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-apple-remote-controls-all-functions-of-turntable/</guid><description>After several weeks of testing, I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share my latest creation: a remote control receiver designed specifically for the Beogram 4002 (5513 model) turntable. This receiver seamlessly integrates with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s existing keypad connector without affecting its functionality.
The receiver board is compatible with the latest Apple TV remote, chosen for its sleek aluminum design that complements the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic. The remote&amp;rsquo;s minimalist button layout also aligns perfectly with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s functions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): End Groove Detection Not Working</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</guid><description>Just when I thought I had finished refurbishing a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a problem surfaced during playback. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t return after playing a record, instead getting stuck in the end groove, repeating the sound of the run-out.
Investigating further, I used an oscilloscope to examine the signal from the position sensor, which tells the control system the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s location. The signal was weak specifically in the end groove area, often indicating misalignment between the sensor&amp;rsquo;s IR diode and the light entry slit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Commander MkII: Remote Control for Beogram 4002 Now With Integrated Auto-Repeat Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-for-beogram-4002-now-with-integrated-auto-repeat-function/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable and planned to install my 4002 Commander Remote control system. This system is great because it keeps the keypad pristine and allows for operation without touching it. You can find demonstration and installation videos on my blog if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in upgrading your own 4002. The Commander board is compatible with all models equipped with a DC motor.
This restoration project inspired me to create an updated MkII version of the 4002 Commander, featuring an auto-repeat function similar to the Beogram 8000 and 8002 turntables.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of the Latest Version of the Beogram Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:57:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-the-latest-version-of-the-beogram-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>While restoring my Beogram 4002 (5513), I decided to improve the Beogram 4002 Commander remote control I had previously designed. I added a &amp;ldquo;pairing&amp;rdquo; feature to prevent conflicts with Apple TVs and other devices that use Apple remotes. To completely eliminate the need to touch the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s delicate keypad, I also included remote switching between 33 and 45 RPM. A detailed video about the latest version explains the functions and demonstrates the remote and its pairing process:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of 4002 Commander MkII Remote Control and Internal RIAA Preamp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 03:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-4002-commander-mkii-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-preamp/</guid><description>I recently completed a Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration, and the customer requested two upgrades I developed: the Beolover 4002 Commander MkII remote control receiver and the internal RIAA pre-amplifier. These upgrades are detailed further on my blog, along with installation instructions. Both are available for purchase; feel free to contact me for more information.
This image showcases both boards:
The lower board is the Commander MkII. This version includes a repeat function, indicated by the CD4 light on the keypad.</description></item></channel></rss>