<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Earphones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earphones/</link><description>Recent content in Earphones on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/earphones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience all-day flexibility with the Plantronics BackBeat 100 Series Wireless Headphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</guid><description>Plantronics, a company known for its audio and wearable technology, has introduced the BackBeat 100 Series. These headphones are the newest addition to their BackBeat stereo product line and offer a unique hybrid neckband design for wireless calls and music.
The BackBeat 100 and BackBeat 105 are designed for comfort throughout the day with an ultra-lightweight build. They provide full-range sound with enhanced bass, making them ideal for listening to music and watching videos on the move.</description></item><item><title>HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 Bluetooth earphones are now available in Singapore through Huawei's official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-freebuds-3-bluetooth-earphones-are-now-available-in-singapore-through-huawei-s-official-launch/</guid><description>Huawei Singapore has introduced the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3, stereo Bluetooth earphones with a groundbreaking open-fit design that incorporates active noise cancellation.
Source: Huawei. Eager customers queue at SITEX to buy the HUAWEI FreeBuds 3 on November 30, 2019.
As the new year approaches, Huawei is focused on creating a comprehensive product ecosystem in Singapore, allowing customers to experience seamless connectivity between their smartphones and other devices such as the new Huawei Watch GT 2 and Gentle Monster – Huawei Eyewear.</description></item></channel></rss>