<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Change on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/change/</link><description>Recent content in Change on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US airlines may now reject your standard carry-on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</guid><description>According to George Hobica from Airfarewatchdog, several US airlines have reduced the allowed size for carry-on luggage.
Traveling Hello Kitty statue at Taoyuan Airport,
Taiwan in 2008.
American, Delta, and United Airlines now permit carry-on bags with a maximum size of 22 inches in length, 14 inches in width, and 9 inches in height. The previous allowed width was 15 inches.
A Yahoo article from March highlighted United Airlines&amp;rsquo; stricter enforcement of carry-on size regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Sudden RPM Changes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 14:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</guid><description>During testing of a restored Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, I noticed the RPM drifting over time. Replacing the original RPM relay and the 5k RPM trimmers fixed this issue. However, a new problem arose: infrequent, sudden drops in RPM.
This image shows the original RPM relay on the main PCB:
The relay design I created for the Beogram 4000 also worked in this model. Here’s the replacement board:
And installed:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-sudden-rpm-changes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): More RPM Measurements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/</guid><description>Following up on the Beogram 4002 (5513) from the previous day, I conducted an overnight RPM (revolutions per minute) performance test using my BeoloverRPM device.
The resulting measurement curve demonstrates excellent performance, typical of DC motor models. It shows minimal fluctuations (less than 0.05%) over time, aligning with the service manual&amp;rsquo;s specifications. The initial upward slope, lasting a couple of hours, is a common trait in the 551x and 552x models...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-more-rpm-measurements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Initial RPM Performance Characterization</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 09:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/</guid><description>This post follows up on my initial writing about the Beogram 4002 (5513). I used my recently created BeoloverRPM device to assess the unit&amp;rsquo;s RPM performance.
This test clearly showed the suspected rapid speed changes. The graph below displays the RPM over a roughly 24-hour period.
The abrupt negative spikes in the graph indicate that the DC motor and its control system require attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-initial-rpm-performance-characterization/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The KPMG index assesses the capacity of 140 countries to adapt to change</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</guid><description>According to the 2019 KPMG Change Readiness Index (CRI), countries in the Asia Pacific region are generally showing improvement in their approaches to climate change. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose two spots to number 2, while Taiwan jumped 18 places.
Published twice a year, the CRI is now in its fourth year. It ranks 140 countries* based on their preparedness for and response to major change events. This edition focuses on the capabilities countries need to effectively combat climate change and minimize related risks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Eight multilateral development banks (MDBs) working together to speed up efforts to reduce transportation emissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/</guid><description>Eight major development banks have come together to address the significant impact of transportation on climate change. These institutions acknowledge that the transportation sector, responsible for a considerable portion of global energy consumption and emissions, needs more action to minimize its environmental footprint and enhance its resilience to climate change.
The African Development Bank, Asian Development Bank (ADB), CAF-Development Bank of Latin America, European Bank for Reconstruction and Development, European Investment Bank, Inter-American Development Bank, Islamic Development Bank (ISDB), and the World Bank (WB) have pledged to expedite their efforts in several key areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eight-multilateral-development-banks-mdbs-working-together-to-speed-up-efforts-to-reduce-transportation-emissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): RPM Performance Measurement after Restoration of DC Motor and Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 23:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</guid><description>Following the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5514) turntable&amp;rsquo;s DC motor and control system, a 24-hour RPM performance test was conducted using a custom-built RPM monitoring device.
The initial performance, measured before the restoration, revealed noticeable, abrupt drops in RPM, indicating typical wear and tear in the DC motor&amp;rsquo;s brass sleeve bearings. These dips, while moderate in this instance, would have been audible due to their 1% magnitude.
After the restoration, which included rebuilding the motor and replacing RPM-related components, the significant RPM fluctuations were eliminated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-rpm-performance-measurement-after-restoration-of-dc-motor-and-control-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>