<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>South on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/south/</link><description>Recent content in South on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/south/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years.</description></item><item><title>South Asia has the potential to become the leading export region in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</guid><description>By implementing policies that enhance productivity, South Asia could substantially increase its global market share in electronics, motor vehicles, and apparel by 2030, according to a new World Bank report titled &amp;ldquo;South Asia’s Turn: Policies to Boost Competitiveness and Create the Next Export Powerhouse.&amp;rdquo; The report emphasizes that improving firm productivity is crucial for boosting competitiveness in Pakistan and the rest of South Asia. While acknowledging the region&amp;rsquo;s investment climate challenges, the report focuses on less-explored factors like the impact of cities and clusters, global value chains, and firms&amp;rsquo; capacity for innovation and efficient resource utilization.</description></item><item><title>Businesses operating in the South China Sea region should be cautious of the Spring Dragon APT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:39:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-operating-in-the-south-china-sea-region-should-be-cautious-of-the-spring-dragon-apt/</guid><description>Kaspersky Lab is issuing a warning about a threat actor targeting nations surrounding the South China Sea. The cybersecurity company has observed a rise in attacks since 2017 from an advanced persistent threat (APT) known as Spring Dragon (or LotusBlossom) using new and enhanced tactics.
Noushin Shabab, Senior Security Researcher at Kaspersky Lab&amp;rsquo;s Global Research &amp;amp; Analysis Team (GReAT), emphasizes the importance of vigilance, stating, &amp;ldquo;We believe Spring Dragon will continue to reappear in the Asian region, making it crucial to be familiar with its methods.</description></item></channel></rss>