<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EEA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eea/</link><description>Recent content in EEA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eea/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the free movement of people in the European Economic Area (EEA) distinct from that in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Karin Fløistad: PhD Candidate, European University Institute; practicing lawyer at Norwegian law firm Simonsen Vogt Wiig
The UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit relationship with the EU often involves discussions about the free movement of people, with the EEA Agreement frequently cited as a potential model. This piece will analyze two key distinctions between the EEA Agreement&amp;rsquo;s approach to the free movement of people and that of full EU membership.
The EEA Agreement integrates the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market with three members of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA): Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Questions &amp; Answers about EU Free Movement Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 09:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;We shouldn&amp;rsquo;t create a misleading impression of the law.&amp;rdquo;
(Measure for Measure, 2.1.1)
Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School, University of York
Laurent Pech, Professor of European Law, Jean Monnet Chair of EU Public Law at Middlesex University London
This article clarifies common misunderstandings about EU free movement rules, often found in British media. We believe much criticism targets a distorted view of the actual system.
The UK shows a desire to restrict EU freedom of movement, yet misinterpretations about these rules persist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-questions-answers-about-eu-free-movement-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit: Explaining the concepts of EFTA and the EEA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</guid><description>Dr. Michael Sánchez Rydelski and Cath Howdle*
*Respectively Member and Deputy Director of the Legal Service of the EFTA Surveillance Authority. Nothing in the present article binds or necessarily reflects the views of the EFTA Surveillance Authority.
1. Introduction
This article doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer a Brexit solution, leaving that to governments and negotiators. Instead, it provides guidance on key aspects of the European Free Trade Association (&amp;ldquo;EFTA&amp;rdquo;) and European Economic Area (&amp;ldquo;EEA&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-explaining-the-concepts-of-efta-and-the-eea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinions on Scotland's Position in Europe: Analysis of the Scottish Government's latest suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 20:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The Scottish government recently released its anticipated paper exploring Scotland&amp;rsquo;s position within Europe. While acknowledging the government&amp;rsquo;s support for both EU membership and Scottish independence, the paper concentrates on potential outcomes should Brexit occur while Scotland remains part of the UK. Accusations that the paper dismisses referendum results, regarding either Brexit or Scottish independence, or simply rehashes arguments for independence are unfounded.
The paper essentially presents two main options: a UK-wide approach to Brexit that considers the concerns of Scottish voters, or, if that fails, a separate approach specifically for Scotland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-on-scotland-s-position-in-europe-analysis-of-the-scottish-government-s-latest-suggestions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>