<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colocation Facilities on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-facilities/</link><description>Recent content in Colocation Facilities on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-facilities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Optic Direct Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 08:56:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-direct-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The internet provides a wide and affordable way to use cloud services. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer consistently low latency, jitter, or high bandwidth, as it was designed for universal connectivity, not specialized performance. If your cloud-based business processes are slower or less reliable than when they were on-site, a direct cloud connection might be beneficial.
A popular cloud service is Amazon AWS Cloud Computing Platform. This platform lets users utilize Amazon&amp;rsquo;s vast computing resources on a pay-as-you-go basis for various services like application and web hosting, backup, storage, content delivery, enterprise IT applications, and scalable databases.</description></item><item><title>Data Center Services For You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</guid><description>Smaller companies often admire the data centers of larger organizations, but they may not realize that similar services are within their reach.
The key is to only own assets crucial to your business and lease the rest, including data center services. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a massive, secure facility with 24/7 staff, backup generators, and unlimited bandwidth. These services are available on a pay-as-you-go basis.
Two types of data centers are eager to accommodate your business.</description></item></channel></rss>