<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EMU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/emu/</link><description>Recent content in EMU on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/emu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions.</description></item><item><title>Preserving the euro: Gauweiler's challenge to the legality of the OMT program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-euro-gauweiler-s-challenge-to-the-legality-of-the-omt-program/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
On June 16th, the Court of Justice ruled in the Gauweiler case, declaring the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program legal under EU law. This decision has significant implications for the ECB&amp;rsquo;s authority, the EU Economic and Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s constitutional structure, and the relationship between the Court of Justice and the referring court, the German Federal Constitutional Court.</description></item><item><title>Should legitimacy be prioritized in the further development of the EMU, or should it be considered as a secondary concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-legitimacy-be-prioritized-in-the-further-development-of-the-emu-or-should-it-be-considered-as-a-secondary-concern/</guid><description>Päivi Leino-Sandberg: Adjunct Professor of EU Law, Academy of Finland Research Fellow, University of Helsinki
In June 2012, the European Council outlined &amp;ldquo;four essential building blocks&amp;rdquo; for the future of the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU): integrated frameworks for finance, budget, and economic policy, and enhanced democratic legitimacy and accountability. The European Council emphasized ensuring democratic legitimacy and accountability at all levels of decision-making and implementation, stating that stronger economic governance requires stronger legitimacy and accountability.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural report of the European Fiscal Board and the outlook for the EU's fiscal framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 05:05:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-report-of-the-european-fiscal-board-and-the-outlook-for-the-eu-s-fiscal-framework/</guid><description>Paul Dermine (PhD candidate in EU institutional law, Maastricht University) and Diane Fromage (Assistant Professor of European Law, Faculty of Law, Maastricht University)
EU Fiscal Governance after the Crisis: A Time for Reflection and the European Fiscal Board&amp;rsquo;s First Report
Recent developments suggest that the Eurozone may be entering a new phase. With the sovereign debt crisis subsiding and economic growth gradually returning, discussions about reforming the Economic and Monetary Union (EMU) are resurfacing at both the EU and member state levels.</description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention.</description></item></channel></rss>