<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sim/</link><description>Recent content in SIM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia.</description></item><item><title>Starting from December 21, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM for Japan will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</guid><description>Source: Plus One Marketing.
Plus One Marketing, a Japanese company known for its FREETEL brand of mobile devices, is launching a prepaid data SIM card specifically for travelers in Japan. Starting December 21, 2015, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM will be available for purchase.
The SIM card is designed with tourists in mind, allowing unlimited access to popular social media platforms like Facebook, Kakao Talk, WeChat, LINE, and WhatsApp for seven days.</description></item><item><title>When you fly with Sri Lankan Airlines to Sri Lanka, you will receive a complimentary Mobitel SIM card and free data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-fly-with-sri-lankan-airlines-to-sri-lanka-you-will-receive-a-complimentary-mobitel-sim-card-and-free-data/</guid><description>Passengers who purchase their tickets online through SriLankan Airlines receive a complimentary SIM card with data and the option to rent a dongle for internet access in Sri Lanka. The airline teamed up with the data network provider Mobitel to offer travelers a free SIM card with 100MB of data. For those who need a dongle, one can be rented for 30 days for a refundable deposit of Rs3,490. Full details about the offer are available here.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a new prepaid SIM card that also functions as a travel card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-new-prepaid-sim-card-that-also-functions-as-a-travel-card/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced the hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card, a first in Asia, which combines a prepaid SIM card with a stored value travel card usable for Singapore&amp;rsquo;s public transportation.
Source: Singtel. The hi!Tourist EZ-Link SIM card is the first in Asia to combine travel and phone services.
Priced at S$18, this SIM card provides 100 GB of 4G data, unlimited access to social media and messaging apps, and 1 GB of roaming data for select countries in the region.</description></item><item><title>A new budget-friendly Lumia is about to be released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The Lumia 430.
Microsoft has released the Lumia 430 Dual SIM, its most budget-friendly Lumia smartphone that can be upgraded to Windows 10*. Priced at approximately S$119, the Lumia 430 joins Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s affordable smartphone lineup alongside the Lumia 435, which features Lumia Camera.
Equipped with Windows Phone 8.1, a Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a 1.2GHz dual-core CPU, and pre-installed Microsoft Office, Skype, and OneDrive, the Lumia 430 Dual SIM enables users to be productive at work, enjoy entertainment, and stay connected while on the move.</description></item><item><title>The HTC One E9+ dual sim will be available in Singapore starting August 29th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:40:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-one-e9-dual-sim-will-be-available-in-singapore-starting-august-29th/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The HTC One E9+ dual sim in rose gold.
HTC has introduced the HTC One E9+ dual sim in Singapore. This lightweight smartphone boasts a sizable 2K display and injects vibrant colors into the signature flagship design.
&amp;ldquo;This latest addition to our HTC One E series capitalizes on the success of our flagship phones, offering both sophistication and style,&amp;rdquo; stated Faisal Siddiqui, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;The HTC One E9+ dual sim represents a continuation of HTC&amp;rsquo;s commitment to innovation and design, showcasing a large 5.</description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience.</description></item><item><title>HTC has launched the HTC Desire 826 dual sim, promising an exceptional mobile audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-launched-the-htc-desire-826-dual-sim-promising-an-exceptional-mobile-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: HTC. The Blue Lagoon version.
HTC is enhancing the mobile audio experience with its Desire 826 dual sim phone, featuring HTC BoomSound and Dolby Audio surround sound. This makes HTC the first smartphone manufacturer to integrate dual front-facing stereo speakers, a precisely adjusted sound profile, and Dolby&amp;rsquo;s decoding technology for a comprehensive multi-channel audio solution.
This combination provides listeners with a level of audio depth and range not typically found in mobile devices.</description></item></channel></rss>