<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Google Android on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/google-android/</link><description>Recent content in Google Android on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/google-android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T-Mobile G1 Google Android Phone Gets Vocal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</guid><description>Choosing your next smartphone can be tough. Touchscreen phones like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone, the BlackBerry Bold, and Samsung Delve are appealing, but some prefer a physical QWERTY keyboard. The BlackBerry Pearl&amp;rsquo;s trackball navigation is another option. Connectivity matters too, with 3G being desirable but not always accessible. WiFi capability for fast web browsing is also important.
The HTC-built G1 for T-Mobile might be the solution if you want it all. This &amp;ldquo;Android Phone,&amp;rdquo; marking Google&amp;rsquo;s entry into mobile wireless, operates on T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s network, offering quad-band service and various data features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID vs DROID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:58:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</guid><description>The DROID phone, running Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system, actually has two versions produced by different companies with distinct specifications. So, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between the two.
The first DROID, manufactured by Motorola for Verizon Wireless, is a touchscreen QWERTY smartphone utilizing the Android 2.0 operating system. This innovative device was recognized as Time.com&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Top Gadget of 2009&amp;rdquo;.
This top-tier DROID boasts a 5.0-megapixel camera, doubling as a camcorder, with features like geo-tagging, auto-stabilization, flash, and built-in editing tools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID is the Woid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</guid><description>Motorola and Verizon have partnered to challenge the dominant Apple iPhone with their highly anticipated DROID phone. Powered by the Google Android 2.0 operating system, the DROID promises exceptional functionality. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore its features.
A key distinction between the iPhone and most other smartphones, aside from the BlackBerry Storm, is the inclusion of a physical keyboard. For those accustomed to texting on physical keys, transitioning to a touchscreen keyboard can be challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Android Phone to Devour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</guid><description>Interested in getting a Google Android smartphone? The Motorola DEVOUR Silver might be the one for you. This Android 1.6 smartphone features a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and a 3.1-inch touchscreen, all within a sleek silver design.
The DEVOUR uses MOTOBLUR, a service that seamlessly syncs your messages, status updates, and contacts directly to your customizable home screens. This eliminates the need to log in or open individual apps, giving you instant access to your information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google's Plan To Chew Up Microsoft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</guid><description>A recent Wall Street Journal article hints at Google&amp;rsquo;s next target: Microsoft.
Google&amp;rsquo;s goals might extend beyond replacing Microsoft as the dominant force in PC operating systems. Their ambition could be complete control over all devices with embedded computers, essentially every electronic device.
This theory stems from reports that PC manufacturers like Hewlett-Packard are experimenting with Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system in netbooks. Android, primarily a mobile phone operating system, might seem harmless to established PC operating systems, but that might be a miscalculation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>