<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Polycom on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/polycom/</link><description>Recent content in Polycom on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:28:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/polycom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Huddle rooms equipped with video capabilities have the potential to enhance collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/</guid><description>India, China, and Singapore are leading the way in Asia Pacific when it comes to using collaboration technology in huddle rooms (small meeting rooms). However, there&amp;rsquo;s still a significant opportunity to boost productivity further through advanced collaboration tools.
A new study by Polycom (now a part of Plantronics) reveals that although content sharing is the preferred collaboration method for Singaporean workers, the country&amp;rsquo;s adoption of video conferencing lags behind other countries in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huddle-rooms-equipped-with-video-capabilities-have-the-potential-to-enhance-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP That Sounds Better Than TDM Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 23:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that VoIP calls are inferior to traditional phone calls using TDM technology. Some even believe VoIP limitations make it impossible to match TDM&amp;rsquo;s voice quality. However, this is a misconception. VoIP has the potential to sound significantly better than TDM, even reaching high-fidelity music quality.
The negative perception of VoIP stems from early experiences with low-quality PC softphones and dial-up internet. While these were acceptable for free international calls, their poor sound quality became problematic when marketed as a replacement for traditional phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-that-sounds-better-than-tdm-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How HD Audio Will Transform VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 19:34:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</guid><description>People who recall the era of analog phones and physical switches often feel nostalgic about the superior audio quality of those systems. The conversations back then possessed a clarity and immediacy that has largely vanished in recent times, though this might be changing soon. A new movement is underway to enhance the fidelity of VoIP calls significantly, aiming to make current phones seem primitive in comparison.
This advancement is known as high-definition audio or HD Voice, a term used by Polycom, a manufacturer of IP phones equipped with this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-hd-audio-will-transform-voip/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>