<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Regulation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-regulation/</link><description>Recent content in Internet Regulation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:01:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Cyber Resilience Act as it relates to the Internet of Things.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 02:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cyber-resilience-act-as-it-relates-to-the-internet-of-things/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip, PhD candidate, Radboud University
Image credit: Grafiker61, via Wikicommons Media
The Internet of Things (IoT), encompassing devices with integrated hardware and software like smartwatches and WiFi security cameras, is becoming increasingly prevalent in homes and industries. However, the cybersecurity of these connected devices is a growing concern. Hackers have exploited vulnerabilities in these devices, as demonstrated by the Mirai botnet attack, where thousands of devices were compromised to disrupt websites and businesses.</description></item><item><title>The complexities of the new EU Media Freedom Act</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-complexities-of-the-new-eu-media-freedom-act/</guid><description>Samira Asmaa Allioui, research and tutorial fellow at the Center for International and European Studies at the University of Strasbourg
Photo credit: Bin im Garten, via Wikimedia Commons
Journalists face various pressures. Recent years have seen media freedom, particularly media pluralism, under threat.
On December 15, 2023, the European Council and Parliament reached an agreement on regulations to protect media freedom, pluralism, and editorial independence within the European Union. The EU Media Freedom Act (EMFA) aims for greater transparency in media ownership and safeguards against government surveillance and spyware targeting journalists.</description></item><item><title>Unresolved concerns regarding the regulations for trusted flaggers under the Digital Services Act regime</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 15:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unresolved-concerns-regarding-the-regulations-for-trusted-flaggers-under-the-digital-services-act-regime/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giorgia Lo Tauro, FratiniVergano European Lawyers
Photo credit: ** Lobo Studio Hamburg**, via Wikimedia Commons
1 Introduction
The EU&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services Act (DSA) formally establishes the roles and responsibilities of &amp;ldquo;trusted flaggers,&amp;rdquo; important entities in the online world that have operated with varying degrees of influence since the early 2000s. This new framework aligns with the DSA&amp;rsquo;s goals: creating consistent, effective, and balanced rules across the EU to improve the online marketplace.</description></item><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 09:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497</description></item><item><title>The proposal by the EU Commission regarding the regulation of media freedom.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 01:33:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-proposal-by-the-eu-commission-regarding-the-regulation-of-media-freedom/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Photo credit: Bin im Garten, via Wikimedia Commons
In the 2021 State of the Union address, EU Commission President von der Leyen underscored the importance of media independence, stating that Europe needs a law to protect it. The proposed Media Freedom Act (MFA) aims to address this, building upon existing regulations like the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and the Digital Services Act (DSA).</description></item></channel></rss>