<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/home/</link><description>Recent content in Home on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone.</description></item><item><title>Businesses have the opportunity to take part in the For a Golden Home charity campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/businesses-have-the-opportunity-to-take-part-in-the-for-a-golden-home-charity-campaign/</guid><description>Cromly.com, a design portal and social media platform, has launched &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home.&amp;rdquo; This online charity campaign aims to improve the lives of needy elderly individuals in Singapore this Chinese New Year. The platform allows organizations to create their own fundraising projects in support of this shared goal.
Source: Cromly.com. Participating companies can create a pledge project to raise funds. Eunice Olsen and Paul Foster are ambassadors for the &amp;ldquo;For a Golden Home&amp;rdquo; campaign.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Home networks must be made more secure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 06:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/home-networks-must-be-made-more-secure/</guid><description>The increasing availability of faster and cheaper internet in Southeast Asia is driving a surge in home users adopting internet-connected devices. This trend is happening alongside more employees working remotely, often from home. While these connected devices offer convenience and improve communication, Fortinet, a global cybersecurity leader, warns that &amp;ldquo;home networks&amp;rdquo; are becoming attractive targets for cybercriminals.
Peerapong Jongvibool, Fortinet&amp;rsquo;s VP for Southeast Asia and Hong Kong, points out the vulnerability of internet-connected devices.</description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October.</description></item><item><title>Epson introduces a new smart gaming projector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 01:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-a-new-smart-gaming-projector/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the EH-TW6250 Smart Gaming Projector, the most budget-friendly option in their 4K PRO-UHD lineup. This projector delivers an impressive home theater experience with a screen size up to 500&amp;quot;, brightness up to 2,800 lumens, and an input lag* under 20 ms, making it ideal for movie nights and casual gaming.
This all-inclusive entertainment solution features scene-adaptive gamma correction, frame interpolation, HDR10/HLG support, and 3LCD technology. These features combine to provide smooth, color-accurate, high-resolution images with balanced white and color light output.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Expo CNY Fair offers daily discounts of S$380 to the first 888 customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</guid><description>Red envelopes containing discounts, called angbaos, can be redeemed for certain products in addition to existing promotions (terms and conditions apply).
Items will be offered at up to 88% off.
The Singapore Expo CNY Fair will distribute complimentary lucky angbao gift packages, each valued at S$380, to the initial 888 attendees daily from January 10th to 12th. The event will be held at Singapore Expo Hall 6, open from 12 pm to 9 pm each day.</description></item></channel></rss>