<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Article 5 ECHR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-5-echr/</link><description>Recent content in Article 5 ECHR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/article-5-echr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met.</description></item><item><title>Examining the Role of the European Court of Human Rights in Addressing Harassment of Human Rights Defenders: Evaluating Democracy, Malicious Intent, and Covert Motives.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:41:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-role-of-the-european-court-of-human-rights-in-addressing-harassment-of-human-rights-defenders-evaluating-democracy-malicious-intent-and-covert-motives/</guid><description>Protecting Critics: The European Court of Human Rights Strengthens its Stance Against Azerbaijan in Aliyev v. Azerbaijan By Dr Marco Antonio Simonelli, PhD, University of Siena, and Alast Najafi, LLM candidate, University of Leiden
Introduction The European Court of Human Rights (ECHR) used Article 18 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), a rarely utilized provision, to condemn Azerbaijan for human rights violations in the case of Aliyev v. Azerbaijan.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on conflicting EU and national law obligations regarding detention time limits. Is this a Prison Break?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD candidate, Utrecht University
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed the conflict between EU and national laws regarding detention periods for individuals subject to a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). Specifically, the case considered whether a longer EU-mandated detention period overrides a shorter national one, and whether unclear national legislation on this matter violates the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</description></item></channel></rss>