<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Award on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/award/</link><description>Recent content in Award on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/award/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two JW Marriott hotels have been ranked in the top 10 TripAdvisor Travelers' Choices for Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:58:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Lotte Hotel Seoul.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for hotels in Korea ranked the following as the top ten:
Lotte Hotel Seoul, with a rating of 4.5 out of 5 from 1,849 reviews. The Plaza Conrad Seoul JW Marriott Dongdaemun Square Seoul Park Hyatt Seoul The Shilla Seoul Sheraton Seoul D Cube City Hotel The Westin Chosun Seoul The Ritz-Carlton, Seoul The JW Marriott Seoul Curious?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-jw-marriott-hotels-have-been-ranked-in-the-top-10-tripadvisor-travelers-choices-for-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Mandiri is seeking submissions for the Young Entrepreneur award 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</guid><description>Bank Mandiri, a prominent bank in Indonesia, launched its yearly competition called Mandiri Young Entrepreneur (WMM) in 2015.
Kartika Wirjoatmodjo, the Director of Finance &amp;amp; Strategy at Bank Mandiri, stated that this competition aims to discover young individuals with entrepreneurial potential who can contribute to Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s growth. Kartika added that the competition also intends to inspire a passion for entrepreneurship and innovation among students and graduates, encouraging more young entrepreneurs to emerge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ICSC's Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards honor D-Cube City, Jem, and Siam Center with gold awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 01:47:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</guid><description>The International Council of Shopping Centers (ICSC) Asia Pacific Shopping Center Awards recently celebrated excellence in the region&amp;rsquo;s shopping center industry. Awards recognized outstanding achievements in marketing, retail property design and development, and retail store design.
The Design &amp;amp; Development category acknowledges retail properties for their overall design quality and development creativity, whether through renovation or expansion of an existing property or the innovative design of a new retail project. This category includes both new developments and renovations &amp;amp; expansions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/icsc-s-asia-pacific-shopping-center-awards-honor-d-cube-city-jem-and-siam-center-with-gold-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017 award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</guid><description>Employee engagement at companies recognized as Aon Best Employers rose by two percentage points this year, reaching 82%.
Aon Best Employers are setting the standard for positive employer branding, achieving scores from 83% to 92% in employee perception across all levels of tenure.
Five special recognitions were given this year, including the introduction of a new award category: Best Employer for Startups.
Source: Aon. Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Stevie Awards for Women in Business welcome participants and organizations from all around the globe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 22:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</guid><description>The Stevie Awards, a leading business awards organization, is accepting entries for the 2020 Stevie Awards for Women in Business. This global competition is open to all female entrepreneurs, executives, and employees, as well as the organizations they lead.
The Stevie Awards recognize exceptional workplace achievements worldwide across various organizations. The Stevie Awards for Women in Business specifically honor the accomplishments of working women in over 100 categories, such as Entrepreneur of the Year, Executive of the Year, and Innovator of the Year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-stevie-awards-for-women-in-business-welcome-participants-and-organizations-from-all-around-the-globe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of the FinTech Awards have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and The Association of Banks in Singapore (ABS) awarded S$1.2 million to 12 fintech companies at the FinTech Awards, held during the third annual Singapore FinTech Festival.
This year&amp;rsquo;s winning solutions focused on financial inclusion and represented a broader range of ASEAN countries. These solutions addressed various business areas, including credit scoring, mobile security, anti-money laundering, and digital investment.
Here are the 12 award recipients:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Winners of the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Awards are influential figures in promoting knowledge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 01:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. A representative from the MiSK Foundation receives the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award.
The Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Award recipients, celebrated on November 21st, share a common goal: shaping the future. This award acknowledges those who significantly contribute to the creation and dissemination of knowledge globally.
Among the winners, Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s MiSK Foundation focuses on developing educational institutions and bolstering scientific research...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/winners-of-the-mohammed-bin-rashid-al-maktoum-knowledge-awards-are-influential-figures-in-promoting-knowledge/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kinoya in Dubai has been awarded the One to Watch Award for 2022 by MENA's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Kinoya restaurant has been awarded the One To Watch Award 2022 by Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. This recognition is given to up-and-coming restaurants in the region that have the potential to earn a spot on the 50 Best list in future years.
Kinoya&amp;rsquo;s founder, Neha Mishra, also known as the Ramen Queen, opened the restaurant after the success of her home-based supper club, A Story of Food...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kinoya-in-dubai-has-been-awarded-the-one-to-watch-award-for-2022-by-mena-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The recipients of the MRM Business Award and MRM Business Innovation Award have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. HH Sheikh Ahmed Al Maktoum acknowledged the recipients of the 10th Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (MRM) Business Award and the 2nd MRM Business Innovation Award in Dubai, UAE.
Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, President of Dubai Civil Aviation Authority, as well as Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive of the Emirates Airline &amp;amp; Group, presided over the ceremony, which was held under the patronage of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice-President and Prime Minister of the UAE and Ruler of Dubai, and organized by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EY introduces the Entrepreneur of the Year 2016 award in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 07:54:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, EY has announced the launch of the Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) 2016 award in Saudi Arabia. This year, the EOY will center on medium-sized enterprises, emphasizing their successes and the significance of their expansion and prosperity. The event has been conducted internationally for 29 years in 150 cities across 60 countries.
Ahmed I. Reda, Office Managing Partner at EY, Jeddah, and Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader at EY, states, “As we celebrate the 30th anniversary of the EOY program globally, we are excited to host the Saudi Arabia EOY program again this year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-introduces-the-entrepreneur-of-the-year-2016-award-in-saudi-arabia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt has recognized DBS as one of the top 25 companies in the world for leadership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 13:58:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been acknowledged by Aon Hewitt as one of the top 25 global companies for nurturing leaders. In Aon Hewitt&amp;rsquo;s 2014 ranking, DBS secured the 18th position, making it the highest-ranking Singapore-based organization on the list. Furthermore, DBS was recognized as a leader in Southeast Asia in the 2014 Aon Hewitt Top Companies for Leaders.
Lee Yan Hong, Managing Director of DBS Group Human Resources, emphasized DBS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to developing future leaders...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-has-recognized-dbs-as-one-of-the-top-25-companies-in-the-world-for-leadership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IHH Healthcare, NUS, Otis, and PSA set new standards for leadership and workplace mental health</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</guid><description>WorkWell Leaders (WWL), a Singapore-based non-profit focused on workplace wellbeing and mental health, has revealed the winners of the WorkWell Leaders Awards 2024. These awards acknowledge exemplary practices in promoting positive change within workplaces. WWL emphasized that these awards are unique in their recognition of specific elements of workplace wellbeing that drive business results, as well as leadership behaviors that foster cultural transformation within organizations.
Anthea Ong, Founder and Chairperson of WorkWell Leaders, stressed the importance of addressing mental health proactively in the workplace, stating, &amp;ldquo;With 70% of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s population employed and spending a significant portion of their day at work, workplaces must serve as catalysts to support employees and their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ihh-healthcare-nus-otis-and-psa-set-new-standards-for-leadership-and-workplace-mental-health/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avanade has been recognized as one of the top employers in Malaysia and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</guid><description>Avanade, a company specializing in Microsoft solutions, has received the 2023 Top Employer award in Malaysia and Singapore from the Top Employers Institute.
Source: Avanade. Kapoor.
The Top Employers Institute Programme grants certifications to companies based on their answers and performance on a survey evaluating their Human Resources (HR) practices. Avanade earned recognition for its exceptional practices in all areas reviewed, including People Strategy, Work Environment, Talent Acquisition, Learning, Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion, Wellbeing, and others...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards are now accepting submissions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 06:32:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</guid><description>Source: GCSA organizers. GCSA winners for 2019 at the GCSF in 2019.
If your company demonstrates a strong dedication to sustainability, we encourage you to apply for the 2020 Global Corporate Sustainability Awards (GCSA).
The Alliance for Sustainable Development Goals (A•SDGs) is hosting the 2020 GCSA in collaboration with the Taiwan Academy of Corporate Sustainability (TACS), the Taiwan Institute for Sustainable Energy (TAISE), and the Center for Corporate Sustainability (CCS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2020-global-corporate-sustainability-awards-are-now-accepting-submissions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Entries are now being accepted for the inaugural HUAWEI Film Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</guid><description>Filmmakers in the Asia Pacific region can win prizes for films made on Huawei smartphones.
The top prize includes $20,000 and a trip to Bangkok for the awards ceremony.
An event in Singapore on December 21 will showcase a film by local director Boris Boo.
Source: Huawei. Poster for the HFA.
Huawei has launched its first film awards, the HUAWEI Film Awards (HFA), in the Asia Pacific region. The competition aims to encourage filmmakers and content creators to use Huawei smartphones to demonstrate their creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/entries-are-now-being-accepted-for-the-inaugural-huawei-film-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singapore Computer Society reveals the top 10 tech companies to work for in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</guid><description>The Singapore Computer Society (SCS), the largest professional organization for infocomm and digital media professionals in the country, has revealed the winners of its &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Company to Work For Award&amp;rdquo;. The announcement took place at the SCS&amp;rsquo;s annual Tech3 Forum conference.
This award recognizes four organizations out of the ten &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Companies to Work For&amp;rdquo; as overall winners. These companies have developed innovative practices and demonstrated workplace excellence within the infocomm and digital media (ICM) industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Booking.com has recognized Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments as a top performer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 06:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</guid><description>Flora Creek Deluxe Hotel Apartments, managed by Flora Hospitality Dubai, has received recognition for its exceptional performance based on guest feedback on Booking.com.
Source: Booking.com website. Flora Creek Delluxe Hotel Apartments receives an 8.6 rating from guest reviews.
This award acknowledges the hotel&amp;rsquo;s dedication to outstanding hospitality. The overall scores reflect a blend of factors such as cleanliness, comfort, location, amenities, staff service, value, and the quality of complimentary Wi-Fi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booking-com-has-recognized-flora-creek-deluxe-hotel-apartments-as-a-top-performer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian destinations emerge victorious in the inaugural KAYAK Travel Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 10:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Winners from the first-ever KAYAK Travel Awards.
The travel search engine KAYAK has revealed the winners of its first KAYAK Travel Awards. Sixteen categories, including airlines, airports, hotels, and destinations, were awarded based on public votes collected over 19 days from June 12th to June 30th, 2018.
Singaporean brands dominated the awards. Singapore Airlines received top honors in four categories: Favourite Airline (Short-haul), Favourite Airline (Long-haul), Favourite Airline Crew, and Favourite In-flight F&amp;amp;B...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CHKLC has announced the winners of the 2014 HK Corporate Governance Excellence Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</guid><description>The Chamber of Hong Kong Listed Companies (CHKLC) recently revealed the winners of the Hong Kong Corporate Governance Excellence Awards 2014. The CHKLC defines corporate governance as respecting shareholder rights and values, maintaining board and management integrity, and demonstrating transparency and accountability.
Dr. Eddy Fong, Judging Panel Chairman, highlighted that the awardees went beyond standard practices, tailoring their governance strategies to address industry-specific risks and challenges.
&amp;ldquo;Furthermore,&amp;rdquo; he stated, &amp;ldquo;winning companies view sustainability as inseparable from good corporate governance, crucial for long-term growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chklc-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-2014-hk-corporate-governance-excellence-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Heroes from Asian brands share their brand journey stories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</guid><description>Influential Brands, a program organized by Brand Alliance, held its 2014 conference in Singapore on November 7th. The event, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes,&amp;rdquo; recognized the success of leading brands in the region. Several individuals representing these successful brands participated in a panel discussion, sharing their insights and experiences.
The panel included (from left) moderator Amy Lim, Founder of Brand Alliance; Esther Tang-Loo, Executive Director of Focus Network Agencies; Han Keen Juan, Executive Chairman of Old Chang Kee Group; Debra Soon, Managing Director of Channel NewsAsia; Woon Tai Ho, Director for Media and Marketing at Singapore’s National Art Gallery; Allen Law, Group Chief Executive of Park Hotel Group; and Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS has been honored with the NTUC Women's Development Secretariat SG50 Special Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 12:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</guid><description>DBS Bank has been granted the NTUC Women’s Development Secretariat (WDS) SG50 Special Award as recognition for its committed flexible working program and employee support systems. These programs are designed to assist staff in improving their time management and balancing their work and personal responsibilities.
Cheong Meng Foong, Managing Director of Group Human Resources – Reward, stated that DBS takes a comprehensive approach to create a workplace where employees feel empowered, connected, and valued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-has-been-honored-with-the-ntuc-women-s-development-secretariat-sg50-special-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TaxiPixi app has been awarded the mBillionth Award in South Asia for its taxi booking services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a mobile application for booking taxis, has won the award for best Travel App in South Asia at the 5th annual mBillionth Awards. The app works by connecting customers to taxi drivers from different companies in real time.
The mBillionth Awards recognize exceptional mobile applications and digital material from eight South Asian countries: Afghanistan, Bangladesh, Bhutan, India, the Maldives, Nepal, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka.
Source: TaxiPixi.
“This award boosts our confidence and reaffirms our commitment to providing a comprehensive solution for urban transportation,” said TaxiPixi CEO Kajal Dubey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-taxipixi-app-has-been-awarded-the-mbillionth-award-in-south-asia-for-its-taxi-booking-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Dubai - Al Barsha has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for the fifth year in a row</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 21:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Dubai – Al Barsha has received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence Hall of Fame award. This award recognizes outstanding hospitality businesses that consistently earn high ratings from travelers on TripAdvisor.
The Hall of Fame honors businesses that have earned a Certificate of Excellence for five years in a row. This year, along with the hotel itself, two of its restaurants also received TripAdvisor awards: The Royal Budha, recognized in the category of Fine Dining – Thai, and the Gharana, recognized for Casual Dining – Indian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/holiday-inn-dubai-al-barsha-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-the-fifth-year-in-a-row/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Submit your entries for the Zayed Sustainability Prize now!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 17:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</guid><description>The Zayed Sustainability Prize, a prominent global sustainability award based in the UAE, is calling for submissions for its 13th annual edition. Winners in each category will receive US$600,000 to further develop their sustainability solutions and create global impact.
Dr. Sultan Ahmed Al Jaber, UAE Minister of State and Director General of the Zayed Sustainability Prize, expressed confidence that the Prize will continue to draw in top innovators worldwide, tackling pressing global sustainability issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/submit-your-entries-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt reveals top employers for Singapore and the region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 04:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: Best Employers website.
Aon Hewitt, a global human resources solutions firm, unveiled its list of top employers in Singapore for 2015 on February 27th. Launched in Asia in 2001, Aon Hewitt’s Best Employers study is currently the most thorough of its kind in the Asia Pacific region. Recognition as an Aon Hewitt Best Employer signifies that a company:
1. Cultivates strong employee commitment and top-tier performance;
2. Achieves strong business results through effective human resources strategies; and, 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas in Vietnam have been recognized with accolades from TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas. The master bedroom of an oceanfront three-bedroom villa at Six Senses Con Dao, Vietnam.
TripAdvisor, a leading travel platform, has revealed its highest-rated properties for the fourteenth consecutive year. These rankings are determined by analyzing user reviews and feedback from travelers globally over the past year. Three properties - Evason Ana Mandara, Six Senses Ninh Van Bay, and Six Senses Con Dao - have earned the prestigious Traveler’s Choice award, signifying TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s highest honor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-in-vietnam-have-been-recognized-with-accolades-from-tripadvisor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can enjoy Careem services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 14:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</guid><description>Source: Careem website. Emirates Skywards partners with Careem to provide benefits for their members.
Emirates Skywards, the loyalty program for Emirates, has partnered with Careem. This makes Emirates Skywards the only frequent flyer program to provide both earning and redemption opportunities with the leading car booking app in the region.
Careem is a rapidly growing company, currently operating in nine countries. Members can earn and redeem Skywards Miles when using Careem services in the UAE, Qatar, KSA, Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt, Pakistan, Kuwait, and Morocco...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-enjoy-careem-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of the SME Exporter of the Month award were honored by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently acknowledged member companies for their exceptional export achievements during the first nine months of 2016.
Nine trading companies received recognition at the &amp;ldquo;SME Exporter of the Month&amp;rdquo; ceremony: Universal International, Moon Flor General Trading, Signature Snacks, Al Khoud Trading, Raheeq Alasal Trading, Rais Hassan Saadi Logistics, Orient Links Co, Mohamed Abdulrahman Al Bahar, and Rayhan Al Sharq General Trading.
These companies were celebrated for excelling in categories such as highest export value, most export markets served, highest number of certificates of origin issued, and highest export value achieved by a start-up within a specific month...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-sme-exporter-of-the-month-award-were-honored-by-the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The award ceremony for the Zayed Sustainability Prize 2019 took place</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:25:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</guid><description>Source: PRNewsfoto/Zayed Sustainability Prize. The 2019 Zayed Sustainability Prize ceremony took place during Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week (ADSW). His Highness Sheikh Mohamed presented awards to 10 winners across categories such as Health, Food, Energy, Water, and Global High Schools. The ceremony was attended by prominent figures including HH Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of Abu Dhabi Executive Council; HH Lt General Sheikh Saif bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of the Interior; HH Sheikh Mansour bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy PM and Minister of Presidential Affairs; HH Sheikh Hamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Chief of the Abu Dhabi Crown Prince&amp;rsquo;s Court; and HH Sheikh Omar bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of the Board of Trustees of Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan Charitable and Humanitarian Foundation; Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan, Minister of Tolerance; and other high-ranking ministers and officials...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>