<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>United Nations on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/united-nations/</link><description>Recent content in United Nations on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/united-nations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cracks in the unity of EU representation are evident in the Global Compact for Migration.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 04:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cracks-in-the-unity-of-eu-representation-are-evident-in-the-global-compact-for-migration/</guid><description>Pauline Melin, PhD, Lecturer in European Law (Maastricht University) and Researcher at the Institute for European Law (KULeuven)
The UN Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration is scheduled for approval at a conference in Marrakesh, aiming for adoption as a UN General Assembly Resolution in New York on December 19th, 2018. However, the political climate surrounding the Compact&amp;rsquo;s adoption has become contentious. Since Austria, an active participant in the negotiations, withdrew its support in late October 2018, multiple EU Member States have followed suit, publicly questioning or withdrawing their support every week.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Be Part Of The Impending Worldwide E-Waste Crisis</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-be-part-of-the-impending-worldwide-e-waste-crisis/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common knowledge that discarding old electronics with regular trash is inappropriate. Many stores provide drop-off boxes for unwanted electronics like phones and batteries, and communities often organize special recycling events. Selling old electronics is also a viable option. Why then is the United Nations issuing warnings about an impending e-waste crisis?
This looming threat stems from the rapid development in nations like China, India, Africa, and Latin America, coupled with existing patterns in developed nations like the U.</description></item></channel></rss>