<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Airport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airport/</link><description>Recent content in Airport on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Changi Airport Group announces the closure of Terminal 2 for a period of 18 months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Changi Airport.
Due to a significant decrease in air travel and the low likelihood of a return to pre-pandemic levels soon, Changi Airport Group (CAG) has decided to consolidate operations at Changi Airport. This move aims to reduce operating costs like utilities and cleaning for CAG and its partners while optimizing resource allocation across the airport&amp;rsquo;s terminals.
Starting May 1, 2020, Terminal 2 (T2) will halt operations for 18 months, relocating airlines to other terminals*.</description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia).</description></item><item><title>The groundbreaking ceremony for Jewel has been successfully completed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-groundbreaking-ceremony-for-jewel-has-been-successfully-completed/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Changi Airport.
Jewel Changi Airport Trustee (JCAT), a collaboration between Changi Airport Group (CAG) and CapitaMalls Asia (the shopping mall branch of CapitaLand), has initiated the construction of Jewel Changi Airport. This mixed-use development, situated in front of Terminal 1 (T1), will feature attractions, retail spaces, a hotel, and airport operational facilities.
Strategically placed at the airport&amp;rsquo;s core, Jewel aims to be a premier lifestyle destination enhancing Changi Airport&amp;rsquo;s global standing and solidifying Singapore&amp;rsquo;s attractiveness as a layover spot for travelers.</description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing.</description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport consolidates early check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Travelers departing from Singapore have increased access to early check-in services for various airlines at Changi Airport. Since the beginning of the year, shared early check-in counters have been established in Terminals 2 and 3. Terminal 1 features a dedicated early check-in lounge for added convenience.
Operational from 6 am to midnight, the counters and lounge offer a centralized service point for passengers flying with 23 participating airlines.</description></item><item><title>Hamad International Airport introduces two innovative dining experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 13:07:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Spizzico is one of two new dining establishments in the North Node at Hamad International Airport.
Qatar Duty Free (QDF), working with global travel dining provider HMSHost International, has revealed two new dining options in the North Node of Hamad International Airport (HIA) in Doha.
Burger Federation, a relaxed dining spot, has opened in the North Node of HIA&amp;rsquo;s main terminal. This restaurant presents elevated burgers made with gourmet ingredients.</description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks.</description></item><item><title>Changi Airport introduces a new reward for the Be a Changi Millionaire campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 03:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-introduces-a-new-reward-for-the-be-a-changi-millionaire-campaign/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. This year&amp;rsquo;s Be a Changi Millionaire competition offers a chance to win a Volvo sedan as well.
Changi Airport has enhanced its well-known *Be a Changi Millionaire*_ retail promotion this year by adding a new prize: a Volvo S90 T5 luxury sedan. This is in addition to the existing S$1 million cash prize. According to Changi Airport, this is the largest retail promotion at any airport globally.</description></item><item><title>The First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport Terminal 1 has been reopened by Etihad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 10:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-and-business-class-lounge-at-abu-dhabi-airport-terminal-1-has-been-reopened-by-etihad/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has officially reopened its First and Business Class Lounge at Abu Dhabi Airport’s Terminal 1 after a complete renovation.
The improved lounge, open around the clock, spans over 1,044 square meters and can accommodate 134 guests. This updated space in Terminal 1 provides a variety of amenities to meet the needs of modern business and leisure travelers. Mirroring the lounge in Terminal 3, the refurbished facility features comfortable seating, a designated dining area, modern business facilities, complimentary Wi-Fi, USB charging ports, restrooms with shower facilities, and a children&amp;rsquo;s play area.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport reveals its fresh new appearance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 03:48:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-reveals-its-fresh-new-appearance/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has finished renovations, adding new rooms, a new Italian restaurant called Allora, another function room, an updated Club Lounge, and a revitalized fitness center.
The new design creates a calming oceanic atmosphere. Natural wood finishes on the furniture bring a feeling of warmth and comfort. This is enhanced by a color scheme of beach tones and ocean shades. Light gray couches, navy blue, and yellow accents contribute to a modern and welcoming feel.</description></item><item><title>Hotels.com provides exclusive information on transportation options to and from the airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotels-com-provides-exclusive-information-on-transportation-options-to-and-from-the-airport/</guid><description>Hotels.com, a website for booking accommodations online, has put together an insider&amp;rsquo;s guide on the top transportation choices from 29 major airports globally. This guide, called the Hotels.com Airport Transportation Insider, compares taxis, private cars, and public transportation in popular international and domestic destinations using data from the recent Hotel Price Index™. Although it&amp;rsquo;s geared towards US travelers, the infographic provides helpful information for cities like Bangkok, Beijing, Singapore, and Sydney.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers.</description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight.</description></item><item><title>An open house event was held at Changi Airport's fourth terminal before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-house-event-was-held-at-changi-airport-s-fourth-terminal-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: CAG. CAG organises open house for Changi T4.
The Changi Airport Group (CAG) has invited Singapore residents to preview Terminal 4 (T4) before its official opening. From August 7th to 20th, 2017, the public can attend an Open House for a sneak peek of the new terminal.
Construction on the 195,000 square meter, two-story T4 began in early 2013 and finished in December 2016. Though only half the size of Terminal 3 (T3), it can accommodate 16 million passengers annually, roughly 70% of T3&amp;rsquo;s capacity.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport is offering mooncakes in a suitcase</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has launched its 2016 mooncake collection, featuring classic baked and contemporary snowskin varieties. These halal-certified treats are packaged in a stylish metal suitcase, making them a great gift for colleagues or loved ones.
For those who prefer a traditional taste, baked mooncakes are available in three flavors: White Lotus Paste with Double Egg Yolk, White Lotus Paste with Single Egg Yolk, and White Lotus Paste with Melon Seeds.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia has relocated its Surabaya operations to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-has-relocated-its-surabaya-operations-to-the-new-terminal-2-at-juanda/</guid><description>AirAsia has relocated its operations from Terminal 1 to the new Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport.
All AirAsia domestic and international flights to and from Surabaya will keep their original schedules and operate as usual.
Terminal 2 at Juanda International Airport opened on February 14th. The terminal is designed to be environmentally friendly and can accommodate 6 million passengers annually. It features 40 check-in counters, an updated baggage handling system, six gates for domestic use, three gates for international flights, 12 avirobridges, and 14 parking stands for both narrow and wide-bodied aircraft.</description></item><item><title>Changi Terminal 3 reveals its new Central Piazza</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. The newly opened Central Piazza at Changi Airport Terminal 3 features a Louis Vuitton duplex store and a dandelion-themed Crystal Garden.
Travelers passing through Changi Airport Terminal 3&amp;rsquo;s Transit Hall can now enjoy the revitalized Central Piazza. This area showcases the airport&amp;rsquo;s seventh featured garden, the Crystal Garden, composed of glass dandelion sculptures.
The Crystal Garden features a multi-level garden design with carefully chosen flowering plants and twelve handcrafted glass dandelion sculptures of different sizes.</description></item></channel></rss>