<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SN1312615 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sn1312615/</link><description>Recent content in SN1312615 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sn1312615/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Beogram 4002 Bonanza!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:24:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-beogram-4002-bonanza-/</guid><description>We seem to be inundated with Beogram 400x turntable restorations.
Beolover is occupied with multiple projects, and I have two Beogram 4002 Type 5513 projects that I began examining back in February of 2020. In those previous posts, I had sent four Beogram 400x platter motors to Beolover for his restoration expertise. He has since completed those motors, and they are now back in my possession, ready to be used.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Adjusting/Calibrating the Detector Arm Circuit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-adjustingcalibrating-the-detector-arm-circuit/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 turntable is nearly ready for use, with most of the necessary adjustments and calibrations finalized.
As planned, the record detection circuit needed adjustment due to a low measurement. Utilizing insights from Beolover&amp;rsquo;s blog post on the Beogram 4002 record detection circuit, the circuit was calibrated to align with the service manual&amp;rsquo;s specifications.
Two components on the main board, 1R26 (a 1MΩ resistor) and 1TR3 (an NPN BC548C transistor), are key in fine-tuning the signal from the record detection circuit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Initial Assessment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 01:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-initial-assessment/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, dropped off by its long-time owner, appears to have been well-maintained.
The control panel buttons show typical wear from use, but the dust cover is in good condition with only minor marks. The tonearm requires adjustment as it sits too low when the turntable is not in use.
The turntable&amp;rsquo;s interior is very clean, suggesting it was kept in a good environment.
The original washers for the floating suspension lock-down are intact.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reinstalling the Floating Chassis Components</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</guid><description>All the necessary restoration parts for the Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable are now available, marking the start of the reassembly process.
The reinstallation begins with securing the floating chassis, equipped with the tangential arm assembly, back into the Beogram 4002 cabinet. The process starts by fitting the Beolover replacement suspension lock bushings onto the floating chassis. Subsequently, the suspension locks are positioned within the cabinet base. The floating chassis is then carefully lowered onto these locking bolts, and the remaining locking mechanisms are put in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Recapping the main controller board and the output board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-recapping-the-main-controller-board-and-the-output-board/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:42:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-recapping-the-main-controller-board-and-the-output-board/</guid><description>The main controller and output boards have had their capacitors successfully replaced.
In addition to replacing the electrolytic and tantalum capacitors on the main controller board, the RPM selection relay and both RPM adjustment trimmers were also replaced.
[Image of speed components on the main controller board]
This image highlights two components within the main controller board&amp;rsquo;s record detection circuit that might require further attention and modification. A determination on whether these components need changing will be made after evaluating all the Beogram 4002 photo sensors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Installing Beolover RPM Indicators, Rechecking Platter Speed, Beginning the Reassembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-installing-beolover-rpm-indicators-rechecking-platter-speed-beginning-the-reassembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 07:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-installing-beolover-rpm-indicators-rechecking-platter-speed-beginning-the-reassembly/</guid><description>I replaced the RPM indicator lamps in my Beogram 400x turntable with LED modules from Beolover. This upgrade, motivated by the LEDs&amp;rsquo; stability rather than longevity, aims to enhance platter motor speed stability, a known benefit observed in Beolover&amp;rsquo;s motor restorations. The interconnectedness of the RPM lamps and the platter motor circuit underscores their impact on performance.
The original incandescent lamps were removed from the Beogram 4002 Type 5513 RPM Indicator Panel and replaced with the Beolover LED modules, which were secured and insulated using the provided double-sided mounting tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going Through the Service Manual Checks and Adjustments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-through-the-service-manual-checks-and-adjustments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 11:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-through-the-service-manual-checks-and-adjustments/</guid><description>This past weekend, I began working on some of the checks and adjustments outlined in the Beogram 4002 service manual. The manual details both electrical and mechanical procedures.
On the electrical side, my primary focus is to ensure that the photo sensors generate strong signals when activated by their light sources. Maintaining correct voltages is crucial for the proper function of the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s analog control system.
Mechanically, I&amp;rsquo;ll be aligning both the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s fixed arm and tonearm.</description></item></channel></rss>