<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fraud on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fraud/</link><description>Recent content in Fraud on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fraud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India no longer accepts high denomination notes in the current series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Reserve Bank (RBI) has decided to discontinue the use of 500 and 1,000 rupee notes. These notes ceased to be legal tender as of November 9, 2016. Consequently, ATMs and other cash transaction machines were shut down on November 9 and 10. However, bank branches and government treasuries remained open on November 10.
This move was prompted by the difficulty in differentiating real banknotes from counterfeit ones. The surge in fake currency was negatively impacting the Indian economy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU bolsters criminal law protection of the EU's finances in The Italian Job.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Contrary to popular belief, fraud against the EU budget is not typically committed by corrupt EU officials. As per EU reports, the usual culprits are individuals or companies exploiting EU funds managed by Member States. These violations also extend beyond spending to include EU income reduction, such as evading customs duties on imports.
Establishing and upholding EU-wide regulations for such misconduct has been challenging. However, the Court of Justice (CJEU) significantly strengthened the law in this area with its recent Taricco judgment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies in the Asia Pacific region anticipate an increase in fraud over the next five years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 20:24:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</guid><description>A new report by Experian Asia Pacific, titled &amp;ldquo;The Economics of Fraud: Mitigating Risk Amidst Fast Growth and Innovation,&amp;rdquo; found that 59% of Asia Pacific businesses anticipate an increase in fraud over the next five years. This has led to more than half (51%) of these businesses investing more in fraud prevention.
The report, which explores the current fraud landscape for businesses in Asia Pacific, reveals some key findings about fast-growing markets:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-in-the-asia-pacific-region-anticipate-an-increase-in-fraud-over-the-next-five-years/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Public Prosecutor’s Office and Fundamental Rights: A Disquieting Lack of Discussion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</guid><description>Michiel Luchtman, Jannemieke Ouwerkerk, Marloes van Noorloos, Pim Geelhoed, Jorrit Rijpma, and Louis Middelkoop are affiliated with the Meijers Committee (www.commissie-meijers.nl/en).
The EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed European Public Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office (EPPO) has sparked significant debate among Member States. The EPPO&amp;rsquo;s role would be to investigate and prosecute fraudulent use of EU funds, with discussions already underway to expand its jurisdiction to include terrorism and other serious crimes. Current political dialogue centers around the necessity of this supranational entity and the potential impact on national sovereignty, particularly within the sensitive realm of criminal justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fake clicks and pageviews can artificially boost digital marketing metrics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve invested in online ads on a platform known for its excellent results, and you&amp;rsquo;re seeing those clicks increase week after week. People are clearly interested enough to visit your store locations, but actual sales remain stagnant. So, what&amp;rsquo;s the deal?
This could be a sign of ad fraud, and not necessarily originating from the platform itself.
The Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB), based in the US, emphasizes the need for greater awareness surrounding non-intentional traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fake-clicks-and-pageviews-can-artificially-boost-digital-marketing-metrics/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>