<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ippbx on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ippbx/</link><description>Recent content in Ippbx on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 03:53:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ippbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Virtual Hosted PBX VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 03:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-hosted-pbx-voip/</guid><description>There are many ways to implement VoIP, with some methods being more effective than others. Your goal with VoIP is likely to reduce expenses and access enhanced features while maintaining high-quality voice communication.
Achieving this balance is possible with the right technology, though proper setup can be challenging. Getting assistance with the installation, specifically by outsourcing complex aspects to a specialized provider, can greatly increase your chances of a smooth implementation.</description></item><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls.</description></item><item><title>XO Launches SIP for Multi-Location Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-launches-sip-for-multi-location-businesses/</guid><description>XO Communications, a large telecommunications company, has introduced a new solution that allows businesses with numerous locations to take advantage of enterprise VoIP technology.
Connecting business locations to a phone service provider through SIP trunking is a well-established method for improving network performance and saving money. XO is building on this concept with a multi-site SIP trunking solution. Instead of requiring each location to connect to a remote service provider separately, branch offices, warehouses, and other locations can now use their existing Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect SIP phones back to a central IP-PBX system at the main office.</description></item></channel></rss>