<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Meal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/meal/</link><description>Recent content in Meal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/meal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AquaMarine in Singapore offers a selection of nutritious buffet options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 00:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</guid><description>Source: Marina Mandarin by Meritus.
This April, AquaMarine, the restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s luxurious 5-star Marina Mandarin hotel, is putting a spotlight on healthy dining. Their halal-certified buffet features a variety of fresh, organic ingredients.
Through the end of April, AquaMarine diners can enjoy live cooking stations, fresh seafood, Singaporean favorites, and international dishes, all prepared with a healthy approach. For instance, the popular chicken rice at the Chinese live station is served with brown rice, and wholewheat flour is used for pasta and tortillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aquamarine-in-singapore-offers-a-selection-of-nutritious-buffet-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Coral Al Khobar will be featuring a selection of dishes from the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions for iftar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 04:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</guid><description>The Coral Al Khobar Hotel, centrally located in the city, is a perfect venue for enjoying an iftar buffet with loved ones. A diverse menu of Arabic and Mediterranean delicacies will be offered for the suhoor buffet, served from midnight to 3 am.
The buffet will showcase a wide array of hot and cold dishes representing the cuisines of the GCC, Levant, and Maghreb regions. Michel Mandrea, the General Manager of Coral Al Khobar Hotel, highlighted the culinary team&amp;rsquo;s efforts, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our chefs have meticulously crafted the iftar and suhoor buffet menus to cater to every palate, including popular desserts traditionally enjoyed during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coral-al-khobar-will-be-featuring-a-selection-of-dishes-from-the-gcc-levant-and-maghreb-regions-for-iftar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with Amara Sanctuary Singapore's special promotion!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa. Singapore laksa.
To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 53rd birthday, the 5-star Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is offering a National Day special at their Shutters restaurant.
During this National Day celebration, Shutters&amp;rsquo; dinner guests will enjoy a discounted Singapura buffet, priced at S$53++ per adult, down from the usual S$75++. This offer is valid from 6:30 pm to 10:00 pm. The buffet features local favorites like Nyonya laksa, barbequed stingray, and charcoal-grilled satay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai introduces special Eid packages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</guid><description>The Grand Millennium Hotel Dubai has revealed its plans for a lavish Eid celebration, including a grand feast and special offers throughout the holiday.
The Atrium restaurant will host an Eid Lunch Buffet, priced at AED150 per person. Guests can enjoy signature dishes representing various Arab regions, live cooking stations, and international favorites. Peter Mansourian, General Manager of Grand Millennium Dubai, highlighted the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s reputation for exceptional cuisine, stating, &amp;ldquo;The Atrium enjoys the status of an exclusive restaurant for those willing to reward themselves with outstanding culinary fare as the outlet consistently delivers quality dishes in a familiar environment, with a team of dedicated staff to pamper and make you feel at home...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-millennium-hotel-dubai-introduces-special-eid-packages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sparkle under the moonlight during an afternoon tea in Hong Kong this September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</guid><description>Source: The Langham, Hong Kong. The Twinkle in the Moonlight Afternoon Tea set.
The Langham Hotel in Hong Kong is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with a special afternoon tea inspired by Eastern flavors.
Offered throughout September at the hotel&amp;rsquo;s Palm Court restaurant, the menu, created by Executive Pastry Chef David Puig, features treats like &amp;ldquo;The Moon,&amp;rdquo; a lychee and raspberry mousse cake decorated with a galaxy glaze. This dessert also includes rose essence, Sacher sponge cake, and a golden crescent moon topping...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sparkle-under-the-moonlight-during-an-afternoon-tea-in-hong-kong-this-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>NOBU presents Harvest in Aomori at InterContinental Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hong Kong. Steamed abalone, sea urchin shijimi dashi jelly, and cured mackerel sashimi with chrysanthemum dressing.
NOBU InterContinental Hong Kong presents the fifth installment of its GOURMET TOUR OF JAPAN series – Harvest in Aomori – which runs from September 12th to October 22nd.
Executive Chef Sean Mell and Executive Sushi Chef Arakai Kaazunari have crafted special lunch and dinner menus that showcase the fall bounty of Aomori Prefecture, a region in northern Japan&amp;rsquo;s Tōhoku region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GwaKu offers tasty and budget-friendly dishes in the center of Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>Source: Gwaku&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This is their famous ayam percik.
GwaKu, a restaurant situated in Q Sentral close to KL Sentral, offers a rotating menu that keeps nearby office workers surprised about their lunch options. For example, one week could feature ayam perchik, while the following week might offer lamb stews.
Mike Ibrahim, the founder of GwaKu, emphasizes their commitment to using fresh, seasonal, and locally sourced ingredients. He explains, &amp;ldquo;By using in-season produce, we can ensure quality and freshness while also benefiting from lower prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KLGCC will be hosting a dinner buffet during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 20:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Last year&amp;rsquo;s Ramadan dinner buffet at the Kuala Lumpur Golf and Country Club (KLGCC) was very successful. The culinary team is bringing it back this year with a Selera Nostalgia theme.
The Selera Nostalgia buffet will feature dishes from over 100 cuisines. It will be set up in an open-air, stall-style setting by the pool and will include live cooking and performances. Some menu highlights, prepared by approximately 60 chefs, include nasi Arab, tom yam nelayan, kambing panggang, various pizzas and pastas, and local favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/klgcc-will-be-hosting-a-dinner-buffet-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the enchanting Arabian nights under the stars at the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar until July 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</guid><description>From June 21st to July 16th, 2015, the Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar is excited to present a delectable Ramadhan buffet. The culinary team at LINK All Day Dining has crafted a special &amp;ldquo;Starry Arabian Nights&amp;rdquo; themed dinner, featuring a wide selection of traditional Arab and Malay dishes. The restaurant will be adorned with exotic, Arabian-inspired starry lights, and live ‘ghazal’ performances will entertain guests throughout their meal.
Source: Pullman Kuala Lumpur Bangsar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-enchanting-arabian-nights-under-the-stars-at-the-pullman-kuala-lumpur-bangsar-until-july-16th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AFOCH invites businesses to gather for iftar during Ramadan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</guid><description>Source: AFOCH website.
The Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel (AFOCH) in Abu Dhabi is hosting Iftar celebrations ideal for gatherings with business associates.
Peter Freeman, the Deputy Director General of the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, highlighted that the hotel&amp;rsquo;s leading chefs will once again prepare a grand Iftar buffet. The buffet will feature exquisite Arabic delicacies alongside international dishes.
&amp;ldquo;Here at the Armed Forces Officers Club &amp;amp; Hotel, we provide the most authentic Arabic cuisine, meticulously crafted with the freshest ingredients by our highly skilled culinary team,&amp;rdquo; Freeman stated...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/afoch-invites-businesses-to-gather-for-iftar-during-ramadan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FUMI creates authentic Japanese dining experiences for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</guid><description>Source: FUMI Facebook page. FUMI sushi.
FUMI, a new Japanese eatery, seeks to share the finest Japanese cuisine in Hong Kong within a space adorned with Japanese art, furnishings, and tableware. They offer a range of dining experiences, from elaborate omakase and kaiseki dinners to individual dishes and set lunch options.
Situated in California Tower, FUMI sources the highest quality seasonal ingredients directly from Japan daily. Flown in and delivered straight to their kitchen, these ingredients are often prepared and served within hours of being harvested, guaranteeing freshness in their sushi, sashimi, omakase, and kaiseki preparations, as well as a variety of seasonal menus...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the Peranakan Food Festival at Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>The Peranakan* Food Festival is making a comeback at the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy! The hotel is bringing back this popular food festival with new additions to the menu, such as ayam masak rebung lemak (chicken with bamboo shoots in spicy gravy). Returning favorites include bubur cha cha (tapioca in coconut milk) and much more.
Guests can explore booths showcasing Peranakan heritage at the Feast@East Buffet Restaurant.
From June 10th to 19th, enjoy a variety of seafood at Feast@East Buffet Restaurant, featuring Chilean blue mussels, spanner crabs, and other crustacean favorites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the Peranakan culture at your upcoming high tea event</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-culture-at-your-upcoming-high-tea-event/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 10:22:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-culture-at-your-upcoming-high-tea-event/</guid><description>Indulge in Peranakan sweets with the &amp;ldquo;Pay 1 Dine 2 Afternoon High Tea&amp;rdquo; at Hari&amp;rsquo;s Bar Lobby &amp;amp; Lounge.
Source: Holiday Inn Singapore Orchard City Centre. Pink kuih lapis is on the menu at the &amp;ldquo;Nyonya Delights Pay 1 Dine 2 High Tea.&amp;rdquo;
The updated dessert selection showcases authentic Peranakan treats. Try the kuih lapis, a multi-colored steamed cake made from layers of soft rice flour pudding. Another popular choice is the ang ku kueh, a red tortoise cake...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-culture-at-your-upcoming-high-tea-event/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-culture-at-your-upcoming-high-tea-event/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iftar gatherings at AquaMarine, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 03:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</guid><description>Originally from the Marina Mandarin Singapore website, this photo displays the Bakar Station&amp;rsquo;s offerings of chicken, oxtail, prawns, and sea bass cooked in banana leaves.
AquaMarine, a Halal-certified buffet restaurant, has recently renovated its Terrace@AquaMarine space. Now fully air-conditioned, it&amp;rsquo;s an ideal location for larger gatherings.
The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s current iftar menu, available until July 17th, features dishes like dates, slow-roasted baby lamb seasoned with Moroccan spices, bulgur wheat with raita, and a traditional Indonesian oxtail soup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iftar-gatherings-at-aquamarine-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>During this Ramadan, the Corp Amman will offer Iftar dining and entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Corp Amman Hotel website.
The 4-star Corp Amman Hotel has put together a special offering for iftar and suhoor during Ramadan, showcasing traditional Jordanian hospitality. Guests can enjoy evenings filled with food and music for JD18 per person, not including services and taxes.
The celebration starts with an iftar menu at the Boulevard Restaurant &amp;amp; Poolside Terrace, available all day. The menu features Ramadan favorites such as juices, dried fruits, Arabic breads, soups, salads, pickles, and mezze...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-this-ramadan-the-corp-amman-will-offer-iftar-dining-and-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay to celebrate F1 with special meal promotions and parties at Attica</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 18:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay website.
Clarke Quay is celebrating the Singapore Grand Prix season with special offers and events for both racing fans and those just looking to enjoy the festivities.
Everyone can take advantage of dining deals like buy-one-get-one-free offers at District 10, special Grand Prix menu items at Hooters, and a free meal for every four diners at Peony Jade.
Those with Grand Prix tickets can also enjoy discounts of 10% to 20% at participating restaurants...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Big Street set meals provide even greater value for your money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</guid><description>Source: Big Street.
The Singaporean eatery Big Street is offering a special multi-course meal for S$26 per person during June. This offer requires a minimum of two diners and is valid for both lunch and dinner.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the special meal includes:
Appetiser: Garden greens with cherry tomato salad Soup: Oriental chicken with snow fungus and wolfberry soup Main dishes: Hainanese steamed kampong chicken Seasonal vegetables with mushrooms Big Street chili king prawn Thai fragrant steamed rice If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something else, Big Street&amp;rsquo;s standard set lunch costs S$9...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>May's Big Street meal promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Big Street. Chilli slipper lobster in prata bag.
Big Street, a restaurant and lounge with air conditioning and multiple levels, is offering a special set meal deal throughout May in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day, available to everyone.
Priced at S$26 per person (minimum of two people), this deal includes an appetizer, soup, main course, and dessert.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the set meal promotion includes:
Appetiser: Fresh garden salad served with crispy chicken..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>