<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Commerce on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-commerce/</link><description>Recent content in E-Commerce on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-commerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HOTPING's international sales reach 100 million won</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</guid><description>Source: HOTPING website.
Pants with high elasticity.
HOTPING, a Korean online clothing retailer specializing in women&amp;rsquo;s apparel, expanded globally in July 2015. Since then, their international sales have consistently surpassed 100 million won each month, accounting for 10% of their total revenue.
CEO Kim Yeo-jin attributes this success to their early focus on international expansion. Shortly after launching in 2014, they introduced English, Chinese, and Japanese versions of their online store through the global e-commerce platform cafe24...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotping-s-international-sales-reach-100-million-won/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Success in business relies on establishing a broad network, having a strong passion, dedicating time, and learning from numerous failures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 03:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</guid><description>Alex Foo, co-founder of the entrepreneur-focused psychometric profiling tool Starteur, offers three key tips for entrepreneurial success. These insights, derived from both his attendance at the Global Entrepreneurship Summit 2016 (June 22-24, USA) and his personal journey as a young entrepreneur, were shared during a Shopee University session. Foo&amp;rsquo;s trip to GES 2016 was sponsored by Shopee, the e-commerce platform by Garena. This sponsorship reflects Shopee&amp;rsquo;s commitment to nurturing the next generation of Singaporean entrepreneurs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/success-in-business-relies-on-establishing-a-broad-network-having-a-strong-passion-dedicating-time-and-learning-from-numerous-failures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon has introduced exclusive holiday offers for Prime Now members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</guid><description>This holiday season, Amazon Prime members in Singapore can enjoy thousands of deals on local and international products through the Prime Now app. These deals cover a wide range of categories, from toys and electronics to beauty products and holiday essentials.
Since its launch, Prime Now has expanded its offerings to include new brands like Yakult, Dell, Tefal, Sambucol, Bausch &amp;amp; Lomb, and Pinkfong. New categories such as fresh flowers, organic fruits (including durians), and international foods have also been added...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-has-introduced-exclusive-holiday-offers-for-prime-now-members/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The best beauty products chosen by Shopee Malaysia for the month of July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 00:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</guid><description>Shopee, a Southeast Asia-focused mobile marketplace designed for simple and secure online buying and selling, monitors top-selling items across various categories. Here are some of the best-selling beauty products on Shopee Malaysia during July:
Source: Shopee Malaysia portal. Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream.
Cloud 9 Blanc de Whitening Cream
According to its Shopee description, this cream is enriched with natural organic herbs to provide an immediate whitening effect that can last up to 12 hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-best-beauty-products-chosen-by-shopee-malaysia-for-the-month-of-july/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai Chamber partners with Souq.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry and Souq.com, the leading online retail and marketplace platform in the Middle East, have partnered to boost Chamber members’ participation in regional e-commerce.
The agreement grants Dubai Chamber members exclusive benefits from Souq.com, including complimentary access to its Fulfilled by SOUQ services for three months and specialized onboarding training. These benefits also encompass enhanced search visibility, customer support, and promotional opportunities.
In turn, Souq...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-chamber-partners-with-souq-com/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia's MyCyberSale provides discounts of up to 90%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 07:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</guid><description>Source: Shopee. Part of a banner for MyCyberSale.
During Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;MyCyberSale,&amp;rdquo; which ends September 30th, shoppers on Shopee have a chance to win an iPhone 7 and other prizes. Free shipping is also offered during this period.
Featured sale items include:
Jabra SPORT CORDED Stereo Headset This black, waterproof headset is designed for athletic individuals. Offered by Jabra Malaysia, this headset comes with a two-year warranty. Shopee is offering a 69% discount on this product...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-s-mycybersale-provides-discounts-of-up-to-90/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You Can Afford a Content Delivery Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The internet is great for communication, allowing businesses to connect with anyone globally at a low cost and creating countless opportunities. However, this popularity has led to congestion, potentially slowing down websites.
You can work around this issue without sacrificing connectivity. Large content providers use Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) to bypass internet congestion. CDNs don&amp;rsquo;t connect directly to users but deliver content through servers near service providers, resulting in faster speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-afford-a-content-delivery-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Viva La Fleur has launched online sales of its durable, all-natural floral arrangements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</guid><description>Since its establishment in October 2013, Viva La Fleur Floral Boutique has impressed businesses with its enduring, all-natural floral arrangements and bouquets. The company holds the exclusive distribution rights for LavieFlo, a technology that makes flowers appear freshly cut for months, eliminating the need for water or sunlight.
Sourced globally, fresh flowers from countries like Japan and China undergo a meticulous preservation process. This process substitutes the plant&amp;rsquo;s sap with a solution that retains the natural appearance and texture of the petals and leaves...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viva-la-fleur-has-launched-online-sales-of-its-durable-all-natural-floral-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Today marks the return of Amazon's Prime Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/</guid><description>Amazon.sg is holding its first-ever Prime Day event in Singapore on October 26 and 27, 2020, shortly after the company&amp;rsquo;s first anniversary in the country on October 8, 2020.
This event is predicted to drive substantial sales for both Amazon and its retail competitors, marking an unofficial start to the holiday shopping period.
The changes in shopping habits this year, with many consumers reducing physical store visits, are anticipated to result in a boost in online revenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/today-marks-the-return-of-amazon-s-prime-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is launching the 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day in September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</guid><description>Source: Shopee website. The countdown begins 1 September.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace owned by Garena Interactive Holding, is launching its first-ever 9.9 Mobile Shopping Day. This one-day event will take place on September 9th and offer shoppers a mobile shopping experience.
The event is anticipated to be the largest mobile shopping sale in the region. Shoppers in Singapore can expect 24 hours of continuous deals and promotions. These include discounts of up to 90%, a selection of items under S$0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-launching-the-9-9-mobile-shopping-day-in-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo emphasizes that e-commerce must be integrated into the retail strategy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, predicts that mobile will play an even greater role in the e-commerce industry this quarter.
Eric Eichmann, President and COO of Criteo, believes that 2015 will be a year of significant change for e-commerce as consumer online shopping habits continue to evolve rapidly. The increased use of multiple devices presents a challenge for marketers targeting consumers. Eichmann suggests that advertisers who adapt quickly by investing wisely in solutions such as cross-device targeting and mobile-optimized websites and apps will be best equipped to meet consumer demand and boost sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-emphasizes-that-e-commerce-must-be-integrated-into-the-retail-strategy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aramex logistics support is available to Shopmatic merchants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 23:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</guid><description>Shopmatic, a Singapore-based e-commerce software as a service (SaaS) provider, has partnered with Aramex, a global logistics and transportation company. This partnership aims to provide online merchants with efficient and secure delivery options.
Shopmatic offers a comprehensive, commission-free e-commerce platform for businesses to establish and manage their online presence. By integrating with Aramex&amp;rsquo;s services, Shopmatic strengthens its position as a one-stop solution for anyone looking to sell online.
Anurag Avula, CEO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Shopmatic Group, highlights the significant growth potential of online shopping in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-logistics-support-is-available-to-shopmatic-merchants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become one of the top 10 e-marketplaces worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 04:46:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Aladdin Group. A lion dance to welcome Aladdin
Street Singapore.
The Aladdin Group is launching Aladdin Street Singapore, an e-commerce platform serving both businesses and individual consumers. It will operate through two websites: a Singapore-specific site at www.aladdinstreet.com.sg, and an international platform at www.aladdinstreet.com. Both sites are expected to launch in the fourth quarter of 2016.
Aladdinstreet&amp;rsquo;s goal is to be a reliable and secure online marketplace for merchants to sell and consumers to buy premium, halal products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-one-of-the-top-10-e-marketplaces-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carly users now have the ability to post on Carousell as well</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 21:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</guid><description>Carousell, a popular online classifieds platform, has acquired Caarly, a Singapore-based startup, as part of its strategy to dominate the classifieds market.
Caarly is a mobile-first tool designed to simplify inventory management for used car dealerships. Since launching in Singapore in 2014, Caarly has partnered with over 200 car dealerships, representing a large portion of the market in Singapore. Existing Caarly partners can continue managing their inventory on the Caarly platform and seamlessly cross-post their listings to the cars category on Carousell with just one click...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carly-users-now-have-the-ability-to-post-on-carousell-as-well/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The e-marketplace is focused on small and medium-sized retailers in Java</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 11:53:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</guid><description>Since its launch, Ula, a marketplace app revolutionizing distribution and credit for traditional retail, has experienced a tenfold growth. Customers are returning to make purchases up to three times their original volume.
Ula emphasizes its success by pointing out that despite the challenges of COVID-19, stores made more purchases in May than ever before.
Launched in January 2020 and headquartered in Jakarta, Indonesia, Ula is a multi-category wholesale e-commerce marketplace that blends the technology and tools of modern retail with the cost-effectiveness of traditional micro-retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-e-marketplace-is-focused-on-small-and-medium-sized-retailers-in-java/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Before you start shopping online, be sure to check out Trend Micro's shopping tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</guid><description>E-commerce is rising in Singapore and the surrounding region, with experts predicting the online retail market in ASEAN countries could expand by as much as 25% each year until 2017.
While online shopping provides advantages like quick (and often free) delivery, and saves time, energy, and money, it also carries significant, frequently disregarded risks. Trend Micro cautions that these threats range from cybercriminals to online fraudsters targeting consumers&amp;rsquo; personal data and finances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-start-shopping-online-be-sure-to-check-out-trend-micro-s-shopping-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MatahariMall.com in Indonesia is growing its O2O network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</guid><description>Source: MatahariMall.com website.
The online shopping platform MatahariMall has broadened its Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD and eLocker services through a partnership with PT Pos Indonesia in Jakarta. This collaboration uses an online-to-offline approach, enabling customers to receive, return, and pay for their online purchases at physical locations.
This partnership introduces more Pickup&amp;amp;PayCOD points at designated post offices. Additionally, MatahariMall will install eLockers at strategic post office locations across Jakarta, Bogor, Depok, Tangerang, Bekasi, and Bandung...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mataharimall-com-in-indonesia-is-growing-its-o2o-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AppDine has launched a beta version of its F&amp;B and lifestyle e-commerce marketplace in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: AppeDine. Screenshot of the AppeDine app for consumers.
AppeDine has launched the public beta version of its food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and lifestyle e-commerce platform in Singapore. The marketplace facilitates online transactions tailored for F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle businesses, chefs, and consumers.
AppeDine brings together F&amp;amp;B outlets, temporary events, and promotions in one place, enabling F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle providers to generate revenue from their services and spaces online without upfront investment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee's 12.12 sale: 12 million items sold in just 24 minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, achieved record-breaking success during its annual 12.12 Birthday Sale. On December 12th, the platform sold an astounding 12 million items within the first 24 minutes. At its peak, Shopee recorded an incredible 1 million items purchased per minute. Notably, one of the top-performing sellers generated S$1 million in sales within just 24 hours on December 12th.
Zhou Junjie, Chief Commercial Officer at Shopee, expressed gratitude for the overwhelming response to their 12...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-s-12-12-sale-12-million-items-sold-in-just-24-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new NYNJA app allows you to communicate, make purchases, and utilize cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: NYNJA Group. Screen captures of the NYNJA app, currently in beta.
NYNJA Group, a Hong Kong-based communications and mobile technology firm, has introduced NYNJA, a new communications app with a built-in digital marketplace and cryptocurrency wallet.
The NYNJA app works across multiple platforms and integrates voice, text, and visual messaging with business management and e-commerce tools. Its features are powered by its own financial ecosystem and cryptocurrency, NYNJACoin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia honors female entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, marked International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day on March 8, 2017, by recognizing the achievements of women.
This year&amp;rsquo;s International Women&amp;rsquo;s Day centers around empowering women globally and inspiring them to make bold moves. Shopee Malaysia honored this theme by highlighting the stories of women entrepreneurs who took a leap of faith to launch their own ventures. The platform&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly design, free nationwide shipping, and zero-commission fees are designed to encourage more women to tap into their potential as leaders and business owners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-honors-female-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Seller University has been launched by Amazon in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 05:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</guid><description>Amazon has introduced Seller University, an online platform designed to assist small and medium businesses (SMBs) in Singapore, at its inaugural Amazon Singapore Online Seller Summit 2020. Seller University offers interactive e-learning materials, practical exercises, and customized support to equip sellers on Amazon.sg with the skills to thrive.
Bernard Tay, Country Leader of Amazon.sg Seller Services and Head of Amazon Global Selling Southeast Asia, Australia and New Zealand, emphasized Amazon&amp;rsquo;s commitment to empowering local businesses through initiatives like Seller University...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seller-university-has-been-launched-by-amazon-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 11.11 Shopping Festival at Lazada guarantees a more enjoyable experience for everyone involved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s Lazada 11.11 Shopping Festival is breaking records with over 50 million deals, a significant increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 27 million. The event will involve over 400,000 sellers and brands, almost triple the number from the previous year.
Lazada, a leading e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia, organizes this yearly event to demonstrate the convenience and affordability of online shopping. For 24 hours, starting at midnight on November 11th, shoppers across six countries will have access to incredible deals on a wide range of products, with discounts of up to 90%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon Prime is currently being offered at a discounted rate in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 12:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/</guid><description>Amazon Prime, offering perks like expedited shipping, streaming entertainment, and gaming, has launched in Singapore. This marks the 16th country to gain access to the program, following the recent discontinuation of free shipping for Singaporean shoppers on the US Amazon site.
Singaporean Prime members will now have access to free two-hour delivery on local orders over S$40 from a selection of tens of thousands of products through the Prime Now app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-prime-is-currently-being-offered-at-a-discounted-rate-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ten million transactions during the Lazada Mid-Year Festival</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/</guid><description>Lazada&amp;rsquo;s first sale since its rebranding offers 10 million deals.
Lazada&amp;rsquo;s shoppertainment approach is enhanced with the first region-wide livestreamed gameshow.
LazGames now includes a leaderboard and brand customization options.
On July 12th, Lazada will host its first-ever mid-year sale event, the Lazada Mid-Year Festival, throughout six Southeast Asian countries.
Consumers will have access to product discounts ranging from well-known brands to recent releases and one-of-a-kind items from 12:00 a...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ten-million-transactions-during-the-lazada-mid-year-festival/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consumers are seeking additional retail technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</guid><description>Source: Zebra infographic. Almost two-thirds of shoppers surveyed in Europe and the Middle East stated that customer service directly impacts their purchasing decisions. Meanwhile, nearly a third of Asia Pacific respondents prefer collecting online purchases from a physical store.
Consumers are setting higher expectations for their shopping experience, while retailers lag in matching these expectations with their in-store technology investments. Retail customers desire a wide array of options for receiving their purchases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-are-seeking-additional-retail-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Customers in five Asian locations can now purchase Indonesian products on Bukalapak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/</guid><description>The Indonesia-based e-commerce platform Bukalapak has introduced BukaGlobal, a new service connecting over 4 million Indonesian sellers with the international market. Bukalapak claims this makes them the first Indonesian e-commerce platform with global reach, furthering their goal of supporting the digitalization and international expansion of Indonesian small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs).
Bukalapak Co-Founder and President, Fajrin Rasyid, explained that BukaGlobal aims to tackle logistics issues in the region, including the high cost of postal and courier services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-in-five-asian-locations-can-now-purchase-indonesian-products-on-bukalapak/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys provides insights on improving e-commerce strategies for Asian businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
According to Genesys, a company that provides customer experience platforms, many businesses are not meeting the demands of e-commerce or changing along with their customers&amp;rsquo; expectations.
Genesys&amp;rsquo; Head of Marketing in the Asia Pacific, Erwann Thomassain, cites a Forrester report predicting that in the coming years, abandoned online shopping carts will cost businesses $31 billion dollars. He goes on to reference a 2013 Forrester study that found 52% of customers abandon online purchases when they can&amp;rsquo;t get a quick answer to their question...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-provides-insights-on-improving-e-commerce-strategies-for-asian-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adobe: Consumer sentiment in the Asia-Pacific region remains positive in the middle of 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 12:55:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</guid><description>Even though many COVID-19 lockdown restrictions have been lifted globally, research from Adobe, presented at their Adobe Experience Makers Live event, reveals that the extended home confinement has significantly altered consumer shopping habits and brand interactions.
The research highlights how COVID-19 has impacted daily life, with nearly seven in ten consumers (67%) concerned about the pandemic&amp;rsquo;s overall impact, particularly regarding personal health (73%), job security (40%), and the economy (36%). Millennials (72%) expressed higher concern levels compared to Gen Z (58%), Boomers (62%), and Traditionalists (48%)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adobe-consumer-sentiment-in-the-asia-pacific-region-remains-positive-in-the-middle-of-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FedEx packages can now be picked up by customers themselves at any time of day in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 08:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: FedEx. FedEx has launched a new self-collection service in Singapore, allowing customers to pick up their packages at designated locations. These include bluPort and Parcel Santa lockers, and Park N Parcel retail outlets across the island.
FedEx Express, a subsidiary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest express transportation company, now offers 24/7 package collection in Singapore.
Customers can retrieve their parcels from all participating bluPort and Parcel Santa lockers, as well as Park N Parcel retail collection points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fedex-packages-can-now-be-picked-up-by-customers-themselves-at-any-time-of-day-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>11 facts about 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:07:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</guid><description>Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 Global Shopping Festival, beginning on November 11, is generating excitement with its pre-launch preparations. Here are 11 key things shoppers should be aware of:
AI-Powered Multilingual Tools To enhance the shopping experience for global customers, Alibaba has introduced an AI translation tool designed to bridge language gaps between buyers and sellers.
This online chat tool, recently launched on Lazada, enables real-time translation between English and Thai, Vietnamese, and Indonesian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Alibaba truly the top player in the e-commerce industry?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</guid><description>While Alibaba Group Holding is often called the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest e-commerce company, a new report from yStats.com suggests that this depends on how you interpret the data. The report, which ranks companies based on official revenue figures, found that Amazon was the actual leader in 2013.
Amazon&amp;rsquo;s impressive $74 billion in product and service sales surpasses the combined revenue of the next nine companies on the list. Chinese B2C retailer JD...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tmall Global report showcases the preferences of Chinese consumers in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</guid><description>A recent report on import consumption in China, the Annual Report on Tmall Global Data 2016, was released by Tmall Global, an online platform allowing businesses outside China to connect with Chinese consumers, and CBNData. The report reveals the strength of e-commerce in China, showing a growing customer base, expanding product interest, and notable trends influenced by significant events.
The report highlights several key findings. First, cross-border e-commerce is entering a new phase, supported by favorable policies from both the Chinese government and global trade organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tmall-global-report-showcases-the-preferences-of-chinese-consumers-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon is sharing the best-selling Christmas items from Prime Now Singapore orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</guid><description>Amazon has revealed the top-selling items purchased by Prime Now users in Singapore during a record-breaking holiday season worldwide. Customers took advantage of Prime Now&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ultra-Fast Delivery&amp;rdquo; option throughout the holiday period, with tens of thousands of products delivered, even in the final hours. The last Prime Now order was delivered at 10:23 p.m. on December 24th.
&amp;ldquo;The volume of shoppers in Singapore using Prime Now leading up to Christmas was remarkable, as was the number who signed up for a free Prime trial or initiated a paid membership,&amp;rdquo; shared Kourosh Kaghazian, Country Manager for Amazon Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singpost will collaborate with Shippit on final delivery services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</guid><description>Shippit has partnered with Singapore Post (SingPost) to offer their delivery services and special negotiated rates on its platform. This collaboration allows small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to deliver parcels throughout Singapore.
This partnership provides SMEs on Shippit&amp;rsquo;s platform with more e-commerce fulfillment options. They can now offer customers island-wide parcel collection through SingPost&amp;rsquo;s POPStation network. Additionally, Shippit will provide access to SingPost&amp;rsquo;s Speedpost Express Service and discounted, pre-negotiated rates for next-day and economy deliveries—services previously exclusive to larger companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-will-collaborate-with-shippit-on-final-delivery-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SingEx has introduced Last Mile Fulfilment Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 06:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</guid><description>Last Mile Fulfilment Asia (LMFAsia), a debut trade show and conference centered around last-mile fulfillment in logistics and e-commerce, will premiere in Singapore next year.
This is the first event of its kind to hone in on last-mile fulfillment challenges and prospects in Asia. SingEx anticipates the event will attract around 1,500 attendees, representatives, and exhibitors from the Asian region in its first year. LMFAsia aims to unite four crucial sectors – e-commerce, retail, logistics, and parcel delivery – under one roof to maximize business opportunities for e-commerce in Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singex-has-introduced-last-mile-fulfilment-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Attract retail attention with apps and promotions leading up to a holiday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</guid><description>Criteo has noticed a major shift from websites to apps for online shopping. They found a 25% decrease in website traffic but a 4% rise in app traffic, with Thailand (18%) and Singapore (9%) experiencing the largest gains.
All Southeast Asian nations saw growth in overall app traffic volume, with Singapore (207%) and Indonesia (128%) leading the way.
When compared to October 2020, Thailand and Singapore had the highest increases in indexed sales in the app environment, at 12% and 10%, respectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attract-retail-attention-with-apps-and-promotions-leading-up-to-a-holiday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-commerce sellers in Saudi Arabia are invited to join Maroof</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Commerce and Investment (MCI) cautions against the online sale or promotion of counterfeit products. This practice violates the Anti-Commercial Fraud Law and Trademark System, with potential consequences including imprisonment of up to three years and fines reaching SR1 million.
MCI recommends that entrepreneurs register with Maroof (http://www.maroof.sa/), a free e-service. Registration enhances businesses&amp;rsquo; credibility by officially documenting their information with the ministry. Maroof offers transparency through customer feedback, allowing shoppers to assess e-store quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-commerce-sellers-in-saudi-arabia-are-invited-to-join-maroof/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become a leading global e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Aladdinstreet.com.sg, a global e-marketplace specializing in premium and halal products, has officially launched. Catering to both businesses and individual consumers, the platform offers a range of halal-certified products alongside premium items that don&amp;rsquo;t require certification.
Since its initial announcement in July 2016, Aladdinstreet.com.sg has carefully selected 200 merchants for inclusion on the site, formalizing agreements with nearly 60. Approximately half of these merchants provide halal-friendly or halal-certified products, encompassing diverse categories such as food, beverages, vitamins, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, fashion, and more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore launches its flagship store on Shopee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 11:47:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/</guid><description>Epson Singapore is expanding its online presence to adapt to evolving consumer shopping patterns. The company recently launched a flagship store on Shopee, a major e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia, following the 2018 launch of its flagship Lazada store.
Epson Singapore cites a study indicating that 37% of Singaporean consumers have increased their online shopping due to staying home during the COVID-19 pandemic. Furthermore, over 76% of those surveyed plan to maintain this behavior even after the pandemic stabilizes*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-launches-its-flagship-store-on-shopee/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prepare for Chinese New Year with Amazon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</guid><description>Preparing your office for Chinese New Year might be easier with a little help from Amazon.sg&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Chinese New Year store.
Finding the right gifts for clients is made simpler with choices like an abalone gift set, priced at S$310.80 for two 454g cans, or bird&amp;rsquo;s nest, available for S$39.90 for six jars. To help everyone in the office get into the spirit, festive treats are a must-have:
Source: Amazon. Snacks for the office for Chinese New Year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beautiful.me is inviting shoppers in Singapore to donate rice to those in need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 20:18:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</guid><description>Source: Beautiful.me. Beautiful.me partners with Community Chest. From left: Elise Wong, CRM Executive, Beautiful.me; Mae Kng, Senior Associate Director, Community Chest; Olive Tai, MD, Beautiful.me; Wileen Chen, Manager of Relations &amp;amp; Engagement, Community Chest.
Beautiful.me, in partnership with rice importer and distributor Hak Yong Company and the Singapore Community Chest, has initiated the Giving Is Beautiful campaign. This project encourages Singapore&amp;rsquo;s online shoppers to contribute funds to provide rice to those in need...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beautiful-me-is-inviting-shoppers-in-singapore-to-donate-rice-to-those-in-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo analyzes shopping habits during Ramadhan 2016 in Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:50:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Online retail activity in Southeast Asia (SEA) sees a surge in the weeks leading up to and during Ramadan, according to data from performance marketing company Criteo.
E-commerce sales escalate significantly, peaking in the third week of Ramadan with a 110% increase.
However, online browsing and shopping decrease during sunset hours, likely due to the breaking of the daily fast. Post-fast, e-commerce activity experiences a resurgence, presenting a valuable opportunity for retailers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-analyzes-shopping-habits-during-ramadhan-2016-in-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent study by Criteo reveals changing shopping habits in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 04:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</guid><description>· Singaporean shoppers use multiple devices throughout their purchasing journey.
· Physical stores must adapt to the local trend of &amp;ldquo;showrooming&amp;rdquo; and invest in integrating their online and offline channels.
· Enhancing last-mile delivery will help local retailers compete more effectively with international e-commerce businesses.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has discovered that shopping habits are evolving among consumers in Singapore. Research by Edelman Intelligence found that Singaporeans now possess or have access to an average of 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-study-by-criteo-reveals-changing-shopping-habits-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Warrior Forum has introduced a new e-marketplace that leverages the existing reach of its members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:07:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</guid><description>Warrior Forum, a prominent online community and marketplace for internet marketers, has introduced Warrior Payments. This comprehensive platform aims to revolutionize online sales by combining payments, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution tools.
Matt Barrie, CEO of Freelancer.com, which acquired Warrior Forum in 2014, highlights the platform&amp;rsquo;s value for entrepreneurs and startups looking to launch and sell products or services online.
Warrior Payments streamlines the sales process by integrating payment processing, digital product delivery, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Giftano improves the experience of giving gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</guid><description>Giftano, a Singapore-based online gifting platform, has expanded its offerings to include a complete online gifting solution. In addition to their existing digital gift card selection, Giftano now features &amp;ldquo;Giftano Gifts,&amp;rdquo; a curated marketplace for physical presents.
Giftano aims to provide a seamless and personalized online gifting experience, especially with the holiday season approaching. The company has improved its platform by adding a user-friendly search engine and features that allow for custom gift cards and various delivery choices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The key to e-commerce success according to Akamai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 11:09:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</guid><description>Akamai, a content delivery network (CDN) provider, emphasizes the importance of speed in e-commerce, stating that slow loading times can lead to customer loss. They suggest two key ways online retailers can improve their businesses: by understanding modern customer behavior and by prioritizing speed, intelligence, and security in their online operations.
Mobile shopping is a growing trend. Akamai&amp;rsquo;s data shows that mobile and tablet shoppers make purchases 20% more often and spend US$500 more than desktop users in the same timeframe, highlighting the need for strong mobile optimization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-key-to-e-commerce-success-according-to-akamai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get a Web Presence For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</guid><description>Starting a new business or moving an existing one online can feel overwhelming with all the options available. Is it really worth the effort?
Absolutely! Many business owners will attest to the value of establishing an online presence. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be complicated. You can simplify the process by seeking guidance from experienced professionals. Take a look at this engaging introductory video from Network Solutions to see what I mean&amp;hellip;..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Barter and location-based services contribute to Jualo's success in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Chaim Fetter, a Dutch programming prodigy and entrepreneur, has balanced building businesses with a spirit of exploration and philanthropy. As a teenager, he created his first online venture, developing e-commerce websites. He spent his twenties traveling in Southeast Asia before establishing the Peduli Anak Foundation in 2005 to support former street children in Lombok, Indonesia.
Source: Jualo website.
Last year, Fetter transitioned the foundation&amp;rsquo;s leadership to a local team, relocating to Jakarta to pursue a new business venture, Jualo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/barter-and-location-based-services-contribute-to-jualo-s-success-in-indonesia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee Malaysia and Pos Malaysia are working together for order fulfillment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 15:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</guid><description>Shopee Malaysia has partnered with Pos Malaysia, the national courier service, to offer free shipping to all sellers on its platform.
Shopee, a mobile-first social marketplace with a strong regional presence of over 12 million users, operates as a free online customer-to-customer (C2C) platform. Launched in December 2015, Shopee aims to empower both individual and business entrepreneurs to conduct secure buying and selling transactions on their mobile devices. In Malaysia alone, Shopee&amp;rsquo;s app has been downloaded over a million times within a six-month timeframe...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-malaysia-and-pos-malaysia-are-working-together-for-order-fulfillment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>On average, eBay sellers based in Singapore are able to reach 41 international markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 01:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</guid><description>Source: eBay report.
eBay recently released a report highlighting the increasing success of Singaporean businesses using its online marketplaces. This growth is attributed, in part, to the rising value of the US dollar.
The report indicates that Singaporean retailers selling internationally on eBay reach an average of 41 markets. This ranks them second in Southeast Asia, trailing only Thailand, and five positions ahead of US-based retail exporters.
Jason Lee, eBay South East Asia Director, points to the US as the primary trading partner for these Singaporean businesses and highlights the strengthening US dollar as a significant growth factor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-average-ebay-sellers-based-in-singapore-are-able-to-reach-41-international-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Double 12 Global Shopping Festival aims to attract Alipay users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</guid><description>Source: Alipay Facebook page. Flag advertising the Double 12 Global Shopping Festival.
Alipay, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading online and mobile payment and lifestyle platform operated by Ant Financial Services Group, launched its 2017 Double 12 Global Shopping Festival in Southeast Asia. The festival includes Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, and the Philippines.
Double 12 is a global event spanning 15 countries and territories across four continents. Over 500 brands and 100,000 merchants worldwide participate, offering Alipay users exclusive promotions throughout December...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Alibaba's 11.11 Global Shopping Festival generated more than $17 billion in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</guid><description>Alibaba Group reported that on November 11, 2016, its China and international retail marketplaces achieved a gross merchandise volume (GMV) of RMB120.7 billion (US$17.8 billion), settled through Alipay. This represents a 32% growth compared to 2015. Mobile GMV settled through Alipay reached RMB99 billion (US$14.6 billion), making up 82% of the total GMV.
&amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 provides a glimpse into the future of retail, where entertainment, commerce, and interactive engagement blend seamlessly,&amp;rdquo; said Daniel Zhang, CEO of Alibaba Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Utilize online brand ambassadors to add a personal touch to your online presence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 07:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</guid><description>Source: Oomph! Lee.
Oomph!, a Singapore-based staffing agency, has introduced ENGAGE, a new online platform and service for brand ambassadors. This platform aims to replicate the personalized customer service of physical stores in the digital world.
ENGAGE connects businesses with trained online brand ambassadors who can interact with customers through a chat box, including video chat options. These ambassadors can help customers find suitable products, answer their questions, and even book in-person store visits for a more traditional shopping experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/utilize-online-brand-ambassadors-to-add-a-personal-touch-to-your-online-presence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aramex is constructing private parcel lockers to meet the demands of the expanding e-commerce industry in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 15:04:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Aramex, a leading provider of global logistics and transportation solutions, has partnered with InPost, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest parcel locker network. This collaboration aims to provide consumers in the Middle East with convenient access to private, automated parcel lockers for all their e-commerce needs by the end of 2014.
Aramex attributes the significant growth of the e-commerce sector in the region to several factors. These include a growing affluent urban population, increased interest in and demand for online products and services, and a rise in new online retailers entering the market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aramex-is-constructing-private-parcel-lockers-to-meet-the-demands-of-the-expanding-e-commerce-industry-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai CommerCity aims to establish Dubai as a leading e-commerce destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 12:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</guid><description>Dubai CommerCity, a new AED2.7 billion, 2.1-million sq ft e-commerce free zone, has been jointly launched by Dubai Airport Freezone Authority (DAFZA) and wasl Asset Management Group. As the first of its kind in the MENA region, this project aims to solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a major e-commerce hub, boost economic diversification, and advance smart transformation strategies.
This initiative seeks to capitalize on the burgeoning GCC e-commerce market, predicted to reach US$20 billion by 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-commercity-aims-to-establish-dubai-as-a-leading-e-commerce-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great Eastern has introduced additional rewards for online shopping in collaboration with RebateMango</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 02:32:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/</guid><description>Great Eastern&amp;rsquo;s rewards platform, UPGREAT, has partnered with RebateMango to provide users with an enhanced rewards experience. This collaboration aligns with the insurer&amp;rsquo;s strategy to increase online engagement with its customers across the region.
UPGREAT members can now enjoy a wider selection of rewards from over 500 retailers in Singapore, including popular names like Shopee, Agoda, AliExpress, Booking.com, and Lazada. This integration creates a seamless shopping experience where users can earn UPGREAT points easily...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-eastern-has-introduced-additional-rewards-for-online-shopping-in-collaboration-with-rebatemango/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shoppers are interested in clothes, cosmetics, and baby products on 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</guid><description>Source: Alizila blog. The 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival logo is illuminated in neon.
Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival is surpassing the sales of the previous year. Alizila reports show that it took a mere 1 minute and 25 seconds for the festival to reach over US$1 billion in total gross merchandise volume (GMV).
By 1:15 p.m., Tmall Global had already exceeded its total GMV from the entire 2017 11...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo measures the passion for travel among Singaporeans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 15:18:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</guid><description>Mobile travel purchases saw a 35% surge between 2011 and 2016, a trend predicted to continue its upward trajectory. Accessibility (74%) and convenience (69%) are the primary motivators for respondents&amp;rsquo; preference to browse travel products online. A significant 78% choose smartphones over desktops/laptops for browsing due to their on-the-go functionality.
Criteo, a performance marketing technology firm, highlights the continuous growth of mobile travel sales, emphasizing it as a prime growth avenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-measures-the-passion-for-travel-among-singaporeans/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee reveals birthday flash sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 15:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</guid><description>Shopee, a prominent mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is marking its first anniversary. To commemorate the occasion, they are holding hourly flash sales with discounts of up to 70% on December 12, 2016.
Two products will be discounted every hour on December 12th, from 12 pm to 7 pm.
Along with the hourly flash sales on December 12th, Shopee is running a lucky draw for users who take advantage of daily category vouchers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-reveals-birthday-flash-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Card-not-present fraud is on the rise, leaving two-thirds of credit card issuers in the Asia-Pacific region vulnerable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 11:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</guid><description>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing a surge in e-commerce, but this growth is accompanied by an increase in online fraud. A survey of fraud professionals in the region, conducted by predictive analytics firm FICO, revealed that card-not-present (CNP) fraud is the fastest-growing type of fraud. Nearly all (94%) of the survey respondents reported an increase in CNP fraud.
eMarketer, a research firm, projects that B2C e-commerce sales in the Asia Pacific region will reach US$525...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/card-not-present-fraud-is-on-the-rise-leaving-two-thirds-of-credit-card-issuers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-vulnerable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Artisan Nook's goal is to empower women</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artisan-nook-s-goal-is-to-empower-women/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 04:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artisan-nook-s-goal-is-to-empower-women/</guid><description>Artisan Nook, a new e-commerce platform and community designed specifically for women, has been established. The platform is built upon the idea of driving positive societal change by empowering women to find personal fulfillment, gain financial freedom, and establish their own legacies.
&amp;ldquo;Artisan Nook is about giving women a platform to pursue their entrepreneurial aspirations, build their own legacies, and simultaneously create a lasting positive impact for future generations,&amp;rdquo; shared Reena Yin, Founder of Artisan Nook...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artisan-nook-s-goal-is-to-empower-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artisan-nook-s-goal-is-to-empower-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InPost has officially started its operations in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: InPost.
InPost, a global leader in automated parcel locker networks, has expanded its services to Malaysia. The launch was accompanied by a roadshow, themed &amp;ldquo;Malaysia E-commerce Day (MED) 2015,&amp;rdquo; aimed at raising awareness about the latest advancements in e-commerce, e-payments, and logistics.
According to InPost Malaysia Managing Director Rosland Mohd Jannes, the initiative seeks to connect with businesses and individuals, boosting consumer confidence in online shopping and alleviating delivery-related anxieties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inpost-has-officially-started-its-operations-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The free WooCommerce WordPress plugin has reached 4 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 06:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</guid><description>WooThemes, a developer of WordPress themes, plugins, and shopping cart features, announced that its WooCommerce WordPress plugin has been downloaded over 4 million times. WooCommerce is WooThemes&amp;rsquo; free flagship product, officially partnered with companies like Amazon, Mastercard, and PayPal.
Source: WooThemes website.
WooCommerce enables businesses to operate e-commerce sites using WordPress as their content management system.
WooThemes uses a freemium model. The basic plugin and some add-ons are free, while more advanced extensions and themes require payment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-woocommerce-wordpress-plugin-has-reached-4-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopmatic has partnered with Easyship to make it easier for merchants to deliver their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:15:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</guid><description>Source: Shopmatic. Shopmatic co-founders from left: Kris Chen,
Anurag Avula, and Yen Ti Lim. Shopmatic, the Singapore-based e-commerce company, has teamed up with Easyship, a comprehensive shipping platform for global e-commerce. This partnership will enable Shopmatic merchants to streamline product delivery and expand their businesses internationally.
Easyship offers integrated shipping services from over 100 providers, including DHL, FedEx, and UPS. It allows for immediate order shipping with discounts of up to 70%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopmatic-has-partnered-with-easyship-to-make-it-easier-for-merchants-to-deliver-their-products/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>