<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Carrier Hotel on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier-hotel/</link><description>Recent content in Carrier Hotel on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/carrier-hotel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Colo Bandwidth Pricing Is Lowest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</guid><description>Intrigued by the idea of significantly cheaper bandwidth? Take a look at the pricing for colocation bandwidth and see for yourself.
It&amp;rsquo;s tempting, right? The cost per Mbps at a colocation center is often much lower than standard bandwidth costs for your servers, even with a discounted rate from a telecom broker. While this might seem unfair, it&amp;rsquo;s simply a matter of economics.
Colocation facilities can offer these reduced costs for a couple of reasons...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colo-bandwidth-pricing-is-lowest/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Carrier Neutral Connectivity at Colocation Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses struggling to find enough bandwidth might be overlooking a simpler solution. Instead of waiting for carriers to come to them, companies can benefit by going where the carriers already are.
Colocation Centers: A Hub for Connectivity
Carriers are drawn to locations called colocation centers, or colos, and carrier hotels. These large data centers are designed to accommodate multiple tenants, unlike typical data centers that serve a single company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/carrier-neutral-connectivity-at-colocation-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation vs Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:29:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</guid><description>The choice between &amp;ldquo;make&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;buy&amp;rdquo; is about deciding whether to handle tasks internally or outsource them. IT managers frequently face this dilemma when contemplating between managing an on-site data center and opting for a colocation facility. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a third option: the cloud.
While both colocation and cloud services are obtained from external providers, the differences between them are significant from an operational standpoint.
Colocation facilities shine by offering a physical space designed for IT needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-vs-cloud-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Making The Move For Higher Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</guid><description>Are you experiencing bandwidth limitations in your organization? With the rapid advancement of online technology, many organizations are facing a shortage of bandwidth. While contacting your service provider to increase your line speed might seem like the solution, they might inform you that you already have the maximum speed available. So, what are your options?
Have you thought about relocating? Bandwidth availability and cost vary significantly by location. Some places have many choices and reasonable prices, while others might not be able to meet your basic needs regardless of your budget...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/making-the-move-for-higher-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Type of Data Center Connectivity Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</guid><description>When thinking about moving to a colocation center or building a data center or private cloud off-site, you&amp;rsquo;ll face both opportunities and difficulties in setting up your network connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the key factors and uncover potential cost-saving opportunities.
The main difference between on-site and remote data centers, including colocation facilities, lies in how you manage network connections. On-site, you have full control over your local wiring. Off-site, you lease connections through service providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Rush To Cloud Service Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 12:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</guid><description>Many companies are moving away from managing their own servers and rapidly shifting towards public data centers. This article explores the reasons behind this trend and its potential future.
Cost savings have always been a major driver for companies considering data center colocation. Instead of investing in their own data centers, companies can move their equipment to a colocation facility. These facilities provide economies of scale by housing servers and network devices from multiple companies, sharing the costs of cooling, power, security, and bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-rush-to-cloud-service-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantage of Colocation Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</guid><description>Companies frequently grapple with the decision of whether to handle a product or service internally or outsource it to a specialized vendor. This dilemma extends to telephone and computer services, demanding a careful evaluation of the most advantageous approach.
The optimal choice concerning technical services hinges significantly on your specific circumstances at any given moment. It is advisable to reassess these decisions periodically, perhaps annually. While the merits of internally managing your telephone and computer systems might be clear, it&amp;rsquo;s equally crucial to understand the upsides of outsourcing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>