<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commission President on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commission-president/</link><description>Recent content in Commission President on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commission-president/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is it appropriate for the outcome of the European Parliament elections to dictate the selection of the next President of the European Commission, or are there valid concerns about this democratic process?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s doubtful the European Court of Justice will decide the next European Commission President. Election laws typically set the stage but don&amp;rsquo;t directly determine the winner, although there are notable exceptions like the 2000 US election.
The 2014 Commission President election is unique because the rules changed, and their interpretation is debated. Previously, the European Council appointed the President after European Parliament approval. The Treaty of Lisbon introduced new rules, applied for the first time, stating the Parliament &amp;ldquo;elects&amp;rdquo; the President based on the Council&amp;rsquo;s nomination, &amp;ldquo;taking account&amp;rdquo; of Parliament election results.</description></item><item><title>The Dalli Saga: A Story of Accountability and Defenestration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dalli-saga-a-story-of-accountability-and-defenestration/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City University
The forced resignation of the Santer Commission in 1999 due to accusations of fraud, maladministration, and mismanagement remains a relevant topic even after nearly two decades. The European Commission has faced ongoing criticism for its administrative shortcomings and the structural flaws within the Union&amp;rsquo;s accountability system. Numerous reports have portrayed the Commission as an institution grappling with systemic and political irregularities.</description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President.</description></item><item><title>Is Juncker capable of being a reformist Commission President, like Nixon was in going to China?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A common saying in American politics, &amp;ldquo;only Nixon could go to China,&amp;rdquo; suggests that only a politician with a well-established reputation can persuade their base to accept a major policy shift. Nixon, a staunch anti-Communist, was able to convince American conservatives that engaging with Communist China was in their best interest. This principle might apply to the European Union as well. The recent European Parliament (EP) elections saw a rise in support for anti-EU parties in several Member States.</description></item></channel></rss>