<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Game on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/game/</link><description>Recent content in Game on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/game/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>Dubai-Opoly aims to showcase Dubai as a premier business destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:52:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-opoly-aims-to-showcase-dubai-as-a-premier-business-destination/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. Dubai Chamber creates Dubai-Opoly game to promote
Dubai.
The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry recently introduced Dubai-Opoly, a board game designed to highlight Dubai&amp;rsquo;s standing as a global business and trade hub.
Inspired by the classic game Monopoly, Dubai-Opoly will soon be available in stores across the UAE and GCC region. The game will showcase some of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most iconic landmarks and attractions. This initiative aligns with the Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s efforts to strengthen the emirate&amp;rsquo;s image as a thriving commercial center and top tourist destination.</description></item><item><title>Attend Walton's Cashflow Night to learn how to break free from your routine and achieve significant success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attend-walton-s-cashflow-night-to-learn-how-to-break-free-from-your-routine-and-achieve-significant-success/</guid><description>A board game can help you start aligning your life goals by reassessing how you approach cash flow and investment. The website for Cashflow the Boardgame, which was created by Rich Dad Poor Dad author Robert Kiyosaki, states that &amp;ldquo;You could learn to be wealthy and that would be life changing. You could also learn to be wealthy by playing a game and that would be amazing.&amp;rdquo; The game was first played in 1996 in Singapore and has since gained global popularity, with a community of 1.</description></item><item><title>Atari guarantees a fitness app that incorporates gamification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 07:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/atari-guarantees-a-fitness-app-that-incorporates-gamification/</guid><description>Atari, a company known for interactive entertainment, is launching Atari Fit™, a fitness app with gaming elements, in early 2015.
Atari collaborated with certified personal trainer Michael Porter to create over 150 exercises for the app, including circuit training, running programs, and personalized routines. Users can earn points by exercising alone or with friends to unlock classic Atari games such as Pong, Centipede, and Super Breakout.
Porter highlights that all exercise routines within Atari Fit are certified, ensuring their safety and effectiveness.</description></item><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>SingPost releases stamps showcasing classic board games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singpost-releases-stamps-showcasing-classic-board-games/</guid><description>Source: SingPost. The new traditional board games stamp issue.
Singapore Post (SingPost) is releasing a new set of five square stamps on April 27th. Each stamp features a hand-drawn image of a traditional board game popular in Singapore during the 1970s and 80s: Chinese chess, the diamond game, aeroplane chess, snakes and ladders, and checkers.
Chinese chess (1st local denomination) is a strategic board game for two players simulating a battle between two armies.</description></item><item><title>Stay away from Pokemon Go scams and malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</guid><description>Source: Niantic blog.
The augmented reality game Pokémon Go, highly popular since its July launch, has attracted scammers and cybercriminals. While the game hasn&amp;rsquo;t officially launched in all of Asia, Symantec warns of potential risks for players.
Symantec&amp;rsquo;s blog post details several Pokémon Go scams, from fake PokeCoins to privacy concerns.
Free PokeCoin scams
Pokémon Go offers in-app purchases using real money to buy PokeCoins, a virtual currency. Players use these coins to purchase items like incense to attract Pokémon.</description></item><item><title>Experience cutting-edge VR gaming at Bugis Junction and Bugis+, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-cutting-edge-vr-gaming-at-bugis-junction-and-bugis-singapore/</guid><description>This Halloween, shoppers at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bugis Junction and Bugis+ malls can participate in an immersive virtual reality (VR) gaming experience. This event marks the first time malls in Singapore have hosted a VR experience of this magnitude.
The &amp;ldquo;Time Zombies&amp;rdquo; competition invites shoppers to assume the roles of time-traveling detectives. Their mission: to stop the nefarious Dr. Virago, a mad scientist attempting to unleash a zombie apocalypse. This competition utilizes cutting-edge Arctic Fox wireless technology, allowing players to move freely within the virtual world using a wireless headset, eliminating the need for cumbersome cables or backpack computers.</description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music.</description></item><item><title>In July, Walton will be hosting a gaming session for Cashflow 101</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 10:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-july-walton-will-be-hosting-a-gaming-session-for-cashflow-101/</guid><description>Source: Walton eDM.
The Walton Group (Walton), a multinational real estate investment and development company specializing in pre-development land investments in North America, is hosting another session of the Cashflow 101 board game in Singapore.
Cashflow 101, also known as the Cash Flow game, was created by Robert Kiyosaki, author of Rich Dad Poor Dad. The game aims to help players connect their life goals with their finances by shifting their perspective on cash flow and investment.</description></item><item><title>Customers who purchase the GeForce RTX 3080 and 3090 are eligible to receive a Call of Duty game bundle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</guid><description>Image: Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War promotional image highlighting the Woods Operator Pack and Confrontation Weapons Pack.
NVIDIA is running a limited-time promotion offering a free copy of Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War with the purchase of qualifying GeForce RTX 3080 or 3090 graphics cards and pre-built PCs.
Releasing on November 13, 2020, Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War is the newest installment in the popular Call of Duty series.</description></item><item><title>Usagyuuun will make an appearance in the Claw Stars universe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usagyuuun-will-make-an-appearance-in-the-claw-stars-universe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 19:04:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/usagyuuun-will-make-an-appearance-in-the-claw-stars-universe/</guid><description>Source: Appxplore. The mobile game Claw Stars will soon feature characters from the popular sticker app, Usagyuuun.
Minto, the company behind Usagyuuun, and Appxplore, the developer of Claw Stars, are collaborating to bring the beloved sticker character to the award-winning mobile game. This marks the first game collaboration for Minto, a global leader in character IPs with over 6 billion downloads worldwide.
Appxplore, known for its expertise in game development and creator of games with over 40 million downloads, sees this partnership as a strategic move to merge its experience with the massive popularity of Usagyuuun.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive outfits for My Omamori will be available to Huawei mobile gamers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-outfits-for-my-omamori-will-be-available-to-huawei-mobile-gamers/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. My Omamori offers perks for Huawei users.
Huawei&amp;rsquo;s mobile services branch has teamed up with Original Workshop, the creators of the female-oriented game My Omamori, to give special prizes to mobile players.
Omamori means lucky charm in Japanese. In the game, an ancient warrior, Toki Mamoru, travels to the present to become the player’s guardian angel. Mamoru, who is voiced by Japanese voice actor Yuki Ono, was developed by Taiwanese novelist Deer Li.</description></item><item><title>There is a growing trend of adults purchasing toys and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</guid><description>In 2016, games and puzzles experienced an 8% surge in the global market, surpassing construction toys as the fastest-growing toy category, according to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm. This impressive growth also marks the highest for the category since 2002.
Although construction toys saw a growth of 7.8% in 2016, a dip compared to the double-digit growth of 2015, they still dominated the traditional toys and games market with a value of US$10 billion.</description></item><item><title>Singtel and Riot Games Southeast Asia introduce the world's first gaming bundles for League of Legends: Wild Rift that are zero-rated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-riot-games-southeast-asia-introduce-the-world-s-first-gaming-bundles-for-league-of-legends-wild-rift-that-are-zero-rated/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 03:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-and-riot-games-southeast-asia-introduce-the-world-s-first-gaming-bundles-for-league-of-legends-wild-rift-that-are-zero-rated/</guid><description>Singtel has teamed up with Riot Games Southeast Asia to launch the first-ever zero-rated gaming bundles for League of Legends: Wild Rift. Zero-rating means data used for a specific activity won&amp;rsquo;t count towards a user&amp;rsquo;s data limit and won&amp;rsquo;t incur extra charges.
League of Legends: Wild Rift, a five-versus-five mobile multiplayer online battle arena (MOBA), brings the popular PC game League of Legends to mobile devices.
These new RiotGO and RiotGO+ bundles, available exclusively for Singtel postpaid mobile customers, offer unlimited data-free gameplay and up to S$40 worth of in-game content for Wild Rift.</description></item><item><title>Kramnik will face Alcántara in a rematch on Chessarena.com</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kramnik-will-face-alc-ntara-in-a-rematch-on-chessarena-com/</guid><description>Source: World Chess. Vladimir Kramnik (pictured left) is set to have a rematch against José Alcántara (Jospem, pictured right) in August 2024.
World Chess, an organization dedicated to increasing the popularity of chess worldwide, is organizing &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims 2.&amp;rdquo; This event is a rematch following a controversial first &amp;ldquo;Clash of Claims&amp;rdquo; match between chess players Vladimir Kramnik and José Alcántara. The event will be broadcasted live with commentary from well-known chess personalities and include interactive elements for viewers.</description></item></channel></rss>