<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HFC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hfc/</link><description>Recent content in HFC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hfc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator).</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television.</description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs.</description></item><item><title>Pricing Slashed For Michigan 100 Mbps Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</guid><description>Michigan businesses are facing a common problem: the need for faster internet speeds. Traditional options like T1 lines are no longer sufficient for handling increased data demands from video conferencing, cloud-based applications, and automation. While fiber optic services offer the necessary bandwidth, their high cost often makes them inaccessible.
Comcast Business Class emerges as a potential solution, delivering 100 Mbps download and 10 Mbps upload speeds at a price comparable to T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>PRI over Cable Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 01:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-over-cable-cost-savings/</guid><description>Many businesses use ISDN PRI, a technology that bundles multiple phone lines onto a single digital cable, for cost-effective phone service. While initially implemented with T1 lines, offering 23 usable voice channels after reserving one for signaling, ISDN PRI can now be delivered over cable networks.
Modern phone systems, including PBX and key systems, typically support ISDN PRI, allowing businesses to scale their phone lines up to 46, 69, 92, or more.</description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV.</description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>Redundant Business Internet Connection Using Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 19:14:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/redundant-business-internet-connection-using-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Large companies have avoided using consumer-grade broadband services due to concerns about their reliability and performance. While it is prudent to use dedicated circuits with service level agreements for critical business operations, there is a cost-effective solution available for backing up telecom services and enhancing internet speed.
Cable broadband has grown rapidly and seen continuous technological advancements, primarily due to its popularity as a consumer internet service. While alternatives like satellite, wireless, dial-up, and fiber optic exist, they often come with limitations in bandwidth, high installation costs, or limited availability.</description></item><item><title>D3 vs DS3 Bandwidth Choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/d3-vs-ds3-bandwidth-choices/</guid><description>For a long time, mid-size and large businesses have relied on DS3 services to fulfill their broadband internet needs. However, a new contender has emerged, aiming to either complement or even replace the well-established DS3 connection.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
If your business requires more bandwidth than what bonded T1 lines can provide, you&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with DS3. But how about D3?
D3 stands for DOCSIS 3.0, a cable broadband standard enabling HFC (Hybrid Fiber Cable) systems to deliver fiber-like speeds.</description></item></channel></rss>