<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Shanghai on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shanghai/</link><description>Recent content in Shanghai on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/shanghai/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is the inaugural Hyatt hotel in the Jiangsu province</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 18:10:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</guid><description>The Hyatt Regency Suzhou has officially opened in Suzhou, a city renowned for its historic canals, stone bridges, and UNESCO-recognized classical gardens.
Source: Hyatt. The hotel boasts a 29-floor atrium, the tallest in Suzhou.
&amp;ldquo;The launch of Hyatt Regency Suzhou is a significant move for Hyatt as we expand our brand presence in China,&amp;rdquo; stated Christopher Koehler, Vice President of Operations for Hyatt in China. &amp;ldquo;We aim to create valuable connections among global business and leisure travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hyatt-regency-suzhou-is-the-inaugural-hyatt-hotel-in-the-jiangsu-province/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established a new office in Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 10:37:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</guid><description>To capitalize on promising markets and solidify Dubai&amp;rsquo;s position as a global business hub, the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has established its seventh international office in Shanghai, China.
His Excellency Hisham Al Shirawi, Second Vice-Chairman of Dubai Chamber, emphasized China&amp;rsquo;s significance as Dubai&amp;rsquo;s top trading partner and highlighted the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s decade-long dedication to fostering strong trade relations. The Shanghai office, Dubai Chamber&amp;rsquo;s first in China, reflects this commitment and aligns with the Dubai Plan 2021&amp;rsquo;s goal of bolstering Dubai&amp;rsquo;s status as a leading business and investment destination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-of-commerce-and-industry-has-established-a-new-office-in-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li blends traditional shikumen architecture with modern French elegance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</guid><description>Source: Capella Shanghai website. Villa entrance.
Located in Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French Concession, the Capella Shanghai, Jian Ye Li, offers a journey back to the city&amp;rsquo;s early 20th-century charm. Situated within the Jian Ye Li estate, the property is a rare surviving example of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;shikumen&amp;rdquo; townhouses, characterized by their three-story brick construction and stone accents.
The goal was to develop an ultra-luxury experience while meticulously preserving the site&amp;rsquo;s historical character. Jaya Interior Design and BLINK Design Group drew inspiration from Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s past, seamlessly integrating traditional Chinese elements with French elegance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-shanghai-jian-ye-li-blends-traditional-shikumen-architecture-with-modern-french-elegance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sukhothai Shanghai is set to make its debut in late 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 06:53:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</guid><description>Source: HKRI. The Sukhothai Shanghai.
HKR International will soon expand its Sukhothai Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts portfolio with a second hotel – The Sukhothai Shanghai. This new addition, situated in the Nanjing Road West central business district, is set to launch in late 2017.
Designed by Neri &amp;amp; Hu, The Sukhothai Shanghai is a contemporary luxury boutique hotel. It offers 168 guest rooms and 33 suites, ranging from 44 to 172 square meters in size...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sukhothai-shanghai-is-set-to-make-its-debut-in-late-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cachet Hotel Group unveils the fresh appearance of URBN Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:19:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</guid><description>The Cachet Hotel Group (CHG) has revamped its stylish URBN Hotel in Shanghai, a former warehouse. Led by CHG&amp;rsquo;s renowned fashion designer, Jay Godfrey, the updated interiors offer guests a modern, zen-like ambiance. The use of recycled and reclaimed wood materials adds a natural touch, further enhanced by the neutral color scheme.
Source: CHG. The Jay Godfrey Courtyard Suite.
Photo - http://photos.prnasia.com/prnh/20140911/0861406560
The URBN Shanghai boasts a unique Jay Godfrey-designed suite...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cachet-hotel-group-unveils-the-fresh-appearance-of-urbn-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indulge in Glamour at the Bund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 20:09:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</guid><description>The renowned &amp;lsquo;M&amp;rsquo; Restaurant Group, led by Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s celebrated entrepreneur Michelle Garnaut, has unveiled Glam, a chic new dining lounge and bar in Shanghai. Situated at 5 on the Bund, the location previously housed the iconic M on the Bund restaurant.
Michelle Garnaut, known for establishing new dining benchmarks in Asia, began her restaurant empire with M at the Fringe in Hong Kong in 1989. She later spearheaded Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s return to sophistication with M on the Bund in 1999 and elevated the city&amp;rsquo;s nightlife with The Glamour Bar in 2006...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-glamour-at-the-bund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amara Signature Shanghai has been softly launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 02:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</guid><description>![Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgAfBJYJW9dykG8i4PiZBEX_SuEbBpNrdOHxK7OgjVsJ6TA5Nt3-In_JgJHn8Ca19sRF5j5K5W-upNOpJ4qsG-tQA9WfYeGX2oQViKTULwU3f0PwufZs6HVNmCPk3UB45hfYmL_9NVDfxE/ cursor: pointer; &amp;ldquo;The Amara Signature Shanghai is the first Amara Signature in China.&amp;rdquo;)
Source: Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts. The Amara Signature Shanghai.
The Amara Signature Shanghai, a new luxury hotel under Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Amara Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has recently held its soft opening.
This 30-story, five-star hotel showcases a sleek, all-glass exterior and sits at the crossroads of Changshou Road and Jiaozhou Road in Shanghai, China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amara-signature-shanghai-has-been-softly-launched/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>