<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disruption on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disruption/</link><description>Recent content in Disruption on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disruption/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DBS introduces the first mobile-only bank in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-introduces-the-first-mobile-only-bank-in-india/</guid><description>Source: DBS. From left: Sachin Tendulkar, Cricketer, digor
the digibank mascot, DBS CEO Piyush Gupta.
Introducing a pioneering Virtual Assistant powered by artificial intelligence. Account creation utilizes Aadhaar, the largest biometric identification system globally. DBS Bank, headquartered in Singapore and a prominent financial institution in Asia, has introduced digibank, India&amp;rsquo;s inaugural mobile-centric bank. This innovative banking platform harnesses advanced technologies, including biometrics and artificial intelligence (AI), to offer customers a novel banking experience.</description></item><item><title>Navigating the digital landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 20:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-the-digital-landscape/</guid><description>Business leaders from major telecommunications and media companies recently met to talk about how to thrive in a digital world. IBM iX, the consulting firm that organized the gathering, emphasizes that these challenges are relevant to every industry.
A key takeaway was the urgent need for companies to disrupt themselves before someone else does. This involves understanding emerging digital trends and investing in ways that increase market share and profits.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>