<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EPL on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/epl/</link><description>Recent content in EPL on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/epl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Companies Expand Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 14:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is rapidly gaining ground against the traditional T1 lines. While T1 technology remains relevant, EoC providers are expanding their reach and offering more choices.
For instance, Integra Telecom is actively establishing a presence in numerous telephone company central offices (COs) that serve a vast number of businesses. This strategic move is driven by the value of copper in the telecom industry. Due to regulations, Incumbent Local Exchange Carriers (ILECs), or local phone companies, own the existing copper infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-companies-expand-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Internet Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:22:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</guid><description>Ethernet point-to-point and LAN services have gained popularity among businesses, often replacing T1 lines and outdated Frame Relay networks. Ethernet is also a great way to connect to MPLS VPN networks and the internet.
Carrier Ethernet began as a business-oriented Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) service known as Metro Ethernet, often used by companies to connect multiple locations within a specific geographic region. E-Line point-to-point services like EPL and EVPL provide comparable or superior connectivity to T1 lines, even when multiple T1 lines are used...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-internet-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1 Gbps Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>As companies increasingly adopt cloud services and engage in data-heavy activities like video streaming and big data analysis, the demand for greater WAN bandwidth is on the rise. It&amp;rsquo;s becoming commonplace to see requests for 1,000 Mbps connections, often fulfilled by a 1 Gbps Ethernet or GigE point-to-point connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the details and available choices for Gigabit Ethernet service.
Ethernet, the standard protocol for LANs, commonly operates at speeds of 10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1,000 Mbps, or 10 Gbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-gbps-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EtherSphere Spans The World With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Global Crossing, through its EtherSphere solutions, provides standardized Carrier Ethernet services globally, offering a centralized network solution for multinational companies with dispersed operations.
EtherSphere offers various standardized Ethernet services defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). These services include Point-to-Point Ethernet Private Line (EPL) or E-Line, multipoint connections like Ethernet Virtual Private Line (EVPL), Point-to-Multipoint or E-Tree, and Multipoint-to-Multipoint Ethernet Private LAN or VPLS (Virtual Private LAN Service) E-LAN.
This range of Ethernet services caters to diverse connectivity needs for interconnecting multiple locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>