<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Beauty on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beauty/</link><description>Recent content in Beauty on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/beauty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule.</description></item><item><title>LG introduces a new high-end beauty brand for the home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has introduced LG Pra.L, its high-end line of at-home beauty devices, in Singapore. The collection includes four devices: the Dual Cleanser, Galvanic Ion Booster, Total Lift Up Care, and Derma LED Mask, each designed to cleanse, nourish, lift, and firm the skin.
Inspired by the idea that beauty comes from within, LG Pra.L aims to elevate skincare routines for quicker, visible results. All four devices prioritize user convenience with features like silicone handles for grip, voice-guided instructions, USB-C charging, and long battery life for portability.</description></item><item><title>Activpass provides discounted rates for wellness activities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/activpass-provides-discounted-rates-for-wellness-activities/</guid><description>Source: Activpass. Activpass is a mobile-based marketplace for booking lifestyle activities.
The team behind Activpass, a platform designed for businesses and professionals in fitness, wellness, and beauty, believes in living life to the fullest. Their mobile platform gives users access to over 1,000 services like yoga, training sessions, golf, massages, and beauty treatments, all without requiring a long-term commitment.
Users can easily book and pay for services on their phones.</description></item><item><title>KVD Vegan Beauty marks a decade of success with the Tattoo Liner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/</guid><description>KVD Vegan Beauty is launching a global campaign, CAT EYES FOR ALL, this March to celebrate the tenth anniversary of their Tattoo Liner. The campaign will feature Instagram-famous feline, @CobytheCat, known for his naturally winged eyes.
The campaign will promote the brand&amp;rsquo;s long-lasting liquid eyeliner, Tattoo Liner, available in Trooper Black and Mad Max Brown, along with the volumizing Go Big or Go Home mascara.
The campaign features other diverse models, including KVD Vegan Beauty International Makeup Artist Fanny Maurer, Chloé Nguyen, and Carmen Lee Solomons, as well as a senior model, to illustrate that Tattoo Liner is suitable for all ages, eye shapes, and ethnicities.</description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives.</description></item><item><title>L’Oréal introduces a flexible skin sensor that tracks sun exposure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</guid><description>Source: L’Oréal. Model wearing a My UV patch.
L’Oréal recently introduced My UV Patch at the Consumer Electronics Show. It is the first flexible skin sensor designed to track UV exposure and promote sun-safety awareness among consumers. This innovation arrives as sun exposure has become a significant health concern, with 90% of non-melanoma skin cancers linked to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from the sun, in addition to skin pigmentation and premature aging.</description></item><item><title>Singapore welcomes the arrival of Japanese fashion retail concepts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-japanese-fashion-retail-concepts/</guid><description>Source: WMH Group. Kafuku.
World Mode Holdings Group (WMH Group) aims to improve the Singapore fashion retail sector by establishing its first international branch, iDA Singapore (iDA’SG).
WMH Group is a Japanese fashion retail consultancy firm known for strengthening its clients&amp;rsquo; brands. As Japan&amp;rsquo;s top recruiter for beauty and fashion sales professionals, their Singapore branch will offer expert guidance and support to enhance retail staff skills.
“As Japan&amp;rsquo;s leader in retail job placements, we&amp;rsquo;ve placed 100,000 retail staff with approximately 1,000 clients, primarily in fashion and luxury.</description></item><item><title>More than half of the worldwide facial aesthetics market is made up of Botox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</guid><description>The global demand for facial aesthetic procedures is growing, driven by consumers who are increasingly interested in their appearance and prefer less invasive treatments, according to a report on the Facial Aesthetics Market from 2016-2020 by Technavio.
Technavio&amp;rsquo;s research shows that Botox holds the largest share of the facial aesthetics market, making up roughly 52% of the total. They attribute this dominance to changing cultural perceptions of beauty, higher disposable incomes, and the growing popularity of the brand.</description></item><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress.</description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs.</description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods.</description></item><item><title>Viu introduces exclusive Korean content: Song Ji Hyo's Beauty Views</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 16:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</guid><description>Song Ji Hyo’s Beauty Views is a partnership between Viu and the famous Korean actress from the variety show Running Man.
Viu, a pan-Asian streaming platform owned by PCCW Media, has made investments in Viu Originals to boost user engagement. Viu Originals features Korean, Chinese, Indian, and Southeast Asian content for viewers across Asia.
Given the significant popularity of Korean content in the region, Viu Originals aims to increase user engagement by offering captivating and locally relevant original programs.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports that skincare is a popular trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has reported that the global beauty industry is experiencing growth, particularly in emerging markets, as consumers increasingly adopt more comprehensive beauty routines and upgrade to premium products.
Skincare stands out as the dominant segment in most markets, with global sales projected to exceed US$130 billion by 2019. &amp;ldquo;Consumers are allocating a significant portion of their beauty spending on skincare, averaging US$15 per person annually,&amp;rdquo; notes Irina Barbalova, Head of Beauty and Personal Care at Euromonitor International.</description></item><item><title>Ginvera and Wipro Unza are the top brands on mass-market facial cleanser shelves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</guid><description>Numerous facial cleansers are available at supermarkets, with prices starting at S$3.85 for a 100g tube. This article compares a selection of these cleansers to the author&amp;rsquo;s usual Eversoft avocado cleanser. While all the cleansers effectively cleaned the skin, none particularly stood out in terms of oil control, hydration, or other advertised benefits. The author prioritizes cleansers that lather well and don&amp;rsquo;t leave residue, and ultimately, ingredients, price, and fragrance are the deciding factors for repeat purchases.</description></item><item><title>The beauty industry is increasingly prioritizing sustainability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 19:01:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-is-increasingly-prioritizing-sustainability/</guid><description>The beauty industry needs a complete overhaul in its approach to sustainability and zero waste, focusing on every part of the process, according to market intelligence agency Mintel. The company highlights &amp;ldquo;Sub-Zero Waste&amp;rdquo; as a major trend that will shape the global beauty and personal care markets in the years to come.
The zero-waste movement is picking up speed as consumers become increasingly affected by environmental problems like natural disasters and water scarcity.</description></item><item><title>The ShadeScout Nails app has been launched by FaceCake</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shadescout-nails-app-has-been-launched-by-facecake/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shadescout-nails-app-has-been-launched-by-facecake/</guid><description>Source: iTunes.
FaceCake Marketing Technologies, the company behind the ShadeScout visual search beauty app, has introduced ShadeScout Nails. This free app, downloadable from the App Store, merges FaceCake&amp;rsquo;s unique color search technology with ShadeScout&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly design. The result is an innovative mobile shopping platform specifically for nail polish enthusiasts. This technology allows users to match beauty products to any color they encounter.
Linda Smith, Founder and CEO of FaceCake, highlights that their personalized platform simplifies the process of finding desired products, with ShadeScout apps serving as a prime example.</description></item><item><title>15 beauty tips for 2015 to celebrate the 15th anniversary of Giorgio Armani Beauty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-beauty-tips-for-2015-to-celebrate-the-15th-anniversary-of-giorgio-armani-beauty/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 12:34:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-beauty-tips-for-2015-to-celebrate-the-15th-anniversary-of-giorgio-armani-beauty/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oreal.
Giorgio Armani Beauty is commemorating the 15th anniversary of its makeup line with a series of 15 instructional videos. Released periodically throughout the year, these short clips will feature Linda Cantello, Giorgio Armani&amp;rsquo;s International Make-Up Artist, sharing simple makeup techniques and expert advice.
While the professional tips are specifically tailored for Armani products, the company asserts that anyone can easily understand and implement them.
Curious? Check out the videos:</description></item></channel></rss>