<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Competence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competence/</link><description>Recent content in Competence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/competence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinion 2/15: Report on the Hearing on the Future of EU External Trade Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</guid><description>David Kleimann and Gesa Kübek*
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held hearings on September 13 and 14 to address Opinion 2/15, which focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to finalize the EU-Singapore Free Trade Agreement (EUSFTA). This summary reviews the arguments presented by the Commission, the Council, and member states during the hearing. The initial section provides context and emphasizes the judgment&amp;rsquo;s systemic significance. Section II outlines the parties&amp;rsquo; primary arguments and highlights specific policy-related and novel legal points raised...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-2-15-report-on-the-hearing-on-the-future-of-eu-external-trade-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU foreign policy sanctions: utilizing EU criminal law powers to extend and enforce them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 02:59:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Pierre Blaché, via Wikicommons
*This blog post draws upon research for the forthcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law (OUP, 2023)
The EU Council recently decided to expand its criminal law authority to encompass breaches of EU foreign policy sanctions. Following this, the EU Commission presented a proposal for a Directive that aims to utilize this expanded authority to harmonize the criminal laws of Member States on this subject...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-foreign-policy-sanctions-utilizing-eu-criminal-law-powers-to-extend-and-enforce-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European citizens' initiative and the EU's authority regarding Greek debt restructuring.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 12:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</guid><description>Professor Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
Determining the European Union&amp;rsquo;s legal authority is a sensitive and increasingly complex area of EU law. This complexity is compounded by the intricate body of case law on legal bases, making it difficult to navigate even after decades of precedents. Since the Lisbon Treaty&amp;rsquo;s enactment, EU competency has become a significant area of focus for EU constitutional lawyers, requiring meticulous attention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-citizens-initiative-and-the-eu-s-authority-regarding-greek-debt-restructuring/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice of the European Union mindful of the boundaries of EU authority?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 16:24:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Vilija Vėlyvytė, British Academy Post-Doctoral Fellow, Somerville College, University of Oxford
Photo credit: civarmy, by wikipedia
My recently published book, ‘Judicial Authority in EU Internal Market Law: Implications for the Balance of Competences and Powers’ (Hart Publishing 2022), investigates how the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) broadens the EU’s authority through its interpretation of EU internal market law.
The expansion of EU power, often referred to as ‘competence creep’, into areas where the EU lacks explicit authority, such as public health and social security, has been extensively discussed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-mindful-of-the-boundaries-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>