<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Restaurant on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/restaurant/</link><description>Recent content in Restaurant on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/restaurant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amber is the sole Hong Kong restaurant featured in the World's 50 Best Restaurants 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 05:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</guid><description>Source: World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants website. Dishes from Amber. Amber, located in The Landmark Mandarin Oriental hotel in Hong Kong, has secured a place on the esteemed World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list for the sixth consecutive year, achieving the ranking of 20th. Notably, Amber is the sole representative from Hong Kong to be featured on this prestigious list. The World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants list, likened to the Oscars of fine dining, serves as an annual global celebration of gastronomy, acknowledging restaurants worldwide for their culinary excellence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amber-is-the-sole-hong-kong-restaurant-featured-in-the-world-s-50-best-restaurants-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Now in Hong Kong, exclusive to employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</guid><description>Source: Employees Only. View of the interior.
Employees Only (EO), the speakeasy and restaurant established in downtown Manhattan in 2004, has now opened a branch in Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s vibrant nightlife area, at 19 Lan Kwai Fong, Central.
This marks the group&amp;rsquo;s fourth global location and their second in Asia, following the successful launch of EO Singapore in June 2016.
Co-founder Igor Hadzismajlovic leads this project alongside Singapore-based partners Joshua and Sarissa Rodriguez Schwartz, GM Rachel Tow, and Beverage Director Owen Gibler...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-in-hong-kong-exclusive-to-employees/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Fils has been named the top restaurant in MENA for 2022</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 04:24:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</guid><description>Source: MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants. The Dubai restaurant 3 Fils earned the top ranking in the first Middle East &amp;amp; North Africa’s 50 Best Restaurants awards of 2022.
Located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Jumeirah Fishing Harbour, the casual eatery 3 Fils was established in 2016. Founded by two Emiratis and a Singaporean, the restaurant features a combination of Asian fusion cuisine and welcoming service.
William Drew, Director of Content for MENA&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, shared, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s an honor to name 3 Fils as the No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-fils-has-been-named-the-top-restaurant-in-mena-for-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ramada Abu Dhabi introduces Lebanese fine dining for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:32:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>The Ramada Abu Dhabi, a new hotel in the city&amp;rsquo;s central business district, is now home to Karamna Beirut, an upscale Lebanese dining experience. The restaurant is the brainchild of Tony Karam, a restaurateur whose family owns and operates the Karam restaurant chain.
Source: Ramada Abu Dhabi Hotel. The Karamna Beirut restaurant.
Rene Vincent, General Manager of the Ramada Abu Dhabi, highlights the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s impressive menu, curated to delight guests seeking refined Lebanese cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ramada-abu-dhabi-introduces-lebanese-fine-dining-for-the-first-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has welcomed three new celebrity chefs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. From left: Costa, Joinie-Maurin, Kurdahl, Semblat and Silva.
The Burj Al Arab Jumeirah has added three new chefs to its roster of acclaimed restaurants, aiming to elevate the dining experience for their guests.
Jose Silva, CEO of Jumeirah Group, stated that the addition of these culinary experts to their flagship Dubai hotel signifies the beginning of a more diverse and innovative culinary program. He emphasized their dedication to guest experiences as a crucial aspect of luxury hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-jumeirah-has-welcomed-three-new-celebrity-chefs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Special promotions for the Fireworks Celebration at the Mandarin Oriental, Macau</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Macau has special Fireworks Celebration packages perfect for corporate events, team building, or client appreciation. These packages provide a unique opportunity to experience the 26th Macau International Fireworks Display Contest.
Source: Mandarin Oriental Macau website.
Available on September 8th, 13th, 20th, 27th, and October 1st, 2014, the package starts at MOP4,388 and includes:
Overnight accommodations in a room or suite with panoramic fireworks views through expansive windows. A special four-course fireworks-themed dinner for two at the Vida Rica Restaurant, showcasing Chef Dominique Bugnand’s modern take on classic French cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/special-promotions-for-the-fireworks-celebration-at-the-mandarin-oriental-macau/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Art Basel at the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong offers menus that are inspired by art</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</guid><description>The Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong, the official hotel partner of Art Basel Hong Kong for the third consecutive year, will offer guests a range of special services this March. These include art-themed menus at the Michelin-starred restaurants Mandarin Grill + Bar and Pierre, as well as an exclusive accommodation package.
From March 11th to 17th, 2015, Chef Pierre Gagnaire of the two-Michelin-starred restaurant Pierre will present unique menus entitled &amp;ldquo;The Art of Pierre Gagnaire...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/art-basel-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hong-kong-offers-menus-that-are-inspired-by-art/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GwaKu offers tasty and budget-friendly dishes in the center of Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>Source: Gwaku&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This is their famous ayam percik.
GwaKu, a restaurant situated in Q Sentral close to KL Sentral, offers a rotating menu that keeps nearby office workers surprised about their lunch options. For example, one week could feature ayam perchik, while the following week might offer lamb stews.
Mike Ibrahim, the founder of GwaKu, emphasizes their commitment to using fresh, seasonal, and locally sourced ingredients. He explains, &amp;ldquo;By using in-season produce, we can ensure quality and freshness while also benefiting from lower prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hamad International Airport introduces two innovative dining experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 13:07:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Spizzico is one of two new dining establishments in the North Node at Hamad International Airport.
Qatar Duty Free (QDF), working with global travel dining provider HMSHost International, has revealed two new dining options in the North Node of Hamad International Airport (HIA) in Doha.
Burger Federation, a relaxed dining spot, has opened in the North Node of HIA&amp;rsquo;s main terminal. This restaurant presents elevated burgers made with gourmet ingredients...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hamad-international-airport-introduces-two-innovative-dining-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A more nutritious choice of French-Vietnamese cuisine in Tanjong Pagar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 21:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz. The L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz sautéed beef and spring rolls vermicelli salad (bún bò xào chả giò).
L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz, a Vietnamese eatery located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Tanjong Pagar financial area, serves both lunch and dinner.
The name &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphởriz&amp;rdquo; is a clever fusion of &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;euphorie&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;euphoria&amp;rdquo;), &amp;ldquo;phở&amp;rdquo; (the famous Vietnamese noodle soup), and &amp;ldquo;riz&amp;rdquo; (French for &amp;ldquo;rice&amp;rdquo;), hinting at the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s French-Vietnamese roots.
With origins in Saigon, Vietnam, the restaurant later established itself in Paris and played a key role in the three-decade success of Parisian Vietnamese restaurant Dong Huong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-more-nutritious-choice-of-french-vietnamese-cuisine-in-tanjong-pagar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Chinnery was rejuvenated at the Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong. The Chinnery.
The renowned Chinnery, located within Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Mandarin Oriental, has reopened its doors following a stylish interior update.
Originally a private gentlemen&amp;rsquo;s club, The Chinnery has been a beloved destination since 1963. Its classic British colonial design, featuring rich mahogany, plush carpets, and luxurious leather, continues to offer a peaceful escape amidst the bustling city. The overall ambiance is a perfect blend of history and enduring elegance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinnery-was-rejuvenated-at-the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Tandoor restaurant will be reopening on February 14th at the Holiday Inn Singapore Orchard City Centre</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</guid><description>Source: Holiday Inn Singapore Orchard City Centre. Selected highlights from Tandoor&amp;rsquo;s menu.
The Indian restaurant Tandoor will reopen its doors on February 14, 2023, after a two-year hiatus. Established in 1985, the restaurant boasts a refreshed, modern interior and serves authentic North Indian cuisine.
Chef Sunder, an award-winning chef, leads the culinary team at Tandoor, offering both à la carte and set menus. The menu reflects India&amp;rsquo;s diverse culinary traditions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tandoor-restaurant-will-be-reopening-on-february-14th-at-the-holiday-inn-singapore-orchard-city-centre/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bangi Golf Resort reintroduces the beloved Buffet Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 09:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: BGR.
From June 21st to July 15th, 2015, Bangi Golf Resort Restaurant (BGR) will be offering its special Buffet Ramadhan in honor of the holy month.
Executive Chef Kamaruddin highlights the Buffet Ramadhan&amp;rsquo;s popularity, stating that it has always been a top pick for gatherings of family, friends, and colleagues during Ramadhan. He emphasizes the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a diverse menu with new offerings while upholding the quality and authentic flavors of classic dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bangi-golf-resort-reintroduces-the-beloved-buffet-ramadhan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Singapore is backing F&amp;B and food manufacturers with innovative digital projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</guid><description>RESTAURANT 3.0: Embracing Technology in the Food Industry Enterprise Singapore showcased new digital solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) 2018. These solutions aim to help Singaporean food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and food manufacturing companies expand internationally and enhance their operational efficiency.
The showcased digital initiatives include a B2B online platform for food manufacturers and the RESTAURANT 3.0 exhibition for F&amp;amp;B businesses.
Enterprise Singapore, in collaboration with the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF), launched the &amp;ldquo;SMF SMART App&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Pavilion during FHA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Enjoying a meal out and a cozy overnight stay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:48:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</guid><description>Hong Kong Source: The Upper House. For the past four years, The Upper House has presented a unique, sustainably-crafted Christmas tree. This year, international architectural firm COLLECTIVE partners with Wu Chi Kai, one of Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s three remaining neon sign artisans, to create the Doodle Tree, a work that elevates traditional neon artistry. Rather than a typical flat design, the team created a three-dimensional neon sculpture using classic glass-bending methods and innovative approaches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-enjoying-a-meal-out-and-a-cozy-overnight-stay/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HungryGoWhere is collecting votes for its inaugural foodie awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</guid><description>The inaugural HungryGoWhere Awards voting period has opened. The food review platform HungryGoWhere revealed that public votes will solely decide the 26 award recipients.
Those interested in voting have until February 4th to cast their ballots on the awards website. The awards span five categories: Restaurants, Hawkers, Drinks, Occasions, and Best of the Best. After the voting period ends, participants will be entered into a lucky draw...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FUMI creates authentic Japanese dining experiences for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</guid><description>Source: FUMI Facebook page. FUMI sushi.
FUMI, a new Japanese eatery, seeks to share the finest Japanese cuisine in Hong Kong within a space adorned with Japanese art, furnishings, and tableware. They offer a range of dining experiences, from elaborate omakase and kaiseki dinners to individual dishes and set lunch options.
Situated in California Tower, FUMI sources the highest quality seasonal ingredients directly from Japan daily. Flown in and delivered straight to their kitchen, these ingredients are often prepared and served within hours of being harvested, guaranteeing freshness in their sushi, sashimi, omakase, and kaiseki preparations, as well as a variety of seasonal menus...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Burj Al Arab Terrace redefines the limits of construction, design, architecture, and hospitality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:50:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah Group. The Burj Al Arab Terrace.
The Burj Al Arab Terrace, located in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s most famous hotel, is a unique combination of a restaurant, pool, beach, and cabana area. Constructed using innovative marine and off-site methods, this structure represents a world-first. Marine construction experts ADMARES developed the terrace at a shipyard in Finland, transporting it to Dubai in eight separate sections by ship. This approach minimized any negative impact on hotel guests, the ocean floor, and marine life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-burj-al-arab-terrace-redefines-the-limits-of-construction-design-architecture-and-hospitality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an international Iftar at StraitsKitchen</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 10:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</guid><description>Source: Grand Hyatt Singapore website.
For the observance of Ramadan, StraitsKitchen at the Grand Hyatt Singapore welcomes guests to experience a wide array of Asian flavors. Their iftar buffet features dishes from various countries, including Indonesia, India, Lebanon, Saudi Arabia, and Turkey, alongside Singaporean favorites. All food is freshly made in halal-certified kitchens.
Guests can expect Middle Eastern specialties such as roasted leg of lamb from Saudi Arabia, Lebanese grilled fish (samke harra), shawarma, Moroccan mezze, and classic desserts like baklava, basbousa, and kanafa bil cream...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-international-iftar-at-straitskitchen/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience an innovative approach to Thai cuisine at Jungle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-innovative-approach-to-thai-cuisine-at-jungle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-innovative-approach-to-thai-cuisine-at-jungle/</guid><description>Source: Jungle. Traditional claypot and grilled specialties at Jungle.
Jungle, a Thai grill and bar, has recently opened in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ann Siang Hill. The restaurant features a wide variety of regional dishes crafted with carefully selected ingredients, unique in-house preparation methods, and fire-based cooking techniques.
Inspired by the lively atmosphere of Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s late-night bars and bustling streets, Jungle offers a relaxed dining setting featuring an open-fire kitchen and a soundtrack of classic funk and soul music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-innovative-approach-to-thai-cuisine-at-jungle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-an-innovative-approach-to-thai-cuisine-at-jungle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ottomani offers a fresh and personalized dining experience with a modern twist on Middle Eastern cuisine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ottomani-offers-a-fresh-and-personalized-dining-experience-with-a-modern-twist-on-middle-eastern-cuisine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 04:03:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ottomani-offers-a-fresh-and-personalized-dining-experience-with-a-modern-twist-on-middle-eastern-cuisine/</guid><description>The Ottomani, a new Middle Eastern supper club in Singapore, offers a unique dining experience reminiscent of a time when personalized service was paramount. The restaurant is a collaboration between The Dandy Partnership, known for bringing dining concepts like Neon Pigeon, Summerlong, and Fat Prince to Singapore, and Executive Chef Nic Philip.
Chef Philip, who honed his skills at renowned London establishments such as The Clove Club (#26 on the World&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best list) and Yotam Ottolenghi&amp;rsquo;s Michelin-starred Nopi, brings his extensive expertise in Middle Eastern flavors and ingredients to Ottomani...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ottomani-offers-a-fresh-and-personalized-dining-experience-with-a-modern-twist-on-middle-eastern-cuisine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ottomani-offers-a-fresh-and-personalized-dining-experience-with-a-modern-twist-on-middle-eastern-cuisine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Big Street set meals provide even greater value for your money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</guid><description>Source: Big Street.
The Singaporean eatery Big Street is offering a special multi-course meal for S$26 per person during June. This offer requires a minimum of two diners and is valid for both lunch and dinner.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the special meal includes:
Appetiser: Garden greens with cherry tomato salad Soup: Oriental chicken with snow fungus and wolfberry soup Main dishes: Hainanese steamed kampong chicken Seasonal vegetables with mushrooms Big Street chili king prawn Thai fragrant steamed rice If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something else, Big Street&amp;rsquo;s standard set lunch costs S$9...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>May's Big Street meal promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Big Street. Chilli slipper lobster in prata bag.
Big Street, a restaurant and lounge with air conditioning and multiple levels, is offering a special set meal deal throughout May in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day, available to everyone.
Priced at S$26 per person (minimum of two people), this deal includes an appetizer, soup, main course, and dessert.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the set meal promotion includes:
Appetiser: Fresh garden salad served with crispy chicken..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Marina Mandarin Singapore welcomes the arrival of hairy crabs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</guid><description>Peach Blossoms, the renowned Cantonese restaurant located on the 5th level of Marina Mandarin Singapore, is now offering a seasonal delicacy flown in from Shanghai, China: hairy crabs.
Also at the Marina Mandarin, on the 4th level, the AquaMarine buffet restaurant is spotlighting seafood until October 29th.
Source: Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
AquaMarine features an array of Asian dishes, including Vietnamese Braised Fish in Clay Pot, Thai Curry Mud Crab, authentic Filipino Beef Adobo, fresh Cambodian Fish Curry, and many more...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Toyo Koda will enhance the menus at Le Passage Mohkan Shan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</guid><description>Source: Le Passage Mohkan Shan website.
Le Passage Mohkan Shan, a French-style hotel and restaurant nestled in its own private tea plantation at the base of Moganshan* mountain in China, has appointed Toyo Koda as its new head chef. This strategic hire emphasizes the hotel&amp;rsquo;s aim to become a premier culinary destination in Asia.
Chef Toyo, previously recognized as one of Asia&amp;rsquo;s top chefs by the San Pellegrino Restaurant Awards in 2013 for his role at Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French restaurant Franck, is poised to transform the hotel&amp;rsquo;s culinary offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>