<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Metro Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Metro Ethernet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/metro-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will You Save With Fractional Line Services?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:43:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-you-save-with-fractional-line-services/</guid><description>You might think ordering less bandwidth would save you money, but when it comes to telecom lines, that&amp;rsquo;s not always the case. While getting a fraction of a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s capacity seemed like a good idea for those who didn&amp;rsquo;t need the full 1.5 Mbps, the cost savings weren&amp;rsquo;t as significant as one might expect.
The issue is that the infrastructure for a T1 line, the &amp;ldquo;pipe,&amp;rdquo; has a fixed capacity regardless of actual usage.</description></item><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers.</description></item><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services.</description></item><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth To Support Branch Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</guid><description>Many businesses need multiple locations in a region to stay close to their customers. Connecting these branches seamlessly without breaking the bank is a common challenge. Thankfully, two high-performance networking technologies, Metro Ethernet and MPLS Networks, offer affordable solutions that weren&amp;rsquo;t available even a decade ago.
Carrier Ethernet takes the local networking capabilities of Ethernet and extends them across entire cities. This means easy connection and efficient transmission without needing protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>How Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-works/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you spending too much on connecting your different business locations? Do you desire scalable bandwidth with reliable, dedicated speed, minimal lag, and uninterrupted data flow? You might be overlooking a crucial network solution. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how fiber optic Metro Ethernet connections can benefit your business:
Having a single provider manage both the core network and the connections to each location offers significant cost savings. Leading Metro Ethernet providers can leverage their infrastructure to save you money compared to leasing from local phone companies.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Windfall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</guid><description>When budgets are strained, expanding into new markets and generating much-needed revenue often depends on increasing Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. However, more bandwidth usually means higher expenses, creating a difficult situation.
It&amp;rsquo;s generally accepted that increasing bandwidth leads to increased costs. For instance, 10 Mbps will likely cost more than 1 Mbps, although there might be a volume discount. But is it possible to get more bandwidth while paying less overall?</description></item><item><title>Why Fiber Optic Metro Ethernet Makes So Much Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-fiber-optic-metro-ethernet-makes-so-much-sense/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When it comes to connecting your business locations, having the right network setup is crucial. While multiple options exist, Metro Ethernet networks offer unique advantages for optimal performance.
Metro Ethernet (Metro E) networks, a specialized type of Metropolitan Area Network (MAN), provide two key advantages. Firstly, they maintain the Ethernet protocol throughout your network, unlike other options that require conversions. Secondly, Metro Ethernet networks, especially those based on fiber optics, offer cost advantages compared to alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet.</description></item><item><title>Find Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 04:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses currently using T1 lines for dedicated internet or point-to-point connections might be seeking ways to increase bandwidth without the high costs of upgrading to DS3 fiber optic cable. Metro Ethernet offers a solution. But how can you find it?
Locating Metro Ethernet service is straightforward with the right approach. Similar to finding anything else, the key is knowing where to look. A specialized tool designed to locate and map available Ethernet bandwidth in your vicinity is essential.</description></item><item><title>EarthLink Means Business With 10 GigE Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-means-business-with-10-gige-fiber/</guid><description>EarthLink, known for its dial-up internet service, has a lesser-known side: EarthLink Business. This division provides fiber optic network solutions for businesses of all sizes, with over 28,000 miles of fiber infrastructure already in place and expanding. They are currently establishing two 10 Gigabit Ethernet fiber rings in Ohio and Eastern Pennsylvania, along with a high-speed fiber route between Philadelphia and Pittsburgh.
This growth in high-bandwidth infrastructure is driven by the increasing automation and cloud adoption by businesses.</description></item><item><title>What is Ethernet WAN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 06:55:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>Ethernet WAN is the most significant advancement in business broadband since T1 service prices dropped. What exactly is Ethernet WAN, and why should you care?
Ethernet has become the dominant standard for Local Area Networks (LANs). You could say that Ethernet is everywhere. An RJ45 Ethernet jack is standard on every desktop and laptop computer. You might not get a CD-ROM drive, probably won&amp;rsquo;t get a floppy disc drive, and may never use the phone modem jack again.</description></item><item><title>Why Bandwidth is Cheap Downtown</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 03:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-bandwidth-is-cheap-downtown/</guid><description>Want to increase your business internet speed without breaking the bank? Head downtown! The city center offers more competition and cheaper prices than anywhere else. Can&amp;rsquo;t relocate for better bandwidth deals? There&amp;rsquo;s a comparable solution that works for many businesses.
Why is bandwidth cheaper downtown when real estate is so expensive? The answer is density. Imagine real estate as a pie: limited supply and high demand for the best slices drive up prices.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet DS3 Bandwidth Comparison</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ds3-bandwidth-comparison/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has grown continuously since T1 lines became the norm for dedicated internet access and private point-to-point connections. If you currently use DS3 bandwidth services or are thinking about an upgrade, comparing your wide area network (WAN) bandwidth choices is essential.
DS3, a 45 Mbps service, represents the traditional high-bandwidth network connection and is equivalent in speed to a T3 line. These days, most DS3 services are delivered via fiber optic cables, with a copper handoff point at the demarcation point.</description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>From LAN to MAN to WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-lan-to-man-to-wan/</guid><description>The world is currently experiencing a revolution in network technology. While computer networks have historically relied on various communication protocols, some adapted from the telephone industry, there’s a growing trend towards adopting IP as a universal networking standard. This shift towards IP encompasses all network types, from local area networks (LANs) to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and wide area networks (WANs).
This standardization trend originated in LANs. Today, most LANs utilize Ethernet network interfaces due to economies of scale rather than inherent superiority.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro Ethernet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 04:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is a common standard for local networks. Metro Ethernet expands on this, offering the same functionality over larger distances within a metropolitan area. It&amp;rsquo;s like regular Ethernet but reaches further.
Metro Ethernet feels just like local Ethernet, using the same standard connectors. You can connect two networks in separate locations without needing special equipment.
This simplicity is thanks to the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), which sets standards ensuring compatibility between different providers and devices.</description></item><item><title>Ether Rabbit Finds Cheap Ethernet Fast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ether-rabbit-finds-cheap-ethernet-fast/</guid><description>Looking for the best deals on Metro Ethernet services? Look no further! We&amp;rsquo;re experts in finding affordable business Ethernet connections.
Curious about our services? Check out our updated website:
Need a quote? Tell us what you need using our inquiry form. Whether you have specific requirements or just want to explore options, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help.
Go ahead and use this inquiry form now. We&amp;rsquo;ll find the right service for you quickly.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Buildings Offer High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Do you want to upgrade your internet speed from slow copper or fixed wireless connections to the rapid speeds offered by fiber optic cables? Are you trying to avoid the high cost of installing new fiber optic cables? If so, you should consider moving into a fiber building.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; a fiber building isn&amp;rsquo;t constructed from exotic materials like carbon fiber. The term &amp;ldquo;fiber&amp;rdquo; refers to the type of telecommunication services already available within the building.</description></item><item><title>Can Copper Really Replace Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 00:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-copper-really-replace-fiber/</guid><description>Advancements in telecommunications technology consistently push for increased bandwidth. While twisted pair copper wiring has been the backbone of telecom services since the invention of the telephone, its limitations have become apparent with the demand for higher bandwidths.
Is it possible that copper pair wiring could compete with fiber optic transmission for bandwidths exceeding 1.5 Mbps or support telephone trunks with more than 24 lines? Surprisingly, it can, and the technology is currently available.</description></item><item><title>Speed of Metro Ethernet Zooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speed-of-metro-ethernet-zooming/</guid><description>Forget Superman, when it comes to speed and affordability, Metro Ethernet is the real superhero of business bandwidth solutions. It surpasses conventional options like T1 and DS3, offering significantly faster speeds at a lower cost.
Metro Ethernet is in high demand, rapidly becoming the go-to choice for businesses. Its speed can be significantly higher than what you&amp;rsquo;re currently using, and it&amp;rsquo;s generally more cost-effective per Mbps compared to other options, including T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Future Proofing Your WAN With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Wide area networks (WANs) are changing. While once reliant on telephone technology, core networks are shifting towards packet-switched services to handle the increasing dominance of data and video traffic over voice. This shift raises questions for businesses about adapting their connections to stay current.
Many organizations face growing bandwidth demands. As their service contracts near renewal, they are reevaluating options, considering newer Ethernet services as alternatives to traditional T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Handle Big Data With Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:47:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handle-big-data-with-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>The age of &amp;ldquo;big data&amp;rdquo; is upon us. But what does that mean? Big data refers to massive datasets that are too large for typical database management tools. Think terabytes, petabytes, exabytes, and even zettabytes – each one thousands of times larger than the last.
This surge in data originates from sources like computer simulations, financial modeling, research projects, sensor data, and high-definition video processing, which generate terabytes of information rapidly.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Corporate Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:44:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-corporate-ethernet/</guid><description>For medium to large businesses, a 100 Mbps connection speed is becoming the new norm. While this might seem excessive and expensive, it&amp;rsquo;s actually neither. In essence, Fast Ethernet is taking over the role of DS3.
A decade ago, a 1.5 Mbps T1 line was considered high bandwidth. Today&amp;rsquo;s need for 100 Mbps reflects the significant evolution of application requirements. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from basic video conferencing to high-definition, two-way video and telepresence.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Domination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</guid><description>In the near future, Ethernet may become the sole networking standard.
Previously, local networking involved choices like Token Bus or Token Ring. Today, almost every Network Interface Card (NIC) uses Ethernet, with speeds ranging from 10 to 1,000 Mbps, and 10 Gbps becoming increasingly affordable. Local Area Networks (LANs) predominantly use switched Ethernet over twisted pair copper wiring with RJ-45 connectors, although fiber optics is becoming a competitor.
Cost drives this standardization.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Got a Bandwidth Jones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 13:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/got-a-bandwidth-jones/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s no limit to how much bandwidth we need, similar to how we always desire more money, health, or chocolate. As we gain more bandwidth, we discover new ways to utilize it. The most sought-after types are wireless, offering flexibility, and fiber optic, providing high capacity. Property owners who provide both to their business tenants might find their properties more appealing than those offering health, wealth, or even delicious chocolate.</description></item><item><title>WiMAX 2 Will Challenge Fiber For Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</guid><description>The idea that copper and wireless technologies are outdated in terms of bandwidth is circulating. While copper has found new life as a last-mile solution for Metro Ethernet services, and wireless stands out for its unmatched mobility, a new wireless technology is emerging that might surpass even fiber optic speeds.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to think that wireless could outpace fiber in terms of bandwidth.
While not all fiber optic services offer top speeds of 10 GigE, with many customers receiving 50 to 100 Mbps, especially in the case of Fiber To The Home (FTTH), the prospect of achieving 100 to 300 Mbps wirelessly anywhere in a city is enticing.</description></item><item><title>Steppin' Out With My Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/steppin-out-with-my-ethernet/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard way we connect computers in a local network. Carrier Ethernet extends this familiar technology beyond the office to connect locations across cities and even countries.
While other technologies like DSL and fiber optics offer similar connectivity, Carrier Ethernet provides simpler management. It&amp;rsquo;s like having very long wires connecting all your offices, factories, and warehouses as one network. The other major advantage? Lower costs. Specialized Ethernet providers utilize modern IP networks and are rapidly expanding their reach to connect businesses.</description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item><item><title>T1 Lease Costs Reduced Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</guid><description>In the past, T1 lines were a costly telecommunication option accessible only to large companies and the telecom sector. While competition has significantly lowered prices since then, there&amp;rsquo;s been another recent plunge. But what&amp;rsquo;s driving this trend?
Originally, T1 lines, part of the T-Carrier telephony standard, were trunk lines connecting central offices within telephone companies. Later, corporate telecom departments adopted them for PBX phone systems and internet service. They became crucial for local internet providers, particularly dial-up services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth Gets Incrementally Finer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 04:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-gets-incrementally-finer/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet service has been very beneficial for businesses of all sizes. It not only keeps LAN-WAN-LAN connections using the Ethernet protocol, but lease prices are also typically much lower per Mbps than older services like T-Carrier and SONET. But wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have the ideal line speed without settling for a service that&amp;rsquo;s too small or paying too much for unnecessary bandwidth?
Fortunately, XO Communications, a leading Metro Ethernet WAN service provider, now offers a wide range of bandwidth options for businesses with on-net fiber optic service.</description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV.</description></item><item><title>Eliminating the WAN Choke Point</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 02:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-the-wan-choke-point/</guid><description>The speed difference between LANs (Local Area Networks) and WANs (Wide Area Networks) is often significant. This becomes apparent when accessing the internet or transferring files, as actions that are near-instantaneous within a local network can take much longer externally. This is known as the WAN choke point.
Visualize this by comparing a highway exit onto a crowded street during rush hour or trying to fill a pool using a garden hose connected to the main water supply.</description></item><item><title>Copper Decommissioning Expands Demand for Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-decommissioning-expands-demand-for-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business still relies on DSL, T1 lines, or Ethernet over Copper for internet connectivity, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider Metro Ethernet over Fiber. This superior option offers greater bandwidth at a more competitive price, with the added benefit of long-term availability.
Copper Decommissioning is Now
While copper-based telecom services have been the standard for the past century, their time is ending. Twisted pair telephone lines, despite their long reign, are being phased out as they struggle to meet current and future bandwidth requirements.</description></item><item><title>Cut Telecom Line Expenses, Not Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</guid><description>During economic downturns, businesses often look to cut costs to stay afloat. While eliminating unnecessary expenses is a good start, managers may soon scrutinize even essential budget items.
Instead of panicking and making rash decisions, it&amp;rsquo;s best to proactively identify reasonable cost reductions. This way, you can present well-thought-out proposals and maintain some control over the process.
The key is to maintain productivity while reducing expenses. Instead of completely cutting essential services, focus on achieving the same functionality for less money.</description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably.</description></item><item><title>What is Metro E?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 15:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-metro-e/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) is a widely used network service experiencing rapid growth.
Similar to the Ethernet protocol used in Local Area Networks (LANs), Metro E has been adapted for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) through standardization efforts by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), an industry group focused on Carrier Ethernet.
Here&amp;rsquo;s why Metro E deserves your attention as a potential solution for your business: it&amp;rsquo;s a better fit for contemporary packet-switched networks compared to older telecom options like T1.</description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area.</description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Speeds Without DS3 Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 17:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-speeds-without-ds3-prices/</guid><description>Businesses needing substantial bandwidth for tasks like online commerce, video streaming, medical data transfer, or dedicated internet access have historically relied on DS3 connections. These provided speeds exceeding T1 lines. However, a new option delivers comparable speeds without the high price tag: Metro Ethernet and Carrier Ethernet.
These terms represent regional and long-distance high-bandwidth transport services using the Ethernet protocol. An Ethernet WAN connection connects your LAN to another business location, a network of multiple locations, or a dedicated high-speed internet connection.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Deals for MSPs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 16:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-deals-for-msps/</guid><description>Managed Service Providers (MSPs) can provide more value to their clients by helping them find better deals on WAN bandwidth, in addition to their existing IT services. Many companies are unaware of the changes in the telecommunications market and the cheaper options now available.
A basic bandwidth service that businesses should consider is T1, which offers reliable voice and/or data services with a service level agreement. T1 prices have significantly decreased this decade, often by 50% or even 67%.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard about Metro Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s rise in popularity for business WAN connections, particularly in major cities with concentrated business areas. These areas have been the primary focus of competitive bandwidth providers offering lower per-Mbps pricing. However, you might assume that Ethernet WAN services are only accessible in downtown areas or large suburbs.
This is about to change. Hatteras Networks has introduced a line of repeater and line power modules that extend Mid-Band Ethernet service up to 25 miles over standard telephone lines.</description></item><item><title>Can Ethernet Enable Electronic Health Care?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 01:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/</guid><description>The healthcare industry has significant potential for service enhancement and cost reduction. Digitizing, storing, and transferring medical records, along with automating administrative tasks, are readily achievable improvements. Additionally, innovations like remote diagnostics can extend healthcare access to underserved areas and emergency situations. However, the lack of widespread broadband infrastructure, particularly in rural areas, hinders progress.
The limited availability of high-speed internet connections poses a significant obstacle. Many healthcare facilities rely on outdated T1 lines, which are inadequate for transmitting large, high-resolution medical images and electronic medical records, impacting productivity.</description></item><item><title>Data Center Services For You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 06:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-center-services-for-you/</guid><description>Smaller companies often admire the data centers of larger organizations, but they may not realize that similar services are within their reach.
The key is to only own assets crucial to your business and lease the rest, including data center services. You don&amp;rsquo;t need a massive, secure facility with 24/7 staff, backup generators, and unlimited bandwidth. These services are available on a pay-as-you-go basis.
Two types of data centers are eager to accommodate your business.</description></item></channel></rss>