<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T3 Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t3-lines/</link><description>Recent content in T3 Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:40:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t3-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telecommunication DS3 Affordable For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</guid><description>Modern businesses need increasing levels of bandwidth to accommodate computer-driven processes that enhance productivity. When a T1 line reaches its capacity, and more bandwidth is necessary, there are options to consider.
A logical next step, if bandwidth needs have gradually increased, is to bond a second T1 line with the first. This doubles the capacity, providing a 3 Mbps WAN connection. Additional T1 lines can be bonded to further multiply the bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance.</description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Replaces DS3 and T3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 19:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-replaces-ds3-and-t3/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
T3 lines and DS3 bandwidth, once a cornerstone of telecom services, are becoming outdated with the emergence of newer technologies like Carrier Ethernet WAN, point-to-point microwave for business, and DOCSIS 3 cable broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options available for your business in the 50 to 1000 Mbps speed range.
Transitioning from Traditional Telco T1 Lines
Bell Labs revolutionized long-distance digital transmission after World War II with their T-Carrier system, introducing T1 and T3 services.</description></item></channel></rss>