<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/policy/</link><description>Recent content in Policy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/policy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2018 Budget is on technology, innovation, and building capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Budget 2018 site. View of Singapore skyline.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Trade and Industry (MTI) anticipates more broad-based economic growth across sectors in 2018, albeit at a moderated pace compared to the heights of 2017, according to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Financial Minister Heng Swee Keat during his Budget 2018 speech.
Minister Heng emphasized the need for Singapore to adapt to three major shifts in the coming decade:
Asia&amp;rsquo;s increasing global economic influence.</description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways has implemented improvements to its baggage policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-has-implemented-improvements-to-its-baggage-policy/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Starting September 14, 2015, Etihad Airways will launch its new Fare Choices tariff program, which includes changes to its baggage policy. The airline claims these updates will benefit travelers, particularly those enrolled in the Etihad Guest loyalty program.
This new policy aims to provide more flexibility and align Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; baggage policies with partner airlines by catering to individual customer needs. Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, states: “This is about offering a fair and transparent baggage concept that is an industry best practice.</description></item></channel></rss>