<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-line/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone Line on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services.</description></item><item><title>Residential and Small Business VoIP Rates Crushed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</guid><description>In recent years, VoIP telephony, also known as broadband phone service, has transformed from a niche computer application into a major competitor to traditional telephone services. This shift is largely due to the widespread adoption of broadband internet and its increased availability to small businesses. As a result of increased broadband access, there&amp;rsquo;s been a surge in VoIP providers, with Phone Power emerging as a major player. Phone Power is disrupting the industry by offering unlimited residential and small home-based business service plans for less than $15 per month.</description></item></channel></rss>