<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skin/</link><description>Recent content in Skin on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Herbalife introduces a new skincare line to the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Herbalife, a nutrition company, has expanded its product line with the launch of Herbalife SKIN, a new skincare collection available in Asia Pacific markets. This line complements Herbalife&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;outer nutrition&amp;rdquo; range, which focuses on achieving healthy, youthful skin through a blend of natural ingredients, botanicals, extracts, and scientific formulation.
[Image of Herbalife logo]
Herbalife SKIN products are designed to create softer, smoother, and more radiant skin while minimizing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles.</description></item><item><title>L’Oréal introduces a flexible skin sensor that tracks sun exposure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/l-or-al-introduces-a-flexible-skin-sensor-that-tracks-sun-exposure/</guid><description>Source: L’Oréal. Model wearing a My UV patch.
L’Oréal recently introduced My UV Patch at the Consumer Electronics Show. It is the first flexible skin sensor designed to track UV exposure and promote sun-safety awareness among consumers. This innovation arrives as sun exposure has become a significant health concern, with 90% of non-melanoma skin cancers linked to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from the sun, in addition to skin pigmentation and premature aging.</description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals introduces a new line of mineral color correctors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</guid><description>Source: Everyday Minerals website.
Everyday Minerals claims to have formulated its finest mineral color correctors to date. These all-natural correctors feature jojoba esters, enabling them to conceal imperfections seamlessly without appearing heavy.
The new Jojoba Color Correctors are offered in four shades, each formulated for a specific purpose. The pink-hued Brighten Color Corrector utilizes light-diffusing pigments to instantly illuminate dark circles under the eyes. The Cover Color Corrector, in a natural skin tone, can be used after foundation for concealing blemishes.</description></item><item><title>Luxury handbags by Jennifer Mak are available for purchase at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Jennifer Mak&amp;rsquo;s namesake luxury handbag brand is available on the designer floor of Singapore’s Tangs flagship department store in Orchard Road for a limited time, ending February 28, 2015. The brand uses premium materials like python, ostrich, lizard, stingray, and crocodile skin, creating handbags known for their classic lines, elegance, and one-of-a-kind appeal.
Source: Jennifer Mak. Part of the collection on the second floor at Tang&amp;rsquo;s.
&amp;ldquo;The Jennifer Mak woman doesn&amp;rsquo;t seek attention, but she undoubtedly commands it,&amp;rdquo; says Jennifer Mak, the brand&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>Discover the most common skin conditions on the Better Skin microsite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-common-skin-conditions-on-the-better-skin-microsite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-the-most-common-skin-conditions-on-the-better-skin-microsite/</guid><description>Source: Better Skin Microsite.
A recently launched online platform aims to raise public understanding of common skin issues, like eczema and melasma, and their available treatments.
Supported by Galderma, a company specializing in skincare treatments, the Better Skin microsite features informative videos about various skin conditions. It also includes brief discussions with medical professionals who address questions regarding potential impacts and treatment choices.</description></item></channel></rss>