<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Communications on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-communications/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Communications on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:09:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-communications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1,000,000 Miles of Metro Ethernet Fiber And Growing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 23:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t assume Metro Ethernet is a small, insignificant service. XO Communications alone has a vast network of metro fiber, connecting thousands of buildings. And that&amp;rsquo;s just one provider, not even counting Ethernet over Copper options.
Metro Ethernet and its long-distance counterpart, Carrier Ethernet, are the future of telecommunications. The world is shifting from traditional circuit-based communication to packet-based IP networks. While your current internet might be a T1 line, your data likely transitions to an IP-based backbone at your provider&amp;rsquo;s location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-000-000-miles-of-metro-ethernet-fiber-and-growing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Fiber Diet for Business Not Expensive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</guid><description>With business picking up, many companies are hitting a wall – their internet connections can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the increased data flow. The solution? A high-fiber diet for their network.
Fiber optic cables are incredibly efficient. A single strand can handle massive amounts of voice, data, and video simultaneously, far exceeding the needs of most businesses. This capacity can be further multiplied by splitting the light into different wavelengths, each carrying gigabits per second...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-fiber-diet-for-business-not-expensive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 GigE in the Long Run</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 14:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</guid><description>As internet and private network users demand increasingly higher bandwidth, long-haul fiber optic networks, including those used by regional and national carriers, are being upgraded to accommodate this growth. The current standard is 40 Gbps, but companies like XO Communications and Infinera are pushing boundaries by showcasing 100 Gigabit Ethernet on XO&amp;rsquo;s long-haul DWDM network.
This partnership addresses two key requirements: a high-capacity long-haul network and equipment capable of utilizing that capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gige-in-the-long-run/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Communications Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 06:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a common understanding that our capacity for using twisted pair copper for bandwidth is reaching its limit. We&amp;rsquo;re even facing a serious shortage of wireless bandwidth. The Federal Communications Commission is searching for underused frequencies to allocate for wireless broadband. However, the idea that technology might stall due to depleted spectral resources is misguided if we consider an innovative solution.
Radio frequencies are a finite resource. Lower frequencies are less useful due to their limited capacity for carrying information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-communications-without-the-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There Will Be Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</guid><description>The 19th and 20th centuries were defined by the gold rush and oil boom, respectively. Similarly, the 21st century is witnessing a fiber optic revolution. Fiber optic communication has become essential for modern businesses. This era presents lucrative opportunities for entrepreneurs to capitalize on the insatiable demand for high-bandwidth communication. A new technology has emerged, promising to reshape the competitive landscape.
Consider a scenario where two telecommunications providers are discussing the industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Network Expansion Underway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</guid><description>Our society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to bandwidth is evident with the recent launch of a massive dark fiber network project by Allied Fiber. This project will encircle the US with 548 dark fibers and 300 tower sites.
Fiber optic communication is experiencing a resurgence and this time it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. Unlike the failed attempt in the 1990s, the unused fiber optic cables laid then are likely to be utilized soon due to the resurfacing of the telecommunication revolution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>