<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trademark on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trademark/</link><description>Recent content in Trademark on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/trademark/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India is enhancing its intellectual property infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</guid><description>The Indian government has decided to continue its efforts to improve its intellectual property (IP) offices. This initiative, part of the 12th Plan (2012-2017), will cost Rs309.6 crore, with Rs258 crore allocated for the 12th Plan and Rs51.6 crore for the 13th Plan.
This decision recognizes the increasing importance of IP in a globalized economy, India&amp;rsquo;s recent membership in the Madrid Protocol (April 2013), and the Controller General of Patents, Designs, and Trademarks (CGPDTM) office&amp;rsquo;s new role as an International Searching and Preliminary Examining Authority (ISA/IPEA) under the Patent Cooperation Treaty (starting October 2013)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>INTA: Companies that invest in trademarks make a significant contribution to the economies of ASEAN countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 22:15:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</guid><description>A new report from the International Trademark Association (INTA) reveals that industries heavily reliant on trademarks play a substantial role in the economies of five key ASEAN nations: Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand. The report, titled The Economic Contribution of Trademark-Intensive Industries in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, Singapore, and Thailand, shows that these industries stimulate job growth across sectors and significantly contribute to international trade. Industries classified as &amp;ldquo;trademark-intensive&amp;rdquo; are those that file a higher number of trademarks compared to others, adjusted for the total employment within each industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inta-companies-that-invest-in-trademarks-make-a-significant-contribution-to-the-economies-of-asean-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>