<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Transport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-transport/</link><description>Recent content in IP Transport on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>