<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Innovation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/innovation/</link><description>Recent content in Innovation on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations.</description></item><item><title>Singapore and Japan will work together to promote collaboration and assist in the development of businesses and startups</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-japan-will-work-together-to-promote-collaboration-and-assist-in-the-development-of-businesses-and-startups/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 22:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-japan-will-work-together-to-promote-collaboration-and-assist-in-the-development-of-businesses-and-startups/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Economic Development Board (EDB) and Enterprise Singapore have partnered with the Japan External Trade Organisation (JETRO) to enhance support for startups and businesses in both Singapore and Japan. This agreement was formalized during the ASEAN Economic Ministers’ Meeting 2018.
The collaboration aims to create opportunities for startups and businesses by facilitating information exchange and organizing joint initiatives and events. This will strengthen the connection between the innovation ecosystems of Singapore and Japan.</description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC).</description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm.</description></item><item><title>Clarivate Analytics states that global innovation is shifting its focus from quantity to quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 07:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarivate-analytics-states-that-global-innovation-is-shifting-its-focus-from-quantity-to-quality/</guid><description>Source: Clarivate Analytics infographic.
Clarivate Analytics, previously known as the Intellectual Property &amp;amp; Science division of Thomson Reuters, has announced its 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators. Utilizing unique proprietary data analysis, the report recognizes the world&amp;rsquo;s most innovative companies and institutions.
Now in its sixth year, the 2016 Top 100 Global Innovators report highlights a significant change in approach among leading global innovators, according to Clarivate Analytics. The report shows a decline in patent filings coupled with an increase in grant rates.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean companies are prioritizing cloud technology to gain a competitive edge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-companies-are-prioritizing-cloud-technology-to-gain-a-competitive-edge/</guid><description>Source: VMware infographic.
VMware, a leading company in virtualization and cloud infrastructure, recently shared the results of their vForum Singapore Business Survey. The survey shows a positive attitude toward hybrid cloud solutions, which combine public cloud services with internal cloud technology, as a method of driving growth, efficiency, and innovation. Almost every business surveyed (90%) believes that the cloud can facilitate innovation, and nearly half (44%) prefer a hybrid cloud model for their IT infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Numerous methods to ignite internal innovation at TRA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-methods-to-ignite-internal-innovation-at-tra/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 06:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-methods-to-ignite-internal-innovation-at-tra/</guid><description>Source: TRA.
The Telecommunications Regulatory Authority (TRA) has implemented new programs to encourage internal innovation. Employees now have expanded opportunities to share their insights and actively participate in the TRA&amp;rsquo;s development.
The Idea for Tomorrow initiative, implemented at both TRA’s Abu Dhabi and Dubai locations, features idea boards on each floor. This allows employees a convenient method for sharing suggestions. TRA’s Innovation Committee will then select ideas with the most potential to improve TRA&amp;rsquo;s services, work environment, and the telecommunications sector as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) reveals initiatives to promote innovation in the industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-monetary-authority-of-singapore-mas-reveals-initiatives-to-promote-innovation-in-the-industry/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) outlined its plans to support the digitalization recommendations put forth by the Committee on the Future Economy (CFE) to help prepare the financial sector for the future.
MAS will facilitate infrastructure projects aimed at driving innovation, enhancing market efficiency, improving customer service, and strengthening Singapore’s regional connectivity. Key projects include:
Electronic Marketplace for Trade Finance Assets
An electronic trade finance platform will allow participating banks to distribute trade finance assets globally, free up capital for new trade finance loans, and increase the availability of trade finance within the region.</description></item><item><title>Dubai ranks in the middle of the global innovation push, according to the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-ranks-in-the-middle-of-the-global-innovation-push-according-to-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry has published the findings from the inaugural Dubai Innovation Index. Introduced last year, this index is part of the Chamber&amp;rsquo;s plan to encourage innovation and global best practices in the private sector. The index identified medical care, media, marketing, IT, and retail industrial sectors as the most innovative, while professional services, agriculture, fisheries, construction, and energy were identified as the least innovative in Dubai.</description></item><item><title>Stars at INSEAD drive innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stars-at-insead-drive-innovation/</guid><description>New research from INSEAD suggests that good mentors are incredibly valuable.
The study, titled &amp;ldquo;Where Do Stars Come From? The Role of Star vs. Nonstar Collaborators in Creative Settings,&amp;rdquo; was published in Organization Science. The authors, Manuel Sosa, Jürgen Mihm, and Haibo Liu, examined the skills needed to effectively combine different elements for maximum creativity and innovation, leading to organizational success.
Their research specifically focused on a new aspect of collaborative creativity: the impact of collaborating with high-achievers (&amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo;) versus average performers (&amp;ldquo;non-stars&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>The recipients of the MRM Business Award and MRM Business Innovation Award have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. HH Sheikh Ahmed Al Maktoum acknowledged the recipients of the 10th Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (MRM) Business Award and the 2nd MRM Business Innovation Award in Dubai, UAE.
Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, President of Dubai Civil Aviation Authority, as well as Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive of the Emirates Airline &amp;amp; Group, presided over the ceremony, which was held under the patronage of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice-President and Prime Minister of the UAE and Ruler of Dubai, and organized by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.</description></item><item><title>The ESET test demonstrates your ability to think ahead and be a visionary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eset-test-demonstrates-your-ability-to-think-ahead-and-be-a-visionary/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 18:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eset-test-demonstrates-your-ability-to-think-ahead-and-be-a-visionary/</guid><description>ESET, a global cybersecurity company, has introduced a new psychometric test called Progress Personas. Created in collaboration with The Myers-Briggs Company, a leader in personality and professional development assessments, this test is designed for curious individuals. The questionnaire helps users discover their place on the spectrum of visionary thinkers.
The Progress Personas test aims to reveal what motivates individuals to innovate and drive societal progress. After completing a series of brief questions, participants receive a personalized report outlining the potential strengths and weaknesses of their forward-thinking personalities.</description></item><item><title>India will receive the India Inclusive Innovation Fund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</guid><description>The Indian Cabinet has approved a proposal from the Ministry of Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSME) to establish a dedicated fund. This fund will focus on promoting grassroots innovations that generate social benefits alongside reasonable economic returns. Union Minister Shri Kalraj Mishra shared this information in a written response to a question in Lok Sabha.
The fund, named &amp;ldquo;India Inclusive Innovation Fund,&amp;rdquo; aims to support businesses developing solutions for citizens at the lower end of India&amp;rsquo;s economic spectrum.</description></item><item><title>The 6th Directors' Conference of the Singapore Institute of Directors will prioritize innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</guid><description>Source: SID brochure.
The critical importance of boards in driving innovation will be the central theme at the Singapore Institute of Directors (SID) sixth annual Directors&amp;rsquo; Conference. Taking place on September 16, 2015, at the Marina Bay Sands, Singapore, this yearly event is designed to cultivate leadership skills for Singaporean businesses and is anticipated to draw over 800 attendees.
Organized by SID, the conference will be inaugurated by guest-of-honor S Iswaran, Minister in the Prime Minister’s Office; Second Minister for Home Affairs; and Second Minister for Trade and Industry.</description></item><item><title>Creating new ideas in environmentally friendly buildings and construction areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 21:21:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-new-ideas-in-environmentally-friendly-buildings-and-construction-areas/</guid><description>Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s premier trade show for green building solutions, has commenced at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre. The event is anticipated to draw visitors from over 50 nations, all eager to witness the latest advancements in Asian green building, HVAC-R (heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, and refrigeration), water, energy, and heating technologies.
BEX Asia, which runs until September 14, 2017, is held in conjunction with Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional trade show specializing in energy-efficient solutions for industrial, commercial, and residential structures.</description></item><item><title>CA Technologies believes that Asia has the potential to become a central hub of global innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</guid><description>Lionel Lim, President for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies, believes the significant data exchange happening within Asia indicates the region&amp;rsquo;s potential to become a leading force in innovation.
During a Chinese New Year event in Singapore, Lim stated that Asia is capable of matching Europe and the US in driving innovation. He emphasized that the focus is shifting from cost reduction to accelerating innovation.
Lim highlighted four key areas for innovation and differentiation: improving user experience, ensuring convenient, fast, and secure data access, utilizing technologies that boost business growth, and strengthening IT skills.</description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras.</description></item><item><title>Innovators under 35 in Singapore are looking for applicants from Southeast Asia and Australia/New Zealand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</guid><description>EmTech Singapore is searching for ten innovative individuals under 35 from Southeast Asia, Australia, and New Zealand. These individuals should embody innovation in business and technology and will be featured in the Innovators Under 35 Singapore competition. The competition seeks those responsible for significant advancements, innovations, and impactful contributions to their target audiences.
Organized by MIT Technology Review since 1999, Innovators Under 35 has acknowledged some of the world&amp;rsquo;s brightest minds.</description></item><item><title>In August, an innovation event will be held in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-august-an-innovation-event-will-be-held-in-singapore/</guid><description>The second one-north Festival, a celebration of research, innovation, creativity, and enterprise, will take place on August 18th and 19th, 2017, at Biopolis in Singapore.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOAcpbDhuBLMHwpNFri5j6kbRVLkScIKw4TiGhwymXBdx3y6jgeTVWIOLN9OP71ghrtTERYqlpvKkMaup28rURdUpbA6fK2EH9AWxwQi-iB9M-tHLvfmrD43zz1zcSGOThoKLcuV0Yd6k/s1600/20170720_125101.jpg)
This advertisement for the one-north Festival was seen at Raffles station.
Organized by A*STAR and JTC, the festival&amp;rsquo;s theme, Pioneering an Innovation Future, centers around future health, living, and work. This year&amp;rsquo;s festival will incorporate Science Centre Singapore&amp;rsquo;s X-periment!, showcasing cutting-edge health innovations.
Highlighting the collaborative spirit of the one-north community, the festival showcases how partnerships between research performers and industry partners drive advancements in research, innovation, and enterprise, benefiting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s economy and enhancing lives.</description></item><item><title>Acquire the necessary knowledge to thrive in the era of the fourth industrial revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 21:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acquire-the-necessary-knowledge-to-thrive-in-the-era-of-the-fourth-industrial-revolution/</guid><description>Source: Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Knowledge Foundation. The summit&amp;rsquo;s opening was attended by notable figures such as HH Sheikh Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s VP and PM, and Ruler of Dubai (6th from left), Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Crown Prince of Dubai (2nd from right), and Sheikh Ahmed Bin Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (right).
At the opening of the fourth Knowledge Summit in the UAE, speakers emphasized that knowledge will be crucial for success in a digital world.</description></item><item><title>Fikra Labs aims to speed up innovation in the travel and tourism industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 18:07:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fikra-labs-aims-to-speed-up-innovation-in-the-travel-and-tourism-industry/</guid><description>In February, during UAE Innovation Month, which promotes the country&amp;rsquo;s global innovation hub status and recognizes innovators, four Abu Dhabi groups are collaborating with Wamda, an entrepreneurship platform, to launch the Fikra Labs acceleration program. The partners, including the Department of Culture and Tourism – Abu Dhabi, Miral Asset Management, Etihad Aviation Group, and Abu Dhabi National Exhibitions Company (ADNEC), with support from Abu Dhabi Global Market (ADGM), aim to boost innovation and entrepreneurship in Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s travel and tourism industry.</description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport.</description></item><item><title>Adjusting the workforce culture to the current reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adjusting-the-workforce-culture-to-the-current-reality/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. Digital transformation requires change both externally and internally.
A recent study by Microsoft highlights the need for Singaporean organizations to adopt a new work culture to successfully navigate digital transformation. The research reveals that a significant 77% of surveyed employees believe their organizations could invest further in cultural development.
The Microsoft Asia Workplace 2020 Study identified several factors impacting Singapore&amp;rsquo;s current work culture:
A More Mobile Workforce and New Security Concerns:</description></item></channel></rss>