<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Commercial on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commercial/</link><description>Recent content in Commercial on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/commercial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seminar on Intellectual Property and Legal Issues by the RHT Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</guid><description>RHT Academy and RHTLaw Taylor Wessing are holding a half-day seminar titled &amp;ldquo;Commercial Contracts: Latest Case Law Developments, Negotiation Strategies and Intellectual Property&amp;rdquo; on March 4, 2015, at the Suntec Convention &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre in Singapore.
Designed for legal professionals, business development executives, company secretaries, and compliance officers, this seminar aims to:
Offer a practical, business-focused overview of recent key case law developments related to commercial contracts in Singapore and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The commercial property forecast for Q4 2014 is at its lowest in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 20:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Singapore Marina Bay business district at night.
The Royal Institution of Chartered Surveyors (RICS) Global Commercial Property Monitor for the fourth quarter of 2014 suggests that while economic indicators show a decline in the Hong Kong economy, growth is expected to rise steadily this year.
In Hong Kong, the RICS Occupier Sentiment Index (OSI) decreased slightly from +4 to -3 during the last quarter. The RICS Investment Sentiment Index (ISI) remained negative at -3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commercial-property-forecast-for-q4-2014-is-at-its-lowest-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP's Elite business PCs excel in performance, productivity, and security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 22:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</guid><description>HP has introduced its latest Elite business PCs, including the exceptionally thin and light HP EliteBook 705 series, an all-in-one (AiO) model, and a refreshed desktop lineup featuring the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest business-class desktop.
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the demand for high-end Elite notebook innovation to be extended to a wider range of employees and devices. HP&amp;rsquo;s response is the Elite 705 and 800 Series PCs, which bring sleek design, enhanced collaboration features, and robust security to mainstream business devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ibn Battuta Gate Office building is experiencing increased demand as Expo 2020 Dubai approaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</guid><description>Source: Seven Tides website.
As Expo 2020 Dubai approaches, Ibn Battuta Gate Offices, a property developed by Seven Tides, is leveraging its prime location in New Dubai. Situated near the Mövenpick Hotel, Ibn Battuta Mall, and a metro station, the office building is attracting significant attention.
The appeal of this location is further enhanced by the planned expansion of Ibn Battuta Mall. The AED160 million project will add 28,000 square meters, including a 350-room hotel, 150 shops, 50 restaurants, and a cinema with 21 screens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HP believes that the digital printing revolution has the potential to make businesses even more agile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 21:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</guid><description>Source: HP. High-impact retail graphics, floor covering and corrugated display applications printed using HP Latex and Scitex Digital printing technologies at the new HP Graphics Solutions Centre of Excellence in Singapore.
The way businesses approach printing is being transformed by commercial digital printing presses. Unlike traditional offset printing, which requires large quantities for cost-effectiveness, digital printers can economically personalize any volume of items, from a single piece to thousands, across diverse materials...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-believes-that-the-digital-printing-revolution-has-the-potential-to-make-businesses-even-more-agile/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>