<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog Action Day on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blog-action-day/</link><description>Recent content in Blog Action Day on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/blog-action-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Green Energy Fairy Tale is Real</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-energy-fairy-tale-is-real/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 05:42:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-energy-fairy-tale-is-real/</guid><description>For decades, we&amp;rsquo;ve been promised a utopian future powered by clean energy sources like solar, wind, and fusion. This ideal world, fueled by boundless energy, feels perpetually out of reach, forcing us to rely on polluting coal and oil.
This is absurd. We possess the technology to transition away from fossil fuels immediately.
Our obstacle isn&amp;rsquo;t technological, but mental. We cling to the misconception that clean energy is impractical, a belief so deeply rooted that we accept it without question...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-energy-fairy-tale-is-real/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-energy-fairy-tale-is-real/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Banish Vampires To Reduce Global Warming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</guid><description>Electronic devices, like hidden vampires, silently drain electricity even when seemingly off. This &amp;ldquo;vampire power&amp;rdquo; not only increases your electricity bill but also contributes to global warming.
These &amp;ldquo;vampires&amp;rdquo; hide within devices, indicated by glowing lights, active displays, running fans, or warm surfaces, even when the device is switched off. Remote-controlled devices are prime suspects, as they constantly use power to stay ready for remote signals. Similarly, wireless networks and devices are notorious power consumers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>