<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ar/</link><description>Recent content in AR on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google Tango experiences were introduced as a part of the Visual SG festival</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 12:32:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/</guid><description>To celebrate its 40th anniversary, the Science Centre Singapore has introduced an augmented reality (AR) experience powered by Google Tango technology.
This immersive experience is available at the Science Centre&amp;rsquo;s recently updated E3 exhibition (E-mmersive Experiential Environments), specifically designed for virtual and augmented reality. Visitors with Tango-enabled phones, like the Lenovo Phab 2 Pro or Asus ZenFone AR, can view moving objects and information overlaid onto their surroundings.
One notable Google Tango exhibit at E3 is Space Adventurer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-tango-experiences-were-introduced-as-a-part-of-the-visual-sg-festival/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>