<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Star on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/star/</link><description>Recent content in Star on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/star/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates has struck marketing gold with its incredible video featuring football superstars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-struck-marketing-gold-with-its-incredible-video-featuring-football-superstars/</guid><description>Emirates Airlines has launched a global marketing campaign centered around soccer in anticipation of the World Cup in Brazil. An email sent to customers teases, &amp;ldquo;Watch the moment when two football legends meet in the Emirates A380 Onboard Lounge.&amp;rdquo;
The campaign features a video of soccer stars Pelé and Cristiano Ronaldo, who are Emirates&amp;rsquo; new Global Ambassadors, interacting on an Emirates A380 plane. The airline encourages viewers to share the video on social media using the hashtag #AllTimeGreats.</description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef.</description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction.</description></item><item><title>The InterContinental Dubai Marina is now accepting advance bookings for Marina Social</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intercontinental-dubai-marina-is-now-accepting-advance-bookings-for-marina-social/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental
Dubai Marina. Atherton.
The InterContinental Dubai Marina has announced the official opening date for Marina Social and The Social Room, the first restaurant in the region from Michelin-starred UK chef Jason Atherton. Located in the heart of Dubai Marina, the restaurant and bar will begin taking reservations on August 2nd and will open to the public on September 4th.
Marina Social will bring Jason Atherton&amp;rsquo;s signature style of refined yet approachable dining to the recently opened InterContinental Dubai Marina.</description></item><item><title>HP introduces a limited edition notebook featuring a Star Wars theme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-introduces-a-limited-edition-notebook-featuring-a-star-wars-theme/</guid><description>In anticipation of the release of Star Wars: &amp;ldquo;The Force Awakens,&amp;rdquo; HP has launched a special edition notebook.
“As the only PC vendor collaborating with Disney and Lucasfilm, HP is providing an incredible Star Wars experience by creating a truly unique notebook,&amp;quot; shared Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore. &amp;ldquo;This collaboration granted us access to Lucasfilm’s media archives, which we used to create customizable screen savers, desktop backgrounds, and sound profiles.</description></item></channel></rss>