<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Last-Mile Access on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/last-mile-access/</link><description>Recent content in Last-Mile Access on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:47:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/last-mile-access/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Internet Is a Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</guid><description>Internet access has evolved from slow modems, but connecting still requires converting between protocols and Ethernet used in offices. Now, direct Ethernet internet is possible.
Ethernet for internet access is popular in cities, mainly due to cost savings and simpler networking. Called Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet, it extends your network using Ethernet across cities, countries, or to the internet.
Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) is the top choice for businesses, providing exclusive bandwidth unlike shared services like DSL, WiFi, and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>