<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BPL on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bpl/</link><description>Recent content in BPL on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:35:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bpl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part IV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</guid><description>The most desirable wireless frequencies will soon be completely allocated. These prime frequencies, ranging from a few hundred to a few thousand MHz, offer high bandwidth, strong building penetration, and accommodate small antennas. The problem is that the number of these channels is finite. Similar to real estate, once the best spots are taken, expansion continues into less ideal areas.
Finding more bandwidth means moving up or down the electromagnetic spectrum, which presents challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>