<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Marketplace on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marketplace/</link><description>Recent content in Marketplace on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/marketplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products.</description></item><item><title>Telecom and Network Domain Names For Sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 10:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecom-and-network-domain-names-for-sale/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong domain name is crucial for any online business. The best names reflect your business, are easy to remember for offline use, and are pronounceable. Owning your own domain provides a much stronger online identity compared to generic alternatives. This ownership gives you full control over your website, email, and branding.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in business telecom for almost 15 years and acquired many domain names related to that industry.</description></item><item><title>AppDine has launched a beta version of its F&amp;B and lifestyle e-commerce marketplace in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: AppeDine. Screenshot of the AppeDine app for consumers.
AppeDine has launched the public beta version of its food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and lifestyle e-commerce platform in Singapore. The marketplace facilitates online transactions tailored for F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle businesses, chefs, and consumers.
AppeDine brings together F&amp;amp;B outlets, temporary events, and promotions in one place, enabling F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle providers to generate revenue from their services and spaces online without upfront investment.</description></item><item><title>Booqed offers a selection of workspaces available for rent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 10:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/booqed-offers-a-selection-of-workspaces-available-for-rent/</guid><description>Booqed, an online marketplace for booking meeting rooms and workspaces, has introduced its mobile app on the Apple App Store. This app offers a convenient way to find and reserve available spaces in a city, allowing users to book instantly or in advance and make payments directly from their smartphones or tablets.
Businesses can also benefit from this service by monetizing their underutilized meeting or conference rooms. Booqed provides a platform for them to list and rent out these spaces.</description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become a leading global e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Aladdinstreet.com.sg, a global e-marketplace specializing in premium and halal products, has officially launched. Catering to both businesses and individual consumers, the platform offers a range of halal-certified products alongside premium items that don&amp;rsquo;t require certification.
Since its initial announcement in July 2016, Aladdinstreet.com.sg has carefully selected 200 merchants for inclusion on the site, formalizing agreements with nearly 60. Approximately half of these merchants provide halal-friendly or halal-certified products, encompassing diverse categories such as food, beverages, vitamins, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, fashion, and more.</description></item></channel></rss>