<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asylum on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asylum/</link><description>Recent content in Asylum on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asylum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rights to due process and secondary protection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The initial Common European Asylum System (CEAS) legislation defined &amp;lsquo;subsidiary protection,&amp;rsquo; which protects individuals ineligible for refugee status but shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be returned to their home country. However, other initial CEAS legislation, particularly the asylum procedures Directive, didn&amp;rsquo;t cover those seeking subsidiary protection or clarify the connection between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses.
This gap has been addressed in several ways. Firstly, future second-phase CEAS legislation fully applies to subsidiary protection applicants and defines the relationship between refugee and subsidiary protection statuses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-to-due-process-and-secondary-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How the EU Migration and Asylum Pact Can Address its Blind Spot on Statelessness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 07:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</guid><description>Chris Nash, the Director of the European Network on Statelessness, highlights their recent analysis of the EU Pact on Migration and Asylum. The analysis focuses on how the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s proposals within the Pact could affect the fundamental rights of stateless migrants and refugees. It offers suggestions for addressing these concerns during Pact negotiations and implementation.
The Pact, as it stands, fails to directly address the rights of stateless individuals or offer solutions to the specific protection issues they encounter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-eu-migration-and-asylum-pact-can-address-its-blind-spot-on-statelessness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European academics are appealing for the EU to avoid becoming a lawless zone.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 22:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</guid><description>The situation at the Polish-Belarusian border briefly gained public awareness, with images of suffering refugees stranded in terrible conditions sparking outrage. While there were discussions and reactions, the humanitarian crisis persists.
Since September 2021, the Polish government has restricted access to the border zone, putting migrants in danger and denying aid organizations access. People are facing dire circumstances, including death, due to lack of basic necessities and medical help...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-academics-are-appealing-for-the-eu-to-avoid-becoming-a-lawless-zone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ has upheld the EU law on relocating asylum-seekers, but some question if it is a Pyrrhic victory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</guid><description>The EU Court Rules on Refugee Relocation: A Pyrrhic Victory? Professor Steve Peers examines the European Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s (ECJ) decision regarding the mandatory relocation of asylum-seekers, highlighting the complex interplay between legal effectiveness and political realities.
In 2015, facing a significant influx of asylum-seekers, the EU implemented a measure requiring member states to relocate 160,000 individuals from overburdened Italy and Greece. This decision faced resistance, particularly a legal challenge from Slovakia and Hungary, questioning its legal basis and practicality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-has-upheld-the-eu-law-on-relocating-asylum-seekers-but-some-question-if-it-is-a-pyrrhic-victory/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's failure to grasp the dysfunctional French asylum system in cases of removal orders and the right to be heard.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</guid><description>Marie-Laure Basilien-Gainche Professor in Law University Jean Moulin Lyon III Member of the Institut Universitaire de France Introduction
This paper examines two recent rulings from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) concerning the right to be heard for individuals facing removal orders under the Returns Directive. These rulings raise concerns about the practical application of this right. While the CJEU has previously interpreted the right to be heard in detention cases, these new rulings clarify how it applies to undocumented immigrants facing removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-failure-to-grasp-the-dysfunctional-french-asylum-system-in-cases-of-removal-orders-and-the-right-to-be-heard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Denmark truly choosing to rejoin EU Justice and Home Affairs Law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Danish Prime Minister recently revealed that Denmark would hold a referendum in 2015 regarding its relationship with the EU. While widely reported as a vote on rejoining EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) law, the referendum actually focuses on replacing Denmark&amp;rsquo;s complete opt-out with a selective one. This post will examine the details of this issue, including which measures Denmark could potentially opt back into.
The origin of this opt-out can be traced back to the 1992 Danish referendum on the Maastricht Treaty...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-denmark-truly-choosing-to-rejoin-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Union and the Crisis in the Spanish Constitution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</guid><description>Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated both to Université Saint-Louis Bruxelles and Université libre de Bruxelles
Background
For over a month, Spain has been grappling with a constitutional crisis stemming from pro-independence sentiments in Catalonia. These sentiments culminated in an independence referendum held on October 1, 2017, orchestrated by the Catalan government under President Carles Puigdemont. Barcelona claims that 90% of the 43% voter turnout favored independence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-and-the-crisis-in-the-spanish-constitution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reconsidering Gender-Based Asylum: Examining the Advocate General's Perspective on Female Refugees Escaping the Taliban</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 19:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand (Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law) and Salvo Nicolosi (Senior Assistant Professor, Utrecht University School of Law)
Photo credit: USAIDAfghanistan, via Wikimedia Commons
A central question in international refugee law is whether women can qualify for refugee status based solely on their gender. This debate recently reached the Court of Justice through two connected cases, AH and FN, concerning women seeking asylum. Advocate General Richard de la Tour issued his opinion on these cases on November 9, 2023...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reconsidering-gender-based-asylum-examining-the-advocate-general-s-perspective-on-female-refugees-escaping-the-taliban/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advancing Gender-Sensitive EU Asylum Law: Examining the Situation of 'Westernised Women'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</guid><description>Türkan Ertuna Lagrand, Assistant Professor, and Salvo Nicolosi, Senior Assistant Professor, University of Utrecht
Photo credit: Mystslav Chernov, via Wikimedia Commons
Recent developments in EU law show a growing recognition of gender-based asylum claims. A notable example is the June 11, 2024, judgment by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of K, L v Staatssecretaris van Justitie en Veiligheid. This case, concerning two Iraqi sisters seeking asylum in the Netherlands, centers around interpreting &amp;ldquo;membership of a particular social group&amp;rdquo; within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, specifically regarding &amp;ldquo;westernized women&amp;rdquo; who fear persecution upon returning to their home countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advancing-gender-sensitive-eu-asylum-law-examining-the-situation-of-westernised-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice's initial decision on detaining asylum-seekers within the Dublin system and its implications for the rule of law in immigration detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</guid><description>Tommaso Poli, LL.M. candidate in Human Rights and Humanitarian Law at the University of Essex, School of Law.
The detention of those seeking asylum is a contentious issue within immigration law. While not initially covered by the European Common Asylum System (CEAS), it is now addressed in several of the second-phase CEAS measures. These measures include the Asylum Procedures Directive, the Reception Conditions Directive, the Qualification Directive, the Dublin Regulation, and the EURODAC Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 2: Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights under ordinary EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 16:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Can the EU penalize its member states for consistently violating human rights and the rule of law? And if so, how?
This article, the second in a three-part series, explores this question. The first installment analyzed the official mechanism designed for this purpose: Article 7 TEU. As previously discussed, this process, which could result in the suspension of certain EU membership rights for a member state, is highly political, offers limited involvement from EU courts, and is challenging to implement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights-under-ordinary-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Strategy on immigration policy in the EU by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</guid><description>This is an unofficial preview of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s communication on the EU migration agenda, scheduled for release on May 13th. Please be aware that the content may change before publication and may be incomplete.
I. Introduction
Migration has been a constant throughout human history, driven by a range of factors such as political oppression, war, poverty, opportunity, and family reunification. Each migrant&amp;rsquo;s story is unique, and their movement has diverse impacts on society, necessitating a variety of responses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating Discontent: Questions and Answers about the legal concerns of asylum-seekers crossing the Channel.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Supported by an ESRC Priority Brexit Grant on &amp;lsquo;Brexit and UK and EU Immigration Policy&amp;rsquo;.
Some politicians are trying to create unnecessary fear and outrage over a relatively small number of people crossing the English Channel. This situation does bring up important legal questions. While the legal aspects have been discussed elsewhere, such as in the Free Movement blog, this post aims to clarify some of these legal issues in a straightforward question-and-answer format...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 6 of the new EU asylum laws: The updated Dublin regulations regarding the accountability for asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway, University of London
Photo credit: Ggia, via Wikimedia Commons
(last updated 10 June 2024: changed text marked by an asterisk)
Shortly before Christmas 2023, the European Parliament and the Council finalized an agreement on five crucial components of EU asylum law. These components address asylum procedures, the &amp;lsquo;Dublin&amp;rsquo; system for determining responsibility for asylum applications, the supporting &amp;lsquo;Eurodac&amp;rsquo; database, migrant/asylum seeker screening, and crisis derogations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three main points about the EU's New Pact on Migration and Asylum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</guid><description>Lilian Tsourdi, Assistant Professor, University of Maastricht
*Photo credit: Délmagyarország/Schmidt Andrea
The EU&amp;rsquo;s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, along with its accompanying legislative proposals, represents the latest policy framework for asylum, migration, and border management. Its stated goal is to create streamlined migration procedures and stronger governance. Since September 2020, negotiations on the Pact&amp;rsquo;s legislative components have been underway.
Recently, both the European Parliament (April 2023) and the Council of the European Union (June 2023) have adopted negotiating positions on two significant instruments: the Asylum Procedures Regulation (APR), which updates regulations on determining asylum and related rights, and the Asylum and Migration Management Regulation (AMMR), which reforms the EU&amp;rsquo;s system for allocating responsibility for processing asylum requests and establishing a solidarity framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the non-refoulement principle in the EU's qualification Directive considered invalid?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 14:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</guid><description>By Pieter Boeles, visiting professor migration law, VU University Amsterdam, emeritus professor University Leiden
Introduction
The principle of non-refoulement, which forbids returning individuals to unsafe nations, is generally considered absolute. However, ambiguity persists concerning its application within the EU&amp;rsquo;s Qualification Directive, which governs the determination of refugee or subsidiary protection status. The Czech Nejvyšší správní soud inquired with the Court of Justice of the European Union on July 14, 2016, about the potential conflict between Article 14(4) of the Qualification Directive and the principle of non-refoulement (Case C-391/16)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-non-refoulement-principle-in-the-eu-s-qualification-directive-considered-invalid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing Complex Legal Issues from a Legal Standpoint with Partiality and Passion, or The European Union's Approval of the Istanbul Convention: Jurisdiction, Foundations, and Consensus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre, University of Oxford - @CateBriddick*
On March 11, 2021, Advocate General Hogan of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) presented his legal opinion on the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s inquiry regarding the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) potential membership in the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women and Domestic Violence (Istanbul Convention)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-complex-legal-issues-from-a-legal-standpoint-with-partiality-and-passion-or-the-european-union-s-approval-of-the-istanbul-convention-jurisdiction-foundations-and-consensus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 4: Immigration in the EU Referendum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
How does the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the European Union (EU) affect immigration and asylum? This piece examines this complex topic, focusing on migration to the UK by both non-EU and EU citizens.
Non-EU migration
It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between non-EU and EU migration in the Brexit referendum discussion for two key reasons. Firstly, while EU migration is inherently linked to the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership, non-EU migration is not...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-4-immigration-in-the-eu-referendum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preserving the Formal Rule of Law in the EU's Asylum Policy: The CJEU's Ruling on the Asylum Relocation Mechanism</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</guid><description>Niels Kirst, Ph.D. Researcher in European Union Law at the School of Law and Government of Dublin City University*
*Reblogged from the Bridge Network blog
Introduction
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling found Poland, Hungary, and the Czech Republic to be in violation of European Union (EU) law. The violation stems from their failure to implement two Council Decisions outlining the relocation of asylum seekers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preserving-the-formal-rule-of-law-in-the-eu-s-asylum-policy-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-asylum-relocation-mechanism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU truly dedicated to addressing violence against women, or is it just empty words?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 23:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</guid><description>Catherine Briddick, Martin James Departmental Lecturer in Gender and Forced Migration at the Refugee Studies Centre of the University of Oxford - @CateBriddick
Background
The European Union (EU) has a core legal commitment to fight discrimination, including sex-based discrimination, and to promote gender equality. However, it has faced ongoing and valid criticism for not upholding these commitments, especially regarding its treatment of female migrants and refugees. Therefore, the Commission&amp;rsquo;s 2016 announcement that the EU would sign and ratify the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence Against Women (the Istanbul Convention) was welcomed by activists and academics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-truly-dedicated-to-addressing-violence-against-women-or-is-it-just-empty-words/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comments on the outcomes of the most recent European Council meeting regarding EU migration policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU faces another crisis alongside &amp;ldquo;Grexit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;: a surge in immigration. Initial EU responses culminated in an emergency summit in April. I previously discussed the outcomes of that summit. Subsequently, the Commission released its EU migration &amp;ldquo;Agenda&amp;rdquo; in mid-May, followed by detailed proposals. Last week, the European Council revisited immigration, reaching several conclusions. This post outlines those conclusions and offers my commentary. The third part of the conclusions, which vaguely promises increased cooperation with third countries, is omitted...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comments-on-the-outcomes-of-the-most-recent-european-council-meeting-regarding-eu-migration-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU's reaction to migrant fatalities focused on safeguarding and stopping them, or is it merely a way to disguise policy laundering?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU foreign and interior ministers recently agreed on a ten-point plan to address the tragic loss of migrant lives in the Mediterranean. While a summit and a new strategy are forthcoming, this initial plan is disappointing. It lacks crucial specifics and prioritizes border control and restrictive measures over aiding migrants facing perilous journeys and seeking safety.
This analysis will examine each of the plan&amp;rsquo;s ten points, followed by a look at the suggested &amp;ldquo;Australian solution&amp;rdquo; and the controversial &amp;ldquo;Christians only&amp;rdquo; approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Processing applications for international protection in the EU from external sources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 20:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The significant loss of life near Lampedusa last autumn, when numerous migrants drowned attempting to cross the Mediterranean, represents one of the most recent and tragic outcomes of irregular migration across this sea. This event should have prompted a thorough reevaluation of EU policies concerning border control and visas but did not. This inaction is likely due to concerns that far-right parties would exploit heightened public anxiety around migration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/processing-applications-for-international-protection-in-the-eu-from-external-sources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Could a third phase of the Common European Asylum System bring wisdom and goodness to those who are considered vile?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 05:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
The EU is looking to overhaul its Common European Asylum Policy, and the Commission has laid out its suggestions in a new discussion paper. These proposals, which are expected to lead to further legislation, aim to address the flaws in the current system. This blog post will break down these proposals and analyze their potential impact.
The EU&amp;rsquo;s asylum policy has been developed in phases, with the initial legislation implemented between 2003 and 2005 and the second phase between 2011 and 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-a-third-phase-of-the-common-european-asylum-system-bring-wisdom-and-goodness-to-those-who-are-considered-vile/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Union Migration Agencies: Frontex, EASO, and Europol's Operations and Collaborations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</guid><description>Dr. David Fernández-Rojo, Universidad de Deusto - davidfrojo@deusto.es
The recent surge in migration, often called the “refugee crisis,” highlighted the urgent need to strengthen both the Schengen area and the Common European Asylum System (CEAS). It also underscored the need to support EU member states dealing with large numbers of migrants and to consistently apply EU policies on migration, asylum, and border control. EU agencies such as Frontex, EASO, and Europol have become central to these efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Examine what you observe and I will determine if you are homosexual: Evaluating the Advocate General's viewpoint in Case C-473/16, F v Bevándorlási és Állampolgársági Hivatal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</guid><description>By Nuno Ferreira (Professor of Law, University of Sussex) and Denise Venturi (PhD student, Scuola Sant Anna, Pisa)*
Hungary&amp;rsquo;s Actions Raise Concerns Again
Hungary has been under scrutiny for controversial actions. Viktor Orban&amp;rsquo;s right-wing government has faced criticism from parts of Hungarian society and European institutions for policies targeting specific universities, constructing border barriers to deter refugees, and implementing other contentious measures. A recent source of alarm is Hungary&amp;rsquo;s treatment of asylum seekers, particularly those claiming persecution based on sexual orientation, an area already subject to criticism...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examine-what-you-observe-and-i-will-determine-if-you-are-homosexual-evaluating-the-advocate-general-s-viewpoint-in-case-c-473-16-f-v-bev-ndorl-si-s-llampolg-rs-gi-hivatal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's responses to the Iraq war and EU asylum law are uncertain.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:43:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Almost twelve years after it began, the Iraq war remains a point of contention, with many believing Tony Blair and George W. Bush initiated an unlawful conflict. These critics believe only a trial for war crimes for both Bush and Blair would be a satisfactory outcome. While I believe this may happen someday, it would require a jury of highly improbable individuals. (Perhaps those individuals disappeared alongside the supposed weapons of mass destruction)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-responses-to-the-iraq-war-and-eu-asylum-law-are-uncertain/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Nigel Farage's claim that the EU's asylum policies will allow in half a million terrorists accurate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, the UK Independence Party leader, recently asserted that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s response to the migrant crisis could unintentionally allow a large number of terrorists into the EU. He bases this on the threat by ISIS to use smuggling routes to infiltrate the EU and urges David Cameron to block the EU&amp;rsquo;s plans.
These claims lack merit. The EU&amp;rsquo;s approach essentially maintains the existing situation. The current maritime surveillance efforts, while being expanded, may not become full-scale rescue missions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for EU law to rescue Paddington Bear? The CJEU is creating a new form of protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 18:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</guid><description>Many people might already know about Colin Yeo&amp;rsquo;s blog post that imagines Paddington Bear having a tough time with British immigration law. However, could EU law potentially protect Paddington, particularly by offering a new kind of protection for those forced to leave their home countries?
Background
EU law has detailed rules for two types of international protection: refugee status (based on the UN&amp;rsquo;s Geneva Convention) and subsidiary protection status for those who don&amp;rsquo;t qualify as refugees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-eu-law-to-rescue-paddington-bear-the-cjeu-is-creating-a-new-form-of-protection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Navigating a legal minefield: the potential dangers of expanding the reach of the EU Temporary Protection Directive past March 2025.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 07:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</guid><description>Dr Meltem Ineli-Ciger, Associate Professor, Suleyman Demirel University Faculty of Law; Migration Policy Centre Associate, European University Institute
Photo credit: Falin, on Wikimedia Commons
A crucial question arises as the March 2025 deadline for the Council Directive 2001/55/EC (Temporary Protection Directive), applicable to those fleeing the Ukraine conflict, approaches. This issue revolves around the fate of these individuals once this directive expires. Numerous experts, including myself, have explored potential solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/navigating-a-legal-minefield-the-potential-dangers-of-expanding-the-reach-of-the-eu-temporary-protection-directive-past-march-2025/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It is time for the EU to address the origins of informal agreements in EU migration law when cooperating on migration with third countries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 18:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</guid><description>Dr Céline Hocquet, Teaching Fellow, Birmingham Law School, University of Birmingham
Photo credit: Issam Barhoumi, via Wikimedia Commons
As the EU proposes yet another collaboration with a non-EU nation to manage migration beyond its borders, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to critically examine the EU&amp;rsquo;s externalization policy and its use of informal cooperation. This analysis should consider the historical, legal, and political context of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external migration and asylum policy.
From the EU-Turkey to the EU-Tunisia deal?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-time-for-the-eu-to-address-the-origins-of-informal-agreements-in-eu-migration-law-when-cooperating-on-migration-with-third-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How can the EU address migrant fatalities in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 15:07:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>The recent tragedies in the Mediterranean Sea have added to the already significant number of migrant deaths. EU officials are responding to this urgent issue, and this is what their response should include.
First, a large-scale search and rescue operation is needed. The EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Triton&amp;rsquo; operation, which replaced the Italian &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum,&amp;rsquo; is insufficient for saving lives. It was incorrectly assumed that ending &amp;lsquo;Mare Nostrum&amp;rsquo; would deter migrants and reduce deaths...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-eu-address-migrant-fatalities-in-the-mediterranean/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mr. Avramopolous travels to Brussels: reflections on the European Parliament hearing for the new Migration Commissioner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Throughout his extensive three-hour hearing at the European Parliament, Dimitris Avramopolous, the nominee for Commissioner for migration and home affairs, consistently emphasized his commitment to liberal values. He expressed strong support for upholding the Schengen system, adopting a liberal stance on asylum and legal migration, and protecting the freedom of movement for EU citizens. However, he fell short of providing specifics on the implementation of these principles and how the various facets of EU policy in this domain would harmonize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Evaluating the new proposal on "Safe countries of origin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission recently introduced several new immigration and asylum initiatives. Three proposals, in particular, suggest binding measures: a temporary relocation measure for asylum-seekers, a permanent relocation system for asylum-seekers, and a regulation establishing a common list of &amp;ldquo;safe countries of origin.&amp;rdquo; This list would include Western Balkan countries and Turkey. This article will focus on the &amp;ldquo;safe country of origin&amp;rdquo; rules.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the UK, Ireland, and Denmark are not subject to these measures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resistance is useless: examining the new Eurodac Regulation – part 4 of the analysis of recent EU asylum legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 18:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Rachmaninoff, via Wikimedia Commons
This blog post has been amended since its initial publication, with asterisks marking the changes.* The most recent update was on June 18, 2024.
Shortly before Christmas, the European Parliament and the Council, the EU body representing ministers from Member States, agreed on five crucial aspects of EU asylum law. These aspects include asylum procedures, the ‘Dublin’ system for determining responsibility for asylum claims, the ‘Eurodac’ database that supports the Dublin system, the screening process for migrants and asylum seekers, and derogations during crises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>