<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Lines on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-lines/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Lines on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-lines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Voice and Data Bandwidth for Hospitals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 22:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voice-and-data-bandwidth-for-hospitals/</guid><description>Healthcare facilities rely heavily on electronic communication to function effectively. This reliance is only expected to increase as technology advances and electronic record-keeping becomes more common. This naturally raises concerns about the rising costs associated with these growing telecom needs. However, there are ways to manage and even reduce these expenses.
The most fundamental requirement for any organization is voice communication. For larger facilities, this typically involves a PBX phone system.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>We're Looking For Successful IT Consultants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</guid><description>Are you an experienced IT professional looking to expand your consulting business? If you specialize in voice and data network design, implementation, and troubleshooting, and perhaps even hold certifications with equipment vendors, we have an opportunity for you.
We&amp;rsquo;re offering a chance to grow your business with minimal effort. Gain access to new clients in your area and expand your service offerings without any upfront costs or extensive training. This is a simple way to boost your existing business.</description></item><item><title>Choose Your Trunk, Choose Your Handoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-your-trunk-choose-your-handoff/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Although the telephone system has evolved for the better with advancements like wireless smartphones and VoIP, many companies hesitate to abandon their existing infrastructure. Fortunately, &amp;ldquo;handoffs&amp;rdquo; bridge the gap between old and new phone systems.
A handoff is essentially a point of connection between telecom lines and equipment. The traditional analog POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service) line, using a single twisted pair of copper wires, remains a simple solution for businesses needing a single line.</description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>SDN Performance Takes a Leaf of Faith</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sdn-performance-takes-a-leaf-of-faith/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cloud computing has highlighted the importance of reliable internet connections, known as WANs (Wide Area Networks). In the past, slow file transfers or unreliable internet were acceptable because crucial tasks were handled within the company&amp;rsquo;s internal network. However, now that businesses rely on cloud services, the performance of the WAN is just as crucial as the internal network (LAN).
WAN Challenges
The main challenge with WANs is that businesses don&amp;rsquo;t control them like they do their internal networks.</description></item></channel></rss>