<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Medicine on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/medicine/</link><description>Recent content in Medicine on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/medicine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs.</description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Angsana now offers allergy testing specifically for Asians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angsana-now-offers-allergy-testing-specifically-for-asians/</guid><description>Angsana Molecular &amp;amp; Diagnostics Laboratory announced a partnership with Thermo Fisher Scientific to offer allergen sensitivity tests tailored for the Asian population. These tests, utilizing Thermo Fisher&amp;rsquo;s ImmunoCAP technology and conducted by Phadia Laboratory Systems, address the growing understanding that allergen sensitivities can differ across ethnicities and geographical regions due to factors like genetics, environment, diet, and social behaviors.
Angsana aims to create and validate specific allergen sensitivity tests meeting local needs by leveraging the high specificity, sensitivity, quantitative results, quality, and extensive allergen menu of ImmunoCAP technology.</description></item><item><title>Asia Plantation Capital is researching the advantages of agarwood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-plantation-capital-is-researching-the-advantages-of-agarwood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-plantation-capital-is-researching-the-advantages-of-agarwood/</guid><description>Source:
Asia Plantation Capital
website.
Asia Plantation Capital (APC) has initiated a new investment program to collaborate with Southeast Asian academics in studying the science of agarwood, a valuable substance derived from infected Aquilaria trees and known by various names like gaharu, jinkoh, aloeswood, and oud. The program aims to pinpoint areas for in-depth research and potential clinical trials to gain approval from European and American medical authorities.
In Thailand, APC&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Prince Songkhla University, led by Prof.</description></item></channel></rss>