<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sydney on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sydney/</link><description>Recent content in Sydney on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sydney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vivid Sydney will once again enchant audiences starting on May 27th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</guid><description>The longest-running Vivid Sydney will illuminate Sydney Harbour and other beloved locations for 23 nights, from May 27 to June 18, 2016. This year marks the eighth anniversary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest festival of light, music, and ideas. The festival is owned, managed, and produced by Destination NSW, the NSW Government&amp;rsquo;s tourism and major events agency.
Sandra Chipchase, Destination NSW Chief Executive Officer and Executive Producer of Vivid Sydney, stated that this year&amp;rsquo;s Vivid Sydney promises an incredible program where art, creativity, and innovation converge, captivating both local and international visitors.</description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art.</description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area.</description></item><item><title>In 2017, Etihad will assume control of Virgin's Sydney-Abu Dhabi slots</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</guid><description>Etihad Airways will increase flights between Abu Dhabi and Sydney to twice daily starting February 6, 2017. Flights EY450 departing Abu Dhabi in the morning and EY451 departing Sydney in the afternoon will now operate seven days a week.
This schedule change coincides with strategic partner Virgin Australia&amp;rsquo;s move to shift its Abu Dhabi operations from Sydney to Perth, effective June 9, 2017. Etihad Airways will expand its current codeshare agreement with Virgin Australia to include their new tri-weekly Perth-Abu Dhabi flights.</description></item><item><title>Preparations for Vivid Sydney start two weeks before Lights On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</guid><description>Sydney is getting ready for Vivid Sydney, a major festival celebrating light, music, and ideas in the Southern Hemisphere. Over 50 light installations and projections will illuminate the city starting May 24th.
Source: Vivid Sydney. An artist&amp;rsquo;s impression by Andrew Thomas Huang &amp;amp; Bemo on the Austral Floral Ballet, part of Vivid Light 2019. For 23 days, Vivid Sydney will transform the city into a captivating display of color with stunning light sculptures and large-scale projections.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight.</description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike.</description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport.</description></item><item><title>The Autograph Collection is ready to make its first appearance in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</guid><description>Australian companies have a new, upscale event location. Pier One Sydney Harbour is joining the Autograph Collection, a curated group of almost 60 unique hotels globally. This harborside hotel provides a picturesque setting for meetings and events, featuring eight meeting rooms with expansive water views.
Source: Marriott International. From Sydney to San Diego - Autograph Collection set to debut in three new world class destinations, including Pier One Sydney Harbour in Sydney, Australia.</description></item><item><title>Hyatt Regency is back in Sydney and is now focusing on positioning the hotel for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels announced that a hotel situated at 161 Sussex Street, previously operating under the Four Points by Sheraton brand, will transition to Hyatt Regency Sydney starting November 30, 2016. This change signifies the return of the Hyatt Regency brand to Sydney. The company is strategically positioning the Hyatt Regency Sydney as a prime location for conferences.
The introduction of Hyatt Regency Sydney aligns with the growing demand for business, meetings, incentives, conferences and exhibitions (MICE), as well as leisure travel within the Australian market.</description></item><item><title>Come to Vivid Sydney and immerse yourself in the biggest festival of light, music, and ideas in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</guid><description>Source: Vivid Sydney/Destination NSW.
Vivid Sydney, a global festival celebrating light, music, and ideas, will illuminate Sydney until June 8th. Last year, the festival drew in 1.43 million attendees.
Stuart Ayres, the NSW Minister for Trade, Tourism and Major Events, highlighted the festival&amp;rsquo;s ability to transform Sydney for 18 days and nights with creativity and vibrant light displays. He emphasized it as a must-see event for showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s pride.</description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020.</description></item><item><title>Every night in Sydney, it's Lights On for Vivid Sydney!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Destination NSW. Vivid Sydney in action.
The tenth anniversary of Vivid Sydney, the world’s largest festival of light, music and ideas, has begun. As Australia’s largest event, Vivid Sydney transforms the city into a captivating display of illumination, sound, and creativity.
The festival commenced with the symbolic &amp;lsquo;Lights On&amp;rsquo; moment, with all eyes on the Sydney Opera House for the &amp;lsquo;Lighting of the Sails&amp;rsquo;. This year&amp;rsquo;s display, created by Australian artist Jonathan Zawada, featured dynamic digital sculptures of commonplace objects and elements from nature, morphing and changing before the viewers&amp;rsquo; eyes.</description></item></channel></rss>