<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-service/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Service on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Metro Ethernet Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 03:18:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</guid><description>When your company needs more bandwidth, you might wonder about your options. Metro Ethernet is a popular choice, often providing more bandwidth for less money than traditional telecommunications services. But is it available in your area?
You can easily check availability using an Ethernet service finder to view a map of &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; buildings nearby. A lit building has active fiber optic service, meaning the fiber optic cables are installed and operational with active laser light...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-metro-ethernet-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Distance Sensitivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 04:27:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</guid><description>The arrival of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers businesses a range of bandwidth options previously unavailable without fiber optic connections. EoC surpasses the speed limits of traditional T1 lines, provides easy scalability, and often comes at a lower price point, making it an attractive option for businesses seeking robust internet solutions.
However, a few limitations hinder the widespread use of EoC. Firstly, it requires compatible equipment at the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office (CO), where your copper lines terminate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-distance-sensitivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated Symmetric Internet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you unhappy with how the internet performs for your business? Do you think it&amp;rsquo;s more for entertainment and casual use than for getting work done quickly and efficiently? You need the internet to function, though. Your customers and suppliers, along with important information, are online. Even your software and communication tools might be cloud-based. What you likely need is a business-grade broadband connection with better performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-symmetric-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Can Be A Lifesaver</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 06:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</guid><description>Imagine your company facing a critical situation. It&amp;rsquo;s growing, and you need more bandwidth than your reliable T1 line can offer. Upgrading to DS3 seems logical, but your provider can only offer a limited increase, nowhere near the 25 or 50 Mbps you require. They suggest fiber optic service, but your location lacks it, meaning months of waiting and a hefty construction bill.
This presents a difficult choice: secure funding and wait for fiber installation, or relocate to a fiber-ready area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-can-be-a-lifesaver/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bonded T1 Solution Increases Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</guid><description>A 1.5 Mbps T1 bandwidth has long been a standard for small businesses, often proving sufficient for their needs. Some businesses even utilize an Integrated T1 solution for combined internet and telephone services. However, as bandwidth demands increase, many find T1 bandwidth limiting their productivity.
A simple solution to increase bandwidth is adding a second T1 line, doubling it to 3 Mbps. However, for these lines to function as a single, larger line, they should be ordered from the same provider with a &amp;ldquo;bonded T1 solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bonded-t1-solution-increases-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Internet Connection Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</guid><description>Businesses require internet access for both customer communication and internal operations. Unlike residential internet, business connections demand higher reliability because downtime directly translates to financial losses, especially for online businesses. Cost-effectiveness is also crucial.
Ethernet Internet is a relatively new technology that offers advantages in both cost and reliability. Additionally, it may provide bandwidth options previously unavailable in your area. A quick search with this Ethernet Internet Finder can reveal your options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-connection-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</guid><description>This document provides more answers to common questions about fiber optic service for businesses. You can find more information in the first and second parts of this FAQ series.
What is a lit building? A lit building already has fiber optic cable installed and activated for service. Typically, only one carrier provides service to a building. If your building is lit, getting bandwidth services from that specific carrier is straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>