<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electronics on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronics/</link><description>Recent content in Electronics on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cash For Clunker Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</guid><description>While the government&amp;rsquo;s Cash for Clunkers program for cars might be ending, there&amp;rsquo;s a similar concept for old electronics. You can get cash for your unwanted devices, including cell phones, laptops, and more!
You might not have heard about this, but it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to earn money from your unused gadgets. From cell phones and laptops to gaming consoles and cameras, many devices have value. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them sit around collecting dust – see how much they&amp;rsquo;re worth!</description></item><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen.</description></item><item><title>The exclusive offers available at the 26th edition of The PC Show</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-exclusive-offers-available-at-the-26th-edition-of-the-pc-show/</guid><description>The PC Show, celebrating 26 years of IT and consumer electronics in Singapore, is back. Major brands like Best Denki, Canon, Courts, Creative, Dell, Epson, Harvey Norman, HP, Lenovo, M1, Newstead, Samsung, Seagate, Singtel, and Toshiba will offer exciting products, deals, and competitive prices.
Gillian Loh, Project Manager at Lines Exposition and Management Services, highlighted that attendees often look for great deals and the latest technology at the show. Organizers aim to continually improve the visitor experience, and this year they are introducing dedicated zones for specific interests and providing online updates on deals and new products.</description></item><item><title>Green Your Cell Phone For St. Patrick's Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 23:36:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/green-your-cell-phone-for-st-patricks-day/</guid><description>On this St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day, let&amp;rsquo;s think about being green in more ways than one! Before the festivities begin, take a few moments to consider how you can help the environment.
You might be surprised to learn that millions of old cell phones are discarded yearly. They contain valuable resources like gold – enough to create a significant treasure if they were all collected. Instead of letting these resources go to waste, retrieve that old phone you have lying around, and let&amp;rsquo;s discover how it can benefit you and the planet.</description></item><item><title>Sell Your Free Cell Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You were wise to get your new, top-of-the-line smartphone for free when you signed up for service. You understand that service plan costs are consistent, and it&amp;rsquo;s the phone&amp;rsquo;s price that fluctuates.
Now that your contract is up, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to upgrade. As you search for another discounted or free phone, you might wonder what to do with your old one.
Many people keep their old phones, thinking they might be helpful someday.</description></item><item><title>Recycle Your Cell Phone To Save A Gorilla</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-cell-phone-to-save-a-gorilla/</guid><description>Recycling old cell phones is beneficial for many reasons, with one significant reason being the protection of the Eastern Lowland Mountain Gorilla in the Democratic Republic of Congo.
You might wonder how cell phone usage impacts gorillas in Africa. The answer lies in the interconnected nature of our ecosystem. Cell phones contain various electronic components, including tantalum capacitors. Tantalum, a scarce and valuable metal, enables the miniaturization of capacitors, making them suitable for slim cell phones.</description></item><item><title>Get your hands on StarHub's flyers for CEE 2017 by downloading them now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-hands-on-starhub-s-flyers-for-cee-2017-by-downloading-them-now/</guid><description>Source: StarHub.
StarHub, recognized as Singapore&amp;rsquo;s most environmentally friendly telecommunications company, will participate in the 2017 Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE).
Details about StarHub&amp;rsquo;s mobile, television, broadband, and bundled services are available in online promotional flyers. These flyers, which include information about the Business Fibre Broadband Bundle, are specifically designed for business customers.
The 2017 CEE will take place at Suntec from June 1st to June 4th. The event will be open from 11 am to 9 pm on levels 1 and 3, and from 12 pm to 9 pm in Halls 403 to 406 on level 4.</description></item><item><title>Banish Vampires To Reduce Global Warming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/banish-vampires-to-reduce-global-warming/</guid><description>Electronic devices, like hidden vampires, silently drain electricity even when seemingly off. This &amp;ldquo;vampire power&amp;rdquo; not only increases your electricity bill but also contributes to global warming.
These &amp;ldquo;vampires&amp;rdquo; hide within devices, indicated by glowing lights, active displays, running fans, or warm surfaces, even when the device is switched off. Remote-controlled devices are prime suspects, as they constantly use power to stay ready for remote signals. Similarly, wireless networks and devices are notorious power consumers.</description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists.</description></item><item><title>LG has introduced the G3 Beat, a mid-tier model of the G3, in Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the LG G3 Beat in Korea on July 18th. This mid-range version of their flagship G3 smartphone provides a comparable high-quality experience, incorporating the Floating Arc design and rapid Laser Auto Focus technology in a smaller form factor with a 5-inch thin-bezel display.
Dr. Jong-seok Park, President and CEO of LG Electronics Mobile Communications Company, emphasized the growing consumer demand for a balanced mix of aesthetics, functionality, performance, and affordability.</description></item><item><title>The Unified Electronic Contract will come into effect in January 2018 in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 17:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-unified-electronic-contract-will-come-into-effect-in-january-2018-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: DED. Al Zaabi.
Dubai Economy&amp;rsquo;s Commercial Compliance &amp;amp; Consumer Protection (CCCP) sector held a workshop for electronics businesses. The goal was to clarify the rules of the unified contract. Starting in 2018, this contract is required for selling or servicing electronic devices and components in the UAE.
This Unified Electronic Contract combines sales, warranty, maintenance, and spare parts agreements into a single document. It became mandatory in early January 2018 and must detail the product, serial number, and purchase date.</description></item><item><title>The Painless Way to Find Network Technicians</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-painless-way-to-find-network-technicians/</guid><description>Your company might be large and technologically advanced, utilizing an internal data network and a PBX phone system, or even a converged enterprise VoIP system. However, you may lack the resources for a dedicated IT department, let alone a telecom team. Hiring necessary services on an as-needed basis is a reality for your business. But is there a simple solution for finding contractors to handle this work?
Now there is. The solution is called the VAR Network.</description></item><item><title>Drowning in a Sea of Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drowning-in-a-sea-of-cell-phones/</guid><description>Current estimations show approximately three billion mobile phone users globally, with a billion new devices sold annually. Given that phones are typically replaced every two to three years, this equates to roughly one billion phones becoming obsolete yearly. The question then arises: where do these discarded devices end up?
Contrary to assumptions that they are forgotten in drawers, a recent study revealed that only 44% of old phones remain unused at home.</description></item><item><title>Taking a Read on the Amazon Kindle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 17:14:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taking-a-read-on-the-amazon-kindle/</guid><description>Despite predictions that computers would lead to the disappearance of paper, the opposite has occurred. The demand for paper has increased significantly due to printers, and traditional media like newspapers and books remain popular. This raises the question: why is paper so persistent in the digital age?
Several factors contribute to this. E-books lack the tactile experience of physical books and the convenience of annotating paper copies. Additionally, reading on backlit screens can cause eye strain, unlike paper.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Expo CNY Fair offers daily discounts of S$380 to the first 888 customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-expo-cny-fair-offers-daily-discounts-of-s-380-to-the-first-888-customers/</guid><description>Red envelopes containing discounts, called angbaos, can be redeemed for certain products in addition to existing promotions (terms and conditions apply).
Items will be offered at up to 88% off.
The Singapore Expo CNY Fair will distribute complimentary lucky angbao gift packages, each valued at S$380, to the initial 888 attendees daily from January 10th to 12th. The event will be held at Singapore Expo Hall 6, open from 12 pm to 9 pm each day.</description></item><item><title>Great deals on a wide range of gadgets at the Shopee Online IT Fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/great-deals-on-a-wide-range-of-gadgets-at-the-shopee-online-it-fair/</guid><description>Shopee&amp;rsquo;s Online IT Fair offers consumers a chance to find great deals on tech gadgets until March 19, 2017, all from the convenience of their devices. The mobile-first marketplace has something for everyone:
March 15: Everything at S$5 Sale
Purchase selected items like the Xplorer 3300 Mouse &amp;amp; Keyboard bundle for just S$5.
March 16: Everything at S$3 Sale
Find select products, such as the Toshiba 8GB Thumbdrive, available for only S$3.</description></item></channel></rss>