<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chef on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chef/</link><description>Recent content in Chef on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore emerges victorious at the Culinary Olympics 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 23:12:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</guid><description>Source: the Singapore National Culinary Team. The Singapore National Culinary Team outperformed over 30 countries to become the champions of the Culinary Olympics 2016. The team achieved gold medals in both the Cold Display and Hot Cooking categories, proving the country&amp;rsquo;s chefs are world-class. From left: Teo Yeow Siang, team captain, from Lavish Catering; Triston Fang, team member, from Ocean Restaurant by Cat Cora, Resorts World Sentosa; Alan Wong, team member, from Lavish Catering; team manager Louis Tay from Swissotel Merchant Court; Roy Lim, team member, from Unilever FoodSolutions; and Alex Chong, team member, from The Regent Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-emerges-victorious-at-the-culinary-olympics-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant is launching a fresh new menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 18:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
The Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant, found within the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, has introduced a new menu to coincide with the arrival of their new head chef, Victor. The dishes are meant to complement the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s modern Eastern aesthetic and embody the Chinese principle of &amp;ldquo;家味,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;flavors of home.&amp;rdquo;
The menu features popular Eastern dishes like Chef&amp;rsquo;s superior fish maw served with seafood soup, and fresh prawns accompanied by two special sauces...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jia-wei-chinese-restaurant-is-launching-a-fresh-new-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Toyo Koda will enhance the menus at Le Passage Mohkan Shan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</guid><description>Source: Le Passage Mohkan Shan website.
Le Passage Mohkan Shan, a French-style hotel and restaurant nestled in its own private tea plantation at the base of Moganshan* mountain in China, has appointed Toyo Koda as its new head chef. This strategic hire emphasizes the hotel&amp;rsquo;s aim to become a premier culinary destination in Asia.
Chef Toyo, previously recognized as one of Asia&amp;rsquo;s top chefs by the San Pellegrino Restaurant Awards in 2013 for his role at Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s French restaurant Franck, is poised to transform the hotel&amp;rsquo;s culinary offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toyo-koda-will-enhance-the-menus-at-le-passage-mohkan-shan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>