<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Promotion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/promotion/</link><description>Recent content in Promotion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/promotion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HP has announced a new promotion offering free roaming Wi-Fi for specific notebooks and tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:02:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-has-announced-a-new-promotion-offering-free-roaming-wi-fi-for-specific-notebooks-and-tablets/</guid><description>HP and iPass, the largest Wi-Fi network globally, recently revealed a partnership. Select HP laptops and tablets will now offer access to the iPass network.
Source: HP website.
This collaboration aims to provide users in Asia Pacific and Japan (APJ) with easier and more budget-friendly internet access both locally and during their travels. Customers purchasing new HP laptops and tablets with this feature will enjoy automatic access to millions of hotspots on the iPass network for a year, free of charge, upon registration.</description></item><item><title>In 2017, a settlement network powered by blockchain announced that it would waive fees for transfers to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:21:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-a-settlement-network-powered-by-blockchain-announced-that-it-would-waive-fees-for-transfers-to-singapore/</guid><description>OKLink, a global settlement platform, has introduced the first entirely free remittance corridor. The company stated that transfers up to US$100,000 each month to Singapore will be free throughout 2017.
Previously, OKLink applied a 0.1% fee on cross-border payments to Singapore, while other companies might charge up to US$5 per transaction.
&amp;ldquo;As the world&amp;rsquo;s largest blockchain-powered global settlement network, we can process cross-border payments faster and more affordably as more partners join,&amp;rdquo; explained Jack Liu, Chief Strategy Officer at OKLink.</description></item><item><title>Sony Singapore's year-end promotions are valid until the beginning of January 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</guid><description>Are you looking for some of Sony&amp;rsquo;s top products from 2019? Here are a few:
Digital imaging
Sony A7 III
Source: Sony. The α7 III.
The A7 III boasts five-axis stabilization, 4D Focus for reliable focusing in low light (down to EV-3), and the capability to record 4K HDR videos.
Promotional price: S$2,699 (usual price S$2,899)
Sony α7 III with 35mm full-frame image sensor (ILCE7M3K) Sony RX100 VII
The compact RX100 VII features an extensive zoom range and remarkable speed.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces three new exclusive routes with a 20% discount on all flights until February 16th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 05:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-three-new-exclusive-routes-with-a-20-discount-on-all-flights-until-february-16th/</guid><description>AirAsia is the sole airline offering flights for three new routes: Johor Bahru to Tawau, Singapore to Kota Bharu, and Singapore to Terengganu. The airline is currently promoting these routes with fares as low as RM69* for travel between Johor Bahru and Tawau. This offer is valid for bookings made before February 16th, 2014, for travel dates between April 18th, 2014 and January 31st, 2015.
Welcome banners at Changi Airport</description></item><item><title>Use #GrabTaxi to #GrabDurian in Singapore on August 1 and 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 03:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-grabtaxi-to-grabdurian-in-singapore-on-august-1-and-2/</guid><description>Source: GrabTaxi.
GrabTaxi, a popular taxi booking app in Southeast Asia, is giving back to its loyal Singaporean users with a special durian treat.
For a limited time on August 1st and 2nd, customers can order a box of fresh Mao Shan Wang durian through the GrabTaxi app for S$10. Deliveries will be carried out by a dedicated GrabCar durian fleet throughout the island. Orders can be placed between 2 pm and 9 pm, but availability is limited, so early ordering is recommended.</description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates is offering reduced fares to more than 70 locations. Bookings must be made by August 20, 2018, for travel dates between September 1, 2018, and March 31, 2019.
Economy Class fares start at AED945 to Beirut, Lebanon, AED995 to Mumbai, India, and AED2,345 to Bangkok, Thailand. Business Class fares to these destinations cost AED5,245, AED2,795, and AED9,795, respectively.
Travelers can enhance their experience with Emirates Holidays, adding a five-star hotel stay to their trip.</description></item><item><title>During Ramadan, Volvo is offering special deals on their cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-ramadan-volvo-is-offering-special-deals-on-their-cars/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. The Volvo XC60.
Trading Enterprises – Volvo, the sole distributor of Volvo cars in the UAE and a member of the Al-Futtaim Group, has revealed its Ramadan promotional offers for several popular models.
The Volvo XC90 and XC60, both luxury SUVs, come with a 20% dealer contribution towards the down payment through the Volvo Selection program. This offer also includes a two-year buyback guarantee and monthly payments starting at AED 2,999 for the XC90 and AED 1,999 for the XC60.</description></item><item><title>The Business Plan package at The Shilla Seoul includes access to The Executive Lounge</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-business-plan-package-at-the-shilla-seoul-includes-access-to-the-executive-lounge/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. The Executive Lounge.
Through June 30, 2019, The Shilla Seoul is offering its Business Plan package, which gives guests the opportunity to experience The Executive Lounge.
Guests selecting the Executive Business Deluxe option receive exclusive access to The Executive Lounge, complimentary breakfast at The Parkview, and access to both the gym and indoor swimming pool.
The Executive Lounge at The Shilla Seoul, situated on the hotel&amp;rsquo;s top floor, is designed as a luxurious penthouse.</description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):</description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with the One Lagi Best Deal!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-the-one-lagi-best-deal/</guid><description>Source: One Faber Group. Cable car visual.
In honor of Singapore’s 52nd birthday, One Faber Group is offering the One Lagi Best Deal, featuring local promotions on its leisure activities and services from Faber Peak Singapore to Sentosa Island.
Until September 17th, Singaporeans* can take advantage of a special offer: a S$52 bundle for adults and a S$42 bundle for children. The adult bundle includes a round-trip Singapore cable car ride, a standard ticket to the Wings Of Time show, a standard ticket to Sentosa Merlion, a three-course meal at the Good Old Days restaurant, and a batik orchid magnet.</description></item><item><title>Escape to Bintan Lagoon Resort for a Global Wellness Day retreat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/escape-to-bintan-lagoon-resort-for-a-global-wellness-day-retreat/</guid><description>Bintan Lagoon Resort (BLR) is commemorating this year&amp;rsquo;s Global Wellness Day with a special getaway package full of wellness activities on June 10th and 11th.
A quick 75-minute ferry trip from Singapore, BLR is nestled on 300 hectares of lush land, boasting a private 1.5km beach. With a wide range of over 50 indoor and outdoor activities, from adventurous to relaxing, and delicious, healthy culinary options, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Jumeirah City Break</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-jumeirah-city-break/</guid><description>Source: Jumeirah website.
City Breaks at Jumeirah Emirates Towers, Jumeirah Creekside Hotel, and Jumeirah Living World Trade Centre Residences come with perks like free entry to Wild Wadi Waterpark and Zero Gravity Private Beach.
Jumeirah Emirates Towers boasts shopping at the Boulevard, various dining and nightlife options, and a convenient location just five minutes from Dubai Mall, accessible via the hotel&amp;rsquo;s complimentary shuttle service.
Reserve a room for three or more nights at participating Jumeirah hotels in Dubai with the Jumeirah City Break promotion and enjoy a 20% discount on the best available rates, along with:</description></item><item><title>Vanity, Thy Number is Toll Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-thy-number-is-toll-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 23:21:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vanity-thy-number-is-toll-free/</guid><description>Vanity definitely has a place in business. Any technology that provides a competitive advantage, including a vanity toll-free number, is worth considering.
What distinguishes a vanity number from a regular toll-free number is the connection between letters and numbers on a standard telephone keypad. While the &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; button lacks letters, numbers &amp;ldquo;2&amp;rdquo; through &amp;ldquo;9&amp;rdquo; each have three letters assigned to them.
This letter-number association allows phone numbers to be dialed as words.</description></item><item><title>W Retreat &amp; Spa Bali - Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary with a month-long celebration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/w-retreat-spa-bali-seminyak-is-celebrating-its-fifth-anniversary-with-a-month-long-celebration/</guid><description>Source: W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali website.
The W Retreat &amp;amp; Spa Bali in Seminyak is celebrating its fifth anniversary on March 5, 2016. The resort will commemorate this milestone with a month-long celebration titled &amp;ldquo;FIVE ON FIVE,&amp;rdquo; showcasing five unique highlights.
WOOBAR will present special edition Paletas Wey popsicles, a Mexican-style frozen treat crafted by the Bali-based company. Meanwhile, W THE STORE will offer an exclusive, limited-edition collection of &amp;ldquo;Wanitas&amp;rdquo; décor.</description></item><item><title>StarHub is offering a deal of 3GB for S$3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 06:57:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-is-offering-a-deal-of-3gb-for-s-3/</guid><description>StarHub is offering a new &amp;ldquo;3GB-for-$3&amp;rdquo; data upsize option for its mobile postpaid customers. For a limited time, customers who sign up for or renew their StarHub 4G plans can get an extra 3GB of data for S$3 per month. This promotional price will increase to S$6 per month for customers who sign up on or after April 1, 2016.
Here are the details for StarHub&amp;rsquo;s two-year mobile postpaid plans:</description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces a special upgrade offer for owners of 2G phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-a-special-upgrade-offer-for-owners-of-2g-phones/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced a special offer as they prepare to discontinue 2G services in Singapore, starting in April 2017.
Source: Singtel.
The Alcatel Onetouch 2052x is available for S$48, and the Onetouch Pop D3 is priced at S$95.
Prepaid customers can take advantage of S$70 in free talk time and 350MB of data, along with an additional S$30 in free talk time when they trade in a 2G phone.
Postpaid customers on Silver Plan Combo 1 and 2 will receive a 20% discount on their monthly bills.</description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher).</description></item><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen collaborate for a flash sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 01:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-hong-kong-and-grand-hyatt-shenzhen-collaborate-for-a-flash-sale/</guid><description>Grand Hyatt Hong Kong and Grand Hyatt Shenzhen have teamed up to offer the Grand Spring Voyage flash sale, featuring accommodation packages ranging from two to five nights in both cities. This convenient travel opportunity is made possible by the newly extended MTR East Rail line, which directly connects the two hotels. The journey between the nearest stations, Exhibition Centre Station in Hong Kong and Lo Wu Station in Shenzhen, is a quick 40 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality.</description></item><item><title>Book with ONYX in February to receive exclusive discounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-with-onyx-in-february-to-receive-exclusive-discounts/</guid><description>Source: Onyx web page. Several ONYX Hospitality Group properties are offering special deals for the Chinese New Year.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, guests can enjoy up to a 20% discount at the Oriental Residence Bangkok or at one of the 25 participating Amari, OZO, Shama, and Mosaic Collection hotels. These offers are available at locations in Thailand, Sri Lanka, mainland China, Hong Kong, Qatar, and Bangladesh.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th.</description></item><item><title>Dell and Alienware are currently offering promotions at SITEX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 22:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-and-alienware-are-currently-offering-promotions-at-sitex/</guid><description>Dell and Alienware are offering promotions on select products at SITEX 2016, taking place from November 26th to 27th at the Singapore Expo Halls 5 and 6.
XPS 13 Laptop
Known as the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest 13&amp;quot; laptop, the latest XPS prioritizes performance, portability, and impressive visuals. Its stand-out feature is the InfinityEdge display, which is practically borderless. This model boasts a powerful 7th Gen Intel Core i7 processor for enhanced performance and prolonged battery life.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years.</description></item><item><title>Complimentary stopovers offered to Etihad Economy Class passengers traveling from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is offering a complimentary one-night stay at the Radisson Blu hotel on Abu Dhabi’s Yas Island. This offer is open to Economy Class passengers flying from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan who have a layover in Abu Dhabi.
Mohammad Al Bulooki, Etihad Airways Executive VP Commercial, expressed the airline&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for showcasing Abu Dhabi to its guests. He highlighted the diverse attractions of the UAE capital, ranging from cultural landmarks and beaches to sports and adventure activities.</description></item><item><title>The Nathan Hartono concert is brought to you by Singtel Music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 23:45:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-nathan-hartono-concert-is-brought-to-you-by-singtel-music/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel Music presents Hartono concert.
At the beginning of 2017, music enthusiasts will have the opportunity to connect with Singaporean singing star Nathan Hartono. Singtel Music is showcasing its support for local musical talent by holding an exclusive event, Up-Close with Nathan Hartono, on January 21, 2017.
Singtel states that fans can experience Hartono&amp;rsquo;s performance and interact with him during the event. Hartono, backed by a full band, will perform a selection of songs in both English and Chinese, including new original pieces from his EP scheduled for release in early 2017.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music.</description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5.</description></item><item><title>Preview the SG50 National Day promotion at Fairmont Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 14:04:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-the-sg50-national-day-promotion-at-fairmont-singapore/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 50th anniversary, the Fairmont Singapore is offering a special package. This package provides guests with a prime location to view the fireworks display during the National Day preview parade on August 1st.
Ranging from S$400++ to S$750++ for a one-night stay, the package includes a premium room with views of Marina Bay and the Padang. Guests will also enjoy complimentary breakfast for two and a 24-hour self-parking coupon at Raffles City Shopping Centre.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers.</description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa.</description></item><item><title>During the month of September, BODUM is offering a promotion on coffee makers and toasters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-month-of-september-bodum-is-offering-a-promotion-on-coffee-makers-and-toasters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-month-of-september-bodum-is-offering-a-promotion-on-coffee-makers-and-toasters/</guid><description>BODUM is offering a special deal for customers in Singapore throughout September. When you buy a BODUM ePEBO Vacuum Coffee Maker, you&amp;rsquo;ll receive a complimentary BODUM Toaster. Alternatively, shoppers can choose a 15% discount on BODUM Toasters.
Source: BODUM. The ePEBO coffee maker.
Here are the specifics:
Purchase a BODUM ePEBO Vacuum Coffee Maker for S$369 and receive a free BODUM toaster valued at S$99. Enjoy a 15% price reduction on BODUM toasters, bringing the cost down to S$84.</description></item><item><title>Customers who purchase the GeForce RTX 3080 and 3090 are eligible to receive a Call of Duty game bundle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</guid><description>Image: Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War promotional image highlighting the Woods Operator Pack and Confrontation Weapons Pack.
NVIDIA is running a limited-time promotion offering a free copy of Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War with the purchase of qualifying GeForce RTX 3080 or 3090 graphics cards and pre-built PCs.
Releasing on November 13, 2020, Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War is the newest installment in the popular Call of Duty series.</description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the Singapore Mother's Day contest for a chance to win a Huawei P20 in Pink Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</guid><description>Source: Huawei Mobile Singapore
Facebook page. Watch the video
In Singapore, Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group is holding a contest in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day (May 13th), ending on May 24th.
To participate, Singaporean residents simply need to comment on the contest video found on the Huawei Mobile Singapore Facebook page. The comment should answer the question: &amp;ldquo;What lengths would your mother go to for you?&amp;rdquo; and include the hashtag #SeeMooore.</description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days.</description></item><item><title>The MICE offer at Ajman Palace Hotel is valid until the end of September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mice-offer-at-ajman-palace-hotel-is-valid-until-the-end-of-september/</guid><description>Source: Ajman Palace Hotel website.
The Ajman Palace Hotel, home to extensive meeting and conference spaces, including the largest ballroom in the Northern Emirates, has introduced a new MICE package available until September 30, 2015.
Managed by HMH – Hospitality Management Holdings, the hotel is conveniently located 22 km from Dubai International Airport and 11 km from Sharjah International Airport. Situated on a private beach, this resort offers 254 rooms, suites and serviced residences, a variety of restaurants and lounges, and comprehensive meeting and event facilities.</description></item><item><title>Take advantage of the week-long Vietjet promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet website.
Vietjet Aviation Joint Stock Company (Vietjet), an airline with 32 domestic and international routes, is offering a limited-time promotion with 500,000 discounted tickets. This offer is valid for one week, ending on Wednesday, July 29th, 2015.
The promotion applies to all of Vietjet&amp;rsquo;s current domestic and international routes for travel between September 7th, 2015 and December 31st, 2015. Discounted fares will be displayed in a separate column during booking.</description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments.</description></item><item><title>Residents of Hong Kong can enjoy an additional complimentary night at New World Millennium Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</guid><description>The New World Millennium Hong Kong Hotel, a prominent five-star establishment situated on the Victoria Harbour waterfront in Tsim Sha Tsui East, is offering a special &amp;ldquo;1+1 Bonus Night&amp;rdquo; room package to Hong Kong residents. Until September 30th, residents booking a one-night stay can enjoy an additional night free of charge.
This promotion is exclusively available to Hong Kong residents and requires HKID verification upon check-in. By reserving a City View room or a higher category for a single night, guests will automatically receive a second night&amp;rsquo;s stay complimentary.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the early bird iftar promotion at the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:58:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-early-bird-iftar-promotion-at-the-shangri-la-hotel-dubai/</guid><description>From June 18th to July 17th, 2015, the Shangri-La Hotel Dubai is offering a special promotion for iftar.
Starting at sunset, Dunes Café will serve a selection of traditional Arabic dishes from across the region, along with special beverages and an assortment of desserts.
For the first week of Ramadan, the buffet at Dunes Café is priced at AED150 per person. After the first week, the price will be AED175 per person.</description></item><item><title>Ascott Star Rewards is marking its second anniversary with special promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 20:34:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ascott-star-rewards-is-marking-its-second-anniversary-with-special-promotions/</guid><description>Ascott Star Rewards (ASR), the loyalty program of The Ascott Limited, is marking its second anniversary with a &amp;ldquo;Celebrate The Little Joys&amp;rdquo; campaign. This campaign offers double bonus points and complimentary tier upgrades to show appreciation and reward its members.
Since its 2019 launch, ASR has experienced over 400% membership growth. ASR members are responsible for roughly 90% of Ascott’s direct online bookings, and over 60% are repeat guests. Compared to non-members, ASR members spend 36% more with Ascott.</description></item><item><title>Experience the unique Kampong culinary specials at the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-unique-kampong-culinary-specials-at-the-intercontinental-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>This June, the Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur in Malaysia is offering a special deal for gatherings with colleagues, business contacts, and potential clients. The promotion is valid in their newly renovated ballrooms and private function rooms.
Source: Intercontinental Kuala Lumpur website.
For every ten paying guests, one person can attend for free. The Selera Kampong package is priced at RM155 nett per adult, while the Kampong Boys Special is RM172 nett per adult.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the successful first year of Hyatt Regency Suzhou with our Anniversary Meeting Package</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 11:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-successful-first-year-of-hyatt-regency-suzhou-with-our-anniversary-meeting-package/</guid><description>Source: Hyatt Regency Suzhou.
The Hyatt Regency Suzhou is commemorating its first anniversary with various special offers as a thank you to its loyal and valued guests for their support throughout the year.
Having opened its doors on August 24, 2014, in the Suzhou Industrial Park (SIP), the conveniently located Hyatt Regency Suzhou boasts 355 rooms and suites. Amenities include a Regency Club, five dining options, and over 15,000 square feet of space for events.</description></item><item><title>Experience the Peranakan Food Festival at Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-peranakan-food-festival-at-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>The Peranakan* Food Festival is making a comeback at the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy! The hotel is bringing back this popular food festival with new additions to the menu, such as ayam masak rebung lemak (chicken with bamboo shoots in spicy gravy). Returning favorites include bubur cha cha (tapioca in coconut milk) and much more.
Guests can explore booths showcasing Peranakan heritage at the Feast@East Buffet Restaurant.
From June 10th to 19th, enjoy a variety of seafood at Feast@East Buffet Restaurant, featuring Chilean blue mussels, spanner crabs, and other crustacean favorites.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes.</description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich.</description></item><item><title>Big discounts on Honda vehicles in the UAE during the month of Ramadhan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-discounts-on-honda-vehicles-in-the-uae-during-the-month-of-ramadhan/</guid><description>Source: Al-Futtaim Group. Honda cars are on Ramadan offer in the UAE.
This Ramadan, Al-Futtaim Honda, the exclusive distributor of Honda vehicles, motorcycles, marine engines, and power products in the UAE, is offering reduced starting prices and complimentary service and warranty coverage across their car lineup. Ramadan is typically a popular time for purchasing new vehicles in the GCC region, and various brands offer promotions during this period.
Honda Civic</description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer.</description></item><item><title>Experience the Singapore F1 promotion at BIG Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 06:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-singapore-f1-promotion-at-big-hotel/</guid><description>Source: BIG Hotel.
Travelers can take advantage of a Formula One promotion at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s BIG Hotel. Bookings made by September 12th will receive a 10% discount on room rates, complimentary Wi-Fi throughout their stay, and access to free on-demand movies. This offer is valid for stays during the F1 night race in Singapore, from September 18th to 21st.
The hotel is conveniently situated on Middle Road, a short distance from Bras Basah station.</description></item><item><title>Join us at Clarke Quay to celebrate F1 with special meal promotions and parties at Attica</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 18:52:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-at-clarke-quay-to-celebrate-f1-with-special-meal-promotions-and-parties-at-attica/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay website.
Clarke Quay is celebrating the Singapore Grand Prix season with special offers and events for both racing fans and those just looking to enjoy the festivities.
Everyone can take advantage of dining deals like buy-one-get-one-free offers at District 10, special Grand Prix menu items at Hooters, and a free meal for every four diners at Peony Jade.
Those with Grand Prix tickets can also enjoy discounts of 10% to 20% at participating restaurants.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council.</description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is offering a promotion during Golden Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 13:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-offering-a-promotion-during-golden-week/</guid><description>The Sanya EDITION hotel is offering a special promotion for travelers visiting China during Golden Week, which falls on October 1st to 7th.
To celebrate, the hotel is hosting guest chef Matthew David Ona from Roof 325 Restaurant and Bar in Shanghai. Chef Ona, known for his culinary expertise at one of Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s top dining destinations, will be at The Jade Egret restaurant from October 1st to 3rd. He has designed special steak and seafood tasting menus for the occasion.</description></item><item><title>The Big Street set meals provide even greater value for your money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 15:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-big-street-set-meals-provide-even-greater-value-for-your-money/</guid><description>Source: Big Street.
The Singaporean eatery Big Street is offering a special multi-course meal for S$26 per person during June. This offer requires a minimum of two diners and is valid for both lunch and dinner.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the special meal includes:
Appetiser: Garden greens with cherry tomato salad Soup: Oriental chicken with snow fungus and wolfberry soup Main dishes: Hainanese steamed kampong chicken Seasonal vegetables with mushrooms Big Street chili king prawn Thai fragrant steamed rice If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for something else, Big Street&amp;rsquo;s standard set lunch costs S$9.</description></item><item><title>May's Big Street meal promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/may-s-big-street-meal-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Big Street. Chilli slipper lobster in prata bag.
Big Street, a restaurant and lounge with air conditioning and multiple levels, is offering a special set meal deal throughout May in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day, available to everyone.
Priced at S$26 per person (minimum of two people), this deal includes an appetizer, soup, main course, and dessert.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what the set meal promotion includes:
Appetiser: Fresh garden salad served with crispy chicken</description></item><item><title>The Marina Mandarin Singapore welcomes the arrival of hairy crabs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-marina-mandarin-singapore-welcomes-the-arrival-of-hairy-crabs/</guid><description>Peach Blossoms, the renowned Cantonese restaurant located on the 5th level of Marina Mandarin Singapore, is now offering a seasonal delicacy flown in from Shanghai, China: hairy crabs.
Also at the Marina Mandarin, on the 4th level, the AquaMarine buffet restaurant is spotlighting seafood until October 29th.
Source: Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
AquaMarine features an array of Asian dishes, including Vietnamese Braised Fish in Clay Pot, Thai Curry Mud Crab, authentic Filipino Beef Adobo, fresh Cambodian Fish Curry, and many more.</description></item></channel></rss>