<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Diabetes on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/diabetes/</link><description>Recent content in Diabetes on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:25:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/diabetes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The intelligent coach for individuals with diabetes is designed to improve long-term quality of life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 23:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intelligent-coach-for-individuals-with-diabetes-is-designed-to-improve-long-term-quality-of-life/</guid><description>A new &amp;ldquo;smart coach&amp;rdquo; service aims to assist individuals with type 2 diabetes in developing healthier lifestyle choices for improved long-term well-being. Diabetes, particularly when poorly managed, can result in complications such as vision loss, kidney issues, and nerve damage. It has also been linked to Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease, sometimes referred to as &amp;ldquo;type 3 diabetes.&amp;rdquo;
The global rise of diabetes presents significant healthcare cost concerns. Holmusk, a digital health and data analytics company, highlights that over 415 million people worldwide have diabetes, a figure that continues to grow annually.</description></item><item><title>Fosun Trade Medical Devices introduces a dual-function blood glucose and uric acid tester called BUZUD</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fosun-trade-medical-devices-introduces-a-dual-function-blood-glucose-and-uric-acid-tester-called-buzud/</guid><description>Source: BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This image showcases the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System from BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices. This system allows for convenient at-home testing of both uric acid and blood glucose levels.
BUZUD, Fosun Trade Medical Devices, a medical device company, has launched the Safe AQ UG Blood Glucose and Uric Acid Monitoring System. This innovative device allows users to measure both blood sugar and uric acid levels from the comfort of their homes with ease and a high degree of accuracy.</description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach.</description></item><item><title>Diabetes is having a greater impact on older employees in the workforce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diabetes-is-having-a-greater-impact-on-older-employees-in-the-workforce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 23:12:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/diabetes-is-having-a-greater-impact-on-older-employees-in-the-workforce/</guid><description>Source: IDF.
The International Diabetes Federation (IDF) believes that over 70% of type 2 diabetes cases worldwide, or 150 million new cases by 2035, could be prevented or postponed through healthier lifestyle choices.
Dr. Petra Wilson, CEO of IDF, emphasizes that good health translates to economic prosperity, urging governments to recognize the burden of rising diabetes cases on development and healthcare systems. Investing in healthy lifestyle initiatives, she argues, makes financial and societal sense.</description></item><item><title>FairPrice promotes healthier options and takes a stand against diabetes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fairprice-promotes-healthier-options-and-takes-a-stand-against-diabetes/</guid><description>NTUC FairPrice (FairPrice) is starting a series of initiatives this year to encourage healthy eating habits and raise awareness about diabetes. The first of these initiatives is a three-month-long 5% discount on all FairPrice housebrand wholegrain rice. Additionally, for the next two weeks, FairPrice will offer the same discount on all 1,000 products across its 133 supermarkets that carry the Healthier Choice Symbol. These discounts are anticipated to save FairPrice shoppers over half a million dollars.</description></item><item><title>A study conducted by Abbott reveals concerning patterns among diabetics in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 22:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</guid><description>Special thosai set.
A recent study, the Abbott Food, Spikes and Diabetes Survey, suggests that 70% of individuals managing diabetes in urban India may not be carefully managing their food intake. This survey, conducted by Ipsos India on behalf of Abbott, involved over 4,100 participants aged 36 to 65 with Type 2 diabetes (diagnosed for over 18 months) from various socioeconomic backgrounds across eight major cities. The study aimed to understand their eating habits, the impact of meals on blood sugar fluctuations, and its effect on diabetes management.</description></item></channel></rss>