<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CloudXchange on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloudxchange/</link><description>Recent content in CloudXchange on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloudxchange/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telx Cloud Exchange Reduces Service Lag Time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</guid><description>Cloud services promise cost savings by replacing your data center with rented infrastructure, platforms, and software. While this sounds good in theory, some users experience performance issues.
Cloud computing boasts virtually unlimited resources, instantly available when needed. So why do some cloud-based operations become slower than their local counterparts?
It boils down to connectivity. Although electrical signals travel at the speed of light, distance still matters. Light speed is significantly reduced in terrestrial circuits compared to a vacuum, and signals face further delays due to network equipment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-cloud-exchange-reduces-service-lag-time/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Connection Centers Go Beyond Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</guid><description>Businesses exploring the shift of their IT infrastructure from on-site data centers to colocation facilities have a new choice to consider: Telx Cloud Connection Centers. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the offerings of a cloud connection center that surpass traditional colocation or carrier hotel services.
Traditional colocation provides cost reductions and service improvements due to economies of scale. The underlying concept is that a single, large, environmentally controlled, highly secure, and well-connected data center is more efficient than numerous individual private data centers with similar requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-connection-centers-go-beyond-colocation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>