<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content/</link><description>Recent content in Content on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In January, StarHub will be featuring high-definition Korean movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-january-starhub-will-be-featuring-high-definition-korean-movies/</guid><description>StarHub TV customers will be the first in Asia to enjoy the latest and greatest Korean films in high definition (HD), 24 hours a day. The company announced that tvN Movies HD, Asia’s first channel dedicated to Korean films, will launch on StarHub TV (channel 818) on January 11, 2017. For added convenience, the channel will also be available on demand as tvN Movies VOD HD. Customers can watch it anytime on StarHub TV Channel 819, or stream it via StarHub Go, StarHub&amp;rsquo;s online streaming service.</description></item><item><title>Tips from Akamai for optimizing app engagement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 04:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-from-akamai-for-optimizing-app-engagement/</guid><description>A report from Akamai highlights that 95% of gamers quit playing a game within the first month. The company states that slow loading times are a major factor, causing 40% of players to abandon games. Additionally, 20% of gamers expect instant page loads.
To enhance user retention, Akamai suggests strategies applicable to any app:
Anticipate Large-Scale Success: Be prepared for a global player base. Utilize a robust content delivery network to handle high traffic.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV provides complimentary previews and free gifts for new subscribers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 03:39:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-provides-complimentary-previews-and-free-gifts-for-new-subscribers/</guid><description>Singtel is offering several benefits to its Singtel TV subscribers for the holiday season.
Until January 2, 2017, Singtel TV customers can enjoy complimentary access to the following channels:
Available on the Singtel TV set-top box:
FOX Movies Premium (channel 414) FOX Action Movies (channel 408) FOX Family Movies (channel 406) Sundance Channel (channel 401) Thrill (channel 415) Turner Classic Movies (channel 420) Available on Singtel TV GO (for both set-top box and catch-up channels):</description></item><item><title>HubSpot reveals the secrets of inbound marketing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-reveals-the-secrets-of-inbound-marketing/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot presentation. A higher volume of content leads to increased lead generation.
Ryan Bonnici, HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Director of Marketing for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan, argues that traditional methods of customer acquisition are no longer effective. During the launch of HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Singapore office, which also serves as the company&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters, Bonnici explained the effectiveness of inbound marketing compared to outbound marketing.
Traditionally, marketing involved bombarding consumers with advertisements and flyers.</description></item><item><title>The HALCYON VR murder mystery from Syfy will soon be accessible on the Samsung Gear VR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 08:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-halcyon-vr-murder-mystery-from-syfy-will-soon-be-accessible-on-the-samsung-gear-vr/</guid><description>Source: Syfy. HALCYON investigates a VR murder.
Syfy, known for its imaginative entertainment, will debut its unique hybrid virtual reality (VR) series, HALCYON, on September 22nd at 10 pm. The series is a creation of Secret Location, a multi-award-winning content studio specializing in cutting-edge platforms.
Set in 2040, HALCYON centers on Julie Dover, a detective in the Virtual Reality Crimes Unit. She tackles the first-ever murder within virtual reality, a seemingly impossible crime, and unravels the hidden conspiracy behind it.</description></item><item><title>Air France provides complimentary newspapers and magazines for tablets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-provides-complimentary-newspapers-and-magazines-for-tablets/</guid><description>Air France has launched a new app, Air France Press, allowing Flying Blue members to enjoy complimentary digital media offline.
Flying Blue members can download a selection of French and international newspapers and magazines at no cost. This content is accessible offline before, during, and after their Air France flights. Passengers can download publications with their ticket, starting 24 hours before their flight until departure.
Access to the service is granted by logging into the app using Flying Blue credentials or a reservation number.</description></item><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race.</description></item><item><title>Singtel TV broadens its entertainment offerings with the addition of HBO</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 09:40:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-tv-broadens-its-entertainment-offerings-with-the-addition-of-hbo/</guid><description>Singtel is adding HBO programming to its television offerings. The deal means Singtel TV and its Singtel TV GO app users will have access to HBO Asia’s six channels. To mark the occasion, Singtel is offering a free preview of all six channels until February 28, 2019.
Beginning March 15, subscribers can access HBO GO, HBO Asia’s streaming service, through CAST, Singtel’s video app for mobile and smart TV.
Yuen Kuan Moon, CEO, Consumer Singapore, Singtel, said the company is “thrilled” to welcome HBO to its roster.</description></item><item><title>Singtel celebrates National Day with Olympics film honoring Singapore's resilient spirit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 21:42:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-celebrates-national-day-with-olympics-film-honoring-singapore-s-resilient-spirit/</guid><description>Singtel has chosen an Olympics theme for its annual National Day (August 8) tribute.
Source: Singtel. Sprinter Shanti Pereira is featured in Leading Through Uncertainty, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s National Day tribute for 2021.
This year&amp;rsquo;s film, Leading Through Uncertainty, spotlights several of the nation&amp;rsquo;s top athletes who represented Singapore at the 2020 Olympics in Tokyo. It chronicles the athletes&amp;rsquo; journey to the Games amidst the uncertainty of the COVID-19 pandemic and its impact on the 2020 Games.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users now have the option to subscribe to iflix</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 08:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-now-have-the-option-to-subscribe-to-iflix/</guid><description>iflix, a Southeast Asian internet TV provider, has teamed up with Malaysian mobile network operator Celcom Axiata to offer TV series, movies, and other content to Celcom&amp;rsquo;s over 12 million subscribers in Malaysia.
Starting March 15, 2016, all Celcom subscribers will get two free months of iflix, allowing them to stream content seamlessly on Celcom&amp;rsquo;s 4G network (a value of RM20). After the two-month promotional period, customers can continue enjoying iflix for a discounted rate of RM9 per month.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces Malaysia's tonton to its CAST app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</guid><description>Singtel has added Media Prima&amp;rsquo;s tonton, a popular Malaysian streaming platform, to its CAST video streaming app. This partnership, along with existing offerings on Singtel TV, makes Singtel a leading provider of Malay entertainment content in Singapore.
This is the first time tonton is available outside of Malaysia. Through CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus pack, subscribers will have access to over 23,000 hours of Malay entertainment, including content from TV3, TV9, and tonton originals.</description></item><item><title>Fans in Singapore of Song Seung Heon may have the opportunity to meet him</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fans-in-singapore-of-song-seung-heon-may-have-the-opportunity-to-meet-him/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for Saimdang featuring Song.
To kick off the new year, Singtel is bringing South Korean celebrity Song Seung Heon to Singapore on January 7, 2017. Song&amp;rsquo;s visit will promote the drama Saimdang (师任堂), which premieres on Singtel TV&amp;rsquo;s Oh!K channel (channel 525/611) on January 25, 2017, at 9 pm.
Singtel TV subscribers can enter to win 20 pairs of tickets to a meet-and-greet and autograph session with Song.</description></item><item><title>The Aneka Plus pack on Singtel CAST now features Tribe from Astro</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The show &amp;ldquo;Qadr&amp;rdquo; from Tribe is now available through CAST.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CAST platform now includes Tribe, a regional video service by Astro. Showcasing content from Astro&amp;rsquo;s Malay channels, like Astro Ria and Astro Prima, Tribe will be part of CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus package.
For the first time in Singapore, viewers can access Astro&amp;rsquo;s premium on-demand Malay programs anywhere. Tribe offers complete seasons of drama series, variety shows, movies, and award shows.</description></item><item><title>Golden Village Multiplex is the first in Singapore to introduce Auro 11.1 audio technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-village-multiplex-is-the-first-in-singapore-to-introduce-auro-11-1-audio-technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/golden-village-multiplex-is-the-first-in-singapore-to-introduce-auro-11-1-audio-technology/</guid><description>Golden Village Multiplex is the first cinema chain in Singapore to offer Auro 11.1 by Barco, an immersive 3D sound technology.
Long, Long Time Ago portrays Singapore approximately 50 years in the past.
Audiences can experience Auro 11.1 at Golden Village Suntec City in Singapore with the debut of Jack Neo&amp;rsquo;s newest Chinese New Year film, Long, Long Time Ago (我们的故事), premiering February 4th. To fully utilize this immersive audio technology, the film was mixed at Galaxy Studios Belgium specifically for Auro 11.</description></item><item><title>PowerDVD from CyberLink now has the capability to play 360 degree videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 02:26:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/powerdvd-from-cyberlink-now-has-the-capability-to-play-360-degree-videos/</guid><description>Source: CyberLink. Couple experiencing a 360-degree video.
CyberLink, a company known for its multimedia software, has updated its primary media player, PowerDVD. The latest version allows users to view 360-degree videos.
Users can manipulate their viewpoint while watching a 360 video in PowerDVD. By panning and rotating, viewers can experience the content from various angles, providing a more immersive experience. Dr. Jau Huang, CyberLink&amp;rsquo;s CEO, believes that &amp;ldquo;360-degree video is a perfect way to introduce virtual reality.</description></item><item><title>ACCA is sponsoring a MOOC on FutureLearn that grants learners an exemption from the F1 paper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/acca-is-sponsoring-a-mooc-on-futurelearn-that-grants-learners-an-exemption-from-the-f1-paper/</guid><description>The Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (ACCA) is breaking new ground as the first professional accountancy body to use massive open online courses (MOOCs) for professional recognition. They are partnering with FutureLearn, a UK-based social learning platform, to offer free online courses in accounting, finance, and business.
This partnership aims to reach a global audience, providing valuable supplementary knowledge for professionals and introducing career paths to those new to the field.</description></item><item><title>Angloinfo and Nexus have joined forces to launch additional expat sites in Asia through a joint venture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/angloinfo-and-nexus-have-joined-forces-to-launch-additional-expat-sites-in-asia-through-a-joint-venture/</guid><description>Source: Angloinfo&amp;rsquo;s Hong Kong portal.
Angloinfo, a global network for expats, has partnered with Nexus to establish Angloinfo Asia, a joint venture. Their first project is the Angloinfo.com/hongkong website, which has been launched gradually and is expected to be fully operational by August 2016.
The joint venture aims to introduce more localized versions of Angloinfo throughout Asia and China in the coming months, catering to the growing number of expats in these regions.</description></item><item><title>Viu introduces exclusive Korean content: Song Ji Hyo's Beauty Views</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 16:44:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-introduces-exclusive-korean-content-song-ji-hyo-s-beauty-views/</guid><description>Song Ji Hyo’s Beauty Views is a partnership between Viu and the famous Korean actress from the variety show Running Man.
Viu, a pan-Asian streaming platform owned by PCCW Media, has made investments in Viu Originals to boost user engagement. Viu Originals features Korean, Chinese, Indian, and Southeast Asian content for viewers across Asia.
Given the significant popularity of Korean content in the region, Viu Originals aims to increase user engagement by offering captivating and locally relevant original programs.</description></item><item><title>Advertisers must take into account a world with multiple screens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 01:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advertisers-must-take-into-account-a-world-with-multiple-screens/</guid><description>A new study by global research firm TNS, titled &amp;ldquo;Connected Life,&amp;rdquo; reveals that television viewers are increasingly seeking out additional content while watching TV, leading to a surge in online content consumption and &amp;ldquo;screen-stacking.&amp;rdquo; This trend has significant ramifications for businesses aiming to optimize their advertising strategies.
TNS discovered that nearly half of evening TV viewers (48%) engage in other digital activities simultaneously, such as using social media, checking emails, or online shopping.</description></item><item><title>The video-on-demand service HOOQ has been launched in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 06:52:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-video-on-demand-service-hooq-has-been-launched-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: HOOQ. Bithos.
HOOQ, a leading premium video-on-demand service targeting the Asian market, has officially launched in Singapore. This expansion follows successful launches in the Philippines, Thailand, India, and Indonesia, bringing their reach to a potential audience exceeding 1.6 billion people.
Established in Singapore in 2015, HOOQ is a joint venture between Singtel, Sony Pictures Television, and Warner Brothers. This partnership represents a significant collaboration between major media companies to revolutionize entertainment consumption in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Newsstand service is launched by Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/newsstand-service-is-launched-by-singtel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 17:51:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/newsstand-service-is-launched-by-singtel/</guid><description>Singtel has introduced Singtel Newsstand, a service providing discounted digital subscriptions to major international and local newspapers and magazines. Subscribers can save up to 20% off standard rates.
Singtel postpaid mobile subscribers can access global news, business, and lifestyle content, including podcasts and videos, without using their local mobile data.
Initially, Singtel Newsstand will feature The Straits Times and international publications like The Wall Street Journal, TIME Magazine, and Fortune Magazine.</description></item><item><title>The Minute List focuses on dining experiences created by talented chefs and baristas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-minute-list-focuses-on-dining-experiences-created-by-talented-chefs-and-baristas/</guid><description>Hurrah! Productions, a TV and digital content agency based in Asia, has introduced The Minute List, a first-of-its-kind video-driven guide for bars and restaurants in Singapore.
This online platform features one-minute videos showcasing popular restaurants, bars, and cafes in the city. It allows users to make direct reservations at these establishments. Featured venues are nominated by industry professionals, such as chefs, bartenders, and baristas. Each nominated venue is presented through a video interview with the head chef, bartender, or barista.</description></item><item><title>AdAsia Holdings introduces new video production services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adasia-holdings-introduces-new-video-production-services/</guid><description>Source: AdAsia website. Drones can give bird&amp;rsquo;s eye views of scenes.
AdAsia Holdings, an advertising company, has introduced AdAsia Video Production, a new service within its AdAsia Digital Platform that caters to video and animation production needs.
Clients can utilize this service for a range of video formats, from traditional productions to drone footage, 360-degree videos, and animations. Video quality options span from 140p to 2,160p. The produced materials can be featured on the AdAsia Video Network as well as other distribution channels.</description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations.</description></item><item><title>Viu, a service provided by Vuclip, delivers an average of 20 videos per month to viewers in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:44:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viu-a-service-provided-by-vuclip-delivers-an-average-of-20-videos-per-month-to-viewers-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Vuclip, a PCCW Media company, has released key engagement data for its OTT service, Viu, based on an analysis of app and desktop viewership.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEiOh1EZVWoEhfM9h_KB5E2oDQtVX9NIYnObrOM6oWpK6xB_fWBVmqMwQv5MQtoq5jTe338bKg_10JMMP4wDeSWDCbwHwC8jKXx1VMXkYHCYTrGVSsm8QO-dG0eKaUelNE4fQSA8esO5InKk/s1600/image.png)
Source: Viu Malaysia website.
In the two months since its launch in Malaysia, Viu has seen average user engagement of 20 videos per month. Peak viewing times are after work hours, with Wednesday to Sunday being the most popular days.
Korean dramas, Bollywood films, and Malaysian TV series rank among the top ten most-watched content, highlighting the strong demand for Asian entertainment.</description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is providing complimentary content and data to commemorate Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-providing-complimentary-content-and-data-to-commemorate-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 51st birthday on August 9th, Singtel is offering customers complimentary mobile data, alongside free access to Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO.
Postpaid mobile users will enjoy free data from 12:01 am to 11:59 pm on August 9th, allowing them to connect with family and friends on social media, stream music, and watch videos.
From August 5th to 9th, Singtel TV subscribers will have free access to over 140 channels, including popular options like Disney Channel, National Geographic Channel HD, FOX Movie Premium HD, KBS World HD, Astro Ria, and Sun TV.</description></item><item><title>HOOQ is launching new original content produced by Globe Studios</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 10:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hooq-is-launching-new-original-content-produced-by-globe-studios/</guid><description>Globe Studios and HOOQ are launching the first episode of their original series, &amp;ldquo;OTJ: The Missing 8,&amp;rdquo; in early 2017. This series promises a cinematic experience that&amp;rsquo;s different from typical television, mirroring the gritty and fast-paced style of the original movie, which premiered at the 2013 Cannes Film Festival. This six-part series, based on Erik Matti&amp;rsquo;s award-winning film &amp;ldquo;OTJ&amp;rdquo; (or &amp;ldquo;On The Job&amp;rdquo;), is the first major production made specifically for an online video service in the region.</description></item></channel></rss>