<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Designer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/designer/</link><description>Recent content in Designer on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/designer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Four fashion trends from New York Fashion Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</guid><description>Milanoo.com, an online retailer for apparel and other goods, has recently highlighted the major trends observed during February&amp;rsquo;s New York Fashion Week.
Source: Milanoo website.
One trend was wrapped skirts that sit above the knee. This is a departure from the more revealing styles seen in past fashion events, which Milanoo refers to as &amp;ldquo;the consistent sexy style.&amp;rdquo; The company observed, &amp;ldquo;Skirts have been very popular these years. But things are changing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>