<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Luxury on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/luxury/</link><description>Recent content in Luxury on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/luxury/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates introduces new premium offerings in First and Business Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced new luxury products for its First and Business Class passengers, partnering with brands like BYREDO, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and Bulgari to elevate the travel experience.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgd9y3iVi6anaC1N4Cso7QmgPJovqGEwEKcXCffrreFoqNcy3Bnr-B79U45k6PqBzF2gV2uzc94przcIphwRp2ecePtOYdspt9-PjYc3KQTh976kDvFOItJfkbCCO02xL93YGyDNrANYHYE/s1600/Emirates+byredo+wellness.jpg)
Source: Emirates. The BYREDO for Emirates Wellness kit.
First Class passengers in Emirates&amp;rsquo; private suites will receive a specially designed BYREDO travel wellness kit. This hypoallergenic skincare line, featuring chamomile, was created specifically for Emirates and introduced initially on the airline&amp;rsquo;s new Boeing 777 suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dawn Black Badge provides luxurious open-top driving in a striking black color</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</guid><description>Source: Rolls-Royce Motor Cars. The Rolls-Royce Dawn Black Badge.
Rolls-Royce Motor Cars has introduced the Dawn Black Badge, a new addition to their lineup.
This model joins the Wraith Black Badge and Ghost Black Badge, offering a luxurious and bold take on open-top driving with a darker and more sensual aesthetic. The Dawn Black Badge was revealed in a strikingly deep black shade, achieved through a meticulous painting and polishing process that is the most extensive ever employed by Rolls-Royce for a solid paint color...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dawn-black-badge-provides-luxurious-open-top-driving-in-a-striking-black-color/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Wanda Vista brand expands globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</guid><description>Qian Jin, the head of the upscale hotel group Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, has revealed the global growth plan for their Wanda Vista brand.
Wanda Vista represents the top tier of luxury within Wanda Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, designed specifically for guests who appreciate art and culture. Situated in major international cities and drawing inspiration from Eastern aesthetics, the brand focuses on providing personalized service catered to each guest&amp;rsquo;s individual requirements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-wanda-vista-brand-expands-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi First Class Lounge &amp; Spa has been opened by Etihad Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has opened a new flagship First Class Lounge &amp;amp; Spa in Terminal 3 of Abu Dhabi International Airport. This space highlights the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to offering exceptional and desirable hospitality.
Inspired by top-tier hotels, private clubs, and fine dining establishments, the lounge provides an exclusive environment. It features unmatched design, style, comfort, world-class dining, and personalized beauty and relaxation services.
The lounge offers 16 distinct zones for guests to unwind, recharge, and enjoy entertainment in complete luxury before their flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AccorHotels establishes a high-end presence in the Maldives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>AccorHotels is entering the Maldives market with its first luxury resort there, the Dhevanafushi Maldives Luxury Resort. Located on the private island of Meradhoo, the resort will undergo improvements in late 2018 and subsequently become part of the prestigious Raffles brand.
Currently, the resort offers 21 island villas and 16 ocean villas, all with private pools. Guests can enjoy three restaurants and a variety of amenities and activities for relaxation and rejuvenation, such as a luxurious spa, an overwater fitness center, yoga classes, watersports, and private dining options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-establishes-a-high-end-presence-in-the-maldives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JeweLuxe Singapore introduces a unique luxury retail concept unlike any other</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 22:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</guid><description>JeweLuxe Singapore, a curated showcase featuring design, craft, artistry, and innovation from around the world, will launch in Singapore this October at TENT@Ngee Ann City along Orchard Road.
The exhibition, open to the public from October 6 to 15, 2017, will showcase items for collectors, connoisseurs, and enthusiasts across various luxury lifestyle segments, including jewelry, timepieces, vintage items, eyewear, fashion, art, and living.
Supported by the Singapore Tourism Board’s Kickstart Fund, this first-of-its-kind exhibition combines offline and online concepts, featuring aspects of a retail exhibition and an e-commerce marketplace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jeweluxe-singapore-introduces-a-unique-luxury-retail-concept-unlike-any-other/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fragrance Du Bois opens a temporary store at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Fragrance Du Bois.
Fragrance Du Bois has opened a temporary boutique at TANGS, a major department store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road shopping area, until September 4, 2015. This marks their second appearance at TANGS this year. The pop-up offers customers a direct encounter with niche perfumery and showcases Fragrance Du Bois&amp;rsquo; fragrances, all made with 100% pure, natural oud.
Nicola Parker, Brand Director of Fragrance Du Bois, noted a rising interest in niche perfumery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Anantara Angkor Resort is now open again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</guid><description>Source: Anantara Angkor Resort website. View of the exterior.
The luxurious Anantara Angkor Resort has reopened in Siem Reap, offering an all-suite boutique experience close to the wonders of the ancient Khmer Empire.
Just a short drive from the city center, the 5-star resort provides easy access to vibrant markets, riverside attractions, and the charming French colonial quarter. The UNESCO World Heritage Site of Angkor Archaeological Park is also conveniently located a mere 10 minutes away...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-anantara-angkor-resort-is-now-open-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DAMAC introduces Maison Cour Jardin in the heart of downtown Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 21:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</guid><description>At the end of December 2014, DAMAC Properties, a high-end real estate developer, launched its third luxury serviced apartment complex in Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Burj Area. Located just a short distance from popular attractions like the Dubai Mall and Dubai Fountain, DAMAC Maison Cour Jardin joins the company&amp;rsquo;s growing portfolio, which includes DAMAC Maison Dubai Mall Street and DAMAC Maison Canal Views.
Source: DAMAC Properties.
“DAMAC Properties is expanding its hospitality offerings, both in terms of scale and quality, to cater to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s visitors,” stated Niall McLoughlin, Senior Vice President of DAMAC Properties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/damac-introduces-maison-cour-jardin-in-the-heart-of-downtown-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australians share their thoughts with Kleenex about cleanliness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-share-their-thoughts-with-kleenex-about-cleanliness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 10:25:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-share-their-thoughts-with-kleenex-about-cleanliness/</guid><description>Source: Kleenex.
Kimberly-Clark&amp;rsquo;s toilet tissue brand, Kleenex, has released findings about Australian attitudes towards cleanliness alongside their new Kleenex Luxury Collection.
Nearly one-third of Australians (32%) believe they could be cleaner.
Over 80% (84%) would avoid a first date if they didn&amp;rsquo;t feel clean.
Feeling clean significantly impacts emotions: Australians associate cleanliness with feeling refreshed (84%) and more confident (48%).
When compared to topics like sex, religion, politics, and finances, half of those surveyed found &amp;ldquo;cleaning your intimate area&amp;rdquo; the most difficult to discuss...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-share-their-thoughts-with-kleenex-about-cleanliness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-share-their-thoughts-with-kleenex-about-cleanliness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the behavior of luxury travelers from China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</guid><description>A recent study on Chinese luxury travelers, conducted by Marriott International and the Hurun Research Institute, reveals evolving travel preferences among young, affluent Chinese travelers aged 18 to 36. These travelers seek personalized experiences, value-added services throughout their journey, and seamless integration of technology.
The study indicates a preference for digital platforms, with WeChat emerging as the primary source for travel information, followed by official accounts, recommendations from friends, and travel professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple has released new Apple Watch options, including the addition of the Hermès collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The Apple Watch.
Apple has launched new Apple Watch cases and bands, updated its watch operating system, and introduced new gold and rose gold aluminum models for the Apple Watch Sport.
Available as a free update on September 16, the watchOS 2 operating system delivers new features and native third-party apps to Apple Watches. With watchOS 2, apps run faster. Users will also find new watch faces, third-party app information viewable on the watch face, and a &amp;ldquo;Time Travel&amp;rdquo; feature that provides chronological context...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-released-new-apple-watch-options-including-the-addition-of-the-herm-s-collection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Purify and detoxify on weekends in July and August at REVĪVŌ in Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 22:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</guid><description>Source: REVĪVŌ. Throughout July and August, cleansing and detox retreats are offered every weekend.
The luxurious REVĪVŌ wellness resort in Bali, Indonesia, has introduced weekend-long cleansing and detox retreats for July and August.
Guests can choose to participate for one or two days. Kicking off at 10:00 am each Saturday, the program begins with a cold-pressed juice, followed by yoga, Pilates, or meditation. Afterward, attendees enjoy kombucha (a fermented tea beverage) and a detox lunch at the NŪTRIŌ restaurant...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purify-and-detoxify-on-weekends-in-july-and-august-at-rev-v-in-bali/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aditus is a platform that links high-end retailers with individuals who own cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Aditus is a platform designed to connect wealthy individuals who hold significant Bitcoin and other cryptocurrency assets (crypto-affluents) with luxury goods and service providers.
The company identifies a gap in the market, noting that while few luxury businesses currently accept cryptocurrency, crypto-affluents are eager to use these digital assets for their purchases. Additionally, Aditus recognizes the importance of data privacy to crypto-users, which contrasts with the need for customer data in luxury marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aditus-is-a-platform-that-links-high-end-retailers-with-individuals-who-own-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports a decrease in luxury demand in China and an increase in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</guid><description>Euromonitor International, a market research firm, predicts the global luxury goods industry will experience a 19% growth, reaching $405 billion by 2019.
Fflur Roberts, the Head of Luxury Goods Research at Euromonitor, pointed out China&amp;rsquo;s significant luxury market growth of $9.6 billion over the past five years. She noted that this growth, while impressive, slowed at the end of 2013, prompting luxury brands to reassess their strategies in China and other emerging markets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-a-decrease-in-luxury-demand-in-china-and-an-increase-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Four Seasons Private Jet offers a luxurious flying experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</guid><description>Source: Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts.
Luxury hospitality company Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts has launched the Four Seasons Private Jet, signifying a major shift in luxury travel. This offering highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding the evolving desires of modern luxury travelers.
Every aspect of the private jet journey, both in flight and on the ground, has been redesigned through the Four Seasons perspective to provide a fully immersive experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury handbags by Jennifer Mak are available for purchase at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Jennifer Mak&amp;rsquo;s namesake luxury handbag brand is available on the designer floor of Singapore’s Tangs flagship department store in Orchard Road for a limited time, ending February 28, 2015. The brand uses premium materials like python, ostrich, lizard, stingray, and crocodile skin, creating handbags known for their classic lines, elegance, and one-of-a-kind appeal.
Source: Jennifer Mak. Part of the collection on the second floor at Tang&amp;rsquo;s.
&amp;ldquo;The Jennifer Mak woman doesn&amp;rsquo;t seek attention, but she undoubtedly commands it,&amp;rdquo; says Jennifer Mak, the brand&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First and business class customers on Emirates can now enjoy a new Japanese menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 01:36:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. A sample dish from the new Japanese menu.
Emirates now offers a specialized Japanese menu to its first and business class passengers traveling between Dubai and Haneda, Narita, and Kansai airports in Japan. The airline&amp;rsquo;s Dubai catering team partnered with a Japanese culinary provider to develop the dishes using the highest quality ingredients.
In addition to their international menu, first-class passengers can enjoy traditional kaiseki, a multi-course Japanese meal, while those in business class have the option of a bento box...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor has moved its luxury and upscale team to Singapore in order to concentrate on the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Accor has shifted its Global Luxury and Upscale marketing hub from Paris to Singapore, demonstrating the Asia Pacific region&amp;rsquo;s increasing significance in these markets. The company stated that Asian consumers now represent nearly half of all luxury purchases worldwide. This shift implies that MICE organizers may need to elevate their events in this region to meet the expectations of attendees from the area.
“Asian travelers are very particular, and the hotel standards in this region are very high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-has-moved-its-luxury-and-upscale-team-to-singapore-in-order-to-concentrate-on-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lexus has launched the new NX luxury crossover, accompanied by video advertisements</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 01:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</guid><description>Source: Lexus. The Lexus NX.
Lexus has launched the NX, a luxury crossover. The 2015 NX marketing campaign highlights how the vehicle surpasses typical SUVs to provide urban drivers with a stylish option that suits their dynamic lifestyles.
“This is Lexus&amp;rsquo; first venture into the entry luxury crossover market. The NX is a dynamic vehicle that combines high-end design with practicality,” said Brian Smith, Lexus&amp;rsquo; VP of marketing. “This campaign showcases the fun driving experience and adventurous spirit of this vehicle, which boasts a bold, angular design and a powerful turbocharged engine...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexus-has-launched-the-new-nx-luxury-crossover-accompanied-by-video-advertisements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indulge in a luxurious 20 Carat Gold Escape with JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay and Maserati</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 14:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</guid><description>Source: JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay.
The lobby lounge.
Upon arrival at the sports university-themed JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, guests will be greeted with a luxurious Maserati transfer*. Building on the success of the resort&amp;rsquo;s previous collaboration showcasing DMC&amp;rsquo;s SS2017 womenswear collection, this partnership with Maserati aims to captivate those passionate about sports and automobiles.
Ty Collins, General Manager at JW Marriott Phu Quoc Emerald Bay, states, &amp;ldquo;This collaboration amplifies the resort&amp;rsquo;s commitment to offering design-focused experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-a-luxurious-20-carat-gold-escape-with-jw-marriott-phu-quoc-emerald-bay-and-maserati/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Subscribe to Grabz for exclusive insider privileges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</guid><description>Source: Grabz website.
Grabz is a subscription service that provides its members with exclusive benefits and special offers. Using location-based alerts and a wide range of affiliated businesses, the app connects its subscribers with exclusive deals and privileges in their city.
For a monthly fee of S$15.98, premium members enjoy invitations to events and promotions such as discounted business class airfare and exclusive access to limited-edition luxury watches.
Premium members also get access to the Grabz Concierge, a personalized booking service that assists members with securing reservations at clubs and getting on guest lists for exclusive parties in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/subscribe-to-grabz-for-exclusive-insider-privileges/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Presidential Villa is now available at Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:01:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort.
The Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain resort is located near Dujiangyan, a UNESCO World Heritage &amp;amp; Natural Cultural site known as the home of giant pandas.
Inspired by the region&amp;rsquo;s history as the birthplace of Taoism, Six Senses Qing Cheng Mountain introduces a new Presidential Villa. This villa embodies Taoist principles of living in harmony with nature, offering a space for reconnection and self-discovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-presidential-villa-is-now-available-at-six-senses-qing-cheng-mountain/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>