<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Inflight on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/inflight/</link><description>Recent content in Inflight on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/inflight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches.</description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes.</description></item></channel></rss>