<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Disney on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disney/</link><description>Recent content in Disney on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/disney/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reserve a magical Disney experience aboard the Disney Adventure through Traveloka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</guid><description>Starting in the fourth quarter of 2024, travelers can book voyages with Disney Cruise Lines departing from Singapore through the Traveloka app, according to an announcement from the Southeast Asian travel platform. This addition to Traveloka&amp;rsquo;s offerings reinforces the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to showcasing the diverse experiences and attractions available in Singapore.
Launching in late 2025, the Disney Adventure will call Singapore its home port. The ship boasts seven themed areas with Disney-themed dining and exciting onboard activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reserve-a-magical-disney-experience-aboard-the-disney-adventure-through-traveloka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Establish a system of experiences that fosters success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/</guid><description>To stand out, be creative and build an engaging experience around your product or service that resonates with your target audience, attracting customers organically. This advice comes from Big Bird Creative Company (BBCC), a Taiwanese integrated media company renowned for its children&amp;rsquo;s content services, including education consulting, production and distribution, and brand development, both in Taiwan and internationally.
Cathy Han, President of BBCC, shared several success stories during the Media Summit at the Asian Festival of Children&amp;rsquo;s Content 2014 in Singapore this past June...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/establish-a-system-of-experiences-that-fosters-success/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>