<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Influential Brands on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/influential-brands/</link><description>Recent content in Influential Brands on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:45:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/influential-brands/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brand Alliance recognizes Singaporean brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-recognizes-singaporean-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 00:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-recognizes-singaporean-brands/</guid><description>Influential Brands, a Brand Alliance program, held a private ceremony earlier today to honor Singapore&amp;rsquo;s top brands.
The 2014 Influential Brands Award recipients were joined by Guest of Honor Seah Kian Peng (fifth from left) and Brand Alliance Group Director Jorge Rodriguez (first from right).
“Singaporean brands have the potential to make a global impact,&amp;quot; remarked Seah Kian Peng, the event&amp;rsquo;s guest of honor, Deputy Speaker of Parliament, and Member of Parliament for Marine Parade GRC.</description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development.</description></item><item><title>Heroes from Asian brands share their brand journey stories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</guid><description>Influential Brands, a program organized by Brand Alliance, held its 2014 conference in Singapore on November 7th. The event, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes,&amp;rdquo; recognized the success of leading brands in the region. Several individuals representing these successful brands participated in a panel discussion, sharing their insights and experiences.
The panel included (from left) moderator Amy Lim, Founder of Brand Alliance; Esther Tang-Loo, Executive Director of Focus Network Agencies; Han Keen Juan, Executive Chairman of Old Chang Kee Group; Debra Soon, Managing Director of Channel NewsAsia; Woon Tai Ho, Director for Media and Marketing at Singapore’s National Art Gallery; Allen Law, Group Chief Executive of Park Hotel Group; and Dr.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's Influential Brands are identified by Gen X</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 21:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-influential-brands-are-identified-by-gen-x/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Leading Brands Chosen by Generation X
A consumer-driven award program spearheaded by Brand Alliance has identified the top Influential Brands in Singapore, as determined by the upwardly mobile Generation X (Gen X) demographic.
Source: Brand Alliance. Brand Alliance presented the 2013 Influential Brands awards in November 2013. The 2014 Influential Brands conference is scheduled for November 10, 2014.
The survey highlighted over 100 prominent brands resonating with consumers in Singapore.</description></item></channel></rss>