<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DIA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dia/</link><description>Recent content in DIA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>DIA and VPN For Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dia-and-vpn-for-europe/</guid><description>Level 3 Communications, a major internet services provider with a global reach, is expanding its Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) and Virtual Private Network (VPN) services into European markets, including France, Germany, and the United Kingdom. The company recognizes the increasing importance of international connectivity for business success in a globalized marketplace.
While large corporations often manage their own private networks, many businesses need reliable internet access without the high investment. These businesses require high-quality internet for e-commerce, customer communication, and connecting geographically dispersed locations.</description></item><item><title>The Cloud Needs Low Latency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:27:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cloud-needs-low-latency/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Economic Appeal of Cloud Computing Opting for cloud services over traditional data centers seems incredibly cost-effective. Instead of large loans and capital investments in servers and infrastructure, businesses can subscribe to a cloud service provider and pay only for the resources they consume. This eliminates the need to predict future business demands and allows for flexibility in scaling resources on-demand.
The Allure of Simplicity The solution appears straightforward: forgo establishing a new data center or dismantle your existing one, and lease the necessary resources from a cloud provider.</description></item><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions.</description></item><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years.</description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption.</description></item><item><title>Symmetrical Internet Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 06:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/symmetrical-internet-providers/</guid><description>The majority of internet users consume content rather than create it. While content has shifted from primarily text to images and video, broadband internet access remains asymmetrical, favoring downloads over uploads.
Why is this the case? Consider how you browse the internet: you click or type to select content, which uses minimal bandwidth. However, receiving the content, like web pages with text, images, and videos, requires significant bandwidth for timely delivery.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>All My Access Is In Texas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-my-access-is-in-texas/</guid><description>For businesses operating in Texas, Alpheus Communications offers a regional network connecting major Texan cities, along with colocation data centers. This provides enhanced security, reliability, and cost-effective connectivity with a localized approach.
Alpheus&amp;rsquo;s fiber optic network provides high bandwidth and low latency connections between various Texan cities, including Dallas, Houston, San Antonio, and more. Their long-haul connections extend throughout North America with bandwidth options ranging from DS-1 (1.5 Mbps) to OC-192 (10 Gbps).</description></item><item><title>Zayo Lights Denver With Expanded Fiber Optic Network Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:55:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zayo-lights-denver-with-expanded-fiber-optic-network-services/</guid><description>Zayo Group, a prominent fiber optic bandwidth infrastructure provider, is expanding its existing metro fiber network coverage in Denver and Colorado Springs. The expansion project will add 521 miles of fiber along the Colorado Front Range, encompassing cities like Boulder, Longmont, Loveland, Greeley, and Fort Collins. This increase brings Zayo&amp;rsquo;s total fiber optic network in the Denver area to 900 route miles, supporting industries such as research, technology, education, and energy.</description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Broadband Business Internet Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:04:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-business-internet-service-options/</guid><description>Almost every business today relies on the internet or will soon. Even small, independent businesses still using old-fashioned credit card machines will eventually adopt electronic verification, email, and basic websites. Meanwhile, businesses already comfortable online are looking to upgrade their bandwidth to handle cloud-based services. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the different broadband options available.
Business internet options can be broadly categorized into two types: shared and dedicated connections. Similar to residential services, shared connections divide bandwidth among multiple users, leading to lower costs.</description></item><item><title>T1 Line Cost At A New Low</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:23:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-cost-at-a-new-low/</guid><description>For many companies, T1 lines have become a standard over time. Larger corporations adopted them early on for dedicated internet access, while smaller businesses often turned to T1 lines after encountering limitations with shared bandwidth services like DSL and Cable. The only drawback to T1 lines was their cost—or was it?
](http://www.t1t3today.com/)
If you associate T1 lines with exorbitant prices, your perception might be outdated. Less than ten years ago, a monthly fee of $1,000 for a standard T1 line wasn&amp;rsquo;t unusual.</description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance.</description></item><item><title>Private IP Networks vs The Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 09:45:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-ip-networks-vs-the-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing between private and public business connectivity services, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to understand the differences and select the right solution.
Private lines, known for their reliability, performance, and high cost, have been essential for businesses. In contrast, the internet has become widely accessible and affordable, offering broadband connectivity from various locations. Businesses often need an internet presence to connect with customers and suppliers.
This raises the question of whether using the internet for all business needs is feasible.</description></item><item><title>What Leased Line Service Providers Offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:14:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-leased-line-service-providers-offer/</guid><description>Many businesses rely on leased line providers for their telecommunication needs, including phone, internet, and point-to-point connections. However, the telecommunications landscape has evolved significantly, offering cost savings and new services.
T-carrier, particularly T1 lines, remains a popular choice. T1 lines, initially designed for multiple phone calls, can be used for point-to-point connections with speeds up to 1.5 Mbps, which can be combined for higher bandwidth. T1 access lines connect to larger networks like MPLS, replacing Frame Relay, and provide flexible bandwidth for various data types.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 04:11:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet-access/</guid><description>There are two main types of broadband internet: shared and dedicated. While you might be familiar with terms like wireless, landline, satellite, or fiber optic, these refer to delivery methods that impact price and availability. Your primary choice lies in deciding between shared and dedicated internet access.
What sets them apart? The names are quite descriptive. Shared internet access resembles a buffet where you might eye a large roast, hoping for a full plate.</description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations.</description></item></channel></rss>