<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Melbourne on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/melbourne/</link><description>Recent content in Melbourne on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/melbourne/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside.</description></item><item><title>New website offers discounted gym classes in Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</guid><description>Source:
FILLMYCLASS.
Similar to discounts for last-minute travel bookings, you can find more affordable gym classes at the last minute too.
A new website called FILLMYCLASS has launched in Melbourne, Australia. This website connects fitness enthusiasts with open spots in fitness classes at gyms and studios nearby.
FILLMYCLASS founder Daniel Waide states, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about flexibility. The aim is to encourage more people to be active. Offering the ability to select classes that fit their schedule at any gym or studio increases the likelihood of people becoming and staying active.</description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems.</description></item><item><title>Etihad plans to increase the number of flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, will begin offering daily A380 flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne starting June 1, 2016. This will affect flight numbers EY460/461, one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily trips between the cities. This change replaces one of the three-class Boeing 777-300ER aircraft currently used. Passengers can now enjoy The Residence by Etihad, a luxurious private three-room suite, and other cutting-edge products and services across all cabins.</description></item></channel></rss>