<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Robot on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/robot/</link><description>Recent content in Robot on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/robot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Drobo Mr. Storage Roboto</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 22:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</guid><description>Hard drive space disappears faster than you can imagine, especially with large digital media files like photos and videos. Even large hard drives fill up quickly.
While upgrading or adding hard drives seems like a solution, it creates new problems like managing backups and worrying about data loss from hard drive failures. These tasks can be time-consuming, especially for professionals working with large files. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like you need a personal assistant to manage it all...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/drobo-mr-storage-roboto/</a></p></description></item><item><title>"Credit Suisse identifies three major trends for 2018"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Cavalli.
The sixth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference 2018, held in Singapore, focused on three significant trends: technology designed to benefit humanity, including AI and robotics; a future shaped by Millennials; and the expanding silver economy.
Benjamin Cavalli, Head of Private Banking Southeast Asia and Singapore CEO of Credit Suisse, explained in his opening remarks that these megatrends represent investment themes based on Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s expert insights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An improved chair designed to alleviate back discomfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</guid><description>Simon Hong, a neuroscientist, is seeking funding for his invention, the Chairbot. This robotic chair aims to eliminate back pain by suggesting new positions to the user based on their current posture.
Source: Kickstarter page
The Chairbot&amp;rsquo;s unique design features a split seat that encourages users to alternate between sitting and standing, reducing strain on the spine. Hong explains on the Kickstarter page that this constant shifting prevents the spinal trauma associated with maintaining a single posture for long periods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Singapore is backing F&amp;B and food manufacturers with innovative digital projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</guid><description>RESTAURANT 3.0: Embracing Technology in the Food Industry Enterprise Singapore showcased new digital solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) 2018. These solutions aim to help Singaporean food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and food manufacturing companies expand internationally and enhance their operational efficiency.
The showcased digital initiatives include a B2B online platform for food manufacturers and the RESTAURANT 3.0 exhibition for F&amp;amp;B businesses.
Enterprise Singapore, in collaboration with the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF), launched the &amp;ldquo;SMF SMART App&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Pavilion during FHA...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Robots have been introduced to the teams at Hotel Jen in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</guid><description>Hotel Jen is pioneering the use of Savioke&amp;rsquo;s Relay robots in Asian hotels. The robots, Jeno and Jena, will be stationed at Hotel Jen Orchardgateway and Tanglin Singapore, respectively. They will handle deliveries of amenities and local food selections from the in-room dining menu.
Cetin Sekercioglu, Executive VP of Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts, stated that Hotel Jen prioritizes technology that can improve efficiency and guest experiences. He believes that the robots will be valuable additions to the team and align with Hotel Jen&amp;rsquo;s playful and surprising brand identity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robots-have-been-introduced-to-the-teams-at-hotel-jen-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>