<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Science on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/science/</link><description>Recent content in Science on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City introduces new meeting and event options in the High Tech Development District</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doubletree-by-hilton-guangzhou-science-city-introduces-new-meeting-and-event-options-in-the-high-tech-development-district/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has expanded its presence in China with the opening of DoubleTree by Hilton Guangzhou - Science City. This new 314-room hotel joins 20 other DoubleTree by Hilton properties in the country, further strengthening Hilton Worldwide&amp;rsquo;s presence in Guangzhou, where the company manages three hotels under the Hilton Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts and DoubleTree by Hilton brands.
Source: Hilton Worldwide.
Bruce McKenzie, Senior VP of operations, Greater China &amp;amp; Mongolia, Hilton Worldwide, highlights the strategic importance of Science City, Guangzhou, as a thriving business hub.</description></item><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers.</description></item><item><title>Learn about data science quickly with CEG Digital's online course</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/learn-about-data-science-quickly-with-ceg-digital-s-online-course/</guid><description>CEG Digital, the flexible learning branch of global education provider Cambridge Education Group (CEG), has teamed up with the Web Science Institute at the University of Southampton (WSI), a top-100 university, to offer short online courses.
Dr. Elena Simperl, WSI Associate Professor and Scientific Director of the European Data Science Academy, emphasized the importance of data science skills, stating, &amp;ldquo;Data science is crucial for our economy. Our new series of short professional courses complement our postgraduate degrees and target decision-makers, business analysts, IT developers, and others interested in cutting-edge data science technologies and applications in fields like digital marketing, finance, and healthcare.</description></item><item><title>LAVISH is bringing a new standard of high-end catering to Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 16:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lavish-is-bringing-a-new-standard-of-high-end-catering-to-singapore/</guid><description>The renowned catering company, LAVISH, celebrated its 18th anniversary with a gala in late January. The event served as a platform for the brand&amp;rsquo;s revitalization and showcased their forward-thinking approach to catering, blending culinary arts with technology and science. LAVISH is well-regarded for its expertise in catering a variety of events, from large-scale conferences and corporate gatherings to intimate private dinners and celebratory functions.
Source: LAVISH. The gala dinner was held</description></item></channel></rss>