<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>First on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/first/</link><description>Recent content in First on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/first/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates introduces new premium offerings in First and Business Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced new luxury products for its First and Business Class passengers, partnering with brands like BYREDO, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and Bulgari to elevate the travel experience.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgd9y3iVi6anaC1N4Cso7QmgPJovqGEwEKcXCffrreFoqNcy3Bnr-B79U45k6PqBzF2gV2uzc94przcIphwRp2ecePtOYdspt9-PjYc3KQTh976kDvFOItJfkbCCO02xL93YGyDNrANYHYE/s1600/Emirates+byredo+wellness.jpg)
Source: Emirates. The BYREDO for Emirates Wellness kit.
First Class passengers in Emirates&amp;rsquo; private suites will receive a specially designed BYREDO travel wellness kit. This hypoallergenic skincare line, featuring chamomile, was created specifically for Emirates and introduced initially on the airline&amp;rsquo;s new Boeing 777 suites.</description></item><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel.</description></item><item><title>Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway will be celebrating their first birthday on March 31st</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 09:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotel-jen-tanglin-and-hotel-jen-orchardgateway-will-be-celebrating-their-first-birthday-on-march-31st/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Jen Orchardgateway website.
Hotel Jen, a new brand from the Shangri-La Group, is turning one year old on March 31, 2016. To mark this milestone, the two Singapore locations, Hotel Jen Tanglin and Hotel Jen Orchardgateway, are joining their sister hotels across nine Asian-Pacific cities for a grand birthday celebration. Each location will host unique events reflecting their city&amp;rsquo;s character, from a Mad Hatter&amp;rsquo;s tea party in Beijing to street art-inspired menus in Brisbane and a pool party in the Maldives.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item></channel></rss>