<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Servers on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/servers/</link><description>Recent content in Servers on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Host Gator Serves The Web On Texas Wind Power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/host-gator-serves-the-web-on-texas-wind-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/host-gator-serves-the-web-on-texas-wind-power/</guid><description>Do you want to support eco-friendly businesses but worry about the cost of web hosting? HostGator offers an affordable and environmentally responsible solution.
Web hosting requires a lot of energy due to the power demands of servers. The more performance required, the more energy is consumed and heat is generated. While energy is essential, our high consumption levels harm the environment. The key is to use clean energy sources to sustain our technological needs while protecting the planet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/host-gator-serves-the-web-on-texas-wind-power/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/host-gator-serves-the-web-on-texas-wind-power/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>