<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Low Latency Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/low-latency-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Low Latency Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/low-latency-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low Latency WAN Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 23:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-wan-options/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly demanding low latency in their WAN connections. But why is latency suddenly so important, and how can you achieve it?
Latency is the time it takes for data packets to travel between two points. While insignificant on local networks, latency can pose major problems on long-distance WAN connections, especially for applications where speed is critical.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that latency and bandwidth are not directly related. You can have slow connections with minimal latency and blazing-fast connections with terrible latency.</description></item><item><title>The Need for Low Latency Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-need-for-low-latency-networks/</guid><description>When discussing network performance, bandwidth is often the primary focus. Higher bandwidth is equated with faster speeds, allowing for quicker file transfers and increased productivity. However, another crucial aspect of network performance, latency, has gained significant attention recently.
Latency refers to the time delay within a network, specifically the time it takes for data packets to travel between nodes. While it might seem related to bandwidth, latency is a distinct characteristic.</description></item><item><title>What Makes High Frequency Trading Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-high-frequency-trading-work/</guid><description>Computerized trading, including high frequency trading, is now the norm in the stock market. As seen on CBS News, algorithms can automatically execute trades when specific conditions are met.
A key challenge of automated trading is ensuring fairness by synchronizing timing for all participants. The New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) addressed this by creating a data center that standardized access time to 65 microseconds for everyone. However, this only applies to trading within the NYSE.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ, Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq-part-2/</guid><description>This document addresses common questions about fiber optic services for businesses, expanding on previous FAQs.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Q: What kinds of services are available through Ethernet fiber?
A: Three standard services cater to businesses, as defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum. Ethernet Private Line (E-Line) offers a direct connection between two business locations or from a location to the internet. Ethernet LAN (E-LAN) creates a network connecting multiple locations. Lastly, Ethernet Tree (E-Tree) is a one-to-many connection often used for content distribution to numerous subscribers.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Low Latency Fiber Network For Orange County</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-fiber-network-for-orange-county/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a rising demand for high-bandwidth, low-latency internet connectivity from businesses, particularly in sectors like finance, automation, cloud computing, and medical imaging. This surge is driving the expansion of fiber optic networks, with a prime example being the ongoing development in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
AboveNet, a prominent fiber optic network provider in the US and Europe, is constructing a major &amp;ldquo;feeder ring&amp;rdquo; in Orange County, California. This ring will connect various business locations, including office buildings, data centers, and carrier hotels, to an existing fiber optic backbone already serving the Irvine and Costa Mesa business districts.</description></item></channel></rss>