<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fixed Wireless on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-wireless/</link><description>Recent content in Fixed Wireless on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fixed-wireless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Maestro Smart Antenna Improves Fixed Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</guid><description>Accel Technologies, a branch of Accel Networks, is launching a groundbreaking product for fixed wireless connections: the Maestro smart antenna system. Maestro aims to make 3G and 4G fixed wireless broadband a more attractive alternative to pricier business connectivity options like T1, MPLS, VSAT, Frame Relay, and point-to-point microwave services.
What makes Maestro so special? Like other smart devices, Maestro utilizes active technology to enhance performance. In this situation, it improves the performance of a typically passive component: the RF antenna...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-maestro-smart-antenna-improves-fixed-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wireless Internet Access For Farms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</guid><description>While living and working on a farm has its perks, getting reliable broadband internet can be a challenge. Conventional options like DSL and Cable might not be feasible due to distance limitations, often leaving farms outside their service areas.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are other solutions for obtaining reasonably priced internet access in rural areas. These alternatives focus on services that overcome distance barriers or eliminate the need for physical cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-internet-access-for-farms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cheaper Business Broadband Abounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 03:39:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</guid><description>Due to budget constraints, many businesses are searching for cost-cutting measures that don&amp;rsquo;t negatively impact operations. Telecom and networking expenses are frequently targeted because they represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s wise to examine these costs closely, as savings can often be found within your business broadband services.
Some managers may believe their telecom costs are fixed and non-negotiable, a perception stemming from contracts signed years ago with the sole provider available at the time - usually the local telephone company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-business-broadband-abounds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless For Rural Retail</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 22:39:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</guid><description>Small businesses outside of cities often struggle to obtain affordable and reliable broadband. While some resort to satellite or T1 lines for internet and point-of-sale systems, others have discovered that 3G wireless offers a secure and cost-effective alternative for credit card processing.
](http://www.sheepfort1.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
We associate 3G with mobile phones and laptops, but a lesser-known application exists. This service combines the widespread availability of 3G signals with powerful multi-carrier equipment and a secure VPN network, making it suitable for business needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-rural-retail/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless for Point of Sale Authorizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</guid><description>Credit card processing is essential for modern businesses, so having a fast and reliable authorization terminal is crucial. While dial-up terminals might have been sufficient in the past, their slow speed can frustrate customers and reflect poorly on your business. Upgrading to a broadband connection is a worthwhile investment.
T1 lines have become more affordable, making them a popular choice for businesses. However, they can still be expensive for smaller companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find Fiber On-Net Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</guid><description>When choosing a new office space, businesses typically prioritize factors like rent, location, and size. However, they often overlook a crucial aspect: internet connectivity. While utilities like water and electricity are standard, reliable fiber optic internet is not guaranteed.
Although bandwidth is becoming increasingly essential, it&amp;rsquo;s not as universally available as other utilities. Finding an office building with existing fiber optic connections is rare. While many buildings may offer standard telephone lines, these are not suitable for high-speed internet needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-fiber-on-net-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business DSL Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:38:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</guid><description>Small businesses have favored Business DSL due to its accessibility and affordability. While effective for some, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t suit all businesses, with some completely unable to access it. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of Business DSL and alternative options for companies dissatisfied with its performance or availability.
](http://www.t1rex.com/)
Similar to residential DSL, Business DSL uses existing telephone wiring, usually a single pair, owned by the telephone company. This means your telephone company is the sole provider, though they may lease lines to other companies offering similar services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-dsl-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Bandwidth Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</guid><description>DS3 WAN connections are a popular choice for businesses that need more bandwidth than T1 lines offer but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for a full OC-3 fiber optic SONET service. However, exploring alternative options might be beneficial due to cost or performance considerations.
There are several bandwidth options available today that might be a better fit than your existing DS3 connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some alternatives.
DS3 bridges the gap between copper wireline and fiber optic bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Fiber Lit Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 18:55:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</guid><description>To secure high bandwidth at affordable rates, you need to be in a &amp;ldquo;lit&amp;rdquo; building. This term refers to buildings equipped with active fiber optic bandwidth services, utilizing laser light to transmit data through fiber optic strands.
If your building is &amp;ldquo;lit,&amp;rdquo; obtaining fiber optic bandwidth is typically straightforward, though construction costs might apply if cabling to your space is absent. However, a bigger challenge arises if your building lacks fiber optic connectivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-fiber-lit-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Lit Towers Improving Rural Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 16:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</guid><description>Living outside the city limits often means limited internet options. While options like 3G and satellite exist, they come with slow speeds and download caps. Businesses might have access to slightly better choices like T1 lines, but high-speed options are generally nonexistent.
Rural areas face a digital disadvantage compared to cities where gigabit and even 10 gigabit ethernet connections are readily available. Fixed wireless and cable options also offer much faster speeds in these areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-lit-towers-improving-rural-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>