<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ecommerce on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecommerce/</link><description>Recent content in Ecommerce on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ecommerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Stress Testing For Your Website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:55:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve successfully launched your website and initiated a marketing campaign. However, what happens when your website crashes during a surge in visitor traffic? This situation is preventable through stress testing. Many companies neglect this step and suffer the consequences, especially during peak seasons like holidays.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let this happen to you. Load testing allows you to assess your website&amp;rsquo;s capacity and make necessary improvements. BrowserMob, a cloud-based service, provides affordable load testing for businesses of all sizes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Try Cloud Website Load Testing Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve established your online presence, but the question remains: how strong is it? Just like the story of the three little pigs, a website needs to be built with strong materials to withstand the elements. While a website might appear impressive when it&amp;rsquo;s not in use, the true test comes with a surge of visitors. Load testing is the only way to determine if your site can handle high traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-cloud-website-load-testing-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tired of Flaky Internet Connections?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:03:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</guid><description>Running a business is challenging when your tools are unreliable. You would think technology would make things easier, but it often has the opposite effect. As processes become more complex and interconnected, they seem to become less dependable. A simple cash transaction can turn into an e-commerce nightmare. Why can&amp;rsquo;t things just work flawlessly all the time?
While expecting perfection might be unrealistic, your business systems should function seamlessly most of the time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tired-of-flaky-internet-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1&amp;1 makes 1.99</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 07:20:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</guid><description>Choosing 1&amp;amp;1 for web hosting is like getting a steal of a deal. They&amp;rsquo;re a leading web hosting company, even internationally recognized, and their starting price is incredibly low at $1.99 per month for the first three months, then $3.99 monthly.
You might think this means low quality, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. This entry-level package is comparable to professional hosting services. Here&amp;rsquo;s what your $1.99 gets you: a free domain name (that you choose!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/1-1-makes-199/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Hosting Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 04:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</guid><description>When you have a website or online store, you&amp;rsquo;re already familiar with web hosting. But did you know there are different types of web hosting? One type you might not know about is managed hosting, which can be more reliable and affordable than trying to handle everything yourself.
In the early days of the internet, businesses often set up their websites by getting server software and using one computer as the web host...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-hosting-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Way to Build an Online Store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 10:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/</guid><description>You possess products or services that have the potential to truly impress your customers. You&amp;rsquo;ve experienced local success and believe you can replicate that online. All you need is a visually appealing and fully functional e-commerce platform.
Perhaps you lack design expertise and worry about creating an unprofessional site that might malfunction, harming your reputation and driving away customers. The complexities of setting up a shopping cart can also seem daunting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-way-to-build-an-online-store/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>