<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Direct Effect on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/direct-effect/</link><description>Recent content in Direct Effect on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/direct-effect/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>Can salvation be found outside of the church? The ECJ makes a decision on religious discrimination in the workplace.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-salvation-be-found-outside-of-the-church-the-ecj-makes-a-decision-on-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>By Dr. Ronan McCrea, Senior Lecturer in Law, University College London
Background
The Court of Justice issued a significant decision concerning the balance between religious organizations&amp;rsquo; autonomy and the right of their employees (or potential employees) to be free from discrimination.
In 2012, Vera Egenberger applied for a temporary position with the Evangelisches Werk für Diakonie und Entwicklung, an organization affiliated with the Evangelische Kirche in Deutschland (a German Protestant church).</description></item><item><title>In what way can the courts enforce Part Two of the Withdrawal Agreement regarding citizens' rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:38:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-what-way-can-the-courts-enforce-part-two-of-the-withdrawal-agreement-regarding-citizens-rights/</guid><description>Ensuring the Enforceability of EU Citizens&amp;rsquo; Rights in the UK Post-Brexit Professor Tamara Hervey, Natalia Miernik and James C Murphy (UG students), University of Sheffield
Acknowledgement is given to the ESRC for its support of Health Governance after Brexit and UK in a Changing Europe.
1. Introduction
Approximately 3.6 million EU citizens and their families reside in the UK. A significant number, estimated to be over 185,000, contribute to the health and social care sector.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice clarifies the vertical direct effect of Directives in cases where Daddy is responsible for paying for your crashed car.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-clarifies-the-vertical-direct-effect-of-directives-in-cases-where-daddy-is-responsible-for-paying-for-your-crashed-car/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 21:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-clarifies-the-vertical-direct-effect-of-directives-in-cases-where-daddy-is-responsible-for-paying-for-your-crashed-car/</guid><description>Albert Sánchez Graells, Reader in Economic Law, University of Bristol*
EU law can be complicated, especially when it comes to Directives. Unlike Regulations, Directives are not automatically binding between private parties. However, individuals can use Directives against the State, creating a need to define what &amp;ldquo;State&amp;rdquo; means in this context, given the variety of public-private relationships across the EU.
EU law addresses this through the concept of &amp;ldquo;emanation of the State,&amp;rdquo; which clarifies which bodies are subject to Directives.</description></item><item><title>Guide for Law Students: Understanding EU Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge*
EU law is a captivating field of study that offers something for everyone, particularly those interested in politics, visionary thinking, and pragmatic solutions. Even if these aren&amp;rsquo;t your primary interests, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to study EU law due to its mandatory nature. However, it&amp;rsquo;s unlike any other legal system you may have encountered, defying categorization and fitting into no single box.
Before diving in, it&amp;rsquo;s helpful to reflect on your existing political perspectives on the EU.</description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws.</description></item></channel></rss>