<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Content Delivery Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Content Delivery Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/content-delivery-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Video Kill The Internet Star?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</guid><description>The considerable growth of online video streaming and downloads has positioned them as the primary bandwidth consumers on the internet today. This begs the question: will the rapid proliferation of video packets lead to internet congestion, similar to traffic jams on physical highways?
Video content follows the same trajectory as previous &amp;ldquo;killer apps&amp;rdquo; such as email, web browsing, instant messaging, blogging, and social networking. These applications all began with a small user base, expanded quickly, and eventually became mainstream.</description></item><item><title>40 Gbps Bandwidth Available For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-gbps-bandwidth-available-for-business/</guid><description>XO Communications has increased business bandwidth options by offering two 40 Gbps network services across its nationwide fiber optic network. Randy Nicklas, XO Communications&amp;rsquo; CTO, highlights the advantages of these new 40 Gbps services:
You can listen to the interview directly on this page:
Clearly, we&amp;rsquo;re entering a new era of high-bandwidth applications for businesses and service providers like cable companies. High-speed financial trading needs the fastest speeds, with even milliseconds of delay impacting outcomes.</description></item><item><title>Amazon's CloudFront Moves In for Content Delivery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</guid><description>Amazon has expanded far beyond bookselling; it&amp;rsquo;s now a major player in network computing. Recognizing the value of their massive infrastructure, Amazon created Amazon Web Services (AWS) to offer cloud computing resources to businesses of all sizes.
AWS includes a range of services, such as Amazon EC2 for computing power, Amazon S3 for storage, and Amazon CloudFront for content delivery. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s global network, with numerous edge locations, makes it well-suited for content delivery.</description></item><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges.</description></item><item><title>Why Content Delivery Networks Need More Capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</guid><description>A significant media shift is underway, marked by a technological revolution since the days of broadcast dominance. Concerns about antenna reception have been replaced by anxieties over 3G and 4G coverage for accessing videos on mobile devices. Cable and satellite TV, which succeeded over-the-air broadcasting, now face competition from the internet as the preferred medium for audio and video content. As over-the-air delivery declines, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are emerging as its replacement.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Network Expansion Underway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-network-expansion-underway/</guid><description>Our society&amp;rsquo;s addiction to bandwidth is evident with the recent launch of a massive dark fiber network project by Allied Fiber. This project will encircle the US with 548 dark fibers and 300 tower sites.
Fiber optic communication is experiencing a resurgence and this time it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. Unlike the failed attempt in the 1990s, the unused fiber optic cables laid then are likely to be utilized soon due to the resurfacing of the telecommunication revolution.</description></item><item><title>Content Delivery Networks Transformed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/content-delivery-networks-transformed/</guid><description>The demand for bandwidth is steadily growing, largely due to the rise of IP video streaming, downloads, and more sophisticated websites with larger graphics and interactive features. To keep up with this demand, networks and websites themselves need to change.
While increasing WAN bandwidth is a given, it&amp;rsquo;s not a complete solution. Despite significant growth in WAN bandwidth, internet traffic congestion persists, leading to the emergence of Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) as a bypass.</description></item></channel></rss>