<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>House of Commons on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/house-of-commons/</link><description>Recent content in House of Commons on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:06:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/house-of-commons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In support of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK House of Commons European Scrutiny Committee recently suggested that the UK should create a law to nullify the application of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights within the UK. This proposal has three major flaws.
Firstly, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually clarify the uncertainty surrounding the Charter&amp;rsquo;s application, as the committee suggests. Instead, it would create more complexity in how human rights are applied in the UK.</description></item><item><title>Dear UK Members of Parliament, We are writing to urge you to prioritize democratic scrutiny of any proposed changes to UK surveillance laws. Thank you.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:53:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dear-uk-members-of-parliament-we-are-writing-to-urge-you-to-prioritize-democratic-scrutiny-of-any-proposed-changes-to-uk-surveillance-laws-thank-you/</guid><description>Steve Peers
I have concerns about the lack of democratic oversight regarding UK law changes that impact privacy rights, especially those connected to EU law. Because of this, I joined others in signing an open letter to MPs. This letter was published in the Guardian and other publications. I want to recognize Andrew Murray and Paul Bernal for leading this effort.
This is the complete letter to all members of the House of Commons:</description></item></channel></rss>