<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Play on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/play/</link><description>Recent content in Play on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/play/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly.</description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts.</description></item></channel></rss>