<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alibaba on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alibaba/</link><description>Recent content in Alibaba on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:15:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/alibaba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ma from Alibaba emphasizes the importance of providing additional support for young entrepreneurs and small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ma-from-alibaba-emphasizes-the-importance-of-providing-additional-support-for-young-entrepreneurs-and-small-businesses/</guid><description>Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s Executive Chairman, Jack Ma, addressed the 34 member states of the Asian Cooperation Dialogue (ACD). He urged them to implement policies and infrastructure that would empower individuals under 30 and businesses with under 30 employees. Ma believes these groups will be the driving force behind future global economic success.
Speaking as both Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Executive Chairman and the UNCTAD Special Adviser on youth entrepreneurship and small business, Ma emphasized the significance of small entities, stating that &amp;ldquo;small is beautiful&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;small is powerful.</description></item><item><title>The fourth group of entrepreneurs successfully complete the eFounders Fellowship program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fourth-group-of-entrepreneurs-successfully-complete-the-efounders-fellowship-program/</guid><description>Thirty-eight entrepreneurs from Asia have successfully finished the fourth eFounders Fellowship program. This joint effort between the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD) and Alibaba Business School equips entrepreneurs with valuable skills and encourages them to share their knowledge.
This initiative stems from a commitment made by Jack Ma, Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s founder and former Executive Chairman, as UNCTAD Special Adviser for Young Entrepreneurs and Small Business. This commitment aims to empower 1,000 entrepreneurs in developing countries over five years, creating leaders for inclusive and sustainable economic development through the digital economy.</description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides.</description></item><item><title>SMU and Alibaba Cloud introduce groundbreaking upskilling program beyond China for the first time</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 17:08:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smu-and-alibaba-cloud-introduce-groundbreaking-upskilling-program-beyond-china-for-the-first-time/</guid><description>Singapore Management University (SMU) and Alibaba Cloud have teamed up to introduce a series of courses designed to enhance the skills of over 1,000 working professionals in Singapore.
This joint initiative, known as the SMU-Alibaba Series, marks Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s first professional continuing education program outside of China. Set to commence in March 2019, the program will be delivered through SMU Academy, the university&amp;rsquo;s professional training division.
With a specific focus on empowering small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs), the Series aims to equip businesses with the necessary competencies to navigate the challenges posed by rapid technological advancements and evolving consumer behavior.</description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience.</description></item><item><title>Cainiao will collaborate with Ethiopian Airlines to provide cold chain air freight services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</guid><description>Source: Alibaba Group. Cainiao will distribute temperature-sensitive medications, including COVID-19 vaccines, globally, excluding Africa, via Dubai in partnership with Ethiopian Airlines.
Cainiao Smart Logistics Network, the logistics branch of Alibaba Group Holdings, has partnered with Ethiopian Airlines. Their collaboration will establish a specialized cold chain air freight system to transport temperature-controlled medical supplies. These shipments will originate from Shenzhen Airport, recognized as China&amp;rsquo;s first medical cross-border cold chain facility.</description></item><item><title>Term deposits from ICBC are available through Alipay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 22:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/term-deposits-from-icbc-are-available-through-alipay/</guid><description>ICBC, the world&amp;rsquo;s largest bank by assets, now offers three-year term deposit services through Alipay, a popular digital lifestyle platform.
This collaboration between Alipay and ICBC began in 2005 with online payment services. In January 2020, ICBC introduced a one-year term deposit service on Alipay, allowing customers to make deposits directly through the platform. This service has seen a sevenfold increase in size since May.
The new three-year term deposit option, called Anxin Cun (Secure Deposits), offers a 3.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud will assist companies in accelerating their entry into the Chinese market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-will-assist-companies-in-accelerating-their-entry-into-the-chinese-market/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud recently introduced its China Gateway Program alongside eight local partners: the Info-communications Media Development Authority (IMDA), Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, Singapore Chinese Chamber of Commerce &amp;amp; Industry (SCCCI), SMU Academy, SGTech, Action Community for Entrepreneurship (ACE), and TechNode.
Alibaba Cloud, the data intelligence branch of the Alibaba Group, recently hosted its second Alibaba Cloud APAC Summit in Singapore, showcasing its dedication to serving Asia.
During the summit, the company announced the China Gateway Program in collaboration with IMDA, Enterprise Singapore, DBS SME Banking, SCCCI, SMU Academy, SGTech, ACE, and TechNode.</description></item><item><title>11 facts about 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:07:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</guid><description>Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 Global Shopping Festival, beginning on November 11, is generating excitement with its pre-launch preparations. Here are 11 key things shoppers should be aware of:
AI-Powered Multilingual Tools To enhance the shopping experience for global customers, Alibaba has introduced an AI translation tool designed to bridge language gaps between buyers and sellers.
This online chat tool, recently launched on Lazada, enables real-time translation between English and Thai, Vietnamese, and Indonesian.</description></item><item><title>By 2046, work as we currently understand it will have evolved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2046-work-as-we-currently-understand-it-will-have-evolved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 04:23:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-2046-work-as-we-currently-understand-it-will-have-evolved/</guid><description>Alibaba Group&amp;rsquo;s research division, AliResearch, has presented its vision for the future of the digital world. During their Vision 2046 summit in Beijing, the company released its Digital Economy 2.0 report, which includes several striking predictions.
The Decline of Traditional Corporations By 2020, AliResearch predicts that most commercial activity will happen on digital platforms. These platforms will offer businesses and consumers essential commercial infrastructure, including data, trade facilitation, payment processing, and logistics.</description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance is set to release a new book highlighting the achievements of influential brands in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</guid><description>Brand Alliance, a brand consulting firm, is releasing its inaugural book, &amp;ldquo;Influential Brands: A documentary of their heroic rise.&amp;rdquo; This book launch coincides with the firm&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;2014 Influential Brands&amp;rdquo; conference, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes&amp;rdquo;, taking place on November 7, 2014, at the Suntec City Convention Centre.
Source: Brand Alliance. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s brand story is in the book.
The book offers never-before-seen insights into the development of well-known brands, particularly those from Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Is Alibaba truly the top player in the e-commerce industry?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 17:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-alibaba-truly-the-top-player-in-the-e-commerce-industry/</guid><description>While Alibaba Group Holding is often called the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest e-commerce company, a new report from yStats.com suggests that this depends on how you interpret the data. The report, which ranks companies based on official revenue figures, found that Amazon was the actual leader in 2013.
Amazon&amp;rsquo;s impressive $74 billion in product and service sales surpasses the combined revenue of the next nine companies on the list. Chinese B2C retailer JD.</description></item><item><title>Alibaba Cloud introduces the Create@Alibaba Cloud startup program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alibaba-cloud-introduces-the-create-alibaba-cloud-startup-program/</guid><description>Alibaba Cloud, the cloud computing branch of Alibaba Group, has launched its first international startup program, Create@Alibaba Cloud. The program was announced in Singapore, home to Alibaba Cloud&amp;rsquo;s international headquarters, which will also serve as the regional hub for the initiative.
Singapore was selected as the regional hub due to its strong ties and access to other ASEAN markets, such as Thailand, Indonesia, and Malaysia. The company explained that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s robust connectivity and reputation as Asia&amp;rsquo;s most entrepreneurial economy enable participating startups to easily connect within Singapore and expand into neighboring markets.</description></item><item><title>The Double 12 Global Shopping Festival aims to attract Alipay users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-double-12-global-shopping-festival-aims-to-attract-alipay-users/</guid><description>Source: Alipay Facebook page. Flag advertising the Double 12 Global Shopping Festival.
Alipay, the world&amp;rsquo;s leading online and mobile payment and lifestyle platform operated by Ant Financial Services Group, launched its 2017 Double 12 Global Shopping Festival in Southeast Asia. The festival includes Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, and the Philippines.
Double 12 is a global event spanning 15 countries and territories across four continents. Over 500 brands and 100,000 merchants worldwide participate, offering Alipay users exclusive promotions throughout December.</description></item><item><title>This year, Alibaba's 11.11 Global Shopping Festival generated more than $17 billion in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</guid><description>Alibaba Group reported that on November 11, 2016, its China and international retail marketplaces achieved a gross merchandise volume (GMV) of RMB120.7 billion (US$17.8 billion), settled through Alipay. This represents a 32% growth compared to 2015. Mobile GMV settled through Alipay reached RMB99 billion (US$14.6 billion), making up 82% of the total GMV.
&amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 provides a glimpse into the future of retail, where entertainment, commerce, and interactive engagement blend seamlessly,&amp;rdquo; said Daniel Zhang, CEO of Alibaba Group.</description></item><item><title>Shoppers are interested in clothes, cosmetics, and baby products on 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</guid><description>Source: Alizila blog. The 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival logo is illuminated in neon.
Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival is surpassing the sales of the previous year. Alizila reports show that it took a mere 1 minute and 25 seconds for the festival to reach over US$1 billion in total gross merchandise volume (GMV).
By 1:15 p.m., Tmall Global had already exceeded its total GMV from the entire 2017 11.</description></item></channel></rss>