<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Office on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/office/</link><description>Recent content in Office on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/office/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach.</description></item><item><title>Groundbreaking ceremony finished for the Fujairah Business Centre, a mixed-use development</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 04:54:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/groundbreaking-ceremony-finished-for-the-fujairah-business-centre-a-mixed-use-development/</guid><description>Al Taif Investment, a collaboration between Dubai Investments and Fujairah Investment Establishment (FIE), the investment branch of the Fujairah Government, has launched its flagship Fujairah Business Centre project.
Scheduled for completion in three years with a budget of AED400 million, the project aims to be a landmark development. Located opposite the Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, it features two towers with a total built-up area of 80,058 sq m. These towers include a 19-story office building and a 19-story Courtyard by Marriott hotel offering 228 rooms and apartment units.</description></item><item><title>Hubspot's new, modern Asia Pacific headquarters in Singapore is designed with Millennials in mind</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 20:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-s-new-modern-asia-pacific-headquarters-in-singapore-is-designed-with-millennials-in-mind/</guid><description>Source: HubSpot. Pictured at the official opening ceremony, from left: Jeetu Mahtani and JD Sherman.
HubSpot has officially launched its Singapore office and revealed plans to add 150 employees to its Singapore-based team over the next three years. Currently, HubSpot Singapore has 30 employees.
The Singapore office, warmly referred to as SingSpot, joins the Sydney, Australia office as HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s second location in the Asia Pacific region and will serve as the company’s Asia Pacific headquarters.</description></item><item><title>Collective Works and CapitaLand are teaming up to launch a new coworking space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 11:54:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-and-capitaland-are-teaming-up-to-launch-a-new-coworking-space/</guid><description>Artist&amp;rsquo;s impression of the new coworking space at Capital Tower, Singapore.
A new high-end coworking space will be launched on the 12th floor of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Capital Tower. This joint venture between two companies will occupy 22,000 square feet and support 250 businesses. The space is adaptable and caters to a variety of businesses, from new startups to large corporations. Technological features include secure server hosting, video conferencing, internet phone services, and fiber optic broadband internet.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are feeling more optimistic than those in Hong Kong and are enjoying a superior work-life balance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-feeling-more-optimistic-than-those-in-hong-kong-and-are-enjoying-a-superior-work-life-balance/</guid><description>While 43% of businesses in Singapore are very confident about their growth prospects this year, only 30% of businesses in Hong Kong share the same level of confidence.
This year, 61% of businesses in Singapore have plans to increase their workforce, whereas only 44% in Hong Kong intend to do so.
A recent report called the Compass Index, which analyzed business trends in Hong Kong and Singapore, reveals a more optimistic outlook among businesses in Singapore, with employees experiencing a better work-life balance than their counterparts in Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>Collective Works, a coworking space located in the business district of Singapore, has been officially launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 01:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collective-works-a-coworking-space-located-in-the-business-district-of-singapore-has-been-officially-launched/</guid><description>A typical co-working space at Collective Works Capital Tower.
Collective Works, the first coworking space in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s central business district, has partnered with CapitaLand to open its second location. This 22,000 square foot “office of the future,” designed for high performance, takes up the entirety of the 12th floor in the 52-story Capital Tower situated in Tanjong Pagar.
Collective Works has built a reputation for its stylish design and meticulous attention to detail, including a focus on ergonomics, ambiance, lighting, and acoustic sound.</description></item><item><title>The most effective productivity hacks for Microsoft Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-effective-productivity-hacks-for-microsoft-office/</guid><description>Microsoft Office 2013 offers several improvements over previous versions, but long-time users may not be aware of these useful additions. At the Singapore launch of Office 365 Personal, Elsie Chong, Marketing Manager for Microsoft Singapore, highlighted her favorite new features:
PDF Reflow in Word 2013 allows users to open PDF files as editable Word documents, retaining the original formatting as much as possible. The modified document can be saved as a PDF or a Word file.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An improved chair designed to alleviate back discomfort</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-improved-chair-designed-to-alleviate-back-discomfort/</guid><description>Simon Hong, a neuroscientist, is seeking funding for his invention, the Chairbot. This robotic chair aims to eliminate back pain by suggesting new positions to the user based on their current posture.
Source: Kickstarter page
The Chairbot&amp;rsquo;s unique design features a split seat that encourages users to alternate between sitting and standing, reducing strain on the spine. Hong explains on the Kickstarter page that this constant shifting prevents the spinal trauma associated with maintaining a single posture for long periods.</description></item><item><title>Hong Leong Group has decided to establish its global headquarters at Damansara City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 13:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-leong-group-has-decided-to-establish-its-global-headquarters-at-damansara-city/</guid><description>Source: Damansara City website.
GuocoLand Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s key project, Damansara City, will soon house the Hong Leong Group&amp;rsquo;s global headquarters. The 33-story, top-tier office building, situated on the southwest side of this notable development, will be a major tenant within Damansara City when fully occupied by the second quarter of next year.
The Hong Leong Group is a prominent Malaysian conglomerate with interests in banking, financial services, manufacturing, distribution, property development, investment, hospitality, leisure, and principal investment.</description></item><item><title>Evernote is unveiling new additions to the Pfeiffer Collection of desktop accessories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:32:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evernote-is-unveiling-new-additions-to-the-pfeiffer-collection-of-desktop-accessories/</guid><description>Evernote has expanded its Pfeiffer Collection, a line of modern desktop accessories designed in collaboration with Eric Pfeiffer.
The latest additions are bent plywood platforms crafted to securely elevate laptops, tablets, and monitors on desks, while also providing extra storage space.
Source: Evernote blog.
The new products include:
Laptop platform: This stand, made of walnut bent ply, supports 13” or 15” laptops. A curved front trough can hold small items, and cables can be routed through the back.</description></item><item><title>Eliminating uncertainty in analytics with BeyondCore Apps for Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eliminating-uncertainty-in-analytics-with-beyondcore-apps-for-office/</guid><description>Source: BeyondCore website.
BeyondCore has introduced BeyondCore Apps for Office, a solution that provides automated analysis for the Microsoft Office suite with a single click. The company recognized the need for accessible and efficient analytics tools for business users who require data-driven insights to make informed decisions and improve their operations.
Arijit Sengupta, CEO and Founder of BeyondCore, highlighted the challenges of traditional analytics, describing it as a manual and time-consuming process.</description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75.</description></item><item><title>Protect your Office 365 emails with the latest Dropsuite cloud solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 08:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protect-your-office-365-emails-with-the-latest-dropsuite-cloud-solution/</guid><description>Smaller businesses can access Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s email backup and archiving tool for Microsoft Office 365 through intermediary companies like Ozhosting in Australia and ICONZ-Webvisions in Singapore.
Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Charif Elansari, emphasized their commitment to developing user-friendly solutions that are easy for small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) to buy and use.
Ozhosting CEO, Doug Endersbee, expressed satisfaction in offering Dropsuite&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive email archiving service, which meets legal requirements for retaining records, to their customers.</description></item><item><title>ERC has opened a co-working space in multiple cities across Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 19:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erc-has-opened-a-co-working-space-in-multiple-cities-across-singapore-thailand-and-vietnam/</guid><description>The University Mentorship program will connect lecturers with the BIG Work community to offer guidance. Users can utilize ERC&amp;rsquo;s expertise in various business areas and schedule consultations with program managers and resource advisors Guests at the BIG Hotel, catering to international and startup business travelers, will have early access to new hospitality-related products and services for research. Entrepreneur Resource Centre Holdings (ERC) has launched BIG Work, a new co-working space with locations in Singapore, Thailand, and Vietnam.</description></item><item><title>The Ibn Battuta Gate Office building is experiencing increased demand as Expo 2020 Dubai approaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 15:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ibn-battuta-gate-office-building-is-experiencing-increased-demand-as-expo-2020-dubai-approaches/</guid><description>Source: Seven Tides website.
As Expo 2020 Dubai approaches, Ibn Battuta Gate Offices, a property developed by Seven Tides, is leveraging its prime location in New Dubai. Situated near the Mövenpick Hotel, Ibn Battuta Mall, and a metro station, the office building is attracting significant attention.
The appeal of this location is further enhanced by the planned expansion of Ibn Battuta Mall. The AED160 million project will add 28,000 square meters, including a 350-room hotel, 150 shops, 50 restaurants, and a cinema with 21 screens.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>The future of work revolves around extracting valuable business insights from data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 01:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</guid><description>The rise of robotics and artificial intelligence (AI) is a significant development for the workforce. The shortage of skilled professionals across industries has made automation increasingly appealing to employers. It is evident that automation and AI have the potential to replace a considerable portion of tasks currently performed by humans.
Reactions to this trend are varied, ranging from optimism to apprehension. An Oracle study reveals that 93% of individuals would readily follow instructions from robots in the workplace, demonstrating a high level of trust in automation.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents.</description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia.</description></item><item><title>The Office of the Future at HP is filled with cutting-edge innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 12:21:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-of-the-future-at-hp-is-filled-with-cutting-edge-innovation/</guid><description>HP has introduced new products and services designed to help businesses create a modern and secure &amp;ldquo;Office of the Future.&amp;rdquo; This initiative focuses on empowering employees with technology that boosts productivity and creativity, while also offering flexibility in how and where they work.
This shift is driven by evolving workforce demographics, as over 70% of Asian employees already work remotely and Millennials and Gen Z, who prioritize workplace flexibility, are becoming the majority.</description></item><item><title>Epson has launched three business inkjet printers that offer a range of connectivity options and high capacity features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 11:23:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-has-launched-three-business-inkjet-printers-that-offer-a-range-of-connectivity-options-and-high-capacity-features/</guid><description>Source: Epson. The WorkForce WF-2661.
Epson, a company that provides digital imaging and printing solutions, has launched three new inkjet printers for businesses in Singapore. These models are designed for small offices and home offices.
The ultra-compact Epson WorkForce series is designed for small spaces and cost-effective printing. These printers include automatic document feeders (ADFs) and Epson Connect, enabling users to print directly from their mobile devices.
The new WorkForce series offers easy and flexible printing over Wi-Fi.</description></item><item><title>Prepare for Chinese New Year with Amazon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 04:15:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-for-chinese-new-year-with-amazon/</guid><description>Preparing your office for Chinese New Year might be easier with a little help from Amazon.sg&amp;rsquo;s dedicated Chinese New Year store.
Finding the right gifts for clients is made simpler with choices like an abalone gift set, priced at S$310.80 for two 454g cans, or bird&amp;rsquo;s nest, available for S$39.90 for six jars. To help everyone in the office get into the spirit, festive treats are a must-have:
Source: Amazon. Snacks for the office for Chinese New Year.</description></item><item><title>Hotdesk and Compass provide short-term workspace solutions in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Hotdesk, a platform for finding temporary office space, has teamed up with Compass Offices to provide on-demand workspaces and meeting rooms for professionals on the move. These spaces can be reserved for various durations, including daily, weekly, or monthly.
Studies from IDC indicate that by 2015, there will be a significant increase in the number of mobile workers globally, with over 1.3 billion individuals adopting this work style. Notably, the Asia Pacific region is projected to have the highest concentration, with over 838 million mobile workers.</description></item><item><title>A worldwide survey reveals that workers do not have the necessary resources to concentrate on their tasks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 08:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-worldwide-survey-reveals-that-workers-do-not-have-the-necessary-resources-to-concentrate-on-their-tasks/</guid><description>Plantronics recently released the findings of a global study conducted by Oxford Economics, which focused on the impact of open workspaces on employees. The study aimed to understand employee preferences regarding work environments and provide insights for managers to maximize productivity and satisfaction among their teams.
Oxford Economics gathered data from over 1,200 senior executives and non-managerial employees across various industries and job functions. Participants represented a global spectrum, including the US, Canada, the UK, Germany, India, China, Australia, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, and Norway.</description></item><item><title>SMBs can access Office 365 through GoDaddy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smbs-can-access-office-365-through-godaddy/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a technology company that supports small businesses, has partnered with Microsoft to offer Microsoft Office 365 to small businesses in Asian markets. This collaboration is part of GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s ongoing effort to provide top-tier business management solutions worldwide.
By offering Office 365, GoDaddy allows its customers to easily access professional email linked to a domain name, secure cloud storage, and a wide range of productivity and collaboration tools.
&amp;ldquo;GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s understanding of small businesses combined with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s email and productivity suite gives small business owners in Asia the tools they need to simplify their operations,&amp;rdquo; said Roger Chen, Vice President of Asia, GoDaddy.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Gift Guide 2020: Office Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 22:04:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/christmas-gift-guide-2020-office-edition/</guid><description>Stationery The Scenic Route 2021 calendar
Victoria McGrane, an illustrator and textile designer, collaborated with Rainforest Rescue, an organization dedicated to rainforest protection and restoration since 1999, to create a 2021 calendar. McGrane, the talent behind The Scenic Route brand, is known for her hand-illustrated designs and stationery that showcase the beauty of Australian nature. Her work has garnered attention and partnerships with prominent brands.
“Protecting and restoring Australia&amp;rsquo;s valuable rainforests is incredibly important to me, and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled that my illustrations and travel inspiration can contribute to safeguarding these ancient forests and their wildlife,” shared McGrane.</description></item><item><title>Singapore customers can test products before making a purchase with Flokk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/</guid><description>Flokk, a Norwegian company known for producing high-quality seating furniture, has joined forces with W. Atelier to introduce Flokk&amp;rsquo;s brands to the Singapore market.
Source: Flokk. HÅG chairs in an office.
Flokk is recognized for its ergonomic and sustainable designs, with all products developed, produced, and manufactured in Europe. Each of Flokk&amp;rsquo;s eight brands represents the highest quality, as demonstrated in W. Atelier&amp;rsquo;s Henderson showroom, where HÅG, RBM, and RH are exclusively featured.</description></item><item><title>In order to work effectively, it is essential to have clean offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-work-effectively-it-is-essential-to-have-clean-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 10:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-work-effectively-it-is-essential-to-have-clean-offices/</guid><description>Source: SoftBank Robotics, Infogrid. A significant number of employees express worry about office hygiene.
A recent study revealed that a majority of employees (64%) are apprehensive about the possibility of contracting COVID-19 in their workplaces. This study, focusing on workplace cleanliness, was carried out by Milieu Insight, a consumer research firm, in partnership with SoftBank Robotics, a provider of automation and robotics solutions, and Infogrid.
The study highlighted that over 80% of employees believe that a clean office environment is crucial for their productivity.</description></item><item><title>Kickstarter's main focus is the standing desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 03:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-s-main-focus-is-the-standing-desk/</guid><description>If you need a desk that allows you to work comfortably while standing, Steven Yu might have a solution. His StandDesk is height-adjustable, ranging from 71cm to 114cm, and incorporates design elements that make frequent adjustments easy.
Source: Kickstarter. The all-black StandDesk version.
&amp;ldquo;The StandDesk is more than a product; it&amp;rsquo;s a positive step towards improving people&amp;rsquo;s lives globally,&amp;rdquo; Yu stated on his Kickstarter page.
An intuitive &amp;lsquo;up/down&amp;rsquo; control button effortlessly raises or lowers the desk to the desired height.</description></item><item><title>Selecting the appropriate tea for the workplace break room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 16:24:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/selecting-the-appropriate-tea-for-the-workplace-break-room/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s common to find pre-mixed tea sachets or teabags in office pantries. While these are convenient and widely available, Teabox, an online retailer specializing in premium Indian teas, suggests there might be downsides to these options.
Source: Teabox website.
Teabox CEO, Kaushal Dugar, explains that tea dust, a byproduct of tea production, lacks the full flavor, taste, and aroma of whole tea leaves. This tea dust is often what ends up in teabags, resulting in a less flavorful and potentially less nutritious cup.</description></item><item><title>Avanta India inaugurates a new office space in Gurgaon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanta-india-inaugurates-a-new-office-space-in-gurgaon/</guid><description>Avanta Business Centre has established a new premium office space in Gurgaon, India, spanning 25,000 square feet. Conveniently situated near the HUDA City Centre Metro station, the Park Centra facility offers easy accessibility.
This marks Avanta&amp;rsquo;s second business center in Gurgaon. The Park Centra location provides a variety of office sizes, ranging from 77 square feet to approximately 20,000 square feet, to accommodate a diverse clientele. The space is ready for occupancy and features around 300 workstations, a communal area, a pantry, and four meeting rooms.</description></item></channel></rss>