<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bangladesh on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bangladesh/</link><description>Recent content in Bangladesh on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bangladesh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India and Bangladesh have initiated connectivity projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-and-bangladesh-have-initiated-connectivity-projects/</guid><description>The Prime Ministers of India and Bangladesh, Narendra Modi and Sheikh Hasina, respectively, along with West Bengal&amp;rsquo;s Chief Minister, Mamata Banerjee, inaugurated multiple connectivity initiatives between the two nations.
These projects include the inauguration of the second Bhairab and Titas Railway Bridges, situated on the 320-km Dhaka-Chittagong railway line in Bangladesh. Additionally, the International Rail Passenger Terminus in Kolkata, India, was also inaugurated.
The dignitaries also launched the first run of the Bandhan Express, connecting Kolkata to Khulna in southwest Bangladesh, covering a distance of over 150km.</description></item><item><title>ZEE5 is attracting viewers from Pakistan and Bangladesh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 01:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zee5-is-attracting-viewers-from-pakistan-and-bangladesh/</guid><description>Source: Zee5. Images for the #ShareTheLove campaign.
Following its initial launch in over 190 countries, the digital entertainment platform ZEE5 is setting its sights on Pakistan and Bangladesh.
The company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;#ShareTheLove&amp;rdquo; campaign highlights the cultural and entertainment commonalities between ZEE5 and these two nations. ZEE5 aims to foster a sense of shared enjoyment by providing a diverse content library that resonates with Pakistani and Bangladeshi audiences, featuring Hindi and Bengali original series like &amp;ldquo;Rangbaaz,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Kaali,&amp;rdquo; and the upcoming &amp;ldquo;Sharate Aaj,&amp;rdquo; original films such as &amp;ldquo;Aranyadeb&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Tigers,&amp;rdquo; and digital premieres of movies like &amp;ldquo;Namaste England&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Praktan.</description></item></channel></rss>