<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Food on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/food/</link><description>Recent content in Food on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches.</description></item><item><title>The demand for milk and yogurt-based beverages is increasing in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-milk-and-yogurt-based-beverages-is-increasing-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Increased advertising in mass media, along with more television shows and magazine content focused on health topics, have made Indonesian consumers more aware of the advantages of drinking milk from 2011 to 2016, according to Euromonitor.
Ultrajaya Milk Industry &amp;amp; Trading Company leads the drinking milk market, holding a 23% value share in 2016. Its most recognized brand is Ultra. Euromonitor attributes the company&amp;rsquo;s success in flavored milk to its strong marketing and enhanced distribution.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi.</description></item><item><title>Food tours are available in Hong Kong, Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo through Eating Adventures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-tours-are-available-in-hong-kong-guangzhou-guilin-and-yangshuo-through-eating-adventures/</guid><description>Source: Eating Adventures website.
Eating Adventures has expanded its food tour services to Hong Kong. The company, already established as the leading provider of food tours in Guangzhou, Guilin, and Yangshuo, China, aims to provide travelers with an authentic cultural and culinary experience by guiding them through local neighborhoods.
Wai Zhou, owner of Eating Adventures Food Tours, highlights that while Hong Kong has existing food tour operators, most are not run by locals.</description></item><item><title>The keto diet market is expected to grow at a CAGR of 5%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:56:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-keto-diet-market-is-expected-to-grow-at-a-cagr-of-5/</guid><description>Technavio reports that the keto diet is gaining popularity, as overweight and obese individuals experience faster weight loss and body fat reduction compared to other diets.
This diet emphasizes extremely low carbohydrate intake and high fat consumption, aiming to initiate a metabolic state called ketosis. Ketosis enables the body to burn fat more effectively.
Technavio forecasts that the keto diet market will grow at a rate close to 5% by 2023.</description></item><item><title>In March, Dario Cecchini explores culinary partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 10:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-dario-cecchini-explores-culinary-partnerships/</guid><description>The renowned Bottega di Carna at the Mondrian Singapore Duxton, known for its unique dining experience crafted by &amp;ldquo;World&amp;rsquo;s Greatest Butcher&amp;rdquo; Dario Cecchini, is excited to announce upcoming collaborations this March. The restaurant&amp;rsquo;s philosophy centers around respecting the entire animal and utilizing traditional methods to showcase the finest produce and ingredients.
Cecchini Returns with Exciting Collaborations Bottega di Carna X Bold &amp;amp; Braised Hawker Pop-up
March 6th-7th
Cecchini and Bottega di Carna&amp;rsquo;s Head Chef Kenny Huang are joining forces with local Chinatown eatery Bold &amp;amp; Braised at Maxwell Food Centre.</description></item><item><title>Experience the global culinary journey at THAIFEX Anuga Asia 2024</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 16:05:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-global-culinary-journey-at-thaifex-anuga-asia-2024/</guid><description>THAIFEX - Anuga Asia 2024, scheduled for May 28th to June 1st, 2024, is set to be the largest and most diverse edition yet, featuring exhibitors from 45 countries and regions and completely booked booth spaces.
_
Source: THAIFEX-Anuga Asia. Hosted buyer programme participants posing for a group picture during THAIFEX-Anuga Asia 2023.
This premier food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) trade show in Asia Pacific has experienced an unprecedented increase in global participation.</description></item><item><title>Numerous innovations showcased at Food&amp;HotelAsia 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</guid><description>Display at the Suntec venue.
The Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) and ProWine Asia (PWA) trade shows are predicted to draw tens of thousands of attendees during their joint four-day run in Singapore, from April 24th to 27th.
This year marks the largest event yet. Visitors can explore exhibits from over 3,500 international food, beverage, and hospitality exhibitors throughout 120,000 sq m at FHA. In addition, PWA 2018 features 300 international wine and spirits exhibitors across 7,500 sq m.</description></item><item><title>NOBU presents Harvest in Aomori at InterContinental Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/nobu-presents-harvest-in-aomori-at-intercontinental-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: InterContinental Hong Kong. Steamed abalone, sea urchin shijimi dashi jelly, and cured mackerel sashimi with chrysanthemum dressing.
NOBU InterContinental Hong Kong presents the fifth installment of its GOURMET TOUR OF JAPAN series – Harvest in Aomori – which runs from September 12th to October 22nd.
Executive Chef Sean Mell and Executive Sushi Chef Arakai Kaazunari have crafted special lunch and dinner menus that showcase the fall bounty of Aomori Prefecture, a region in northern Japan&amp;rsquo;s Tōhoku region.</description></item><item><title>The winners of Asia's 50 Best Restaurants 2016 will be revealed in Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 18:57:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-asia-s-50-best-restaurants-2016-will-be-revealed-in-bangkok/</guid><description>Source: Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best
Restaurants. The fourth annual Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants awards ceremony will be held in Bangkok, Thailand, on February 29, 2016.
Bangkok restaurants have held the No. 1 position on the Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for the past two years, demonstrating Thailand’s increasing culinary impact in the area. David Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Nahm won first place in 2014, while Gaggan Anand&amp;rsquo;s restaurant won first place in 2015. The 2015 list included Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Eat Me (No.</description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout.</description></item><item><title>The Durian Fiesta 2017 has been announced by Goodwood Park Hotel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-durian-fiesta-2017-has-been-announced-by-goodwood-park-hotel/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is hosting its yearly Durian Fiesta, featuring new creations and beloved classics that have delighted guests since 1983. From March 10th to July 31st, 2017, fourteen premium durian desserts, including six new additions, will be available, all crafted using the finest D24 and Mao Shan Wang durians.
The featured desserts include the new D24 Starry Starry Night Ice Cream Cake, the D24 Sunflower Seed Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Cashew Nut Crumble Tartlet, the D24 Matcha Cake, and the D24 Salted Caramel Cuppa.</description></item><item><title>GwaKu offers tasty and budget-friendly dishes in the center of Kuala Lumpur</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 16:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gwaku-offers-tasty-and-budget-friendly-dishes-in-the-center-of-kuala-lumpur/</guid><description>Source: Gwaku&amp;rsquo;s Facebook page. This is their famous ayam percik.
GwaKu, a restaurant situated in Q Sentral close to KL Sentral, offers a rotating menu that keeps nearby office workers surprised about their lunch options. For example, one week could feature ayam perchik, while the following week might offer lamb stews.
Mike Ibrahim, the founder of GwaKu, emphasizes their commitment to using fresh, seasonal, and locally sourced ingredients. He explains, &amp;ldquo;By using in-season produce, we can ensure quality and freshness while also benefiting from lower prices.</description></item><item><title>THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023 begins in Bangkok on May 23rd</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thaifex-anuga-asia-2023-begins-in-bangkok-on-may-23rd/</guid><description>The upcoming THAIFEX – Anuga Asia 2023, a premier food and beverage industry event, will take place from May 23-27, 2023 at IMPACT Muang Thong Thani in Bangkok, Thailand. This year&amp;rsquo;s event features 11 signature trade shows, six special shows, and a focus on innovation, bold concepts, and advanced solutions. With approximately 3,000 exhibitors from 43 countries and over 60,000 trade visitors from more than 120 countries anticipated, organizers aim for a total transaction value of 70,000 million baht, including over 1.</description></item><item><title>Tips for conducting business meetings in Jakarta</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-for-conducting-business-meetings-in-jakarta/</guid><description>The World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF), hosted by the WIEF Foundation, will take place in Jakarta, Indonesia from August 2nd to 4th this year. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for halal dining options for business meetings during the forum, consider these suggestions:
Anomali Coffee
With locations throughout Jakarta and Bali, Anomali Coffee is a great choice for a business meeting. They offer high-quality coffee with a focus on flavor and aroma. Their baristas are highly skilled, and each location provides free Wi-Fi and air conditioning for guests.</description></item><item><title>The Asian Food Network has launched a website in Bahasa Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asian-food-network-has-launched-a-website-in-bahasa-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 16:27:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asian-food-network-has-launched-a-website-in-bahasa-indonesia/</guid><description>Source: asianfoodnetwork.com. Snippet from the Bahasa Indonesia website.
The Asian Food Network (AFN), a prominent TV and online food channel specializing in Asian cuisine and culture, has introduced an Indonesian language website to reach over 200 million Indonesian speakers.
AFN aims to provide a unified digital and linear experience that offers entertainment, convenience, and a community for Asian food enthusiasts. As part of this goal, the website aligns with Discovery Networks Asia Pacific (DNAP)&amp;rsquo;s strategy to enhance its offerings for the substantial Indonesian-speaking audience.</description></item><item><title>Limited edition experiences are a popular trend in the food service industry in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</guid><description>In 2015, Australian diners increasingly embraced their inner foodies, craving novel culinary experiences. Food service operators responded with innovation, experimenting with formats, menus, and dining concepts, according to a Euromonitor blog post.
One example highlighted by the research firm is Hotel Marriott in Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table for 12&amp;rdquo; concept, launched in October 2015. This exclusive dining experience offered a four-course degustation menu for a limited group of twelve guests, available only one night a week.</description></item><item><title>Indulge in these food-themed gifts and enjoy!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 03:45:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indulge-in-these-food-themed-gifts-and-enjoy/</guid><description>As the holiday season approaches, businesses are looking for unique and thoughtful gifts for clients and employees. Here are a few distinctive gift ideas:
Source: Cafédirect.
For coffee lovers, Cafédirect, a British beverage company, introduced a premium freeze-dried instant coffee in Singaporean supermarkets this year. This meticulously crafted blend combines the sweetness and chocolate notes of South American Arabica beans with the well-rounded flavor of Central American beans and the boldness of East African Robusta beans.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel launches a new promotion featuring white asparagus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 22:11:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-launches-a-new-promotion-featuring-white-asparagus/</guid><description>An image showcasing white asparagus from the Goodwood Park Hotel website.
Throughout May, indulge in the sweetness and succulence of imported German white asparagus at two distinct dining destinations: Gordon Grill, the renowned Continental fine-dining restaurant at Goodwood Park Hotel, and Min Jiang at One-North, a modern Chinese establishment in a restored colonial bungalow at Rochester Park.
Established in 1963, Gordon Grill at the Goodwood Park Hotel has earned a stellar reputation for its exceptional steaks and Continental cuisine.</description></item><item><title>AppDine has launched a beta version of its F&amp;B and lifestyle e-commerce marketplace in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 22:22:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/appdine-has-launched-a-beta-version-of-its-f-b-and-lifestyle-e-commerce-marketplace-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: AppeDine. Screenshot of the AppeDine app for consumers.
AppeDine has launched the public beta version of its food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and lifestyle e-commerce platform in Singapore. The marketplace facilitates online transactions tailored for F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle businesses, chefs, and consumers.
AppeDine brings together F&amp;amp;B outlets, temporary events, and promotions in one place, enabling F&amp;amp;B and lifestyle providers to generate revenue from their services and spaces online without upfront investment.</description></item><item><title>Experience the street food of Taiwan at Tea Valley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 18:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-street-food-of-taiwan-at-tea-valley/</guid><description>Tea Valley: Bringing Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s Street Food Flavors to Singapore [Image of Tea Valley Downtown East outlet]
Tea Valley (茶食坊), a casual Taiwanese dining chain in Singapore, has ambitious plans for expansion. At a tasting event held at their first location in Downtown East, Director Lawrence Lim shared his vision for growing the brand beyond just new locations, but also in the variety of services they offer.
[Image of Lawrence Lim, Director of Tea Valley]</description></item><item><title>Join us in celebrating at Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-celebrating-at-eclipse-hospitality-group-restaurants-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Eclipse Hospitality Group restaurants in Hong Kong and Macau are celebrating this December with special holiday menus.
An American feast at Grand Central
Source: Eclipse Hospitality Group. Cardamom spiced snapper fillet combined with winter squash, asparagus and lemongrass broth.
Grand Central, situated on the roof of the Elements shopping mall, is offering three-course dinners for HK$368 and four-course dinners for HK$398. Start with roasted sweet potato soup or roasted beets with blue cheese mousse, poached pears, and pistachios.</description></item><item><title>AccorHotels will be introducing a Gourmet Food &amp; Wine Festival in Singapore in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accorhotels-will-be-introducing-a-gourmet-food-wine-festival-in-singapore-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Source: AccorHotels. Jaan was awarded a Michelin Star in the Singapore Michelin Guide 2016 and secured the 29th spot in Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2016.
AccorHotels, the leading hotel operator in the country, is launching its first-ever Gourmet Food &amp;amp; Wine Festival, anticipated to be one of the most extensive events of its kind in Singapore.
The festival will feature several Michelin-starred chefs. Graham Wilson, Chief Marketing &amp;amp; Distribution Officer for AccorHotels Asia Pacific, stated, “In a city celebrated for its culinary scene, AccorHotels will bring together some of our finest chefs from around the world and showcase the immense talent of Singaporean chefs to create a food festival as lively and diverse as Singapore itself.</description></item><item><title>The second edition of Food and Hotel Penang is back!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-edition-of-food-and-hotel-penang-is-back/</guid><description>Source: FHP 2016 website.
The second Food and Hotel Penang (FHP 2016) event is poised to solidify its standing as the premier trade-only platform in Northern Malaysia. This event will host a curated buyer program, offering access to key figures in the food and hospitality sectors within Penang and nearby northern states like Kedah, Perak, and Perlis.
Supported by the Penang state government and the Malaysian Association of Hotels, FHP aims to build upon the achievements of its 2014 edition, which saw participation from 240 companies spanning 30 countries.</description></item><item><title>Cafédirect introduces new packaging for its premium-quality coffee blends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caf-direct-introduces-new-packaging-for-its-premium-quality-coffee-blends/</guid><description>Cafédirect, a UK beverage company, has launched its Smooth, Lively, and Intense Roast Coffees in redesigned packaging.
These coffees are expertly crafted by Cafédirect’s own Q-graders (coffee experts) to showcase the rich flavor of the beans and highlight specific notes. Q grading guarantees consistency in coffee evaluation, much like sommeliers do for wines.
“The exciting aspect of crafting these blends is our ability to select coffees that complement one another. Blending different varieties and regional beans not only allows Cafédirect to tailor the coffee to a particular taste profile but also provides you with a consistent cup of coffee,” explained Georgios Kokkalis, Q Grader and Production Manager at Cafédirect UK.</description></item><item><title>Grand Hyatt Mumbai reveals its plans for New Year's Eve</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-hyatt-mumbai-reveals-its-plans-for-new-year-s-eve/</guid><description>The Grand Hyatt Mumbai, a premier Hyatt International property and a central hotel for Mumbai, Pune, and Goa, is hosting multiple New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve celebrations.
Starting at 7 pm, guests can enjoy the Grand Courtyard Party. This event features dancing under the stars, drinks, and desserts for INR 3,500 plus taxes.
At 7 pm, several dining options are available. Soma offers North West Frontier cuisine with vegetarian and non-vegetarian choices. Celini provides Italian cuisine, while China House serves a Chinese-themed dinner.</description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist.</description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience.</description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years.</description></item><item><title>Foodpanda has introduced a high-end delivery service in the Central Business District of Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:45:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foodpanda-has-introduced-a-high-end-delivery-service-in-the-central-business-district-of-singapore/</guid><description>Source: foodpanda website.
In celebration of its third anniversary in Singapore, foodpanda Singapore has introduced a premium delivery service. This service includes approximately 50 restaurants and covers the central business district. It aims to serve busy professionals who want diverse food choices delivered directly to their workplaces.
Launched a month after securing US$110 million in funding, this new service reflects the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing user experience and customer service.</description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef.</description></item><item><title>FHA2016 ends on a positive note</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</guid><description>Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), the leading trade show for Asia&amp;rsquo;s food and hospitality sector, concluded successfully.
Source: Singapore Exhibition Services. The showfloor at FHA2016.
Lindy Wee, Chief Executive of Singapore Exhibition Services, noted that as consumer preferences change, so do buyer demands. She expressed satisfaction that FHA remains a crucial platform for exhibitors to introduce innovative products and for global buyers to source them, effectively serving the food and hospitality sectors.
FHA featured a comprehensive range of products and services, from ingredients and equipment to hotel amenities and software.</description></item><item><title>A Singaporean restaurant and art gallery are showcasing hypebeast artworks for diners to enjoy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-restaurant-and-art-gallery-are-showcasing-hypebeast-artworks-for-diners-to-enjoy/</guid><description>Until March 2021, enthusiasts of modern pop culture and Japanese cuisine in Singapore can experience a unique collaboration that blends contemporary art with specialized dining.
Source: simpleArte by iCare.4u. Artworks by the featured artists participating in Hypebeast@Uni.
Doraemon Here We Go by Takashi Murakami (left), Hero number 12 by Shen Jingdong (right, top left quadrant), Chiho Aoshima, artist (right, top right quadrant), Sky Year by Aoshima (right, bottom right quadrant), and Steven Harrington (right, bottom left quadrant).</description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be expanding in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</guid><description>A Nestle Sjora mural was a key feature at the Nestle booth during Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia 2018.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), the largest biennial trade show in the region for food and hospitality, will be split into two separate shows starting in 2020. FHA-HoReCa will take place in early March, and FHA-Food &amp;amp; Beverage will follow at the end of March.
This cake was on display at the Qingdao Kesong Food Company (KFI) booth.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard).</description></item><item><title>Bay Hotel Singapore will be offering a Ramadhan buffet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:11:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bay-hotel-singapore-will-be-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</guid><description>Source: Bay Hotel Singapore. The Ramadhan buffet spread.
Bay Hotel Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Rumah Rasa restaurant will offer a special Ramadan buffet every evening from May 16th to June 14th, 2018.
Leading the culinary team, Executive Chef Esa will showcase highlights like chick kut teh, a flavorful broth simmered overnight and accompanied by taupok (fried tofu puffs), dried mushrooms, and garlic, as part of the Ramadan Iftar Menu.
Another standout dish is ayam woku belanga, featuring marinated chicken infused with a special spice blend inspired by the Manado cuisine of North Sulawesi, Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>The goal of the Taste The World Dining Series is to demonstrate that food serves as a universal form of communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</guid><description>Gourmet Trails, a luxury travel company, presents the first-ever Taste The World culinary series, taking place from May 4th to 26th, 2024. This festival showcases the unifying power of food, emphasizing its ability to connect people and foster understanding.
Taste The World partners with acclaimed restaurants like Appetite, Hashida, CURE, Canchita, Esquina, Ummi Beirut, and ANJU to offer a diverse range of global cuisines. Proceeds from this event will support the United Nations World Food Programme.</description></item><item><title>The restaurants at InterContinental Hong Kong have been awarded a combined total of three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 12:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-restaurants-at-intercontinental-hong-kong-have-been-awarded-a-combined-total-of-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>The 2018 Michelin Guide recognized two restaurants at the InterContinental Hong Kong, awarding a total of three Michelin stars. Yan Toh Heen, their Cantonese restaurant, earned two stars, while Rech by Alain Ducasse, a recent addition opened in March 2017, received one. Rech by Alain Ducasse is not only the hotel&amp;rsquo;s newest culinary venture but also marks the first international location of the acclaimed Parisian seafood restaurant.
Claus Pedersen, General Manager of the InterContinental Hong Kong, expressed his pride, stating that achieving these stars is a testament to the dedication and effort of their entire team.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon, the Korean fine-dining restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, has been awarded three Michelin stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 04:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-the-korean-fine-dining-restaurant-at-the-shilla-seoul-has-been-awarded-three-michelin-stars/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. Nine delicacies at La Yeon.
During the first-ever Michelin Guide Seoul launch in 2017, held at The Shilla Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Dynasty Hall, the hotel&amp;rsquo;s traditional Korean fine-dining establishment, La Yeon, was granted a coveted three-star Michelin rating. Recognized for its authentic flavors, exceptional service, inviting atmosphere, and well-paired drinks, La Yeon stands as the sole Seoul restaurant within a hospitality group to achieve this three-star distinction.</description></item><item><title>HungryGoWhere is collecting votes for its inaugural foodie awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 02:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hungrygowhere-is-collecting-votes-for-its-inaugural-foodie-awards/</guid><description>The inaugural HungryGoWhere Awards voting period has opened. The food review platform HungryGoWhere revealed that public votes will solely decide the 26 award recipients.
Those interested in voting have until February 4th to cast their ballots on the awards website. The awards span five categories: Restaurants, Hawkers, Drinks, Occasions, and Best of the Best. After the voting period ends, participants will be entered into a lucky draw.</description></item><item><title>Godrej Tyson Foods introduces the delectable Galouti Kabab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godrej-tyson-foods-introduces-the-delectable-galouti-kabab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godrej-tyson-foods-introduces-the-delectable-galouti-kabab/</guid><description>Godrej Tyson Foods, a subsidiary of Godrej Agrovet, has introduced a Galouti Kabab under its rapidly expanding Godrej Yummiez brand. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that Godrej Yummiez primarily offers vegetarian products.
Godrej Yummiez already holds a strong position in the kabab market with its chicken seekh kabab and Hariyali kabab options. By adding Galouti Kabab to its offerings, Godrej Yummiez aims to bring this delicacy from the royal kitchens of Lucknow to dining tables across India.</description></item><item><title>March and April dining promotions are being shared by Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 06:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/march-and-april-dining-promotions-are-being-shared-by-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy. Braised beancurd, with salted egg in the background.
The Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy is offering several dining deals throughout March and April 2016.
One promotion focuses on Teochew porridge with side dishes created by Head Chef Victor Lee Appu at the Jia Wei Chinese Restaurant.
Teochew porridge, a classic dish from Eastern Guangdong, China, is a staple for the Teochew people. Unlike Cantonese congee, the Singaporean version is prepared without broth and served with a variety of accompanying dishes and condiments.</description></item><item><title>Aladdin Street strives to become a leading global e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aladdin-street-strives-to-become-a-leading-global-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Aladdinstreet.com.sg, a global e-marketplace specializing in premium and halal products, has officially launched. Catering to both businesses and individual consumers, the platform offers a range of halal-certified products alongside premium items that don&amp;rsquo;t require certification.
Since its initial announcement in July 2016, Aladdinstreet.com.sg has carefully selected 200 merchants for inclusion on the site, formalizing agreements with nearly 60. Approximately half of these merchants provide halal-friendly or halal-certified products, encompassing diverse categories such as food, beverages, vitamins, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, fashion, and more.</description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself to taste delicious food from various regions at RWS Street Eats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</guid><description>Resorts World Sentosa (RWS) is bringing back its popular food event, RWS Street Eats, after it attracted over 100,000 attendees last year. The event will run from May 3rd to 12th, 2019, and showcase new dishes from across Southeast Asia.
Taking place at the Malaysian Food Street in RWS, this 10-day event will feature hidden culinary gems from Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, Vietnam, and Taiwan. These vendors are local favorites, often known only to the savviest eaters in their respective countries.</description></item><item><title>FUMI creates authentic Japanese dining experiences for customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 05:04:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fumi-creates-authentic-japanese-dining-experiences-for-customers/</guid><description>Source: FUMI Facebook page. FUMI sushi.
FUMI, a new Japanese eatery, seeks to share the finest Japanese cuisine in Hong Kong within a space adorned with Japanese art, furnishings, and tableware. They offer a range of dining experiences, from elaborate omakase and kaiseki dinners to individual dishes and set lunch options.
Situated in California Tower, FUMI sources the highest quality seasonal ingredients directly from Japan daily. Flown in and delivered straight to their kitchen, these ingredients are often prepared and served within hours of being harvested, guaranteeing freshness in their sushi, sashimi, omakase, and kaiseki preparations, as well as a variety of seasonal menus.</description></item><item><title>The Shizuoka guide provides exclusive tips for exploring the city</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:27:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-shizuoka-guide-provides-exclusive-tips-for-exploring-the-city/</guid><description>Source: Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division.
The Shizuoka City Tourism &amp;amp; City Relations Division in Japan has created the &amp;ldquo;SHIZUOKA GUIDE,&amp;rdquo; a 52-page guidebook containing coupons. The guide helps inbound tourists enjoy local food and shopping at affordable prices.
Information was collected from locals who typically share recommendations through word-of-mouth. The guide features:
Lists of popular restaurants ranked by popularity. Locations offering local products like green tea and Mount Fuji souvenirs at reasonable prices.</description></item><item><title>The top five consumer trends for 2015 according to Canadean</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:33:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</guid><description>In 2015, market research company Canadean predicts five key trends will shape consumer behavior in the fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) industry:
From Mass Production to Personalization
Canadean anticipates a growing consumer preference for artisanal and handcrafted products. Consumers are seeking out products made on a smaller scale, believing this signifies higher quality and a stronger connection to the brand. Brands can capitalize on this trend by highlighting a product&amp;rsquo;s exclusivity and the care taken in its creation, appealing to consumers moving away from mass-produced FMCG items.</description></item><item><title>La Yeon is now offering its Spring Menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/la-yeon-is-now-offering-its-spring-menu/</guid><description>Source: The Shilla Seoul. La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s chilled pen shell salad with yuzu garlic sauce.
La Yeon, the three-Michelin-starred Korean restaurant at The Shilla Seoul, renowned for its place on Asia’s 50 Best Restaurants list for three years running, introduces its new Spring Menu. This menu highlights the season&amp;rsquo;s freshest ingredients sourced directly from the Korean peninsula, reflecting La Yeon&amp;rsquo;s dedication to celebrating Korea&amp;rsquo;s rich culinary traditions.
The Spring Menu presents delicacies like geoduck, sea bream, king scallops, webfoot octopus, napa cabbage, mulberries, and bellflower seeds.</description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be larger and improved in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</guid><description>Ting speaking at a media preview for FHA.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), a major food and hospitality trade show in Asia, is approaching its 40th anniversary of serving the industry&amp;rsquo;s needs.
Since its 1978 inception, FHA has attracted a predominantly international exhibitor base (over 80%), underscoring its global reach. FHA provides a platform for showcasing innovative products, technologies, and solutions from around the world, facilitating connections and business opportunities for trade buyers and sellers.</description></item><item><title>Experience a Festive Showcase of Cultural Treasures at Min Jiang at One-North</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 01:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-festive-showcase-of-cultural-treasures-at-min-jiang-at-one-north/</guid><description>Min Jiang at One-North is the only Chinese eatery located within a 3,000-square-foot, two-story colonial bungalow.
From July 1 to August 31, 2017, Min Jiang at One-North (岷江在纬壹), a Singaporean restaurant specializing in modern Sichuan and Cantonese cuisine, will host &amp;ldquo;A Celebration of Heritage Delights (欢庆怀念佳肴).&amp;rdquo; This event offers patrons a chance to enjoy classic dishes popular in Singapore during the 1960s, 70s, and 80s.
Since 2006, Master Chef Goh Chee Kong (吴志光) has captivated diners with his exquisitely plated dishes.</description></item><item><title>Firebird Diner offers special deals for breakfast and lunch for business customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firebird-diner-offers-special-deals-for-breakfast-and-lunch-for-business-customers/</guid><description>Firebird Diner offers business breakfast and lunch options every weekday.
The Business Breakfast includes a small smoked salmon bagel served with cream cheese and pickled onions, a fresh market greens salad, seasonal fruit, a Greek yogurt parfait with berries, and granola made in-house.
Source: Firebird Diner website. The Business Breakfast.
A three-course Business Lunch is also available. It starts with a kale and fresh citrus salad, followed by a lobster roll, foie gras sliders, and a Philly cheesesteak with a grilled cheese sandwich.</description></item><item><title>Asia will be able to watch a Hong Kong food series on Discovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 21:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-will-be-able-to-watch-a-hong-kong-food-series-on-discovery/</guid><description>Discovery Channel has released a new show, Kung Food! Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Grandmasters of Cuisine. This show delves into the intricate and special world of Hong Kong cuisine from the viewpoint of Michelin-starred chefs.
Source: Discovery Channel. Chef Chaneton of Mono at a market in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong dominates Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants 2021 list with 11 restaurants featured. Chefs David Lai, Guillaume Galliot, Hideaki Sato, Ricardo Chaneton, Richard Ekkebus and Vicky Cheng, all recognized by Asia&amp;rsquo;s 50 Best Restaurants, were chosen to discuss their passion for Hong Kong and illustrate how they craft their culinary masterpieces.</description></item><item><title>Deliveroo predicts future food trends in Asia with "Snack to the Future"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 17:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</guid><description>Deliveroo, a food delivery platform, has released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Snack To The Future Report&amp;rdquo; predicting how technology and evolving consumer habits will shape food consumption patterns in the region by 2040.
The report, developed by Deliveroo in collaboration with Singaporean food specialists Yip Hon Mun and Luke Tay, along with other global experts, identifies emerging food trends driven by technological advancements and changing consumer behaviors. Key predictions include personalized dietary recommendations based on breath analysis (&amp;ldquo;Breath-prints&amp;rdquo;), AI-powered customized diets (&amp;ldquo;Me-ganism&amp;rdquo;), and immersive dining experiences using augmented reality (&amp;ldquo;FOODGASMS&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Japan Food Town provides unique dining experiences in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/japan-food-town-provides-unique-dining-experiences-in-singapore/</guid><description>Japan Food Town: An Authentic Taste of Japan in Singapore [Image of Japan Food Town banner in Wisma Atria with a caption suggesting to take the escalators to the fourth floor]
Opening on July 16, 2016, Japan Food Town promises to bring the genuine flavors of Japanese cuisine to Singapore. Located on the 4th level of Isetan Singapore in Wisma Atria mall, this food hall marks the first in a series of planned Japan Food Town locations worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Introducing a new food tour by Isan Explorer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 21:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-a-new-food-tour-by-isan-explorer/</guid><description>Source: Isan Explorer website.
Isan Explorer, a tour operator specializing in Northeast Thailand, has launched a culinary tour showcasing the cuisine of the lesser-known Isan region.
The day-long tour starts with a visit to a bustling fresh market to gather ingredients for lunch and dinner. Afterward, the tour proceeds to a nearby village.
Participants will enjoy a tasting menu featuring 20 main dishes, such as bamboo shoot curry, sour fish, grilled chicken, steamed mushrooms, green bean salad, and eggplant dipping sauce.</description></item><item><title>A study conducted by Abbott reveals concerning patterns among diabetics in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 22:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-study-conducted-by-abbott-reveals-concerning-patterns-among-diabetics-in-india/</guid><description>Special thosai set.
A recent study, the Abbott Food, Spikes and Diabetes Survey, suggests that 70% of individuals managing diabetes in urban India may not be carefully managing their food intake. This survey, conducted by Ipsos India on behalf of Abbott, involved over 4,100 participants aged 36 to 65 with Type 2 diabetes (diagnosed for over 18 months) from various socioeconomic backgrounds across eight major cities. The study aimed to understand their eating habits, the impact of meals on blood sugar fluctuations, and its effect on diabetes management.</description></item><item><title>2030 Food: Sustainable, Healthier, Personalized</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2030-food-sustainable-healthier-personalized/</guid><description>- Businesses for Good: In the future, successful companies will be those committed to improving the well-being of both the planet and its people.
- Personalized Nutrition: Technological advancements will allow consumers to create highly customized approaches to enhance their physical and mental health.
Source: Mintel.
- Tech-Driven Food Solutions: Consumer confidence in food science and technology will grow as these become essential for securing the food supply. Mintel, a market research firm focused on consumer insights, has identified three significant trends expected to shape the global food, drink, and food service industries in the coming decade:</description></item><item><title>The Creatory weekend festival highlights Singapore's top creative talent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 05:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-creatory-weekend-festival-highlights-singapore-s-top-creative-talent/</guid><description>Source: The Ate Group.
The Ate Group, a Singaporean integrated communications firm, is commemorating its eighth anniversary with CREATORY. This weekend festival spotlights the combined talents of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading creative minds across various disciplines like food, music, art, design, architecture, entertainment, drinks, and retail.
8@ate Productions, a newly established branch of The Ate Group, is producing CREATORY in partnership with Singaporean agencies Ong &amp;amp; Ong Experience Design, Tofu, Hjgher, and Kult.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!</description></item><item><title>Exclusive Mie menus featured at Japan Food Town this December</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-mie-menus-featured-at-japan-food-town-this-december/</guid><description>Japan Food Town is celebrating a &amp;ldquo;Mie Prefecture Fair&amp;rdquo; from December 1st to 7th, 2016, showcasing special menus from over 13 restaurants using ingredients from Mie Prefecture, such as Matsusaka wagyu beef, Ise-ebi lobster, and fresh oysters.
During this limited-time event, visitors can enjoy dishes made with top-grade A4 Matsusaka beef. This highly prized beef, exclusive to Japan Food Town in Singapore, comes from Special Grade Matsusaka Cattle raised in Mie Prefecture under the strict standards of the Matsusaka Cattle Council.</description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey.</description></item><item><title>Eating facai may have negative health effects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eating-facai-may-have-negative-health-effects/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:29:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eating-facai-may-have-negative-health-effects/</guid><description>A vegetarian dish commonly enjoyed during Chinese New Year often features &amp;ldquo;facai&amp;rdquo; fungus, which resembles hair and symbolizes prosperity due to its name sounding like &amp;ldquo;gaining prosperity&amp;rdquo; in Chinese. However, facai, scientifically known as nostoc flagelliforme, is a type of toxic bacteria.
Excessive harvesting led to a ban on facai in China, resulting in most facai today being primarily made from starch. A 2009 study published in Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis revealed that authentic nostoc flagelliforme was rare in commercially available facai, and those genuine samples contained a toxin called beta-N-methylamino-L-alanine (BMAA).</description></item><item><title>The Bazaar Desa buffet at Novotel KL City Centre is a celebration of street food</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 11:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bazaar-desa-buffet-at-novotel-kl-city-centre-is-a-celebration-of-street-food/</guid><description>This Ramadan, enjoy the Bazaar Desa buffet at the Square restaurant in Novotel KL City Centre, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. The buffet is available from June 20th to July 15th and will feature three rotating menus.
Pictured above: grilled squid, the noodle station, an assortment of regional fruits, drinks such as khatirah, peach tea, bandung coconut, sugarcane juice, and sweetcorn juice, and marinated chicken perchik on shawarma.
Executive Chef Huzaidy and their team have designed the Bazaar Desa buffet to showcase the diverse street food culture found throughout Malaysia during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce.</description></item></channel></rss>