<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>E-Book on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-book/</link><description>Recent content in E-Book on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/e-book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bookmate has teamed up with StarHub for its initial launch in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-teamed-up-with-starhub-for-its-initial-launch-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Source: Bookmate. Pictured at the December 17 launch of Bookmate in Singapore are (from left): Simon Dunlop, Bookmate Founder, Andrew Baev, Bookmate Managing Director, and Michael Sim, StarHub Lead Futurist, i3 (Innovation, Investment, Incubation).
Bookmate, a social platform for reading e-books, has launched in Singapore, its initial entry point into the Southeast Asian market. The service offers subscribers unlimited reading for a fixed monthly price, drawing from a library of over half a million e-books provided by 600 publishers.</description></item><item><title>The Kobo eReader ecosystem is now accessible in the GCC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kobo-ereader-ecosystem-is-now-accessible-in-the-gcc-region/</guid><description>Source: Kobo. The Kobo
Aura H2O eReader.
Kobo, the eBook retailer, and distributor Lionfish have announced that Kobo&amp;rsquo;s digital reading platform is launching in the GCC region. This will give readers access to Kobo&amp;rsquo;s eBookstore, which offers over 4.2 million titles. They will also be able to purchase eReaders and apps compatible with iOS, Android, Microsoft, and BlackBerry platforms.
Kobo products will be sold in 34 stores throughout the region.</description></item><item><title>Bookmate has expanded its collection of titles in the English language e-book section</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-expanded-its-collection-of-titles-in-the-english-language-e-book-section/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:49:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bookmate-has-expanded-its-collection-of-titles-in-the-english-language-e-book-section/</guid><description>Bookmate, a subscription service for social e-reading, has broadened its English e-book collection through agreements with several publishers and distributors, including ePubDirect, ProfileBooks, Ingram, Diversion Books, Head of Zeus, Legend Press, and Casemate. This makes Bookmate the first subscription e-reading service outside the US to collaborate with ePubDirect. Notably, the deal with ePubDirect also encompasses Profile/Serpents Tail, Rosetta Books, and Icon Books.
With these partnerships, Bookmate&amp;rsquo;s English selection surpasses 200,000 titles.</description></item></channel></rss>