<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SONET Fiber Optic on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet-fiber-optic/</link><description>Recent content in SONET Fiber Optic on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sonet-fiber-optic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Management Gets Easier With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-management-gets-easier-with-ethernet/</guid><description>The unpredictable nature of bandwidth demand, with its constant fluctuations and potential for rapid growth, presents a challenge for IT managers seeking to balance sufficient resources with cost-effectiveness. Traditional procurement processes, designed for less dynamic times, involve lengthy steps from identifying needs to service activation, making it difficult to adapt quickly to changing bandwidth requirements.
This problem is exacerbated by legacy telecom services like T1 lines or OC connections, which offer fixed bandwidth levels.</description></item><item><title>Improve Cloud Performance With Direct Network Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-cloud-performance-with-direct-network-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many companies are experiencing buyer&amp;rsquo;s remorse after transitioning to the cloud. They expected cost savings, increased performance, and limitless resources, but instead, they&amp;rsquo;re facing performance issues. The problem likely isn&amp;rsquo;t the cloud service itself, but the connection used to access it.
While your current internet connection might be sufficient for tasks like file transfers and email, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for real-time applications like VoIP, video conferencing, or cloud-based software.</description></item><item><title>DS3 and Fractional DS3 Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:43:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-and-fractional-ds3-broadband/</guid><description>Companies seeking to increase bandwidth often consider DS3 bandwidth service. This article explains DS3 and other technologies that provide similar mid-level bandwidth.
DS3, or Digital Signal 3, is a standardized telecom service that uses TDM (Time-Division Multiplexing) technology. To clarify, the fundamental unit is DS0 at 64 Kbps, representing a single digitized phone call. DS1, bundling 24 DS0 channels, operates at 1.5 Mbps and is commonly known as a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>A Dedicated Line Between Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 01:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-dedicated-line-between-offices/</guid><description>Businesses often need to connect multiple offices, whether they are in the same city, different parts of the country, or even internationally. There are several ways to achieve this, each with its own set of advantages.
One traditional method is a dedicated private line, such as a T1 line. These lines offer symmetrical bandwidth, meaning upload and download speeds are equal, which is crucial for business operations that involve heavy data transfer in both directions.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses.</description></item></channel></rss>