<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>5G on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5g/</link><description>Recent content in 5G on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/5g/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces new XO Plus plans powered by 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-xo-plus-plans-powered-by-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:10:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-xo-plus-plans-powered-by-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Singtel&amp;rsquo;s new XO Plus plans come with 5G access, large data packages, and a free three-month subscription to both AR educational materials and live VR music experiences.
Singtel is introducing a new generation of XO plans, bringing customers into the 5G era. These XO Plus plans offer an enhanced mobile experience, featuring the newest 5G phones, data plans up to 150 GB, 5G connectivity, and complimentary three-month subscriptions to Bookful, an augmented reality (AR) educational content platform, and MelodyVR, which provides virtual reality (VR) live music experiences.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>The Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G are both awesome options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-galaxy-a53-5g-and-galaxy-a33-5g-are-both-awesome-options/</guid><description>Source: Samsung. The new Galaxy A series handsets.
Samsung Electronics has released the Galaxy A53 5G and Galaxy A33 5G, incorporating the latest technology to provide a comprehensive mobile experience at an affordable price. These new Galaxy A series phones boast 5G connectivity, robust security features, and a sleek, eco-conscious design. They&amp;rsquo;re powered by a new processor, include Samsung&amp;rsquo;s AI camera, a large, responsive display, and a long-lasting battery.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service.</description></item></channel></rss>