<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quality Report on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/quality-report/</link><description>Recent content in Quality Report on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 13:20:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/quality-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The benefits of reading old, high-quality reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-reading-old-high-quality-reports/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benefits-of-reading-old-high-quality-reports/</guid><description>Occasionally, you might come across an old quality report mentioned in a knowledge base article. Often, these reports seem irrelevant to current issues, having been resolved in past software versions. However, my experience today highlighted how these outdated reports can sometimes provide valuable insights into current problems.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the situation: A client contacted me about duplicate records appearing in their RM30501 (Commission History) table. They handle commissions upon invoice posting, not payment.</description></item><item><title>Issue with Project Accounting Cost Category and Fee ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/issue-with-project-accounting-cost-category-and-fee-id/</guid><description>Last week, a client contacted me with a peculiar problem in Project Accounting. While their actual billings and payments/receipts matched in summary and detail, running the Cash Apply reconciliation (Tools&amp;raquo;Routines&amp;raquo;Project&amp;raquo;PA Reconcile) incorrectly recalculated the payments/receipts as less than the actual billings. This discrepancy, equal to the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee charged on projects, was especially noticeable on projects with a single invoice and payment.
We investigated the database, comparing the &amp;ldquo;FREIGHT&amp;rdquo; fee setup to other fees, but found no differences.</description></item></channel></rss>