<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Equipment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-equipment/</link><description>Recent content in Network Equipment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-equipment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telephone Installers Business Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</guid><description>For businesses selling or installing business telephone systems, there&amp;rsquo;s a valuable networking service to know about. It can provide you with more warm leads and expand your product offerings without any extra cost.
This service is the VAR Partner Network, an online platform run by Telarus, Inc. Telarus is a master agency that works with many different voice and data carriers. But it offers much more than that. Through its VAR Network, Telarus actively connects with businesses seeking not just communication services, but also equipment sales and installation.</description></item><item><title>How Broadband Bonding is Mushrooming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 15:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-broadband-bonding-is-mushrooming/</guid><description>Businesses with high bandwidth demands now have a delicious new option for boosting their WAN capacity thanks to the TRUFFLE from Mushroom Networks, Inc.
What makes the TRUFFLE so appealing? This device can combine the bandwidth of multiple broadband connections – think DSL, Cable, T1, even satellite – to create a single, faster, and more reliable connection, similar to T1 line bonding but with more flexibility. The TRUFFLE BBNA6401 model, for instance, can aggregate up to 6 different connections, reaching download speeds of up to 50 Mbps.</description></item></channel></rss>