<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Twitter on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/twitter/</link><description>Recent content in Twitter on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:39:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/twitter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://i.imgur.com/NhEKjvI.png" alt="Featured image of post How to Get Free Twitter Followers Every Hour Using Toolkity" />Social media presence is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age. Having a robust Twitter following can enhance your online visibility, influence, and credibility. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to grow your Twitter followers without spending a dime, Toolkity offers a simple solution. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps to get free Twitter followers every hour using Toolkity.
Step 1: Visit Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers Page First, head over to Toolkity&amp;rsquo;s Free Twitter Followers page...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-free-twitter-followers-every-hour-using-toolkity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Internet Launches Into Space</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-internet-launches-into-space/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 02:01:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-internet-launches-into-space/</guid><description>The internet has conquered Earth and is now reaching for the stars. While &amp;ldquo;Google ET&amp;rdquo; might be a bit premature, efforts are underway to extend the internet&amp;rsquo;s reach into space.
The initial steps involve using internet technology within Earth&amp;rsquo;s orbit. Eventually, we might be assigning planet and galaxy codes to complement our current country codes. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s explore these initial steps.
Cisco is pioneering the use of routers in orbit through a defense department program called IRIS (Internet Routing In Space)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-internet-launches-into-space/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-internet-launches-into-space/</a></p></description></item><item><title>KKBOX has initiated a Cpop campaign on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 14:47:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</guid><description>Source: Twitter. Screenshot of Tia Ray&amp;rsquo;s tweet.
Twitter and KKBOX, a popular music streaming service in Asia, are collaborating to increase global recognition and appreciation of Chinese pop music, known as Cpop (#Cpop).
To achieve this, KKBOX is developing exclusive Cpop content (#OnlyOnTwitter) for their main Twitter account (@KKBOX). This includes weekly live question and answer sessions with Cpop artists, personalized video messages from Cpop musicians and producers using Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Challenger app, frequent #KKvote contests to encourage international fan participation, and live streams of Cpop concerts and the yearly KKBOX music awards through Periscope (@KKBOXTW)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kkbox-has-initiated-a-cpop-campaign-on-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Twitter has revealed its inaugural collaboration with Singaporean musician @Sezairi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 13:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</guid><description>● #SezairiQA and live songs on Twitter and Periscope @ 6:30pm on August 31, 2016 ● #SezairiLive debut show at Twitter APAC HQ in Singapore @ 7:30pm on September 2, 2016 ● Winners of @Sezairi photo caption contest get free tickets to #SezairiLive event
Singaporean singer Sezairi (@Sezairi) will be performing live (#SezairiLive) on Twitter, Periscope, and at Twitter&amp;rsquo;s Asia Pacific headquarters. The performances follow a pre-listening party (#SezairiPreLP) on Twitter held the previous week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twitter-has-revealed-its-inaugural-collaboration-with-singaporean-musician-sezairi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Down In The Face of Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</guid><description>At the end of 2011, major companies like GoDaddy and Verizon Wireless faced significant public backlash that caused them to reverse recently announced decisions. GoDaddy quickly backpedaled on their support for SOPA after online outrage, while Verizon abandoned their plan to charge a $2 payment fee due to public outcry and potential FCC involvement. These incidents, while seemingly isolated, point to a larger pattern found in other events from the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Twitter Really 75 Years Old?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</guid><description>You might be amazed to discover that the core concept of Twitter predates you, your parents, and possibly even your grandparents.
While Twitter itself wasn&amp;rsquo;t around back then, a similar idea existed. In 1935, London had the &amp;ldquo;Notificator,&amp;rdquo; a robot messenger described by BoingBoing. This public vending machine allowed people to leave notes for friends. Users could write messages on a continuous paper strip, insert a coin, and their message would move up, making room for the next one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Malaysia election, #GE14, generated more than 7.3 million tweets on Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</guid><description>During the short Malaysian election campaign period, over 7.3 million tweets using the hashtags #GE14 and #MalaysiaElection established Twitter as a key platform for political discourse.
On May 9th, election day discussions dominated Twitter in Malaysia, exceeding all other topics. Over 4.2 million #GE14 tweets were sent globally in just 24 hours. The hashtag topped Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s trending list, joined by other politically charged terms like #MalaysiaMemilih and #PakatanHarapan in the top ten...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-malaysia-election-ge14-generated-more-than-7-3-million-tweets-on-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First View is a feature offered by Twitter that allows marketers to use video content for their marketing campaigns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 13:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</guid><description>Twitter Introduces First View Video Ads in Asia Pacific Source: Twitter. How First View works.
Twitter is launching First View in the Asia Pacific region. This feature allows brands to share their stories through video content with Twitter&amp;rsquo;s audience, which, according to Statista, reached 320 million users globally by April 2016.
As the largest and fastest-growing region for Twitter, Asia Pacific presents a significant opportunity for businesses. First View allows any business in the region to elevate their marketing on Twitter&amp;rsquo;s platform, which thrives on real-time public conversations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-view-is-a-feature-offered-by-twitter-that-allows-marketers-to-use-video-content-for-their-marketing-campaigns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrating Social Media And Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</guid><description>We navigate two distinct realms: the digital sphere of communication, online activities, and social media, and the physical world of tangible experiences, relationships, and work. Although these realms overlap, their connection has been tenuous until recently.
Poken has emerged as a solution to bridge this gap between the digital and physical. As expected, it comprises both physical and virtual elements.
The tangible aspect is a device called Poken, resembling a digital avatar or a flash drive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>