<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Headset on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headset/</link><description>Recent content in Headset on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headset/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Evolve 75 is a wireless headset with active noise cancellation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 19:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</guid><description>Jabra designed the new Evolve 75 wireless headset specifically for busy, open office environments. It is the first headset to receive Microsoft Skype for Business&amp;rsquo; Open Office and Outdoor certifications. Notably, it&amp;rsquo;s also the first Evolve headset to combine active noise cancellation and Bluetooth capability.
Source: Jabra. The Evolve 75 in action in an open office.
To expand their Evolve headset range for the modern office worker, Jabra released the wireless Evolve 75...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-evolve-75-is-a-wireless-headset-with-active-noise-cancellation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG has released an updated version of the TONE INIFINIM around-the-neck wireless headset just in time for CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 12:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</guid><description>Source: LG. The TONE INFINIM HBS-910 headsets will debut at CES 2016.
LG Electronics (LG) will introduce its latest LG TONE INFINIM (HBS-910) headsets at CES 2016. The wireless neckband headset boasts a modernized design and exceptional audio quality.
As the next generation of the HBS-900, the new TONE INFINIM retains key features of its predecessor, like retractable earbuds and Harmon/Kardon audio. It also introduces upgraded Quad-Layer Speaker Technology for a top-tier audio experience with enhanced balance across the entire sound spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-released-an-updated-version-of-the-tone-inifinim-around-the-neck-wireless-headset-just-in-time-for-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra is unveiling three new additions to its Elite series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:26:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</guid><description>Jabra introduces the Elite Active 65t (right), Elite 65e (left), and Elite 45e (middle) to the Singapore market.
Jabra is releasing three new products: the Elite Active 65t, Elite 65e, and Elite 45e in Singapore. These devices belong to the Elite family of headphones and earbuds, known for superior music quality and excellent voice capabilities.
The Elite family encompasses various styles like true wireless, headband, neckband, and soft neckband. The suffix &amp;ldquo;e&amp;rdquo; signifies an earbud design, while &amp;ldquo;t&amp;rdquo; indicates true wireless...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-is-unveiling-three-new-additions-to-its-elite-series/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jabra introduces the Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company known for creating intelligent audio devices, has introduced the Jabra Stealth UC Bluetooth mono headset. This new headset is a unified communication (UC) upgrade from their original Jabra Stealth and is designed specifically for professionals who are often on the go.
Weighing in at a mere 0.24 ounces (approximately 6.8 grams), the Jabra Stealth UC is remarkably lightweight, making it both inconspicuous and incredibly easy to carry around...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-introduces-the-stealth-uc-bluetooth-mono-headset/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>