<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mooncake on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mooncake/</link><description>Recent content in Mooncake on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mooncake/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tea Forté Singapore presents three mooncake collections as part of the Autumn in Abundance series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:42:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tea-fort-singapore-presents-three-mooncake-collections-as-part-of-the-autumn-in-abundance-series/</guid><description>Source: Tea Forté.
Tea Forté Singapore, a specialty tea company, has introduced its new Autumn in Abundance mooncake collection, featuring traditional baked mooncakes with reduced sugar, the Creative Infused line, and a special Luxury selection.
The company suggests pairing the traditional mooncakes with its organic white ginger pear tea, the Creative Infused collection with the organic green mango peach tea, and the Luxurious selections with its orchid vanilla tea.</description></item><item><title>Delicious Medallions from Swensen's</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delicious-medallions-from-swensen-s/</guid><description>Swensen&amp;rsquo;s is offering early bird discounts on their chocolate-covered Sweet Medallions mooncakes until September 20th, 2017.
The mooncakes are available in a variety of flavors like cookies &amp;rsquo;n cream surprise, durian royale, Rocher crunch, and sticky chewy chocolate.
Source: Swensen&amp;rsquo;s website. Four chocolate-covered flavours are on offer in Swensen&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017. Place your order to take advantage of the 20% early bird discount available to Swensen&amp;rsquo;s Cool Rewards and Kids&amp;rsquo; Club members.</description></item><item><title>The new snowskin flavors at Goodwood Park are ideal combinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:19:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-snowskin-flavors-at-goodwood-park-are-ideal-combinations/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the Mid-Autumn Festival with new snowskin mooncake flavors that perfectly pair two complementary ingredients. This year, the hotel is even introducing its first-ever chocolate mooncake.
One of the new additions is the Yuzu Lychee Snowskin Mooncake, featuring the bright citrus flavor of yuzu combined with sweet lychee pieces. Another highlight is the limited-edition Dark Chocolate Crunchy Hazelnut Snowskin Mooncake. This decadent treat consists of a crunchy hazelnut chocolate center surrounded by rich dark chocolate mousse, all encased in a snowskin made with crushed vanilla beans and caramel.</description></item><item><title>Bakerzin introduces seven new mooncake collections for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bakerzin-introduces-seven-new-mooncake-collections-for-2017/</guid><description>Bakerzin has introduced its Creme de la Creme mooncake assortment, featuring handcrafted mooncakes made with low-sugar white lotus paste. The collection includes seven distinct lines, available in both traditional baked and snow skin varieties.
[Image of Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s 2017 mooncake collection]
Source: Bakerzin Facebook page. Bakerzin&amp;rsquo;s mooncake collection for 2017.
The Bold Collection showcases baked mooncakes with unique flavors such as American ginseng, ginger, tom yam, and sakura ebi.
The Signature Collection features the return of their popular premium egg yolk blend baked mooncake.</description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar.</description></item><item><title>Would you like to try a mooncake with osmanthus and white lotus?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 03:51:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/would-you-like-to-try-a-mooncake-with-osmanthus-and-white-lotus/</guid><description>For the Mid-Autumn Festival, Hilton Hotel offers a variety of classic baked and contemporary mini snowskin mooncakes.
Baked mooncake choices include white lotus paste, traditional mixed nuts, green tea walnut, and a new osmanthus white lotus flavor. Caramel cheese, lychee chocolate truffle, D24 durian, and black sesame with hazelnut praline are among the snowskin varieties.
Interested?
For a closer look at the selection, view the Hilton mooncake collection brochure (PDF). Mooncakes are available from September 4th to October 4th, 2017.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park introduces new fruit-infused mooncake flavors to its 2017 lineup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 21:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-introduces-new-fruit-infused-mooncake-flavors-to-its-2017-lineup/</guid><description>This mid-autumn, Goodwood Park Hotel is excited to present a selection of new and unique snowskin mooncake flavors. Among the new offerings is the blush pink prickly pear with bergamot snowskin mooncake. This confection features the sweet and succulent fruit of a cactus, complemented by a citrusy bergamot flavor and the crunch of diced pears.
Goodwood Park Hotel will also be bringing back popular snowskin favorites. These include premium durian and tropical fruit varieties alongside traditional baked mooncakes.</description></item><item><title>The Concorde Hotel Singapore is introducing mooncake gift sets in elegant mirror chests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 06:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-concorde-hotel-singapore-is-introducing-mooncake-gift-sets-in-elegant-mirror-chests/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website. Mooncakes from the Concorde Hotel will come in LED mirror chests.
The Concorde Hotel in Singapore is known for its unique mooncake packaging, and this year is no exception. This year, the mooncakes will be presented in a special LED mirror chest that lights up when opened.
Customers can choose from a variety of mooncake flavors, including bamboo charcoal with red dragon fruit and black sesame, golden jade lotus with a single yolk, pure lotus, white lotus, pure lotus with a single yolk, and white lotus with a single yolk.</description></item><item><title>This year, Concorde Hotel is arranging mooncakes in a vertical stack</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website.
For this Mid-Autumn Festival, Concorde Hotel Singapore is offering a selection of classic baked mooncakes. Customers can choose from traditional fillings like pure lotus paste, pure lotus with single or double yolks, and a less sweet white lotus with single yolk. Prices range from S$60 to S$68 for a box of four, including GST. Additionally, they offer a &amp;ldquo;Supreme Manju&amp;rdquo; flavor at S$64 for a box of four.</description></item><item><title>Foh San provides mooncake corporate orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 18:33:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foh-san-provides-mooncake-corporate-orders/</guid><description>Foh San, a restaurant originally known for its dim sum, has become a popular provider of both dim sum and mooncakes. They offer a diverse selection of halal mooncakes, with both baked and non-baked options available. Customers can purchase these mooncakes in elegant presentation boxes designed to hold either two or four mooncakes. Additionally, there is a premium box option which includes four mooncakes and a special gaharu (agarwood or oud) tea.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy introduced black bean mooncakes to their selection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy.
At the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, this Mooncake Festival, indulge in a modern take on classic handmade mooncakes created by Head Chef Lester Wang.
With over 20 flavors, Chef Wang&amp;rsquo;s baked and snowskin mooncakes offer a delightful blend of traditional and contemporary tastes. Popular choices include Jia Wei Durian, Signature Italian Dark Coffee, and Raspberry with Dark Chocolate mooncakes.
This year&amp;rsquo;s selection introduces two new flavors: traditional baked mooncakes with black bean paste and the ‘Ying Yang’ snowskin mooncake, featuring a harmonious blend of white lotus and black bean fillings.</description></item><item><title>Purchase the "liusha" flavored mooncakes from VLV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-the-liusha-flavored-mooncakes-from-vlv/</guid><description>VLV, a multifaceted venue featuring a modern Chinese restaurant, lounge, entertainment courtyard, and riverfront dining, has introduced its mooncake selection for 2017.
The collection showcases two flavors: the lotus paste with salted egg custard liusha mooncake and the white lotus paste black sesame liusha mooncake.
Drawing inspiration from VLV&amp;rsquo;s popular salted egg charcoal bun, Executive Chef Martin Foo has crafted a mooncake version. The lotus paste with salted egg custard liusha mooncake boasts a savory pastry and a smooth lotus paste filling surrounding a creamy, flowing salted egg custard.</description></item><item><title>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport is offering mooncakes in a suitcase</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowne-plaza-changi-airport-is-offering-mooncakes-in-a-suitcase/</guid><description>Crowne Plaza Changi Airport has launched its 2016 mooncake collection, featuring classic baked and contemporary snowskin varieties. These halal-certified treats are packaged in a stylish metal suitcase, making them a great gift for colleagues or loved ones.
For those who prefer a traditional taste, baked mooncakes are available in three flavors: White Lotus Paste with Double Egg Yolk, White Lotus Paste with Single Egg Yolk, and White Lotus Paste with Melon Seeds.</description></item><item><title>Glory mooncakes are available in both traditional and novelty shapes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glory-mooncakes-are-available-in-both-traditional-and-novelty-shapes/</guid><description>Glory Food Products has unveiled its mid-autumn festival collection, featuring a variety of mooncakes in different sizes and shapes. The halal-certified collection includes individually packaged mini mooncakes in unique designs like bears, mice, cats, fish, the Ding Dang cartoon character, and the classic round form, ranging from S$0.50 to S$0.65. For those who prefer a traditional treat, full-sized mooncakes are also available starting at S$4.20, with fillings like lotus paste, single yolk lotus paste, and double yolk lotus paste.</description></item></channel></rss>