<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Protocols on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protocols/</link><description>Recent content in Protocols on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protocols/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 10:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>While your local area network (LAN) might be operating smoothly, connecting to the broader internet for services like dedicated internet access, direct data transfers, or VoIP calls often requires a different approach. T1 lines offer a budget-friendly solution, but they use a different protocol than the Ethernet standard common to many LANs.
Fortunately, modern T1 providers simplify this process with managed routers. These specialized routers are designed to handle the technical aspects of T1 lines, including signal conversion, data framing, and impedance matching...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-t1-to-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How You Can Benefit From Wavelength Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 19:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When requiring robust bandwidth, top-notch security, and adaptable WAN connections, exploring wavelength services might be the solution.
How can you ensure you&amp;rsquo;re getting the optimal bandwidth for your operations? One consideration is choosing between the dedicated point-to-point connections of SONET/SDH and the potentially higher bandwidth of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) at similar costs.
The protocol you need to transport is another factor. Ethernet seamlessly connects with Ethernet WAN services, while SONET/SDH, designed for TDM, can support packet-switched networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-you-can-benefit-from-wavelength-services/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>