<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Oil on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oil/</link><description>Recent content in Oil on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 23:30:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002: From Oil Cleanup to First Operational Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-from-oil-cleanup-to-first-operational-test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 23:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-from-oil-cleanup-to-first-operational-test/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration hit a snag. Although the main board was restored, the presence of rust and corrosion discovered earlier took priority. Addressing rust requires applying neutralizer and paint, which involves drying time between coats, thus delaying the planned reservoir capacitor and output board work.
Images highlighting the most severe rust spots are included.
Despite the significant rust, the turntable&amp;rsquo;s overall condition is good. To combat the rust, three coats of rust neutralizer were applied.</description></item><item><title>Airswift Holdings, a global recruiting company, operates in 57 locations worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 05:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Airswift Holdings. From left, Duncan Gregson, CEO of Air Energi; Janette Marx, COO, Airswift, Ian Langley, Chairman, Airswift; Peter Searle, CEO, Airswift; and Tobias Reed, CEO of Swift Worldwide Resources.
Air Energi Group and Swift Worldwide Resources combined to establish Airswift Holdings, a global staffing company. Airswift specializes in placing contract and permanent employees, providing resource consultation, assisting with global mobility, and developing managed solutions for companies in the energy, process, and infrastructure sectors.</description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>