<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AiO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aio/</link><description>Recent content in AiO on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Pro Series from HP is effective for small and medium-sized businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:29:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pro-series-from-hp-is-effective-for-small-and-medium-sized-businesses/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new line of Pro Series desktops, notebooks, and an all-in-one (AiO) PC tailored for businesses of all sizes, particularly small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the challenges faced by businesses in making technology decisions with limited budgets and IT resources. She emphasized that the HP BusinessNow program aims to provide support and access to solutions like the HP Pro Series.</description></item><item><title>The HP 2 in 1 printer is perfect for home offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hp-2-in-1-printer-is-perfect-for-home-offices/</guid><description>HP has introduced a new PC and printer designed for home offices.
The HP Pavilion x2, available in Singapore starting in October from S$499, offers a stylish and practical solution. This versatile device functions as a 10-inch Windows tablet and easily transforms into a fully functional laptop. It features a detachable magnetic keyboard cover that doubles as both a screen protector and a multi-position stand. Equipped with an Intel Atom processor, the Pavilion x2 boasts front-facing speakers with DTS sound and a battery life of up to 11.</description></item><item><title>HP's Elite business PCs excel in performance, productivity, and security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 22:50:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-s-elite-business-pcs-excel-in-performance-productivity-and-security/</guid><description>HP has introduced its latest Elite business PCs, including the exceptionally thin and light HP EliteBook 705 series, an all-in-one (AiO) model, and a refreshed desktop lineup featuring the world&amp;rsquo;s smallest business-class desktop.
Serena Yong, Managing Director of HP Singapore, highlighted the demand for high-end Elite notebook innovation to be extended to a wider range of employees and devices. HP&amp;rsquo;s response is the Elite 705 and 800 Series PCs, which bring sleek design, enhanced collaboration features, and robust security to mainstream business devices.</description></item><item><title>Dell introduces an improved range of PCs for both consumer and commercial markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 19:11:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-introduces-an-improved-range-of-pcs-for-both-consumer-and-commercial-markets/</guid><description>Dell debuted groundbreaking personal computing innovations at the annual Consumer Electronics Show (CES) in the US. They also updated their XPS, Inspiron, and Alienware consumer lines. Their OptiPlex, Latitude, and Precision commercial products received upgrades to 7th Gen Intel Core processors, USB-C with Thunderbolt 3 connectivity, and new professional graphics from NVIDIA and AMD. Dell&amp;rsquo;s monitor lineup also saw a refresh. The new Dell PC portfolio is equipped with Windows 10 and 7th Gen Intel Core processors, designed to maximize user productivity and creativity.</description></item><item><title>Lenovo introduces new Tiny all-in-one workstations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 18:49:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-introduces-new-tiny-all-in-one-workstations/</guid><description>Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s new TiO features a compact desktop computer (shown on the left) that connects to the back of a 23-inch monitor (on the right). These components can function independently or as a combined unit.
Lenovo introduced workstations and a &amp;lsquo;Tiny-in-one&amp;rsquo; (TiO) as part of its final significant product launch in 2014.
Pictured on the left are Lenovo&amp;rsquo;s latest workstation models.
&amp;ldquo;We carefully considered extensive customer feedback after the recent debut of our P300 workstation,&amp;rdquo; stated Jessie Quek, Lenovo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Country General Manager.</description></item></channel></rss>