<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aviation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aviation/</link><description>Recent content in Aviation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/aviation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emirates reveals updated interiors for its Boeing 777 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:55:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced redesigned interiors for its Boeing 777 fleet, featuring upgraded seats and entertainment systems across all cabins. This multi-million dollar investment reflects the airline&amp;rsquo;s focus on enhancing the customer experience.
The new First Class cabins, designed in collaboration with several firms, offer private suites with sliding doors inspired by Mercedes-Benz S-Class. These suites prioritize comfort and luxury with features like soft leather seats, mood lighting, and ample storage. Retained features include personal minibars and wireless controls for seat adjustment and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-reveals-updated-interiors-for-its-boeing-777-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia and AirAsia X introduce an innovative inflight menu concept</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:38:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia.
AirAsia and AirAsia X have introduced &amp;ldquo;Santan,&amp;rdquo; a new in-flight menu, replacing &amp;ldquo;AirAsia Café.&amp;rdquo; This change aims to elevate the airline group&amp;rsquo;s image and provide travelers with a more sophisticated culinary experience.
Passengers can now purchase or pre-order new menu items, including nasi dagang and chicken curry, a Malaysian dish from the East Coast. Additional on-board purchases on AirAsia flights include teriyaki chicken rice cake and smoked chicken pizza sandwiches...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-and-airasia-x-introduce-an-innovative-inflight-menu-concept/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new premium offerings in First and Business Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 10:47:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced new luxury products for its First and Business Class passengers, partnering with brands like BYREDO, Bowers &amp;amp; Wilkins, and Bulgari to elevate the travel experience.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEgd9y3iVi6anaC1N4Cso7QmgPJovqGEwEKcXCffrreFoqNcy3Bnr-B79U45k6PqBzF2gV2uzc94przcIphwRp2ecePtOYdspt9-PjYc3KQTh976kDvFOItJfkbCCO02xL93YGyDNrANYHYE/s1600/Emirates+byredo+wellness.jpg)
Source: Emirates. The BYREDO for Emirates Wellness kit.
First Class passengers in Emirates&amp;rsquo; private suites will receive a specially designed BYREDO travel wellness kit. This hypoallergenic skincare line, featuring chamomile, was created specifically for Emirates and introduced initially on the airline&amp;rsquo;s new Boeing 777 suites...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-premium-offerings-in-first-and-business-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport Group announces the closure of Terminal 2 for a period of 18 months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Changi Airport.
Due to a significant decrease in air travel and the low likelihood of a return to pre-pandemic levels soon, Changi Airport Group (CAG) has decided to consolidate operations at Changi Airport. This move aims to reduce operating costs like utilities and cleaning for CAG and its partners while optimizing resource allocation across the airport&amp;rsquo;s terminals.
Starting May 1, 2020, Terminal 2 (T2) will halt operations for 18 months, relocating airlines to other terminals*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new, healthier menu choices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has partnered with the Department of Health – Abu Dhabi to introduce Weqaya, a selection of healthy food choices, on flights and in its Abu Dhabi lounges.
Weqaya, meaning &amp;ldquo;prevention&amp;rdquo; in Arabic, is a program created by the Department of Health - Abu Dhabi to encourage healthy and balanced eating habits for improved health and well-being.
Etihad now offers several Weqaya dishes on First and Business Class long-haul and ultra-long-haul flights departing from Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-healthier-menu-choices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hainan Airlines introduces direct flight between Shenzhen and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 11:15:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: Hainan Airlines. Pictured at the Auckland welcoming ceremony are the Consulate General of China in Auckland, Acting Consul General Luo Binhui, Auckland Airport CEO Adrian Littlewood, Hainan Airlines President Sun Jianfeng, and Hainan Airlines&amp;rsquo; VIP customers.
On December 30, 2016, Hainan Airlines launched its inaugural non-stop flight between Shenzhen, China, and Auckland, New Zealand. The new route connects the two cities with an 11-hour flight.
Hainan Airlines will service the Shenzhen-Auckland route with wide-body Airbus A330s, known for their spacious cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-introduces-direct-flight-between-shenzhen-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new sale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates is offering reduced fares to more than 70 locations. Bookings must be made by August 20, 2018, for travel dates between September 1, 2018, and March 31, 2019.
Economy Class fares start at AED945 to Beirut, Lebanon, AED995 to Mumbai, India, and AED2,345 to Bangkok, Thailand. Business Class fares to these destinations cost AED5,245, AED2,795, and AED9,795, respectively.
Travelers can enhance their experience with Emirates Holidays, adding a five-star hotel stay to their trip...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-sale/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Abu Dhabi First Class Lounge &amp; Spa has been opened by Etihad Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has opened a new flagship First Class Lounge &amp;amp; Spa in Terminal 3 of Abu Dhabi International Airport. This space highlights the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to offering exceptional and desirable hospitality.
Inspired by top-tier hotels, private clubs, and fine dining establishments, the lounge provides an exclusive environment. It features unmatched design, style, comfort, world-class dining, and personalized beauty and relaxation services.
The lounge offers 16 distinct zones for guests to unwind, recharge, and enjoy entertainment in complete luxury before their flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-abu-dhabi-first-class-lounge-spa-has-been-opened-by-etihad-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates has prohibited hoverboards and reminds passengers of the approved items for carry-on luggage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates reminds passengers to check before packing, for hassle-free travel this holiday season.
Emirates Airlines is reminding travelers to review the allowed carry-on and checked baggage items for a smooth and secure journey during this holiday period.
To maintain the safety of everyone onboard, loose lithium batteries used in devices like cameras, cell phones, and laptops are not allowed in checked luggage. This includes &amp;ldquo;hoverboards&amp;rdquo; or self-balancing scooters, whether or not the batteries have been removed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-has-prohibited-hoverboards-and-reminds-passengers-of-the-approved-items-for-carry-on-luggage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now offers Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner on flights from Abu Dhabi to Shanghai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:01:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has upgraded its Abu Dhabi to Shanghai route, now offering flights on the Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner. This change increases capacity by 14%, offering 28 business class and 271 economy seats.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Peter Baumgartner, highlighted the significance of the Chinese market, particularly the rising demand from business and leisure travelers. The decision to utilize the Dreamliner reflects Shanghai&amp;rsquo;s status as a major global hub and its importance in Etihad&amp;rsquo;s network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-offers-boeing-787-9-dreamliner-on-flights-from-abu-dhabi-to-shanghai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy a complimentary stay at a luxurious hotel in Doha when you transit overnight with Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 11:42:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Qatar Airways. Doha skyline.
Qatar Airways has teamed up with Qatar Tourism Authority (QTA) to launch a stopover package, aiming to highlight Qatar as a top destination for travelers.
The package allows transit passengers to explore Doha with complimentary luxury hotel stays and transit visas. This unique deal is part of their larger &amp;ldquo;+Qatar&amp;rdquo; campaign, encouraging those passing through to consider extending their trip.
The promotion invites all Qatar Airways transit passengers to include Doha in their travel plans by offering a free one-night stay at some of the country’s top four- and five-star hotels in the capital...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-a-complimentary-stay-at-a-luxurious-hotel-in-doha-when-you-transit-overnight-with-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways introduces more flights on the Abu Dhabi to Doha route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 06:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is commemorating a decade of service to Qatar this year by adding nine weekly flights to its Abu Dhabi-Doha route, strengthening its dedication to this important Gulf market.
Starting August 1, 2016, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s national airline will boost its weekly service to Qatar&amp;rsquo;s capital to 37 flights. These new daily morning and early evening departures on Thursdays and Saturdays offer more flexibility and convenience, catering to business travelers in both Abu Dhabi and Doha...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-introduces-more-flights-on-the-abu-dhabi-to-doha-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will begin flying between Okinawa and Japan in January 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 01:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will launch its inaugural charter flights between Singapore and Okinawa, Japan.
Operated in partnership with Okinawa Tourist Service (OTS) and Jumbo Tours Okinawa, these monthly charters will run from September 9, 2014, to January 3, 2015. Utilizing Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both business and economy class seating, these direct flights aim to provide travelers with a convenient option to visit Okinawa.
From September to October 2014, flights will depart Singapore Changi Airport Terminal 2 at 10:00 am and arrive at Okinawa Naha Airport at 4:15 pm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-begin-flying-between-okinawa-and-japan-in-january-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Arabia has opened a new sales office in Dubai and has also introduced city check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 15:36:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</guid><description>Air Arabia, a leading low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa, has expanded its presence in Dubai, UAE, by opening a new sales office and city terminal check-in facility.
Adel Al Ali, Group CEO of Air Arabia, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to enhancing customer experience and convenience across its network. He emphasized the significance of the new sales office in strengthening their services in Dubai and the UAE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-arabia-has-opened-a-new-sales-office-in-dubai-and-has-also-introduced-city-check-in-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asiana discontinues codeshare agreement with US Airways, impacting flights to Japan and the United States</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 13:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</guid><description>Asiana Airlines will end its codeshare agreement with US Airways on March 30, 2014. Passengers are advised to review their flight reservations. The affected routes are listed below:
Asiana Airlines flights
Japan
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Fukuoka, Osaka, Nagoya, Okinawa, and Shizuoka
America
Seoul (Incheon) to/from Los Angeles, San Francisco, Seattle, Chicago, New York, and Honolulu
US Airways flights
America
Los Angeles to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia San Francisco to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Seattle to/from Charlotte, Phoenix, and Philadelphia Chicago to/from Atlanta, Orlando, Indianapolis, Columbus, Cleveland, and Houston...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asiana-discontinues-codeshare-agreement-with-us-airways-impacting-flights-to-japan-and-the-united-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir expands its route network to include Laos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, has started its first flights to Vientiane and Luang Prabang in Laos. This addition expands SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s network to 51 destinations across 14 countries.
The inaugural flight left Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport at 1:20 PM on October 31st and arrived at Vientiane’s Wattay International Airport at 3:15 PM. The same flight continued on to Luang Prabang International Airport at 4:05 PM, landing at 5:00 PM. The return flight from Luang Prabang departed at 5:50 PM and arrived back in Singapore at 10:05 PM (all times local)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-route-network-to-include-laos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gulf Air reveals its summer 2018 schedule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air. Plane in Gulf Air livery.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has launched its Summer 2018 schedule, increasing both flight frequency and passenger capacity to popular destinations for the peak travel season between mid-June and mid-September 2018.
Flights to Amman, Jordan, will increase to three times daily, while flights to Beirut, Lebanon, will increase to twice daily. Istanbul, Turkey, a popular summer destination, will have 12 weekly flights during peak season, and flights to Baghdad, Iraq, will permanently increase to five times per week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces new flights to Istanbul's Sabiha Gokcen Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 01:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</guid><description>Emirates now offers 18 flights to Istanbul every week, including a new daily service to Sabiha Gökçen Airport in addition to its existing flights to Istanbul Atatürk Airport. This makes Istanbul the third city after London and Tokyo to be served by Emirates from two airports. The new daily flight is operated with an Airbus A330-200, offering 12 First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 183 Economy Class seats, and also provides up to 12 tonnes of cargo capacity each way...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-new-flights-to-istanbul-s-sabiha-gokcen-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cathay Pacific has chosen Hertz as its sole car rental service provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 18:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</guid><description>Hertz Global is now the sole car rental provider for Cathay Pacific, an international airline based in Hong Kong. To streamline the rental process, Hertz created a dedicated website for Cathay Pacific travelers, offering a wide array of vehicles and deals at approximately 10,000 global locations. Furthermore, Cathay Pacific passengers will automatically receive a 5% discount on Hertz car rentals worldwide.
This agreement expands on the existing partnership between Hertz and Asia Miles, Cathay Pacific&amp;rsquo;s frequent flyer program...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cathay-pacific-has-chosen-hertz-as-its-sole-car-rental-service-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will enhance Singapore Airlines' offerings to Male</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 07:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</guid><description>Source: SilkAir. Male.
Starting October 25, 2015, SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will introduce four weekly flights to Male, Maldives. Previously, Singapore Airlines operated between 10 and 14 flights per week to Male. With the addition of SilkAir&amp;rsquo;s new flights, the two airlines will jointly offer two daily round trips, pending regulatory approval.
Lee Wen Fen, Singapore Airlines’ Senior Vice President of Marketing Planning, highlighted the benefits of this collaboration: “By coordinating the networks of both carriers, we can provide our customers with more choices and flexibility when planning their travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-enhance-singapore-airlines-offerings-to-male/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China have partnered on a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 21:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Hawaiian Airlines and Air China, China&amp;rsquo;s national airline, have partnered to provide travelers with expanded options and easier connections. This agreement comes after Hawaiian launched its new non-stop service to Beijing, operating three times a week.
&amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to collaborate with Air China to expand our reach beyond Beijing, allowing our customers to conveniently explore more Chinese cities with a single ticket from Honolulu,&amp;rdquo; said Mark Dunkerley, Hawaiian Airlines President and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawaiian-airlines-and-air-china-have-partnered-on-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>West Air's inaugural international route links Chongqing with Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 08:31:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. A West Air aircraft.
Changi Airport welcomed a new airline, West Air, which launched its first international route from Chongqing, China.
West Air, headquartered in Chongqing, will fly between Singapore and the Western Chinese city three times a week. The airline will utilize an Airbus A320-200 with a capacity of 180 seats for this route. This new service marks West Air&amp;rsquo;s first venture into the international market and stems from a 2016 agreement to boost air travel between Singapore and Chongqing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/west-air-s-inaugural-international-route-links-chongqing-with-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury hotel to cater to Sydney airport guests</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 05:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</guid><description>Accor, the largest hotel operator in Australia, will be a part of a new multi-use development project in Mascot, near the Sydney Airport. The project will include a hotel, commercial space, and retail areas.
Accor signed an agreement with Goodman to oversee a 5-star hotel, named Pullman Sydney Airport, as part of a new A$100 million development. This project will also include office and retail space. Pullman, the biggest upscale hotel network in the Asia Pacific, has over 45 hotels in the area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-hotel-to-cater-to-sydney-airport-guests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>US airlines may now reject your standard carry-on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</guid><description>According to George Hobica from Airfarewatchdog, several US airlines have reduced the allowed size for carry-on luggage.
Traveling Hello Kitty statue at Taoyuan Airport,
Taiwan in 2008.
American, Delta, and United Airlines now permit carry-on bags with a maximum size of 22 inches in length, 14 inches in width, and 9 inches in height. The previous allowed width was 15 inches.
A Yahoo article from March highlighted United Airlines&amp;rsquo; stricter enforcement of carry-on size regulations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-airlines-may-now-reject-your-standard-carry-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Airport consolidates early check-in services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Travelers departing from Singapore have increased access to early check-in services for various airlines at Changi Airport. Since the beginning of the year, shared early check-in counters have been established in Terminals 2 and 3. Terminal 1 features a dedicated early check-in lounge for added convenience.
Operational from 6 am to midnight, the counters and lounge offer a centralized service point for passengers flying with 23 participating airlines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-consolidates-early-check-in-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces the Dreamliner to Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has started using Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners for flights to Perth, Australia. These planes provide passengers with larger windows, improved air quality, spacious storage, and advanced technology for a more comfortable journey.
Flight EY486, the first Dreamliner flight, arrived in Perth on June 2nd and was greeted with a water cannon salute. This daily service replaces the Airbus A330-200, increasing capacity by 14%, with Business Class seating up by 27%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet has teamed up with Apex Air to provide private jet travel services in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</guid><description>VistaJet, a provider of luxury long-range private jet travel, announced that Apex Air, a business jet operator authorized by the Civil Aviation Administration of China (CAAC), will oversee and operate a fleet of aircraft based in China for VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s Flight Solution Program.
VistaJet is prepared to offer point-to-point service within China as early as the third quarter of 2015 with its first Chinese-registered aircraft, a Bombardier1 Challenger 8501. Chinese customers will also have access to VistaJet&amp;rsquo;s fleet of over 50 large-cabin, long-range Bombardier Challenger and Global aircraft for international flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-has-teamed-up-with-apex-air-to-provide-private-jet-travel-services-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces A380 flights connecting Abu Dhabi and Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, will begin operating its Airbus A380 aircraft between Abu Dhabi and Mumbai starting May 1, 2016. This comes after the successful introduction of the A380 on routes to Sydney and, beginning in June 2016, Melbourne.
The airline&amp;rsquo;s 496-seat A380, based in Abu Dhabi, offers 50% more seating capacity than the Boeing B777-300ER it is replacing. This allows Etihad to provide more travel options and boost tourism between India, the US, and Abu Dhabi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-a380-flights-connecting-abu-dhabi-and-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, Etihad will assume control of Virgin's Sydney-Abu Dhabi slots</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</guid><description>Etihad Airways will increase flights between Abu Dhabi and Sydney to twice daily starting February 6, 2017. Flights EY450 departing Abu Dhabi in the morning and EY451 departing Sydney in the afternoon will now operate seven days a week.
This schedule change coincides with strategic partner Virgin Australia&amp;rsquo;s move to shift its Abu Dhabi operations from Sydney to Perth, effective June 9, 2017. Etihad Airways will expand its current codeshare agreement with Virgin Australia to include their new tri-weekly Perth-Abu Dhabi flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Idealo has developed a flight price comparison portal for India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:43:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</guid><description>Source: idealo India website.
Idealo, a company specializing in price comparison, has expanded its services to India. With fourteen successful price comparison websites globally, idealo already helps numerous travelers find the best flight deals. The company proudly launched its fifteenth website, flights.idealo.in, in 2015.
Indian customers can now compare prices on thousands of flights from various online travel agencies and airlines, all without any cost. Idealo&amp;rsquo;s platform features offers from both budget-friendly and high-end airlines, encompassing one-way and round-trip journeys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idealo-has-developed-a-flight-price-comparison-portal-for-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad updates baggage policy and fare structure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
The national airline of the United Arab Emirates, Etihad Airways, is rolling out a new, clearer fare system starting September 14, 2015. This system aims to offer travelers more choices when booking their flights.
Eight new &amp;ldquo;Fare Choices&amp;rdquo; will be introduced, allowing travelers to customize their bookings to fit their needs. These transparent Fare Choices come with different baggage allowances, levels of flexibility, and included benefits that previously needed to be purchased separately...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-updates-baggage-policy-and-fare-structure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flightleaders.com will enhance its programs in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:50:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</guid><description>Source: Flightleaders.com website. An aircraft cockpit.
Flightleaders.com, an aviation-inspired leadership training provider and part of the McGallen &amp;amp; Bolden Group, intends to expand its program offerings throughout 2018.
Dr. Seamus Phan, a Leadership Trainer with Flightleaders.com specializing in corporate leadership and philosophical approaches, believes corporate training will be highly sought after due to generational gaps in the workplace. He argues this need goes beyond technological advancements and other disruptive trends, as managing people and leadership will remain critical challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flightleaders-com-will-enhance-its-programs-in-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new route connecting Dubai with Yinchuan and Zhengzhou</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 14:07:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</guid><description>Emirates airline is increasing its commitment to China by starting a new service from Dubai to Yinchuan and Zhengzhou, two rapidly developing cities in Midwest China. This addition brings Emirates&amp;rsquo; total destinations in mainland China to five, including existing service to Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangzhou.
Source; Emirates. Emirates&amp;rsquo; Chairman and Chief Executive, HH Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, along with other company executives and a delegation of UAE business leaders, were on the inaugural flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-route-connecting-dubai-with-yinchuan-and-zhengzhou/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad transforms new aircraft into a luxurious boutique hotel experience in the sky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has completely redesigned the future of air travel for first, business, and economy classes. These new designs will be featured on their Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft, which are expected to be delivered later this year.
Five years in development, the airline&amp;rsquo;s design goal was to bring the personalized and exclusive experience of a luxury boutique hotel to air travel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-transforms-new-aircraft-into-a-luxurious-boutique-hotel-experience-in-the-sky/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir will be operating SIA flights SQ466 and SQ467 to Colombo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</guid><description>Starting April 8, 2017, SilkAir, the regional branch of Singapore Airlines (SIA), will begin flights to Colombo, the commercial hub of Sri Lanka and a diverse city home to a large population.
SilkAir will take over flights SQ466/SQ467, offering three weekly flights to Colombo. SIA will maintain its daily nighttime service, operating flights SQ468 and SQ469. Adding SilkAir to the Singapore-Colombo route allows the SIA Group to optimize resource allocation and better match capacity with demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-will-be-operating-sia-flights-sq466-and-sq467-to-colombo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates now offers a total of seven daily flights between Dubai and Bangkok</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 19:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Emirates will introduce a seventh daily flight between Dubai and Bangkok to accommodate rising passenger numbers. This will make Bangkok a top destination for Emirates, equal to Kuwait and Doha.
This new Boeing 777-300ER service will bring the total weekly flights to 49, increasing weekly seat capacity by 2,520 and cargo capacity by 134 tonnes each way. This addition complements the existing four daily A380 and two daily 777 flights, boosting travel and trade between Thailand and Emirates&amp;rsquo; global network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-now-offers-a-total-of-seven-daily-flights-between-dubai-and-bangkok/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Complimentary stopovers offered to Etihad Economy Class passengers traveling from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is offering a complimentary one-night stay at the Radisson Blu hotel on Abu Dhabi’s Yas Island. This offer is open to Economy Class passengers flying from the Middle East, Africa, and Pakistan who have a layover in Abu Dhabi.
Mohammad Al Bulooki, Etihad Airways Executive VP Commercial, expressed the airline&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for showcasing Abu Dhabi to its guests. He highlighted the diverse attractions of the UAE capital, ranging from cultural landmarks and beaches to sports and adventure activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/complimentary-stopovers-offered-to-etihad-economy-class-passengers-traveling-from-the-middle-east-africa-and-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JAL's Japan Explorer Pass simplifies travel in Japan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</guid><description>Japan Airlines (JAL) now offers the Japan Explorer Pass, a convenient and affordable fare option for visitors from outside Japan, as well as Japanese citizens residing abroad, to explore various destinations within the country.
Travelers can easily purchase economy class tickets online, adhering to the following guidelines:
Domestic flights operated by JAL and JTA (Japan Transocean Air) can be booked up to 72 hours before the scheduled departure, even if the traveler is already in Japan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jal-s-japan-explorer-pass-simplifies-travel-in-japan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A trial for FAST check-in has been introduced by Changi Airport, Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 22:53:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</guid><description>A new Fast and Seamless Travel (FAST) check-in trial is currently underway at Changi Airport Terminal 2 for passengers flying with Singapore Airlines and SilkAir. This collaborative effort between Changi Airport Group (CAG), Singapore Airlines, and SilkAir will gradually introduce a comprehensive suite of FAST options throughout 2016. These options aim to provide passengers with more check-in choices and potentially faster processing times through automated kiosks and bag drops. Terminal 3 will also see the addition of 24 kiosks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-trial-for-fast-check-in-has-been-introduced-by-changi-airport-singapore-airlines-and-silkair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vietjet's SkyBoss enhances the premium customer experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 14:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet.
Vietjet now offers SkyBoss, a premium travel class. SkyBoss passengers receive priority check-in, a 20kg checked baggage allowance, priority seat selection, airport lounge access, in-flight meals, extra legroom, and flexible flight date and time changes.
Established in 2011, Vietjet Air is Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s first privately held airline. Since its inception, Vietjet has served over 12 million passengers across 32 domestic and international routes. The airline currently operates two daily flights between Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi International Airport and Ho Chi Minh City&amp;rsquo;s Tan Son Nhat International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vietjet-s-skyboss-enhances-the-premium-customer-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ANA has developed an app to assist passengers in relaxing and diverting their attention away from takeoff</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 12:37:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</guid><description>Source: App Store.
All Nippon Airways (ANA), a major Japanese airline, developed an app to alleviate stress during the most anxiety-inducing part of air travel. Based on a survey of US airline passengers revealing that takeoff causes the most anxiety (68%), ANA created &amp;ldquo;ANA Takeoff Mode.&amp;rdquo; This mobile app aims to help travelers relax and focus on something other than takeoff.
The app presents a simple puzzle accompanied by calming music...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ana-has-developed-an-app-to-assist-passengers-in-relaxing-and-diverting-their-attention-away-from-takeoff/</a></p></description></item><item><title>British Airways assures that flying is safe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</guid><description>Source: British Airways. Doyle.
In his initial address after becoming British Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Sean Doyle stated that the airline believes flying poses a minimal health risk. He cited data from IATA suggesting only 44 COVID-19 cases have been linked to flights since early 2020, while 1.2 billion passengers traveled during that time.
During his speech at Airlines 2050: Beyond the Crisis, Doyle emphasized, &amp;ldquo;Ensuring the safety of our customers and crew remains our top priority, and we&amp;rsquo;re implementing all necessary safety protocols to protect them...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet access is available during flights on China Eastern Airlines and Skymark Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</guid><description>Source: Panasonic Avionics.
Both China Eastern Airlines (CEA) and Skymark Airlines, Japan&amp;rsquo;s third-largest airline, are now offering passengers broadband internet access on flights, utilizing technology from Panasonic Avionics.
CEA&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft equipped with this in-flight WiFi, specifically designed to meet China&amp;rsquo;s requirements, is an Airbus A330. Initially, the plane is dedicated to routes between Shanghai and Beijing, allowing government bodies to assess the service before granting full approval for expansion to other domestic and international routes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-access-is-available-during-flights-on-china-eastern-airlines-and-skymark-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three new routes have been announced by Air Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</guid><description>AirAsia is expanding its network in Indonesia and the Philippines with three new routes starting on March 27th. The airline will now offer flights from Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia to Pontianak, Indonesia, from Johor Bahru, Malaysia to Medan, Indonesia, and from Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia to Cebu, Philippines.
The Indonesian routes will operate twice a week, while the Kota Kinabalu to Cebu route, operated by AirAsia Zest, will operate four times a week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-new-routes-have-been-announced-by-air-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates operates flights with the A380 aircraft to Taipei</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced its flagship A380 aircraft to Taipei, making it the sole airline offering A380 service to the city. This expansion caters to the growing demand on the Dubai-Taipei route and the popularity of the A380 among passengers.
Source: Emirates. The inaugural A380 flight from Dubai touched down in Taipei at 4:50 PM local time on May 1st. Since its launch as a daily Boeing 777 service in February 2014, the route has transported nearly 450,000 passengers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-operates-flights-with-the-a380-aircraft-to-taipei/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China and Kunming Airlines have initiated a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Source: Air China. The image shows representatives from Air China and Kunming Airlines at a signing ceremony for a codeshare agreement on September 3.
Air China and Kunming Airlines launched a codeshare partnership on September 15, 2014.
This agreement allows the airlines to link their respective networks through the city of Kunming. Air China will place its &amp;ldquo;CA&amp;rdquo; code on 26 Kunming Airlines routes, encompassing nearly 500 weekly flights. This expands Air China&amp;rsquo;s reach to various cities within Yunnan province and its neighboring areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-and-kunming-airlines-have-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and Changi Airport Group have decided to extend the Changi Transit Programme</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 03:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group.
Singapore Airlines (SIA) and Changi Airport Group (CAG) have prolonged their partnership program, offering rewards to SIA and SilkAir passengers traveling through Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Changi Airport.
Until March 31, 2017, passengers with connecting flights on SIA and/or SilkAir at Changi Airport can receive a Changi Dollar Voucher (CDV). The voucher&amp;rsquo;s value, either S$20 or S$40, depends on the traveler&amp;rsquo;s origin.
Foo Chai Woo, SIA’s Divisional Vice President Sales &amp;amp; Marketing, highlighted the benefit of SIA’s extensive route network combined with Changi Airport’s offerings for global travelers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-changi-airport-group-have-decided-to-extend-the-changi-transit-programme/</a></p></description></item><item><title>World Business Class flights departing from Amsterdam on KLM will now offer meals created by renowned three-star chef Jacob Jan Boerma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 22:46:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</guid><description>Source: KLM. Boerma.
Beginning October 25, 2015, KLM Royal Dutch Airlines will feature meals from three-star Michelin chef Jacob Jan Boerma in their World Business Class on flights departing from Amsterdam*. As the first chef to partner with KLM for an entire year, Boerma brings a unique touch to their in-flight dining experience.
Miriam Kartman, KLM&amp;rsquo;s Executive Vice President of Inflight Services, expressed their pride in collaborating with another Michelin-starred chef...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/world-business-class-flights-departing-from-amsterdam-on-klm-will-now-offer-meals-created-by-renowned-three-star-chef-jacob-jan-boerma/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir have reduced their fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 04:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines and SilkAir, its regional subsidiary, have reduced their fuel surcharges due to decreasing fuel prices.
These new surcharge amounts apply to flights from both airlines and range from US$5 to US$83 lower per one-way trip, depending on the flight distance and class of travel.
Route Surcharge in US$* First Class, Suites Between Singapore and South East Asian gateways[1] 50 Between Singapore and Europe/South Africa[2] 175 Between Singapore and Americas 235 Between Europe and Australia/New Zealand[3] 265 All other flights[4] 131 * Figures in US Dollars, converted into currency of sale at time of ticketing..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-and-silkair-have-reduced-their-fuel-surcharges/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad launches exclusive city-inspired Business Class amenities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Airways.
Etihad Airways has introduced new limited-edition amenity kits for their Business Class travelers. This launch is a collaboration between the airline and the luxury travel brand LUXE City Guides, a company known for its sophisticated travel guides. The kits reflect Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; elegant brand and include in-flight amenities and natural facial products. These products were specially created by Scaramouche + Fandango, a London-based skincare and grooming company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-launches-exclusive-city-inspired-business-class-amenities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etiqa has introduced the first-ever complimentary inflight insurance for travelers from Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 09:01:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</guid><description>The first complimentary in-flight insurance plan in Singapore offers up to S$50,000 in personal accident coverage.
For an added S$4, travelers can purchase coverage for flights delayed by three hours or more.
Claims can be paid out instantly through PayNow.
Etiqa, an online insurance provider based in Singapore, has introduced the nation&amp;rsquo;s first complimentary in-flight insurance for travelers. The company also launched a flight delay add-on for S$4, enabling travelers to receive compensation for flights delayed by three consecutive hours, which is a lower threshold compared to the industry average of six to twelve hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etiqa-has-introduced-the-first-ever-complimentary-inflight-insurance-for-travelers-from-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates outlines guidelines for travel to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 09:07:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</guid><description>Emirates airlines has shared that its flights to and from the Bangkok, Thailand airport are still running on schedule. However, due to anticipated heavy traffic, travelers are advised to give themselves extra time to get to the airport.
[Image of Emirates counter area at Changi Airport in Singapore]
The airline recommends checking flight statuses on emirates.com before heading to the airport.
For passengers with Emirates or Skywards tickets issued on or before May 22, 2014, for travel to or from Bangkok (BKK) or Phuket (HKT) between May 22 and May 29, 2014, the airline is offering flexibility...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-outlines-guidelines-for-travel-to-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover Emirates aircraft in 3D</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 10:06:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates pioneers VR experience on its website.
Emirates has become the first airline to use web-based virtual reality (VR) technology. They&amp;rsquo;ve added 3D seat models to emirates.com.
This 3D model shows a 360-degree view of the inside of their A380 and Boeing 777 aircraft. It allows customers to view the Economy, Business, and First Class cabins, as well as the onboard lounge and shower spa on the A380...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-emirates-aircraft-in-3d/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Korean Air provides a direct flight between Seoul and Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 19:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</guid><description>Korean Air has launched new daily nonstop flights between George Bush Intercontinental Airport (IAH) in Houston and Incheon International Airport in Seoul.
Source: Korean Air. The first 777-200 aircraft arrives in Houston on May 2.
John Jackson, Korean Air&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of Passenger Marketing and Sales for the Americas, stated: &amp;ldquo;We see significant opportunities here and are both proud and excited to join Houston&amp;rsquo;s vibrant business community.&amp;rdquo;
These nonstop flights will depart daily from Terminal D at George Bush Intercontinental Airport at 10:40 am CST, with return flights leaving Seoul at 9:10 am local time from Incheon International Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/korean-air-provides-a-direct-flight-between-seoul-and-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Four Seasons Private Jet offers a luxurious flying experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</guid><description>Source: Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts.
Luxury hospitality company Four Seasons Hotels and Resorts has launched the Four Seasons Private Jet, signifying a major shift in luxury travel. This offering highlights the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to exceeding the evolving desires of modern luxury travelers.
Every aspect of the private jet journey, both in flight and on the ground, has been redesigned through the Four Seasons perspective to provide a fully immersive experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-four-seasons-private-jet-offers-a-luxurious-flying-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates provides appealing packages for stopovers in Dubai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai&amp;rsquo;s skyline, featuring the Burj Khalifa on the right.
Travelers flying with Emirates can benefit from appealing Dubai packages. These packages offer special prices at top-rated hotels and include access to entertainment options like city shows and attractions*.
Starting from US$49 per night, based on double occupancy, visitors can experience Dubai at the Rove Dubai Marina, located in the city&amp;rsquo;s vibrant waterfront area. This package also includes two tickets to Dubai Parks and Resorts, the region&amp;rsquo;s most extensive integrated theme park destination, encompassing MOTIONGATE Dubai, BOLLYWOOD PARKS Dubai, LEGOLAND Dubai, and LEGOLAND Water Park...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-appealing-packages-for-stopovers-in-dubai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad provides a wider range of choices for Mediterranean travel destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 17:06:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, is increasing the number and capacity of flights to Athens, Greece, and Larnaca, Cyprus.
Peter Baumgartner, Etihad Airways Chief Commercial Officer, stated that the new flights to Athens will offer travelers two different departure times to and from Abu Dhabi. The additional flights to Larnaca will provide more options and flexibility, as well as enhanced connectivity through Abu Dhabi.
He added that these additions will support business and leisure travel growth through Abu Dhabi and offer travelers a wider choice of destinations in the Gulf region, Indian Subcontinent, Asia, and Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-provides-a-wider-range-of-choices-for-mediterranean-travel-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air France enhances first class experience with new La Première cabins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 07:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</guid><description>Air France launched its new La Première cabin on January 12th, debuting on flight AF254 traveling from Paris-Charles de Gaulle to Singapore and Jakarta. This move emphasizes the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing top-tier products and services to its Southeast Asian clientele. Starting in February 2015 and continuing through the winter season, these new cabins will be offered on all daily flights to Singapore and Jakarta.
Source: Air France website.
Frédéric Gagey, Air France&amp;rsquo;s Chairman and CEO, stated: &amp;ldquo;Our objective with the new La Première suites is to offer the absolute best in the market, and that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re showcasing today...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-france-enhances-first-class-experience-with-new-la-premi-re-cabins/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China has initiated a codeshare agreement with China Express</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</guid><description>Air China, the national airline of China and a major carrier between China and Europe/US, has partnered with China Express, a regional airline based in Guiyang, starting September 1st. Air China&amp;rsquo;s network covers 162 destinations across 32 countries and regions.
Source: Air China. The agreement was formalized in Guiyang, Guizhou on August 29, 2014.
This agreement will link the cities of Chongqing, Guiyang, and Dalian through the airlines&amp;rsquo; networks. Air China already operates over 50 routes to these areas, including most Chinese provincial capitals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-has-initiated-a-codeshare-agreement-with-china-express/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces a mobile site in Arabic language</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced an Arabic version of its mobile website. This platform allows customers to book flights, check in online, upgrade their travel class, and access and download Apple Passbook boarding passes directly to their smartphones, regardless of the language they use on the Emirates mobile site.
The Arabic mobile platform has been launched concurrently in 15 countries across the Middle East and North Africa, including the UAE, Bahrain, Iraq, Jordan, Kuwait, Lebanon, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Egypt, Morocco, and Sudan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-a-mobile-site-in-arabic-language/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad and Fiji Airways establish codeshare partnership</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</guid><description>Fiji Airways and Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, have established an interline agreement. This partnership enables both airlines to sell tickets to and from a wider range of destinations. Passengers can now travel between 17 cities in the Middle East, 29 cities in Asia, and three cities in Australia to and from Fiji, along with other destinations.
James Hogan, President and CEO of Etihad Airways, expressed enthusiasm for the partnership, stating that Fiji is an excellent vacation destination and enhances Etihad&amp;rsquo;s global network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-and-fiji-airways-establish-codeshare-partnership/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Used cooking oil fuels 1,000 km flight in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:55:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</guid><description>A Hainan Airlines flight recently completed a journey of over 1,000 km from Shanghai to Beijing using a blend of conventional jet fuel and biofuel made from recycled cooking oil. The Boeing 737-800 aircraft, carrying over 100 passengers, was powered by a 50/50 mix of biofuel, produced by Sinopec using waste oil from Chinese restaurants, and standard petroleum fuel.
Sustainable biofuel is gaining traction in the aviation industry for its potential to significantly reduce carbon emissions (by 50-80%) compared to traditional fuels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/used-cooking-oil-fuels-1-000-km-flight-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces the first non-stop flight between Bali and Auckland that operates year-round</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 05:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</guid><description>Emirates has introduced a new daily flight route connecting Dubai, UAE to Auckland, New Zealand, with a stop in Bali, Indonesia. This decision comes as a response to the growing popularity of Bali as a travel destination and aims to enhance connectivity options for travelers flying to New Zealand.
This addition brings the total number of daily Emirates flights to New Zealand to three. It complements the existing non-stop daily Airbus A380 service from Dubai to Auckland and another daily A380 service from Dubai to Christchurch, New Zealand, which includes a stopover in Sydney, Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-the-first-non-stop-flight-between-bali-and-auckland-that-operates-year-round/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take advantage of the week-long Vietjet promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet website.
Vietjet Aviation Joint Stock Company (Vietjet), an airline with 32 domestic and international routes, is offering a limited-time promotion with 500,000 discounted tickets. This offer is valid for one week, ending on Wednesday, July 29th, 2015.
The promotion applies to all of Vietjet&amp;rsquo;s current domestic and international routes for travel between September 7th, 2015 and December 31st, 2015. Discounted fares will be displayed in a separate column during booking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates offers passengers complimentary or heavily discounted in-flight Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 05:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates provides complimentary* Wi-Fi on a significant portion of its fleet, currently 106 aircraft, and is continuously expanding this service. Passengers on ultra long-haul flights (flights exceeding 14 hours) frequently utilize this service, with over 30% connecting to Wi-Fi.
All 59 Airbus A380s and 47 Boeing 777s in Emirates&amp;rsquo; fleet offer Wi-Fi connectivity. A majority of these aircraft provide the first 10MB of data free of charge, allowing passengers to update social media or use messaging apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-offers-passengers-complimentary-or-heavily-discounted-in-flight-wi-fi/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Budget airline flyadeal plans to extend its reach to more destinations in the Middle East in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s new low-cost airline, flyadeal, was officially launched on August 23 at King Abdulaziz International Airport in Jeddah. The event showcased flyadeal&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft, named &amp;ldquo;Al-Nayyir&amp;rdquo; (meaning &amp;ldquo;bright star&amp;rdquo;), which arrived from the Airbus delivery center in Hamburg, Germany.
Source: flyadeal. The budget airline flyadeal was inaugurated at a ceremony on August 24. The airline’s colors – a distinct palette of purple and lime – was on full display at the delivery event, along with members of the cabin crew, which gave guests a tour of the unique features onboard...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vistara, a new airline, launches in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</guid><description>Tata SIA Airlines Limited (TSAL) revealed &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; as the name for its new airline on August 11th. This announcement follows a September 2013 agreement between Tata Sons and Singapore Airlines to create a new Indian airline, aiming to further boost air travel demand.
Source: Twitter. The Vistara logo was unveiled on Twitter and Facebook.
The name &amp;ldquo;Vistara&amp;rdquo; originates from the Sanskrit word &amp;ldquo;vistaar,&amp;rdquo; signifying &amp;ldquo;limitless expanse,&amp;rdquo; symbolizing the boundless sky, the airline&amp;rsquo;s domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistara-a-new-airline-launches-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is using Dreamliners on the route between the UAE and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:28:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched daily Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner flights between the UAE and Singapore, setting a new standard for luxury travel on this route. Passengers can choose from First Suites, Business Studios, and Economy Smart Seats on the Abu Dhabi-Singapore route. The flight schedule is designed for smooth connections to 35 destinations within Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; network.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and Chief Executive Officer, stated that the Dreamliner&amp;rsquo;s deployment on the Singapore route demonstrates the route&amp;rsquo;s significance and the airline&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing a top-tier travel experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-using-dreamliners-on-the-route-between-the-uae-and-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has added Fukuoka to its list of destinations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 23:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</guid><description>Cebu Pacific Air (CEB) initiated flights between Manila and Fukuoka on December 17th, adding a third weekly service to their existing routes in Japan. This marks their fourth destination in Japan, including direct flights from Manila to Osaka, Tokyo (Narita), and Nagoya, as well as flights from Cebu to Tokyo (Narita).
Japan is a top destination for travelers from the Philippines. Data from the Japan National Tourism Organization indicates a 44% increase in Filipino arrivals, reaching over 211,000 between January and October 2015, compared to the same period the previous year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-added-fukuoka-to-its-list-of-destinations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines increases frequency on Hong Kong-Haikou route with two additional flights per week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</guid><description>Starting December 25th, Hong Kong Airlines will offer two more weekly flights on its route between Hong Kong and Haikou, increasing the total frequency to nine flights per week. The new flights to Haikou will operate on Fridays and Sundays.
Flight no.*
Route
Departure/Arrival time*
Frequency
HX157
Hong Kong to Haikou
19:25/20:50
Every Friday
18:15/19:45
Every Sunday
HX158
Haikou to Hong Kong
21:55/23:15
Every Friday
21:15/22:35
Every Sunday
*Flight number and schedule may change without prior notice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-increases-frequency-on-hong-kong-haikou-route-with-two-additional-flights-per-week/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flights to Doha canceled by airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 10:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</guid><description>The diplomatic break between several countries and Qatar on June 5th has resulted in canceled flights for airlines based in the involved nations. These countries, including Bahrain, Saudi Arabia, and the UAE, have severed air, land, and sea connections with Qatar.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, halted daily flights between Bahrain and Doha as of 11:59 PM local time on June 5, 2017, until further notice.
The final Gulf Air departure from Bahrain to Doha (GF530) left at 8:55 PM on June 5th, while the last flight from Doha to Bahrain (GF531) departed at 10:40 PM that same day (all times local)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flights-to-doha-canceled-by-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas has teamed up with Pegasus Airlines to provide flights from Saudi Arabia to Turkey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</guid><description>Source: flynas. Aerial view of Turkey.
The Saudi Arabian airline flynas has partnered with Turkish budget airline Pegasus Airlines to expand its flight offerings in Turkey. This collaboration will initially allow flynas passengers to travel to five new Turkish destinations: Antalya, Ankara, Adana, Hatay, and Trabzon. This will be achieved by utilizing Pegasus Airlines&amp;rsquo; extensive network of domestic flights operating from Istanbul&amp;rsquo;s Sabiha Gökçen International Airport.
Bander Al Mohanna, Group CEO of NAS Holding, stated that Pegasus Airlines is a leading Turkish airline with over two decades of experience in innovation within the country&amp;rsquo;s aviation industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-has-teamed-up-with-pegasus-airlines-to-provide-flights-from-saudi-arabia-to-turkey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting on January 26, 2015, AirAsia will no longer impose fuel surcharges</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 02:27:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</guid><description>Starting January 26, 2015, AirAsia, along with its long-haul affiliates AirAsia X, Thai AirAsia X, and Indonesia AirAsia X, will eliminate fuel surcharges on all flights. This decision aligns with the current downward trend in global oil prices.
Source: AirAsia eDM.
This marks a return to AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s previous policy from 2008, where fuel surcharges were eliminated on all domestic and international flights. However, due to surging fuel prices, surcharges were reinstated in 2011...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-january-26-2015-airasia-will-no-longer-impose-fuel-surcharges/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates launches new Home Check-in service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. The Home Check-in service utilizes a newly acquired fleet of vans and has been undergoing rigorous testing since October of the previous year.
Emirates has launched its &amp;ldquo;Home Check-in&amp;rdquo; service, allowing passengers departing from Dubai, UAE, to check in for their flights from any location. This service is offered to all Emirates passengers, regardless of their travel class, and demonstrates the airline&amp;rsquo;s dedication to delivering exceptional service and convenience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-launches-new-home-check-in-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad improves chauffeur services in the United Arab Emirates</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the UAE, has launched new features to improve its chauffeur services in the UAE.
Passengers can now book and manage Etihad&amp;rsquo;s chauffeur services directly through the airline&amp;rsquo;s updated mobile-friendly website, eliminating the need to contact the Etihad call center or a travel agent. This feature is effective immediately.
Travelers can book and confirm their chauffeur service up to 12 hours before their flight&amp;rsquo;s departure. Developed with Vxceed Technologies, the new system also allows passengers to modify or cancel their chauffeur booking, giving them more control over their travel plans...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-improves-chauffeur-services-in-the-united-arab-emirates/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad plans to increase the number of flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, will begin offering daily A380 flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne starting June 1, 2016. This will affect flight numbers EY460/461, one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily trips between the cities. This change replaces one of the three-class Boeing 777-300ER aircraft currently used. Passengers can now enjoy The Residence by Etihad, a luxurious private three-room suite, and other cutting-edge products and services across all cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Air China is providing a 50% discount on excess baggage fees to North America if paid in advance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 06:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</guid><description>Air China is the first Chinese airline to offer a prepaid excess baggage fee service for flights to North America. Travelers on Air China flights between Beijing and North America who anticipate exceeding their baggage allowance can now pay a discounted fee in advance. This service can be accessed through Air China ticketing offices globally or by calling their Member Services hotline.
Passengers who prepay for excess baggage will save 50% compared to airport rates, paying RMB 650 per piece or the equivalent in local currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-is-providing-a-50-discount-on-excess-baggage-fees-to-north-america-if-paid-in-advance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</a></p></description></item><item><title>First and business class customers on Emirates can now enjoy a new Japanese menu</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 01:36:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. A sample dish from the new Japanese menu.
Emirates now offers a specialized Japanese menu to its first and business class passengers traveling between Dubai and Haneda, Narita, and Kansai airports in Japan. The airline&amp;rsquo;s Dubai catering team partnered with a Japanese culinary provider to develop the dishes using the highest quality ingredients.
In addition to their international menu, first-class passengers can enjoy traditional kaiseki, a multi-course Japanese meal, while those in business class have the option of a bento box...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-and-business-class-customers-on-emirates-can-now-enjoy-a-new-japanese-menu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Mandarin Oriental in Hong Kong and Vistajet provide a rare and unique experience called Once in a Blue Moon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:38:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</guid><description>VistaJet, a prominent business aviation company, has partnered with the Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong to create the &amp;ldquo;Once in a Blue Moon&amp;rdquo; experience. This exclusive offer celebrates the Mid-Autumn Festival with a luxurious private jet journey featuring an in-flight menu designed by Chef Wong, the Executive Chinese Chef of the Michelin-starred Man Wah restaurant at the Mandarin Oriental.
Available from September 15 to October 15, 2020, this unique offering features a customized private jet experience departing from Hong Kong...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-mandarin-oriental-in-hong-kong-and-vistajet-provide-a-rare-and-unique-experience-called-once-in-a-blue-moon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in January 2016, AirAsia will be introducing direct flights between Penang and Ho Chi Minh City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 01:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</guid><description>Budget carrier AirAsia is launching a new direct route between its hub in Penang, Malaysia and Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. This expansion aims to strengthen the airline’s connections within Southeast Asia.
AirAsia&amp;rsquo;s Head of Commercial, Spencer Lee, emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to improving travel options within the ASEAN region, highlighting Penang&amp;rsquo;s tourism potential. This new route directly links Penang and Ho Chi Minh City, benefiting travelers in both cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-january-2016-airasia-will-be-introducing-direct-flights-between-penang-and-ho-chi-minh-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Save up to 40% this Ramadan when you book with Oman Air</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:27:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air website.
Oman Air is offering a 40% discount on economy and business class base fares to select international destinations. This offer is valid for online bookings made by June 24th. Taxes and surcharges are not included.
Flights eligible for the discount can originate from various cities, including Muscat, Salalah, Dubai, Abu Dhabi, and Beirut. However, destinations like London, Jeddah, Riyadh, Cairo, Manila, and India (excluding Goa) are excluded from the offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/save-up-to-40-this-ramadan-when-you-book-with-oman-air/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad is increasing the number of weekly flights between Abu Dhabi and Manila</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2016, Etihad Airways will increase its Abu Dhabi to Manila route from 14 to 17 roundtrip flights per week. This provides convenient connections from Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s hub to popular destinations for Philippine travelers, including Bahrain, Kuwait, Dammam, Doha, Jeddah, and Riyadh.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, highlighted the Abu Dhabi-Manila route&amp;rsquo;s high demand and limited capacity in recent years. The added flights will increase capacity by nearly 2,500 seats weekly, improving travel options between the UAE and the Philippines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-increasing-the-number-of-weekly-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-manila/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines expands its presence in the United States with a new codeshare agreement with Asiana Airlines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines has broadened its codeshare partnership with Asiana Airlines, expanding its network beyond Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Incheon International Airport to include Honolulu, Seattle, and Los Angeles.
These Star Alliance members have been codesharing on flights between Singapore and Seoul-Incheon since September 2005. Singapore Airlines currently offers four daily flights on this route, with one continuing to San Francisco, while Asiana operates daily flights.
Asiana also places its code on Singapore Airlines-operated flights extending beyond Singapore to Jakarta, Indonesia; Perth, Australia; Auckland, New Zealand; and Cape Town, South Africa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-expands-its-presence-in-the-united-states-with-a-new-codeshare-agreement-with-asiana-airlines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Garuda and Turkish Airlines have formed a codeshare agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines have partnered to offer codeshare flights between Jakarta and Istanbul. This agreement is valid until October 24, 2015.
The joint flight schedule for Garuda Indonesia and Turkish Airlines is shown below:
Source: Garuda Indonesia. CGK represents Soekarno–Hatta International Airport in Jakarta, Indonesia, while IST stands for Atatürk International Airport in Istanbul, Turkey. STD indicates departure time, and STA refers to arrival time. +1 signifies arrival on the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/garuda-and-turkish-airlines-have-formed-a-codeshare-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business class passengers on Oman Air can personalize their digital content for in-flight entertainment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 04:17:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</guid><description>Source: Oman Air. The Media Box, with local and Arabic media added, is now available to first and business class Oman Air passengers departing Muscat, Oman.
First and business class passengers flying Oman Air from Muscat, Oman, can now enjoy digital news and entertainment in the recently renovated lounges.
This service is powered by the Media Box, an extensive e-paper library developed by Media Carrier. It allows travelers to create a personalized selection of international magazines and newspapers to read on board...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-class-passengers-on-oman-air-can-personalize-their-digital-content-for-in-flight-entertainment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enter for a chance to win a trip to Barcelona with UberHOLIDAY and Qatar Airways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 18:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</guid><description>Source: Uber Malaysia. Qatar Airways will fly three lucky winners and their partners on a whirlwind trip to Spain.
On January 12, 2017, Uber users in Malaysia have the opportunity to win an unforgettable trip to Barcelona, Spain through UberHOLIDAY. This promotion is a collaboration with the Qatar Airways Travel Festival 2017.
Three winners and their partners will be chosen to receive a ride to the airport and flown to Barcelona on the same day, contingent upon having valid passports and meeting Spain&amp;rsquo;s visa requirements*...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enter-for-a-chance-to-win-a-trip-to-barcelona-with-uberholiday-and-qatar-airways/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates is adding another daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</guid><description>Source: Emirates.
Emirates has launched an additional daily flight between Dubai and Colombo, Sri Lanka. Starting August 1, 2016, the airline will offer five daily flights between the two cities, except on Wednesdays, when four flights will be available. This new flight will provide an extra 2,520 seats and boost cargo capacity by 161 tonnes weekly in both directions, increasing the total weekly services on this route to 34...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-adding-another-daily-flight-between-dubai-and-colombo-sri-lanka/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The US CDC has compiled a list of airports worldwide that are smoke-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</guid><description>Of the 50 busiest airports globally, 23 have implemented completely smoke-free indoor environments. This means that 46% of the busiest airports offer protection from secondhand smoke for travelers and employees, as per a recent report from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). The remaining 27 airports permit smoking in designated areas or spaces equipped with ventilation systems.
An airport was classified as having a smoke-free policy only if smoking was completely prohibited in all indoor areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enjoy the first 15 minutes of free Wi-Fi on Qatar Airways, courtesy of Ooredoo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 12:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo. The MoU was signed by (from left) Waleed Al Sayed, CEO, Ooredoo Qatar and Qatar Airways Group Chief Executive, His Excellency Akbar Al Baker.
Ooredoo and Qatar Airways have established a partnership where Ooredoo will sponsor Qatar Airways&amp;rsquo; in-flight Wi-Fi for the next three years. This agreement will make Ooredoo the sole sponsor for Wi-Fi on all Qatar Airways flights equipped with the service.
This sponsorship allows passengers to use their personal electronic devices to connect to the internet, check emails, and send SMS/MMS messages once the service is active during their flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enjoy-the-first-15-minutes-of-free-wi-fi-on-qatar-airways-courtesy-of-ooredoo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilkAir expands its network to include Colombo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 05:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, has introduced flights to Colombo, Sri Lanka, becoming the second airline in its group to operate on this route. With the addition of three weekly flights to Colombo, SilkAir now reaches 53 destinations in 15 countries.
These flights will operate on Wednesdays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, using Boeing 737-800 aircraft with both Business and Economy Class seating. Passengers will enjoy a full range of services, including meals, in-flight entertainment on SilkAir Studio, and baggage allowances of 40kg for Business Class and 30kg for Economy Class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silkair-expands-its-network-to-include-colombo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates provides LinkedIn Learning courses during flights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 06:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates will offer LinkedIn courses inflight.
Emirates has teamed up with LinkedIn to offer a selection of LinkedIn Learning courses on its inflight entertainment system, ice. This makes Emirates the first international airline to provide these courses during flights.
This new addition to the ice system will launch in November and reflects Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to offering passengers fresh and diverse entertainment options. The free LinkedIn Learning courses, led by experts, range from 20 minutes to over two hours in length...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-provides-linkedin-learning-courses-during-flights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting in October, Air China will offer nonstop flights from Beijing to Mumbai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 09:14:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</guid><description>Air China will commence nonstop flights between Beijing and Mumbai starting October 25, 2015. This decision comes as a response to the growing travel demand between these two BRICS nations, driven by strengthening political and economic ties.
Source: Air China.
The route will operate four times a week, with flights on Tuesdays, Thursdays, Saturdays, and Sundays. The seven-hour journey departs Beijing at 7:40 PM local time and arrives in Mumbai at 1 AM the following day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-in-october-air-china-will-offer-nonstop-flights-from-beijing-to-mumbai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cebu Pacific has been approved for more international routes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 07:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</guid><description>The Philippine Civil Aeronautics Board (CAB) has granted Cebu Pacific (CEB) additional flight entitlements for international routes. These include flights from Manila to the UAE and routes connecting various Philippine cities to Taipei and Kaohsiung in Taiwan.
CEB received approval to operate seven more weekly flights between Manila and the UAE. This allows the airline to offer service to any destination within the UAE, expanding upon its current daily flights between Manila and Dubai...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cebu-pacific-has-been-approved-for-more-international-routes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates and flydubai will share a common frequent flyer program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 05:49:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Emirates Skywards is now the loyalty program for both Emirates and flydubai, replacing flydubai&amp;rsquo;s OPEN program. This decision builds on the strong partnership between the two airlines, which already includes code-sharing across a wide global network and collaborations in areas like commercial strategies, network planning, and airport operations.
Members of Emirates Skywards can now earn both Skywards miles and tier miles when flying with either airline. They can also use these miles, or a combination of miles and cash, to book flydubai flights* and purchase extras like pre-ordered meals or extra legroom seats...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-and-flydubai-will-share-a-common-frequent-flyer-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Changi Terminal 3 reveals its new Central Piazza</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</guid><description>Source: Changi Airport Group. The newly opened Central Piazza at Changi Airport Terminal 3 features a Louis Vuitton duplex store and a dandelion-themed Crystal Garden.
Travelers passing through Changi Airport Terminal 3&amp;rsquo;s Transit Hall can now enjoy the revitalized Central Piazza. This area showcases the airport&amp;rsquo;s seventh featured garden, the Crystal Garden, composed of glass dandelion sculptures.
The Crystal Garden features a multi-level garden design with carefully chosen flowering plants and twelve handcrafted glass dandelion sculptures of different sizes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-terminal-3-reveals-its-new-central-piazza/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>