<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Battery on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/battery/</link><description>Recent content in Battery on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/battery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lenovo issues global recall for Thinkpad batteries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 02:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lenovo-issues-global-recall-for-thinkpad-batteries/</guid><description>Lenovo has expanded a battery recall that was first announced on March 27, 2014. This recall now includes all affected lithium-ion batteries globally. The batteries, as announced in late April 2015, were manufactured for ThinkPad notebook computers shipped between February 2010 and June 2012.
Lenovo stated that they are offering free-of-charge replacement batteries for all recalled batteries in the interest of public safety.
The batteries were sold with new notebook computers or as optional or replacement batteries for the following models:</description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Replacing the RAM Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-replacing-the-ram-battery/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 utilizes a 3V battery to power its 16-word memory chip, an MCM144102, which is described as a peripheral memory unit in the Motorola 6804 manual but lacks readily available detailed specifications. This chip is responsible for storing calibration data and potentially the system time, although further investigation is required. A visual representation of the circuit is included below.
A positive aspect of the design is the inclusion of diode D27, which safeguards the battery against reverse polarity connection.</description></item><item><title>Your Next Battery Is a Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 06:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-next-battery-is-a-capacitor/</guid><description>Benjamin Franklin&amp;rsquo;s experiment with capturing electricity in Leyden Jars, glass jars with foil conductors that store electric charge, laid the groundwork for modern battery technology.
Today, researchers have developed ultracapacitors, like the Graphene Ultracapacitor from the University of Texas at Austin, which are essentially very small but powerful capacitors. These ultracapacitors use nanometer-thin dielectrics instead of bulky glass jars, allowing them to achieve farad-level capacitance, much higher than the picofarad capacity of a Leyden Jar.</description></item><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4.</description></item><item><title>The main focus of Kickstarter is iFind, which is powered by ambient electromagnetic radiation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-main-focus-of-kickstarter-is-ifind-which-is-powered-by-ambient-electromagnetic-radiation/</guid><description>WeTag&amp;rsquo;s iFind tags use Bluetooth to connect with iOS or Android devices and don&amp;rsquo;t require charging. Like similar tracking devices, the tag is attached to an item and located using a smartphone.
If the item goes out of range, the &amp;lsquo;Rope&amp;rsquo; feature notifies the owner. The &amp;lsquo;UHelp&amp;rsquo; feature leverages nearby phones to help find the lost object through Bluetooth. WeTag highlights a unique feature: shaking the iFind tag will cause the paired phone to vibrate.</description></item><item><title>Duracell batteries provide six times the power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</guid><description>Source: Duracell. To commemorate five decades of providing portable power, Duracell has partnered with TRANSFORMERS: AGE OF EXTINCTION, the fourth film in director Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s globally recognized franchise, in a battle of good and evil.
Duracell, the renowned battery manufacturer, is observing 50 years of providing portable power solutions. Although the traditional battery design remains largely unchanged, battery technology advancements have significantly extended battery life.
Duracell&amp;rsquo;s latest CopperTop AA and AAA batteries, equipped with Duralock Power Preserve Technology, are ideal for devices like wireless mice and keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Concentrating on Kickstarter: Making Solar Power Accessible to Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/concentrating-on-kickstarter-making-solar-power-accessible-to-everyone/</guid><description>Spor Solar Charges aims to make convenient solar-powered battery charging accessible to everyone. Their product, Spor, is a portable battery charger for USB devices that can recharge itself using solar energy. It can also be powered up using a standard AC outlet. The company claims that Spor can charge multiple devices simultaneously and replenish a phone&amp;rsquo;s battery almost as quickly as a wall outlet, according to their Kickstarter page.
Source: Kickstarter.</description></item></channel></rss>