<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</link><description>Recent content in Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:55:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Arising from the Depths of the Curriculum Cave</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 00:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</guid><description>My apologies for being absent from this blog for the past six weeks. I&amp;rsquo;ve been busy updating training materials for the Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step 2010 release. My focus has been on the &amp;ldquo;Project Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations with Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step&amp;rdquo; course (80199), which utilizes a case study approach for collaborative learning. Participants work through a fictional company implementation, applying Sure Step tools, templates, and guidance. I&amp;rsquo;ve taught earlier versions of this course and witnessed how it transforms students&amp;rsquo; understanding of Sure Step, shifting from theoretical knowledge to practical application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/arising-from-the-depths-of-the-curriculum-cave/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Caution: Implementation Trauma Upcoming</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in Indianapolis for work and, despite a looming deadline for my blog post, I&amp;rsquo;m feeling a bit short on inspiration. It could be the post-holiday slump, or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m prepping for a training session tomorrow. Either way, I&amp;rsquo;m hoping my readers will bear with me!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing a lot of training and study hall sessions for Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step lately, and it&amp;rsquo;s made me reflect on some common pitfalls I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered during implementations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/caution-implementation-trauma-upcoming/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are you Sure Step Certified, or just Certifiable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/</guid><description>I came across a helpful blog post by a European Sure Step trainer that offers valuable advice for those preparing for the Sure Step exam. I recommend reading the comments too, as they address common concerns about Sure Step that I often hear.
While Sure Step offers a wide range of tools, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that improvement is a gradual process. Focus on identifying areas within your organization that need enhancement, and then leverage the Sure Step guidance to address those specific areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-sure-step-certified-or-just-certifiable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are you feeling overwhelmed by the prospect of managing Microsoft Dynamics implementations? Don't worry, we've got you covered.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-feeling-overwhelmed-by-the-prospect-of-managing-microsoft-dynamics-implementations-don-t-worry-we-ve-got-you-covered/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 06:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-feeling-overwhelmed-by-the-prospect-of-managing-microsoft-dynamics-implementations-don-t-worry-we-ve-got-you-covered/</guid><description>Hey Partners! Still need to conquer the Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations exam? Stop delaying and join me for a virtual study session on March 25th!
Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peek at what we&amp;rsquo;ll cover:
Get ready for the Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementation exam (MB5-858) with our helpful study session. We&amp;rsquo;ll go over essential concepts, examine the exam prep guide, and connect relevant Sure Step elements to sharpen your study approach.
Register here:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-feeling-overwhelmed-by-the-prospect-of-managing-microsoft-dynamics-implementations-don-t-worry-we-ve-got-you-covered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-feeling-overwhelmed-by-the-prospect-of-managing-microsoft-dynamics-implementations-don-t-worry-we-ve-got-you-covered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Debunking Myths About the Sure Step</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debunking-myths-about-the-sure-step/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 15:23:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debunking-myths-about-the-sure-step/</guid><description>For the past few years, I&amp;rsquo;ve been teaching the Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step curriculum. My classes have been the fullest they&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in recent months due to the changes in the partner program. It&amp;rsquo;s great to hear about the various experiences of Dynamics partners (AX, CRM, GP, NAV, SL). Contrary to what many people think, it&amp;rsquo;s not just the &amp;ldquo;big&amp;rdquo; partners who have benefited from using Sure Step in their businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debunking-myths-about-the-sure-step/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/debunking-myths-about-the-sure-step/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Study Hall Fun at Sure Step!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/study-hall-fun-at-sure-step/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 07:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/study-hall-fun-at-sure-step/</guid><description>Microsoft Partners, if you&amp;rsquo;re aiming to achieve the Implementation Methodology certification before the May 1st deadline, consider attending the Sure Step Study Hall at Convergence.
Sunday, April 10, 2011 3:15 PM Room B216, Georgia World Congress Center (Convention Center)
This session provides valuable advice on building an effective study plan for exam success. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore essential Sure Step concepts and highlight helpful tools and guidance within Sure Step to optimize your study efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/study-hall-fun-at-sure-step/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/study-hall-fun-at-sure-step/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>