<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Standard on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/standard/</link><description>Recent content in Standard on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/standard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KPMG has identified gaps in global corporate responsibility reports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 22:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kpmg-has-identified-gaps-in-global-corporate-responsibility-reports/</guid><description>A 2015 KPMG study reveals inconsistencies in how the world&amp;rsquo;s largest companies report their carbon emissions, making it challenging to compare their performance. While 80% of the top 250 companies address carbon in their reports, the information provided varies significantly. For instance, only half declare carbon reduction goals, and among those, two-thirds don&amp;rsquo;t explain their rationale.
The reported emissions types also differ. Most companies (84%) report emissions from their operations and purchased power (79%), but only half include supply chain emissions.</description></item><item><title>TCEB commemorates achievements in Thailand's MICE Venue Standard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 05:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tceb-commemorates-achievements-in-thailand-s-mice-venue-standard/</guid><description>Forty-two venues in Thailand have now received the Thailand MICE Venue Standard award from the Thailand Convention and Exhibition Bureau (TCEB). The announcement was made at the Thailand MICE Venue Standard Certification Ceremony held last month.
This standard is a key element of a robust plan to accelerate the growth of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s MICE industry. Emphasizing Thailand&amp;rsquo;s prominent role in the region, TCEB underscored the need to utilize the expertise of MICE operators.</description></item></channel></rss>