<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Festival on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/festival/</link><description>Recent content in Festival on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/festival/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customize SPD paper and electronic greeting cards with your own branding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 01:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</guid><description>Source: SPD website.
The SPD, a Singaporean organization supporting individuals with disabilities, operates a supported employment facility that creates physical and digital greeting cards. These cards are suitable for various events like birthdays and holidays such as Hari Raya, Deepavali, Christmas, and Chinese New Year.
Customization options are available for these cards, including adding company branding, personalized notes, or designs for other special events.
Interested parties can explore the complete selection of cards on the SPD e-shop...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customize-spd-paper-and-electronic-greeting-cards-with-your-own-branding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Joo Chiat Kim Choo introduces halal rice dumplings at 7-Eleven Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:54:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Joo Chiat Kim Choo/7-Eleven.
- Halal rice dumplings from Kim Choo Kid are now sold at all 7-Eleven stores in Singapore.
- Customers can choose from two flavors: Nonya Chicken and Salted Chicken. For convenience, the leaves have been removed.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 7-Eleven stores now offer a halal version of the famous Joo Chiat Kim Choo rice dumplings. Part of the Neo Group, this top rice dumpling maker in Singapore is known for its Nonya dumplings, made with a recipe handed down through generations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joo-chiat-kim-choo-introduces-halal-rice-dumplings-at-7-eleven-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, come to DiverseCity in KL to experience a diverse range of performing and visual arts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 19:22:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</guid><description>DiverseCity 2016, also known as the Kuala Lumpur International Arts Festival, ran from August 31st to October 2nd, 2016. The festival showcased a diverse range of artistic expressions, including visual arts, crafts, music, dance, and literature at various locations around Klang Valley in Malaysia. Many events were free to attend.
Taking place annually for five weeks at multiple venues in and around Kuala Lumpur, DiverseCity highlights the rich cultural tapestry of Malaysia and explores the country&amp;rsquo;s close relationship with the ASEAN community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-come-to-diversecity-in-kl-to-experience-a-diverse-range-of-performing-and-visual-arts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 18th edition of All That Matters will take place from September 11th to 13th, 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</guid><description>All That Matters, a key event for professionals in Asia&amp;rsquo;s music, sports, gaming, digital, marketing, Web3, and entertainment sectors, is back for its 18th year. It will be held from September 11th to 13th at the Hilton Singapore Orchard.
Source: All That Matters organisers. Event poster.
The event combines a daytime conference with a nightly music festival. It offers attendees, including representatives from major labels, sports organizations, distributors, and publishers, a chance to connect with global brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-18th-edition-of-all-that-matters-will-take-place-from-september-11th-to-13th-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Concorde Hotel is arranging mooncakes in a vertical stack</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</guid><description>Source: Concorde Hotel website.
For this Mid-Autumn Festival, Concorde Hotel Singapore is offering a selection of classic baked mooncakes. Customers can choose from traditional fillings like pure lotus paste, pure lotus with single or double yolks, and a less sweet white lotus with single yolk. Prices range from S$60 to S$68 for a box of four, including GST. Additionally, they offer a &amp;ldquo;Supreme Manju&amp;rdquo; flavor at S$64 for a box of four...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-concorde-hotel-is-arranging-mooncakes-in-a-vertical-stack/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The goal of the Taste The World Dining Series is to demonstrate that food serves as a universal form of communication</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</guid><description>Gourmet Trails, a luxury travel company, presents the first-ever Taste The World culinary series, taking place from May 4th to 26th, 2024. This festival showcases the unifying power of food, emphasizing its ability to connect people and foster understanding.
Taste The World partners with acclaimed restaurants like Appetite, Hashida, CURE, Canchita, Esquina, Ummi Beirut, and ANJU to offer a diverse range of global cuisines. Proceeds from this event will support the United Nations World Food Programme...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-goal-of-the-taste-the-world-dining-series-is-to-demonstrate-that-food-serves-as-a-universal-form-of-communication/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2015, Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy introduced black bean mooncakes to their selection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:23:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</guid><description>Source: Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy.
At the Grand Mercure Singapore Roxy, this Mooncake Festival, indulge in a modern take on classic handmade mooncakes created by Head Chef Lester Wang.
With over 20 flavors, Chef Wang&amp;rsquo;s baked and snowskin mooncakes offer a delightful blend of traditional and contemporary tastes. Popular choices include Jia Wei Durian, Signature Italian Dark Coffee, and Raspberry with Dark Chocolate mooncakes.
This year&amp;rsquo;s selection introduces two new flavors: traditional baked mooncakes with black bean paste and the ‘Ying Yang’ snowskin mooncake, featuring a harmonious blend of white lotus and black bean fillings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-grand-mercure-singapore-roxy-introduced-black-bean-mooncakes-to-their-selection/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>