<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Virtual Server on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-server/</link><description>Recent content in Virtual Server on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/virtual-server/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Server vs Cloud Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</guid><description>Cloud backup services have gained immense popularity among both individuals and businesses. Most people store at least some files online for easy sharing and mobile access, exceeding the need for encrypted backups. Essentially, there&amp;rsquo;s a massive shift of data towards the cloud.
While online file storage has become second nature, cloud computing hasn&amp;rsquo;t gained the same widespread adoption, despite a clear trend in that direction. However, there are strong indicators suggesting that cloud computing will reach a similar level of popularity as cloud storage within a few years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-server-vs-cloud-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Additional HyperV Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-hyperv-resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 09:15:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-hyperv-resources/</guid><description>During my attempt to move a Virtual Server 2005 VHD file to HyperV, I ran into network issues within the virtual server. Thankfully, I came across an article outlining steps to prep a virtual server before a HyperV migration. As a safety measure, creating backups of the VHD and VMC before any changes is recommended.
http://blogs.technet.com/askcore/archive/2008/09/19/migrating-to-hyper-v-from-virtual-server-or-virtual-pc-tips-and-suggestions.aspx
This led me to a tool designed to simplify VMC to HyperV file conversion. Since I only have a handful of servers, creating new virtual servers and attaching the VHD remains efficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-hyperv-resources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-hyperv-resources/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>