<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FMC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fmc/</link><description>Recent content in FMC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fmc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Communications Advantages Explained</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-communications-advantages-explained/</guid><description>Many businesses are unsure if switching their communications to the cloud is a good idea. XO Communications, a large networking and telecom provider, explains why this change is beneficial. Their short video illustrates why this might be the right choice for your business.
XO&amp;rsquo;s Enterprise Cloud Communications provides large businesses with services similar to what hosted PBX systems offer smaller companies. Essentially, it transitions a company from managing its own phone system to simply using a sophisticated service.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap.</description></item></channel></rss>