<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth on Demand on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-on-demand/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth on Demand on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-on-demand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth on Demand Complements Cloud Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:50:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-on-demand-complements-cloud-services/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
One of the biggest advantages of cloud services over traditional IT infrastructure is their flexibility. With a vast pool of virtual servers and storage, businesses can adjust resources on demand, significantly improving productivity and resource usage.
However, connectivity hasn&amp;rsquo;t quite caught up with this shift. Connecting to the cloud often relies on fixed-capacity connections. Upgrading these connections is typically a complex and time-consuming process, creating a bottleneck in an otherwise agile system.</description></item></channel></rss>