<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Private Cloud on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-cloud/</link><description>Recent content in Private Cloud on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:52:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/private-cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Type of Data Center Connectivity Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</guid><description>When thinking about moving to a colocation center or building a data center or private cloud off-site, you&amp;rsquo;ll face both opportunities and difficulties in setting up your network connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the key factors and uncover potential cost-saving opportunities.
The main difference between on-site and remote data centers, including colocation facilities, lies in how you manage network connections. On-site, you have full control over your local wiring. Off-site, you lease connections through service providers.</description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits.</description></item></channel></rss>