<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP Phones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-phones/</link><description>Recent content in SIP Phones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:02:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Dynamic CoS Means to You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern networks are typically converged, meaning they handle various traffic types like backups, file transfers, cloud access, VoIP calls, streaming, and web services. This begs the question: how can we ensure these networks maintain the integrity of each process with so much going on?
The Need for QoS
When we implement Quality of Service (QoS) controls, a network becomes more than just a passive conduit. But why is this necessary?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why NOT to Buy a New PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</guid><description>Traditionally, businesses dealing with outdated or inadequate phone systems have opted for a complete replacement, known as a “forklift upgrade.” While this provided enhanced performance and capacity, like a brand new car, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling alternative in today&amp;rsquo;s world: hosted PBX solutions.
Rather than investing heavily in another physical PBX system, consider a hosted PBX, also referred to as Hosted VoIP or PBX in the cloud. This service eliminates the need for a physical PBX on your premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telephone Trunks for Call Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 11:33:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
All businesses require telephone lines in some form. While independent professionals might depend solely on smartphones for wireless communication, businesses with physical locations or multiple employees typically have landlines. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available analog and digital choices, along with the benefits of using telephone trunk lines for increased capacity and cost savings.
Plain Old Analog Analog phone lines are the traditional technology used by phone companies for over a century...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-trunks-for-call-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Based Unified Communications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 03:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</guid><description>Cloud servers have gained widespread acceptance as many IT departments realize the advantages of readily available and scalable processing and storage over predicting hardware needs. Traditional phone systems, however, often face similar challenges.
PBX systems, often proprietary and inflexible, require upfront investment in anticipated capacity, leading to either underutilization or costly upgrades. Cloud-based communication offers a solution by moving switching and storage to the cloud, eliminating the need for physical PBX hardware and enabling scalability based on demand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-based-unified-communications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does a VoIP Call Work?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</guid><description>VoIP is often called a network service, not a phone service, which matters for technical folks and business owners, but less so for everyday users. After all, a phone is a phone; you expect it to work the same way.
The aim with VoIP has been to closely replicate the experience of traditional landlines. Now that this is largely accomplished, the focus is shifting towards making VoIP calls sound even better than traditional calls, aiming for what&amp;rsquo;s called HD or high-definition voice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing For Disaster Recovery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 22:49:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</guid><description>This year has seen a lot of natural disasters, from massive fires and overflowing rivers to intense storms and widespread tornadoes. These events might make you worry about your business&amp;rsquo;s safety.
It&amp;rsquo;s true that unexpected events can impact anyone. You likely have some safeguards in place, like insurance, backups, and maybe offsite file storage. But how quickly could your business recover from a major local disaster?
Having copies of essential data is crucial, but it won&amp;rsquo;t ensure a seamless recovery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-for-disaster-recovery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>