<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>QoS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qos/</link><description>Recent content in QoS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location.</description></item><item><title>Is Voice Over MPLS The New PSTN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</guid><description>Packet-switched networks are undeniably replacing circuit-switched networks, so much so that the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) might be phased out by the FCC. This signals the potential end of the century-old telephone system, raising the question of what will replace it. VoIP is a strong contender, but not in its current form.
VoIP&amp;rsquo;s strengths lie in its established standards for coding, signaling, and its compatibility with Ethernet data networks. However, its widespread adoption is hampered by incompatible implementations, concerns from wireless carriers about network overload, and inconsistent voice quality on the internet.</description></item><item><title>What Dynamic CoS Means to You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern networks are typically converged, meaning they handle various traffic types like backups, file transfers, cloud access, VoIP calls, streaming, and web services. This begs the question: how can we ensure these networks maintain the integrity of each process with so much going on?
The Need for QoS
When we implement Quality of Service (QoS) controls, a network becomes more than just a passive conduit. But why is this necessary?</description></item><item><title>Wireless SIP Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 10:24:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-sip-trunking/</guid><description>Traditionally, business phone lines and dedicated internet relied on physical wires. However, wireless SIP trunking is emerging as a new option.
](http://www.affordablevpn.com/usa/FixedWireless/fixed-wireless-broadband.php)
Airband Communications, a frontrunner in this technology, offers business-class voice services packaged with wireless internet access. This is comparable to a SIP trunk or an integrated voice and data service in the wired world, but Airband&amp;rsquo;s offering presents unique benefits.
Similar to other integrated services, a single connection provides both phone and internet access, only in this case, it&amp;rsquo;s wireless.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Shows How The Converged Business Network Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</guid><description>Larger organizations have been moving towards network convergence since IP became the standard network protocol. However, smaller companies, often lacking substantial IT departments, haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted this approach as readily. This is changing. Convergence is now a viable option for businesses of all sizes.
What&amp;rsquo;s driving this shift? The answer, as always, is cost savings. In today&amp;rsquo;s business climate, reducing expenses is crucial. The real game-changer is the availability of managed convergence services.</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>The PBX Disappears With Hosted Voice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pbx-disappears-with-hosted-voice/</guid><description>Mid-size and large businesses are accustomed to managing their in-house phone systems, believing that a PBX or Key telephone system is necessary for internal calls. Hosted voice service challenges this notion, requiring only the phones themselves and sometimes providing even those.
Hosted Voice, also called Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, is a cloud-based service. The PBX system still exists but resides at the service provider&amp;rsquo;s location, not yours.
This model resembles what companies used decades ago when telephone service was provided by a single entity like Bell System.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item><item><title>Meshed MPLS Forms a Cloud of Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</guid><description>Modern MPLS networks are replacing outdated Frame Relay networks for connecting multiple business sites. Their ability to handle almost any protocol with high quality and reliability has driven their popularity. A long-standing desire has been the ability to use multiple carriers across locations seamlessly within a managed MPLS network. This desire has finally been fulfilled.
AireSpring, a rapidly growing and innovative carrier, now offers a &amp;ldquo;Meshed MPLS Network.&amp;rdquo; But what exactly does this entail and how does it differ from the inherent mesh capabilities of any MPLS network?</description></item></channel></rss>