<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ILEC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ilec/</link><description>Recent content in ILEC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ilec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Long Range Ethernet Goes Beyond The LAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-range-ethernet-goes-beyond-the-lan/</guid><description>Ethernet, first introduced in the 1980s as a leading Local Area Network (LAN) protocol, is gaining traction as the preferred choice for Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs). This trend suggests a future dominated by Ethernet for network connectivity. What&amp;rsquo;s fueling this shift, and how can your business benefit?
](http://www.megatrunks.com/)
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s staying power in the LAN realm, both presently and in the future, is rooted in its cost-effectiveness and widespread availability.</description></item><item><title>Is MagicJack The Next Ma Bell?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</guid><description>The telephone industry is facing challenges as young people are increasingly abandoning traditional landlines, which were once considered essential by previous generations. The breakup of the Bell System into smaller regional companies suggests that the era of a single, all-encompassing telephone provider is over. However, the story doesn&amp;rsquo;t end there.
While it&amp;rsquo;s true that cell phones have replaced landlines for a significant portion of the population, particularly among younger demographics who have grown up with wireless technology, the evolution of the industry goes beyond this shift.</description></item><item><title>What Is VoIP For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about the benefits of switching from traditional phone services to VoIP, and for good reason. Businesses can gain a lot from enterprise VoIP solutions. However, there are potential downsides to watch out for to ensure a smooth transition. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what VoIP is and how it compares to your current phone service.
One thing that often causes confusion about VoIP is the name itself.</description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology.</description></item></channel></rss>