<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/portal/</link><description>Recent content in Portal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:25:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/portal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>LG Electronics has introduced a new website dedicated to product security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 00:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</guid><description>LG Electronics has launched a dedicated website to address security concerns related to their mobile products. The website, managed by LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security Response Team (PSRT), will serve as a central hub for security announcements, updates, and a platform for reporting vulnerabilities.
LG&amp;rsquo;s Product Security website will feature regular updates and bulletins on security matters concerning their mobile products, aiming to provide a secure and safe user experience. The website will prioritize vulnerabilities based on their severity, starting with the most critical ones, followed by high, moderate, and low-risk threats, including those identified by Google for the Android operating system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-electronics-has-introduced-a-new-website-dedicated-to-product-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover financial products in Malaysia with GoBear</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</guid><description>GoBear, a metasearch engine that simplifies financial product comparison, has officially launched in Malaysia. The platform offers unbiased, side-by-side comparisons of products like travel insurance and credit cards, with over 1,000 options currently listed and more to come.
Iskandar Ezzahuddin, GoBear&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, emphasized the platform&amp;rsquo;s mission: &amp;ldquo;GoBear stems from the understanding that modern consumers demand convenient access to service information and straightforward product comparisons before making financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-financial-products-in-malaysia-with-gobear/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globetrekker Challenge creates a wellness portal for Garmin in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Globetrekker Challenge, a Singapore-based corporate wellness software company, will provide their corporate wellness platform to Garmin for distribution across Asia and the Pacific. This collaboration leverages each company&amp;rsquo;s strengths, allowing them to focus on their core offerings.
Globetrekker&amp;rsquo;s platform offers customizable wellness programs, real-time analytics reporting, and health risk profiling for employers. Through this partnership, Garmin&amp;rsquo;s clients can access these features and integrate them with Garmin&amp;rsquo;s wearable devices, creating a comprehensive employee health improvement solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AWOK.com is planning to expand its operations beyond the UAE and is set to launch a mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: AWOK.com. Ulugbek Yulshadev, the founder of AWOK.com, the e-commerce platform currently celebrating its second anniversary.
AWOK.com, the UAE-based online shopping website, celebrated its second anniversary in April 2015. It has experienced a remarkable 500% surge in sales compared to its first year. Initially focusing on electronics and gadgets, the company has broadened its product range to encompass a diverse selection of household appliances, jewelry, consumer electronics, along with health and beauty products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/awok-com-is-planning-to-expand-its-operations-beyond-the-uae-and-is-set-to-launch-a-mobile-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guardian Health &amp; Beauty introduces a new interactive online shopping platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</guid><description>Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s leading health and beauty retailer, has introduced a US$1.3 million e-commerce platform. The platform offers the full range of products found in Guardian stores, along with curated content and virtual healthcare consultations.
Source: Guardian website.
Sarah Boyd, CEO of Guardian Health &amp;amp; Beauty, highlighted that Singapore is the first in Asia to launch such a comprehensive e-commerce site for the company. This decision was driven by the fact that Singaporean consumers are active digital shoppers and increasingly rely on online resources for their health and beauty needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guardian-health-beauty-introduces-a-new-interactive-online-shopping-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Expatstoday provides important advice for expatriates living in the Gulf region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</guid><description>Source: Expatstoday
A new online platform, Expatstoday, aims to attract individuals considering a move to Bahrain, Kuwait, Oman, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, or the UAE. The website provides insights into living conditions in these Gulf countries.
The company behind the platform emphasizes its commitment to providing accurate, current, and trustworthy information. While the sections dedicated to Gulf countries appear well-established, suggesting an active user base, pages for other countries seem relatively new, often lacking listings in various categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expatstoday-provides-important-advice-for-expatriates-living-in-the-gulf-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The most sought-after digital freelance work worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 19:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s job market, digital skills are essential. Freelancer.com, a global online marketplace, reports that the most sought-after skills are all digital.
The publicly traded company behind the site states that web and software development, web and graphic design, internet marketing (including SEO and SEM), and online sales and content development (including corporate content and social media) are the most active out of 600 job categories.
The platform boasts over 10 million users, connecting businesses with freelancers for over 5 million projects to date...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-sought-after-digital-freelance-work-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CrowdsUnite offers convenient crowdsourcing updates all in one location</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 22:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</guid><description>CrowdsUnite (crowdsunite.com) aims to be the &amp;ldquo;Yelp&amp;rdquo; for crowdfunding, featuring over 800 platforms in its database. The website provides guidance on crowdfunding and helps startups find the best platforms for their needs.
Alex Feldman, CEO of CrowdsUnite, points out that crowdfunding sites vary in features, customer support, and transparency. He emphasizes the risk of fraudulent campaigns that disappear with investors&amp;rsquo; money.
Source: CrowdsUnite blog. Feldman presents crowdfunding at a July 2014 talk in New York, US...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsunite-offers-convenient-crowdsourcing-updates-all-in-one-location/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>