<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Common Travel Area on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-travel-area/</link><description>Recent content in Common Travel Area on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/common-travel-area/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice.</description></item></channel></rss>