<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smartphone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartphone/</link><description>Recent content in Smartphone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smartphone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HTC introduces smartphone and imaging ecosystem components in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 12:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</guid><description>HTC debuted its new camera, the RE, alongside the HTC Desire EYE smartphone, HTC Eye Experience imaging software, and Zoe, a collaborative video editing community, in Singapore.
Jack Yang, President of South Asia, HTC Corporation, stated that similar to how HTC allowed people to replace laptops with smartphones in 1997, HTC is again revolutionizing technology by offering powerful hardware coupled with exceptional software. He emphasized HTC&amp;rsquo;s aim to change the way we perceive imaging — taking users beyond the viewfinder and placing them in the midst of the action with innovative software that enhances the use of technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-smartphone-and-imaging-ecosystem-components-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Stylus 2 will make its first appearance at MWC 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</guid><description>LG will introduce the LG Stylus 2 at the upcoming Mobile World Congress 2016 in Barcelona, Spain.
Source: LG. The LG Stylus 2.
The LG Stylus 2 is slimmer and lighter than its predecessor, measuring 7.4mm thick and weighing 145g. This follow-up to the G4 Stylus boasts a 5.7&amp;quot; HD display for an enhanced viewing experience.
Using the LG Stylus 2 mimics the experience of writing with a traditional pen and notepad...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-stylus-2-will-make-its-first-appearance-at-mwc-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Apple reveals special edition iPhone to celebrate 10th anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:35:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/</guid><description>Image Source: Apple. The iPhone X is dust- and water-resistant.
Apple has unveiled the iPhone X, its tenth-anniversary smartphone, sporting an all-glass design. Although Samsung phones already offered some of the phone&amp;rsquo;s debut features, the iPhone X introduces facial recognition for unlocking, authentication, and payments, alongside the ability to animate emojis with facial expressions.
The iPhone X boasts a 5.8&amp;quot; Super Retina display, A11 Bionic chip, wireless charging, and an upgraded rear camera with dual optical image stabilization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-reveals-special-edition-iphone-to-celebrate-10th-anniversary/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore gets a sneak peek at the HUAWEI Mate 20 icon before its official launch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 03:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. The square icon at various malls in
Singapore.
People in Singapore were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through an unexpected display of an illuminated square icon projected onto buildings throughout the city over the weekend.
This symbolic imagery appeared on structures in various locations such as Raffles City, Bugis Junction, Bugis+, and Plaza Singapura.
This readily identifiable square represents the phone&amp;rsquo;s camera setup, which includes a Leica Triple Camera and flash seamlessly integrated into the back of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series smartphones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-gets-a-sneak-peek-at-the-huawei-mate-20-icon-before-its-official-launch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the 'Butterfly' smartphone in specific Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 20:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 to the Japanese market through KDDI. This phone, also known as the HTC Butterfly 2, will be available from various carriers, including Chunghwa Telecom in Taiwan, CSL in Hong Kong, and others in South Asia.
Source: HTC.
The new HTC Butterfly 2 simplifies daily tasks with features like HTC Sense 6, an HTC Duo Camera, and the Motion Launch sensor.
Using au carrier aggregation*, the HTC J Butterfly HTL23 offers download speeds up to 150Mbps and supports WiMAX2+...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-butterfly-smartphone-in-specific-asian-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>OPPO empowers Singaporeans to discover the ultimate experience with #UncoverTheUltimate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 00:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</guid><description>Last week, OPPO, a global provider of smart devices, introduced its latest lineup of smartphones, including the brand&amp;rsquo;s first 5G offering, the Find X2 Pro 5G, and a new addition to its creative Reno series, the Reno3.
This unveiling follows the global online launch of the Find X2 series on March 6. The Find X2 Pro boasts a 120 Hz QHD AMOLED screen, 65 W SuperVOOC Flash Charge 2.0 technology, and the Qualcomm Snapdragon 865 processor, delivering an enhanced overall photography and video experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/oppo-empowers-singaporeans-to-discover-the-ultimate-experience-with-uncovertheultimate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Torch Fires Up Mobile Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Torch symbolizes a new era in mobile business communication, much like the Olympic torch marks the start of the Games.
This smartphone combines a touch screen with a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and introduces the BlackBerry 6 operating system. BlackBerry highlights the new OS&amp;rsquo;s ability to aggregate social media and RSS feeds, enable faster web browsing with multiple open tabs, provide universal search functionality, offer enhanced multimedia with a YouTube app, and ensure easy setup and personalization with a user-friendly design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting today, the Apple iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus are now available in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 04:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone 6 and iPhone 6 Plus will be offered in China starting October 17th through various channels like Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, major carriers, and authorized retailers. These smartphones will also be available in 36 more countries and territories by the end of October, reaching a total of over 115 countries by the year&amp;rsquo;s end.
Source: Apple. The iPhone 6 and
the iPhone 6 Plus.
Both iPhone models support TD-LTE and FDD-LTE, allowing customers to use 4G/LTE networks from China Mobile, China Telecom, and China Unicom throughout mainland China...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-today-the-apple-iphone-6-and-iphone-6-plus-are-now-available-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Huawei nova 2i is a mid-range phone with four cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 10:34:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</guid><description>Source: Huawei website. The nova 2i boasts a 5.9&amp;quot; FullView display.
Huawei has released the nova 2i, a 4G LTE mid-range phone designed for users who love taking selfies. This device stands out with its four cameras - two in the front and two on the back.
Clement Wong, Director of Global Product Marketing for the Huawei Consumer Business Group, highlighted that four cameras are uncommon in mid-range phones. He explained that Huawei aims to make its cutting-edge technology accessible to a wider customer base...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-nova-2i-is-a-mid-range-phone-with-four-cameras/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are You A Sentio Being?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re someone who likes to stay ahead of the curve in technology without breaking the bank, now is the time to make a move. The LG Sentio, a free high-quality smartphone, is a prime example of getting significant value without spending a lot.
You might be wondering how a high-value phone can be free. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of taking advantage of technological advancements at the right moment and knowing where to find the best deals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new bronze pink Xperia XZ Premium phones are now on sale in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The Bronze Pink Sony Xperia XZ.
After the June release of the Sony Xperia XZ Premium, Sony Mobile has launched a third color option in Singapore: Bronze Pink.
This new pink-hued phone will be available at select retailers starting July 8th. The Xperia XZ Premium has a suggested retail price of S$1,098.
Sony claims its Xperia XZ Premium is the world&amp;rsquo;s fastest smartphone, boasting a 4K HDR display...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-bronze-pink-xperia-xz-premium-phones-are-now-on-sale-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 210, an entry-level dual SIM phone, is priced at less than S$160</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 12:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</guid><description>HTC will launch its budget-friendly smartphone, the HTC Desire 210, in Singapore on Wednesday, September 3, 2014. The phone will be sold through various retailers in two colors: Stealth Black and Polar White. A notable feature of the Desire 210 is its dual SIM card support, allowing users to manage personal and work profiles easily from a single device.
Source: HTC.
“The HTC Desire 210 brings impressive technology and design to the entry-level smartphone market,” stated Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-210-an-entry-level-dual-sim-phone-is-priced-at-less-than-s-160/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Intercept Android Phone Goes NASCAR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s both thrilling and fast-paced, almost too much to handle?
NASCAR is a fitting example, but so is the Samsung Intercept Android phone. And surprisingly, they&amp;rsquo;re connected!
The Samsung Intercept M910 for Sprint is a dual phone, offering both a large 3-inch touchscreen display and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with spacious keys for efficient typing and texting.
As an Android 2.1 phone, it offers access to thousands of customizable apps from the Android market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phones become unresponsive due to Android vulnerability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</guid><description>Trend Micro has identified a weakness in the Android operating system that can cause a phone to seem non-functional. Affected phones exhibit symptoms like no ringing or notification sounds, an inability to make calls, and an unresponsive screen. Additionally, locked phones cannot be unlocked.
This vulnerability affects Android versions from 4.3 (Jelly Bean) to 5.1.1 (Lollipop), encompassing over half of all Android devices currently in use. Despite being reported to the Android Engineering Team in late May, no official fix has been released through the Android Open Source Project (AOSP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG G Flex2 provides a greater amount of curved excellence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 03:11:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the G Flex2, the newest iteration of its curved smartphone, at the 2015 International CES. The first G Flex received praise for its unique design and innovative approach. A year later, the G Flex2 improves upon its predecessor with an enhanced design, increased speed, and added user convenience.
The LG G Flex2 features a Qualcomm Snapdragon 810 processor for faster performance, making it the first smartphone to officially utilize this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-flex2-provides-a-greater-amount-of-curved-excellence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Altec Lansing introduces durable mobile accessories at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</guid><description>Altec Lansing is launching new lines of durable chargers, power banks, cables, and cases for smartphones and tablets. Expected to be available around the second quarter of 2016, these accessories will have rugged features like IP67-rated, military-grade construction for waterproof, dustproof, and shock-resistant functionality and device protection.
The new products will include:
Altec Lansing Everything Proof Power Packs (3,000, 6,000, and 10,000 mAh): These power banks are designed for smartphones, tablets, and MP3 players, offering up to 100 hours of talk time, 75 hours of music, 50 hours of video, or 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/altec-lansing-introduces-durable-mobile-accessories-at-ces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternative Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>For those living and working in rural areas, limited internet options can be a major problem. While major providers often only service cities, there are ways to stay connected without spending a fortune or waiting years for expanded infrastructure.
Forget DSL or cable – those are rare finds outside city limits. While universal telephone service guarantees basic phone lines (and thus, very slow dial-up internet), there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for fast, affordable internet: the existing cell phone network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI Mate 20 is receiving a warm welcome in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 19:18:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Huawei. Over one thousand people lined up at Causeway Point mall in Singapore for the HUAWEI Mate 20 series launch.
Huawei Consumer Business Group Singapore reported a queue of over a thousand people awaiting the launch of the HUAWEI Mate 20 series.
The first person in line, Kishore Lal, arrived at six in the morning and is a first-time Huawei user. He shared, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve read many positive reviews about Huawei smartphones and their camera quality, so I decided to try one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-20-is-receiving-a-warm-welcome-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI Mate 10 Pro was first launched in Singapore, making it the first country in the world to introduce the device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 00:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</guid><description>Huawei recently launched its Mate 10 Series smartphones, including the Mate 10, Mate 10 Pro, and PORSCHE DESIGN Mate 10, in Singapore. The launch makes Singapore the first country globally to have the Mate 10 Pro available for purchase.
A key feature of these phones is the Kirin 970 AI chipset, which significantly boosts system response speed and ensures smoother performance. According to Cheng Jiangfei, Country Head of Huawei Singapore, Consumer Business Group, the company is committed to providing Singaporean customers with the latest and greatest technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-mate-10-pro-was-first-launched-in-singapore-making-it-the-first-country-in-the-world-to-introduce-the-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sell Your Free Cell Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 21:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You were wise to get your new, top-of-the-line smartphone for free when you signed up for service. You understand that service plan costs are consistent, and it&amp;rsquo;s the phone&amp;rsquo;s price that fluctuates.
Now that your contract is up, it&amp;rsquo;s a great opportunity to upgrade. As you search for another discounted or free phone, you might wonder what to do with your old one.
Many people keep their old phones, thinking they might be helpful someday...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sell-your-free-cell-phone-for-cash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Vivo V5s smartphone guarantees improved selfie quality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vivo-v5s-smartphone-guarantees-improved-selfie-quality/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 01:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vivo-v5s-smartphone-guarantees-improved-selfie-quality/</guid><description>Source: Vivo. NBA star Stephen Curry promotes the Vivo V5s, a phone designed for capturing flawless selfies.
Vivo has unveiled its latest flagship phone, the V5s, furthering the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing users with the ability to take &amp;ldquo;perfect selfies&amp;rdquo;.
Alex Feng, Vivo&amp;rsquo;s Global VP, stated, &amp;ldquo;Our research indicates that selfies are a common part of our users&amp;rsquo; daily lives. The V5s is a revolutionary smartphone designed to help users achieve flawless selfies, even in low light, and satisfy their desire for naturally enhanced portraits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vivo-v5s-smartphone-guarantees-improved-selfie-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vivo-v5s-smartphone-guarantees-improved-selfie-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Captivated By Samsung’s Android Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:23:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</guid><description>Ready for the newest smartphones? Check out the Samsung Captivate, available through AT&amp;amp;T. It&amp;rsquo;s a fast, sleek, and runs on the Android operating system – specifically, the Galaxy Android version.
The Samsung Galaxy series is creating a lot of excitement. These phones will have different names depending on the carrier. The Captivate is specifically designed for AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s network, and it lives up to its name!
This phone pushes the boundaries of slimness, measuring a mere 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/captivated-by-samsung-s-android-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro demonstrates ways to enhance the security of Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</guid><description>In 2014, Android controlled the global smartphone market, shipping one billion units and representing 81% of all smartphones shipped, as reported by Strategy Analytics.
Trend Micro researcher, Paul Oliveria, points out that Android&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its affordability, efficient data storage, and availability across various brands and price points.
This widespread use makes Android a prime target for hackers. To combat this, Trend Micro proposes seven security measures for mobile users:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting on August 17, Singtel will be accepting pre-orders for the Samsung Galaxy Note7</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The Galaxy Note7.
Singtel has revealed that registered customers can pre-order Samsung&amp;rsquo;s Galaxy Note7 starting August 17th. Pre-orders will be delivered or available for pickup on August 19th, preceding the official launch.
The large-screen Galaxy Note7 and its S Pen boast IP68 certification, making them water and dust resistant. The Note7 features cutting-edge iris recognition technology for enhanced security, complementing the defense-grade Samsung Knox security platform for an unparalleled level of protection and user-friendliness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-on-august-17-singtel-will-be-accepting-pre-orders-for-the-samsung-galaxy-note7/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BlackBerry Storm Just Blew In at a Lower Price</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 02:51:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on getting a BlackBerry Storm in stores. You can buy one online from Cell Phone Plans Finder with free shipping.
Although I can&amp;rsquo;t disclose the price here, you can easily find it on the cellphone special offers page. You can then order the phone with your preferred Verizon Wireless service package, all delivered directly to you without shipping fees.
The BlackBerry Storm 9530 Black, the first BlackBerry with a touch keyboard, offers a unique experience for those accustomed to physical keys...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-blackberry-storm-just-blew-in-at-a-lower-price/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G1 Google Android Phone Gets Vocal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 08:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</guid><description>Choosing your next smartphone can be tough. Touchscreen phones like Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone, the BlackBerry Bold, and Samsung Delve are appealing, but some prefer a physical QWERTY keyboard. The BlackBerry Pearl&amp;rsquo;s trackball navigation is another option. Connectivity matters too, with 3G being desirable but not always accessible. WiFi capability for fast web browsing is also important.
The HTC-built G1 for T-Mobile might be the solution if you want it all. This &amp;ldquo;Android Phone,&amp;rdquo; marking Google&amp;rsquo;s entry into mobile wireless, operates on T-Mobile&amp;rsquo;s network, offering quad-band service and various data features...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g1-google-android-phone-gets-vocal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC HD2 Smartphone With Movies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</guid><description>Have you ever been offered a cell phone with two full-length movies already on it? That&amp;rsquo;s only the beginning of what the HTC HD2 smartphone for T-Mobile offers. This phone doesn&amp;rsquo;t just offer entertainment, it delivers it in spades!
The massive touchscreen display immediately suggests this phone is designed for multimedia. It boasts a 4.3-inch screen with 800 x 480 pixel resolution. Those specs sound more like a small computer than a phone, and that&amp;rsquo;s a good thing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-hd2-smartphone-with-movies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TaxiPixi cab booking app is now available in Kuala Lumpur and will soon be expanding to more countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 04:44:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid><description>TaxiPixi, a cab booking app, has expanded its reach to Malaysia and will be pre-installed on Celkon phones in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal.
Developed by India-based On Time Technologies, TaxiPixi launched in Malaysia this week. Celkon, a mobile phone manufacturer, will pre-install the app on its devices in several countries. Pradeep Yerraguntla, Celkon&amp;rsquo;s Head of Digital, stated that Celkon will promote the app through its app store and website, targeting consumers in India, Sri Lanka, South Africa, and Nepal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/taxipixi-cab-booking-app-is-now-available-in-kuala-lumpur-and-will-soon-be-expanding-to-more-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Smartphone of Mythic Proportions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-smartphone-of-mythic-proportions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 18:26:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-smartphone-of-mythic-proportions/</guid><description>Thinking about a new smartphone? Don&amp;rsquo;t settle for just any phone when you can get a fantastic deal on the Samsung Mythic A897 Black for AT&amp;amp;T. This high-end phone is surprisingly available for free with an instant online discount and free shipping.
What makes this phone so special? It boasts a vibrant 3.3-inch touchscreen display, perfect for enjoying AT&amp;amp;T Mobile TV and engaging in video calls with AT&amp;amp;T Video Share. This phone is also 3G and world-phone capable, operating on AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s GSM network for extensive coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-smartphone-of-mythic-proportions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-smartphone-of-mythic-proportions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry 8830 is World Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</guid><description>Verizon Wireless has engineered a BlackBerry that functions domestically and internationally. This is notable because Verizon uses the CDMA network in the US, while the rest of the world primarily uses GSM.
Previously, this difference prevented Verizon phones from roaming internationally. To solve this, Verizon created a device with both CDMA and GSM capabilities. In the US, the CDMA component accesses the 800 and 1900 MHz bands, including EV-DO broadband. Outside the US, the GSM component accesses the 900 and 1800 MHz bands, including GPRS broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Less expensive smartphones are available for those in developing markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</guid><description>To prepare for future growth, smartphone manufacturers are looking beyond China to other emerging markets. Although China represented a third of global smartphone shipments in 2013, the International Data Corporation (IDC) indicates this market is reaching its saturation point.
IDC reports that smartphones constitute over 80% of China&amp;rsquo;s total phone sales. Consequently, they predict that India and Africa will be the primary sources of the next half billion smartphone customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC unveils its latest flagship smartphone, the HTC 10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/</guid><description>Source: HTC. HTC Themes allows users to personalize their phones with thousands of professionally designed themes, each featuring unique icons, backgrounds, and sounds.
HTC has introduced its newest flagship smartphone, the HTC 10. Representing &amp;ldquo;the Power of 10&amp;rdquo; - signifying greatness and independence - this latest addition to the HTC phone lineup combines what HTC claims is the best smartphone camera available, the first-ever stereo 24-bit high-resolution audio recording capability in a smartphone, and exceptional performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-unveils-its-latest-flagship-smartphone-the-htc-10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Cash For Your Used or Broken iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</guid><description>Your old iPhone may be worse for wear, but don&amp;rsquo;t throw it away! It&amp;rsquo;s still valuable. Discarding it wastes money and harms the environment when you can easily sell it for cash.
Surprisingly, companies will buy your used iPhone regardless of its condition. Naturally, better condition means more money, but even damaged phones have value, ranging from a few dollars to over $100! A functional iPhone 4S can fetch over $100, far more than you&amp;rsquo;d get tossing it in the garbage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-cash-for-your-used-or-broken-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smartphone manufacturers are experimenting with various marketing strategies to stand out in the competitive Indian market</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 20:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</guid><description>Source: Zinnov website.
As the Indian smartphone market becomes more competitive, vendors are shifting their go-to-market approaches, according to management consultancy Zinnov. In their report &amp;ldquo;India Smartphone Market: Witnessing Exponential Growth,&amp;rdquo; Zinnov highlights the intense pressure local vendors face from Chinese competitors. Xiaomi, for example, recently took the lead in 4G LTE smartphone sales, and Micromax is challenging Samsung&amp;rsquo;s dominance.
To stand out, smartphone vendors are exploring different strategies. These include online-only retail partnerships (like Motorola&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Flipkart), establishing physical experience centers to enhance customer interaction (such as Xiaomi&amp;rsquo;s plan for 100 centers in India), and investing in traditional brick-and-mortar retail models (like Gionee&amp;rsquo;s plan for 250 stores)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartphone-manufacturers-are-experimenting-with-various-marketing-strategies-to-stand-out-in-the-competitive-indian-market/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The iPhone SE is introduced by Apple</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 06:02:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Apple has launched the iPhone SE, boasting a 4-inch display and impressive processing power in a familiar compact design. This updated model features smooth, angled edges, a color-coordinated stainless steel Apple logo, and a choice of four metallic finishes, including rose gold.
“The iPhone SE is a fresh take on a beloved design — we took a popular, iconic look and completely redesigned its internals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-se-is-introduced-by-apple/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Recycle Your BlackBerry Phone For Cash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 10:44:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/</guid><description>You can make money off your old BlackBerry phone instead of throwing it away. Even without a service plan, your old BlackBerry might be worth a significant amount of money depending on its model, age, and condition. Selling it yourself can be a hassle, but there&amp;rsquo;s an easier way.
An electronics recycling company will pay cash for used BlackBerry phones and other cell phone models. To see if yours qualifies, visit their website and search for your BlackBerry model...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-your-blackberry-phone-for-cash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee has started a sale on mobile phones in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Shopee, a leading mobile marketplace in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, is holding a Lowest Price Guaranteed Mobile Phone Sale in Malaysia until April 27, 2017. This sale offers discounts of up to 80% on popular smartphone brands like Apple, Samsung, and Huawei. Shopee is committed to offering the lowest prices and will compensate shoppers 120% of the price difference if a phone is found cheaper on another platform.
This sale features phones priced as low as RM60, with deals on models like the Samsung Galaxy J2 Prime and the Apple iPhone 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-has-started-a-sale-on-mobile-phones-in-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Vu to an iPhone Kill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:52:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</guid><description>The Apple iPhone 3G is the current target for every cell phone company, indicating its leading position in the market. While iPhone enthusiasts might find alternatives underwhelming, the LG Vu smartphone offers a compelling option with unique features.
One standout feature is live TV. The LG Vu CU920 supports AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s MEdia FLO, a subscription-based digital TV service delivered through a dedicated over-the-air broadcasting system, requiring specific hardware in compatible phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-vu-to-an-iphone-kill/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID vs DROID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:58:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</guid><description>The DROID phone, running Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system, actually has two versions produced by different companies with distinct specifications. So, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to differentiate between the two.
The first DROID, manufactured by Motorola for Verizon Wireless, is a touchscreen QWERTY smartphone utilizing the Android 2.0 operating system. This innovative device was recognized as Time.com&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Top Gadget of 2009&amp;rdquo;.
This top-tier DROID boasts a 5.0-megapixel camera, doubling as a camcorder, with features like geo-tagging, auto-stabilization, flash, and built-in editing tools...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-vs-droid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A new budget-friendly Lumia is about to be released</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 10:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. The Lumia 430.
Microsoft has released the Lumia 430 Dual SIM, its most budget-friendly Lumia smartphone that can be upgraded to Windows 10*. Priced at approximately S$119, the Lumia 430 joins Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s affordable smartphone lineup alongside the Lumia 435, which features Lumia Camera.
Equipped with Windows Phone 8.1, a Qualcomm Snapdragon processor with a 1.2GHz dual-core CPU, and pre-installed Microsoft Office, Skype, and OneDrive, the Lumia 430 Dual SIM enables users to be productive at work, enjoy entertainment, and stay connected while on the move...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-budget-friendly-lumia-is-about-to-be-released/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The V40ThinQ smartphone by LG has been revealed in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has launched the LG V40ThinQ, a new smartphone with five cameras. Designed for today&amp;rsquo;s multimedia storytellers, the device is marketed as a powerful tool for content creation.
Source: LG.
Staying true to the V series design, the LG V40ThinQ boasts an enhanced 6.4&amp;quot; FullVision OLED display with even slimmer bezels. It runs on the Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 Mobile Platform, coupled with 6 GB of RAM and 128 GB of internal storage, promising a superior smartphone camera experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-v40thinq-smartphone-by-lg-has-been-revealed-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Smartphone Business Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-smartphone-business-office/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 19:32:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-smartphone-business-office/</guid><description>Microelectronics have brought us the era of the portable office, enabling employees and independent professionals to work from anywhere.
This freedom is thanks to the smartphone, which combines a cell phone and a computer. While each uses its own wireless network, they work together to support your work.
Voice communication happens through the cell phone. Many professionals use Bluetooth headsets, not just to free their hands but also to view the screen and utilize apps while talking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-smartphone-business-office/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-smartphone-business-office/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID 2 Global is a World Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 03:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</guid><description>The DROID 2 Global is a smartphone with a 1.2 GHz processor capable of making and receiving calls in over 200 countries. This Verizon phone works internationally through its unique ability to utilize both GSM and CDMA networks.
While Verizon primarily uses CDMA, incompatible with most global networks, the DROID 2 Global incorporates multiple network support. This includes WCDMA, GSM, HSDPA, CDMA EV-DO, EDGE, GPRS, and HSUPA, encompassing various forms of communication...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel announces pricing for iPhone SE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</guid><description>Source: Apple. The iPhone SE.
Singtel has revealed its plans to offer Apple&amp;rsquo;s 4-inch iPhone SE starting March 31, 2016. Customers can pre-order the device now. A 16 GB model with the most affordable plan, costing S$27.90 per month for two years, is priced at S$350.
The telecom provider recently conducted a crowdsourced study, highlighting its superior 4G network speed and coverage in Singapore. The study, based on data from IDA&amp;rsquo;s MyConnection SG crowdsourced survey and 4G Mobile Service Coverage results, positioned Singtel as a frontrunner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-announces-pricing-for-iphone-se/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the Sony Xperia XA1, Xperia XZ1, and Xperia XZ1 Compact by #SonyMobileSG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications has introduced the Xperia XZ1 and Xperia XZ1 Compact, expanding its flagship smartphone lineup. These phones are equipped with cutting-edge technology, including the Motion Eye camera, capable of capturing detail beyond human perception, and innovative 3D scanning for mobile devices.
The Xperia XZ1 boasts a 5.2” Full HD HDR display enhanced with Sony&amp;rsquo;s BRAVIA TV technology, delivering vibrant colors and sharp contrast. In contrast, the Xperia XZ1 Compact offers top-tier features in a compact design with a 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-sony-xperia-xa1-xperia-xz1-and-xperia-xz1-compact-by-sonymobilesg/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID is the Woid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 09:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</guid><description>Motorola and Verizon have partnered to challenge the dominant Apple iPhone with their highly anticipated DROID phone. Powered by the Google Android 2.0 operating system, the DROID promises exceptional functionality. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore its features.
A key distinction between the iPhone and most other smartphones, aside from the BlackBerry Storm, is the inclusion of a physical keyboard. For those accustomed to texting on physical keys, transitioning to a touchscreen keyboard can be challenging...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-is-the-woid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing work and play on your smartphone: Four helpful tips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft. View the full infographic.
It&amp;rsquo;s becoming harder to separate our work and personal lives with smartphones being used for both. For instance, Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Lumia 640 and 640 XL come with an Office 365 subscription.
Dr. Mark Batey, an Organizational Psychologist at Manchester Business School in the UK, collaborated with Microsoft to offer advice on finding a good balance:
1. Capture inspiration immediately.
He says, &amp;ldquo;Make use of note-taking apps on your phone to jot down brilliant ideas as they come, anytime and anywhere...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-work-and-play-on-your-smartphone-four-helpful-tips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have you ever witnessed the power of a Leica Triple Camera and a single flash?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</guid><description>On the evenings of October 19th and 20th, Singaporeans were introduced to the distinctive HUAWEI Mate 20 Matrix Camera System through a series of unannounced projections.
This recognizable design, featuring a square arrangement of three Leica cameras and a flash, was displayed on buildings throughout Singapore, including Tampines Mall, Bugis+, and Star Vista. This camera setup, found on the back of HUAWEI Mate 20 smartphones, uses a 12 MP main RGB lens, an 8 MP telephoto lens, and a 16 MP ultra-wide-angle lens, all from Leica, along with a flash...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-you-ever-witnessed-the-power-of-a-leica-triple-camera-and-a-single-flash/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going Incognito With SANYO and Sprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</guid><description>When you need a phone for discreet texting, the SANYO Incognito from Sprint is the perfect choice. Its sleek, minimalist design resembles a small, black monolith. Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by its understated appearance, though, as this phone is packed with features. The mirrored shell conceals a monochrome display and essential buttons for making calls.
Open the SANYO Incognito to reveal a full QWERTY keyboard with generously sized keys, perfect for rapid texting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Omnia Smartphone for Smart People</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 21:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Omnia&amp;rdquo; means &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; in Latin, a fitting name for a high-tech wireless device designed for mobile professionals.
The Samsung Omnia is a cutting-edge smartphone using the Windows Mobile 6.1 Pro operating system. It boasts a complete HTML web browser, Opera Mobile, on a 3.2-inch LCD touchscreen enhanced with Samsung TouchWiz technology. This technology provides tactile feedback through slight vibrations, while an accelerometer automatically adjusts the display based on the phone&amp;rsquo;s orientation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-omnia-smartphone-for-smart-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Desk Just Moved To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 10:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The 20th century saw a significant shift in employment, moving from farm work to factory jobs and finally to office positions. Now, the 21st century is experiencing another major change as workplaces transition from offices to the cloud.
The Cloud is Here and Now
Contrary to the idea of the cloud being a distant concept, it has become an integral part of our present reality. Nearly everything we do has or will soon have a cloud connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-desk-just-moved-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The iPhone 8 and 8 Plus will be released in late September</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/</guid><description>Apple has unveiled the iPhone 8 and iPhone 8 Plus, featuring a sleek glass and aluminum design available in three colors. The new models boast Retina HD displays, the powerful A11 Bionic chip, and are optimized for augmented reality (AR) experiences.
Source: Apple. The new iPhone 8 and iPhone
8 Plus feature all-glass designs.
The inclusion of single and dual cameras with Portrait Lighting on the iPhone 8 Plus, along with wireless charging capabilities, brings exciting new features to the iPhone lineup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-iphone-8-and-8-plus-will-be-released-in-late-september/</a></p></description></item><item><title>There is currently a blanket flight ban for the Samsung Note7, and the issue of owners currently overseas has not been addressed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</guid><description>Airlines across the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions are mirroring a ban started by the US Department of Transportation (DOT), the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), and the Pipeline and Hazardous Materials Safety Administration (PHMSA). The US ban prohibits all Samsung Galaxy Note7 smartphones from air travel. This restriction was announced on October 14th (October 15th, Singapore time) and went into effect at noon, eastern time on October 15th (October 16th, Singapore time)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-currently-a-blanket-flight-ban-for-the-samsung-note7-and-the-issue-of-owners-currently-overseas-has-not-been-addressed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HUAWEI P30 completely sold out on its first day in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 19:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Huawei P30 Series launched in Singapore at VivoCity yesterday and quickly sold out, with the first people in line having arrived the night before to buy the newest model in Huawei&amp;rsquo;s photography-focused smartphone line.
The Huawei P30 Series has garnered attention since its global launch last week in France for its Leica Quad Camera, the first of its kind, which boasts cutting-edge zoom and low-light capabilities.
Yvelyn Tey, the first person in line, waited with her fiance to purchase the phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p30-completely-sold-out-on-its-first-day-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Samsung Epic 4G offers Epic Performance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 17:56:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</guid><description>Imagine a smartphone so powerful it surpasses a netbook. Picture yourself declining WiFi because your cellular connection is faster. That&amp;rsquo;s the kind of speed the Samsung Epic 4G offers with its impressive 10+ Mbps download speeds, thanks to the Sprint WiMAX 4G network. You can even share your connection as a mobile hotspot for your other devices.
Beyond speed, the Epic boasts a stunning Super AMOLED touchscreen display with near-HD quality and unmatched contrast...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-samsung-epic-4g-offers-epic-performance/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In February, the Pink Gold version of Huawei's Mate 10 Pro will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:23:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</guid><description>Huawei has added a new Pink Gold color option to its Mate 10 Pro lineup. However, it is a limited edition with only 1,000 sets available in Singapore.
The HUAWEI Mate 10 Pro features the world’s first AI chipset, the Kirin 970, and dual Leica SUMMILUX-H f1.6 lenses for exceptional image quality.
Here are some key features:
A 6-inch HUAWEI FullView OLED display. The intelligent Kirin 970 AI processor, capable of adapting and reacting to real-world scenarios instantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-february-the-pink-gold-version-of-huawei-s-mate-10-pro-will-be-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mandarin Orchard and Marina Mandarin in Singapore are now providing free local smartphone services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 20:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</guid><description>The Mandarin Orchard Singapore and Marina Mandarin Singapore have added a convenient amenity to all guestrooms: &amp;ldquo;handy,&amp;rdquo; a smartphone solution. This provides registered guests with complimentary unlimited 4G data, local and international calls, online city guides, and ticket booking services for Singapore attractions. Both hotels are managed by Meritus Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts.
With handy now available in all 1,077 rooms at Mandarin Orchard Singapore and 575 rooms at Marina Mandarin Singapore, guests can stay connected while exploring Singapore using their own personalized smartphone outside the hotel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mandarin-orchard-and-marina-mandarin-in-singapore-are-now-providing-free-local-smartphone-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Daddy Wants a BlackBerry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</guid><description>With Father&amp;rsquo;s Day around the corner, forget the usual tie or car-related gifts. This year, give Dad what he truly desires: a cutting-edge BlackBerry Bold for both work and personal use. And here&amp;rsquo;s a secret: you can find it online at a great price.
The BlackBerry Bold combines style and functionality. Its sleek black design exudes professionalism and practicality. This BlackBerry boasts an impressive email client with the renowned &amp;ldquo;push&amp;rdquo; email feature, seamlessly integrating up to 10 accounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG has introduced the G3 Beat, a mid-tier model of the G3, in Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG Electronics (LG) introduced the LG G3 Beat in Korea on July 18th. This mid-range version of their flagship G3 smartphone provides a comparable high-quality experience, incorporating the Floating Arc design and rapid Laser Auto Focus technology in a smaller form factor with a 5-inch thin-bezel display.
Dr. Jong-seok Park, President and CEO of LG Electronics Mobile Communications Company, emphasized the growing consumer demand for a balanced mix of aesthetics, functionality, performance, and affordability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-has-introduced-the-g3-beat-a-mid-tier-model-of-the-g3-in-korea/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei smartphones in Singapore are now receiving the EMUI 9.1 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 06:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group started releasing its newest software update, EMUI 9.1, in Singapore on June 27th. This version is based on Android 9.0 Pie.
The update will be available in stages, beginning with the Mate 20 Series in late June. Following that, the P20 Series and Nova 3 Series will get the update in July, and finally, models like the Mate RS, P10, and P10 Plus will receive it in August...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-smartphones-in-singapore-are-now-receiving-the-emui-9-1-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei is advancing while other smartphone vendors are trying to catch up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 21:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</guid><description>Huawei&amp;rsquo;s consumer division introduces the Mate 20 smartphone series, emphasizing a blend of aesthetics and innovation. This lineup offers various sizes and models, including the Mate 20, Mate 20 Pro, Mate 20 X, and the Porsche Design Mate 20 RS. Richard Yu, CEO of Huawei Consumer Business Group, highlights the series&amp;rsquo; role as a digital companion, enhancing users&amp;rsquo; lives through advanced technology.
Design The Mate 20 series prioritizes comfortable one-hand use, with nature-inspired design elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-is-advancing-while-other-smartphone-vendors-are-trying-to-catch-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Android Phone to Devour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 06:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</guid><description>Interested in getting a Google Android smartphone? The Motorola DEVOUR Silver might be the one for you. This Android 1.6 smartphone features a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and a 3.1-inch touchscreen, all within a sleek silver design.
The DEVOUR uses MOTOBLUR, a service that seamlessly syncs your messages, status updates, and contacts directly to your customizable home screens. This eliminates the need to log in or open individual apps, giving you instant access to your information...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-android-phone-to-devour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV2 Sparks Envy Too</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</guid><description>The LG enV, nicknamed the &amp;ldquo;envy phone,&amp;rdquo; certainly attracted attention. Its successor, the enV2 VX9100, takes it up a notch, especially for those who love texting, gaming, and enjoying media on their phone.
The standout feature of the enV2 is its hidden full QWERTY keyboard. No need to fumble with a virtual keyboard on this phone! It boasts a real keyboard with comfortably sized keys. Keep your enV2 closed for calls, just like any other standard phone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env2-sparks-envy-too/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei has released the schedule for the EMUI10 update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</guid><description>Huawei has released the global update schedule for EMUI 10. This latest version features an updated interface, a &amp;ldquo;Dark Mode&amp;rdquo; setting, performance and security improvements, and &amp;ldquo;Multi-screen Collaboration&amp;rdquo; which allows Huawei PCs and Android devices to seamlessly connect.
Starting this month, users with the HUAWEI P30 Pro, HUAWEI P30, HUAWEI Mate 20 Pro, HUAWEI Mate 20, HUAWEI Mate 20 X (4G) and HUAWEI nova 5T will get push notifications to install the EMUI 10 update...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-released-the-schedule-for-the-emui10-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry's Bold Move to HSDPA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</guid><description>BlackBerry, the company known for its wireless devices, is launching a new model called &amp;ldquo;Bold&amp;rdquo; with enhanced features like a sharper display, increased storage, a faster processor, and a 2-megapixel camera. However, the most significant advancement lies in its connectivity. The Bold surpasses standard EDGE data services by incorporating tri-band HSDPA and Wi-Fi, catering to the growing demand for desktop-like web browsing and video streaming among professionals.
Adding to the excitement, rumors are circulating about Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone selling out in anticipation of a new model featuring HSDPA technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guests at ibis Singapore on Bencoolen can enjoy complimentary calls and data with the smartphone service provided</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</guid><description>The ibis Singapore on Bencoolen hotel now offers guests a &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; smartphone service with unlimited 3G internet, free local and international calls, and a comprehensive Singapore city guide.
Source: Accor.
The handy smartphone.
This service, included in the &amp;rsquo;extra benefits&amp;rsquo; room package, provides a smartphone for use both within the hotel and around Singapore, allowing guests to stay connected and navigate the city without incurring high data charges. The &amp;ldquo;handy&amp;rdquo; phone also aligns with the hotel&amp;rsquo;s sustainability goals by replacing printed materials like in-room directories with a digital alternative and offering information about the hotel&amp;rsquo;s environmentally friendly initiatives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-at-ibis-singapore-on-bencoolen-can-enjoy-complimentary-calls-and-data-with-the-smartphone-service-provided/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Honor Magic is redefining the limits of smartphone capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Honor. Honor Magic utilizes AI technology to anticipate user needs.
Honor, a Huawei Group brand targeting young, tech-savvy consumers, celebrated its third anniversary by introducing the innovative Honor Magic smartphone. This device incorporates artificial intelligence (AI) for a more interactive user experience.
The Honor Magic boasts a sleek and ergonomic design featuring a 3D curved glass body. Powered by a Kirin 950 processor, it offers a 5.09&amp;quot; 2K AMOLED curved screen, intelligent sensors, and advanced recognition technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/honor-magic-is-redefining-the-limits-of-smartphone-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC introduces the Desire 616 dual SIM smartphone for entry-level users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 14:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</guid><description>HTC, a company known for mobile innovation and design, has introduced the HTC Desire 616 dual sim phone. This new phone offers high-end features at an affordable price. Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;The HTC Desire 616 dual sim is a powerful phone with a great price tag,&amp;rdquo; says Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia. &amp;ldquo;This new phone in the popular HTC Desire line offers an eight-core processor, fast processing speeds, and top-tier features at an accessible price, giving users a best-in-class experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-introduces-the-desire-616-dual-sim-smartphone-for-entry-level-users/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going Rogue But Not Rouge With Samsung</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a go-getter in need of a powerful cell phone that won&amp;rsquo;t let you down, the Samsung Rogue U960 Black for Verizon Wireless is a top contender among smartphones.
Does your current phone offer easy access to social media apps like Facebook and MySpace? How about web browsing, YouTube videos, and photo editing on a bright screen, even in sunlight? Can you stream music wirelessly, get directions, or message easily with a physical QWERTY keyboard?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Huawei P10 Plus has the potential to serve as a substitute for a digital SLR camera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:13:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</guid><description>Fashion and beauty photographer Richard Chen, also a Leica Akademie Instructor, believes the Huawei P10 Plus offers the capabilities of a professional camera in a pocket-sized device.
During a Huawei P10 Plus Masterclass held in Singapore, Chen, a professional Leica photographer, shared his growing preference for the Huawei P10 Plus&amp;rsquo;s mobile camera over traditional cameras for personal photography. He appreciates the portability and convenience of the smartphone, noting, &amp;ldquo;If I&amp;rsquo;m exploring I actually don&amp;rsquo;t bring the (conventional digital) camera nowadays&amp;hellip; I&amp;rsquo;m starting to use it as the main camera...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-huawei-p10-plus-has-the-potential-to-serve-as-a-substitute-for-a-digital-slr-camera/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alcatel A5 LED is the first smartphone in the world to feature an interactive LED cover</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-a5-led-is-the-first-smartphone-in-the-world-to-feature-an-interactive-led-cover/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 22:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-a5-led-is-the-first-smartphone-in-the-world-to-feature-an-interactive-led-cover/</guid><description>Source: Alcatel. The Alcatel A5 LED features colorful light shows.
Alcatel unveiled the A5 LED smartphone at Mobile World Congress. As the first smartphone globally to feature an interactive LED cover, the A5 LED redefines personalization.
&amp;ldquo;The A5 LED allows Alcatel to provide entertaining new features. These include illuminated notifications, customizable LED cover patterns and themes, and an improved multimedia experience. It also offers more ways to capture and share selfies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-a5-led-is-the-first-smartphone-in-the-world-to-feature-an-interactive-led-cover/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alcatel-a5-led-is-the-first-smartphone-in-the-world-to-feature-an-interactive-led-cover/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Ally In The Android vs iPhone Battle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 20:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</guid><description>LG&amp;rsquo;s initial Android offering, the LG Ally for Verizon Wireless, is a remarkable device. It boasts a range of features and access to a vast library of apps on the Android Market.
If you prioritize texting and email, you&amp;rsquo;ll appreciate the tactile feedback of real keys. The LG Ally features a 3.2-inch touchscreen and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with well-sized keys. With five customizable home screens, you can personalize it with numerous Android apps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-ally-in-the-android-vs-iphone-battle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC Aria Social Networking Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to stay connected, forget dogs – get FriendStream! This service lets you interact with friends through Facebook, Twitter, and Flickr, all from the HTC Aria, a cutting-edge Android smartphone.
The Aria boasts a sleek, seamless design crafted from a single piece of black aluminum. It&amp;rsquo;s compact enough for your pocket yet powerful enough for work and play. Its sizable 3.2-inch touchscreen features pinch-to-zoom functionality, automatically adjusting text size for comfortable website browsing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new Mate 10 from Huawei: a portable desktop experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 12:38:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</guid><description>The Huawei Mate 10, unveiled in 2017, builds upon the success of its predecessors like the Mate 7 and Mate 9, offering even more power and efficiency in a compact design. Distinguishing itself as a pocket desktop, the Mate 10 series, particularly the Mate 10 and Mate 10 Pro models, boasts a pioneering AI processor known as the Kirin 970. This processor integrates a neural-network processing unit (NPU), enabling functionalities like real-time computer vision and enhanced photography...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-mate-10-from-huawei-a-portable-desktop-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Red, Red, LG Vu Wine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 22:49:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</guid><description>Everyone enjoys a nice wine with dinner, but what about in business or on the go? It&amp;rsquo;s perfectly acceptable when that &amp;ldquo;wine&amp;rdquo; is the new touchscreen phone available from AT&amp;amp;T.
This &amp;ldquo;red wine&amp;rdquo; phone boasts more features than a full-bodied Cabernet. Its compact size of 4.3 x 2.1 x 0.5 inches makes it easy to carry in your pocket or bag. You read that correctly – this device is only half an inch thin!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-red-lg-vu-wine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Democracy In a Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/democracy-in-a-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 02:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/democracy-in-a-cell-phone/</guid><description>At this very moment, the American Red Cross has already received $22 million in donations for Haiti earthquake relief through text messages, a number that is expected to climb even higher. This massive demonstration of support is considered groundbreaking, possibly indicating a societal shift rather than a one-time occurrence.
The $22 million figure is impressive considering it was accumulated in approximately a week, with each donor contributing $10. This means millions of people acted independently yet almost simultaneously when the call for help was issued...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/democracy-in-a-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/democracy-in-a-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new smartphones and audio-visual solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications (Sony Mobile) has introduced new consumer experiences centered around innovation.
“Xperia Touch represents a groundbreaking interface,&amp;quot; stated Hiroki Totoki, President and CEO of Sony Mobile Communications. &amp;ldquo;A year after revealing our updated brand direction and vision for the future of communications, we are not only introducing the Xperia XZ Premium, packed with cutting-edge technologies to improve core smartphone features, but also creating entirely new interactive communication experiences with our Xperia Smart Products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>