<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Headphones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headphones/</link><description>Recent content in Headphones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/headphones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intel-powered SMS Audio headphones will monitor fitness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</guid><description>Intel and SMS Audio, a headphone and accessories company founded by Curtis &amp;ldquo;50 Cent&amp;rdquo; Jackson, have teamed up to create the SMS Audio BioSport In-Ear Headphones powered by Intel. This new personal audio system aims to blend technology with fitness.
These headphones, part of the recently introduced SMS Audio Sport Collection, are engineered to provide high-quality audio while simultaneously collecting valuable fitness data.
Michael Bell, Corporate VP and GM of the New Devices Group at Intel, emphasized the significance of this collaboration, stating that it signifies Intel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to leading innovation in wearable technology and merging lifestyle with technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-powered-sms-audio-headphones-will-monitor-fitness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Jabra Halo Smart is designed to enhance both your calling and music experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</guid><description>Jabra Halo Smart headphones are designed for users who prioritize call quality but also enjoy listening to music. Research indicates that 79% of consumers desire headphones suitable for both calls and music, yet find most music headphones lacking in call performance.
These headphones prioritize calls with features like high-quality microphones, wind-noise reduction, and a dedicated button for Google Now or Siri. At the same time, they offer great audio quality for music with 10mm speakers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-jabra-halo-smart-is-designed-to-enhance-both-your-calling-and-music-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BeoPlay H8 wireless headphones have made their debut in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 09:59:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/</guid><description>The Beoplay H8 headphones, in argilla bright.
BANG &amp;amp; OLUFSEN introduces their wireless headphones: elegant and with a long battery life. The B&amp;amp;O PLAY headphones provide up to 14 hours of battery life with active noise cancellation. Their lightweight design features a sleek aluminum touch interface.
Controlling the B&amp;amp;O PLAY Beoplay H8 on-ear headphones is done through gestures on the aluminum ear cup. Tapping and swiping can control various activities, like answering calls, adjusting the volume, selecting tracks, and activating or deactivating noise cancellation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beoplay-h8-wireless-headphones-have-made-their-debut-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience all-day flexibility with the Plantronics BackBeat 100 Series Wireless Headphones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:37:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</guid><description>Plantronics, a company known for its audio and wearable technology, has introduced the BackBeat 100 Series. These headphones are the newest addition to their BackBeat stereo product line and offer a unique hybrid neckband design for wireless calls and music.
The BackBeat 100 and BackBeat 105 are designed for comfort throughout the day with an ultra-lightweight build. They provide full-range sound with enhanced bass, making them ideal for listening to music and watching videos on the move...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-all-day-flexibility-with-the-plantronics-backbeat-100-series-wireless-headphones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The market welcomes four new Surfaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 08:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</guid><description>Microsoft has introduced four new Surface products designed for the modern world.
Source: Microsoft website. The Surface Pro 6.
&amp;ldquo;Today, people need devices and technology that move with them and are ready whenever and wherever inspiration strikes,&amp;rdquo; stated Microsoft Chief Product Officer, Panos Panay, in a blog post.
&amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s the power of Surface, Windows, and Office working together through the cloud to provide the perfect tool. We designed these products together, optimizing every detail to empower your productivity and creativity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-market-welcomes-four-new-surfaces/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LinkBuds S from Sony provide an immersive audio experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</guid><description>Source: Sony. The LinkBuds S.
Sony has expanded its LinkBuds series with the new LinkBuds S. This model offers a new audio experience by utilizing Sony&amp;rsquo;s sensor technology and collaborations, while still providing a seamless &amp;ldquo;always-on&amp;rdquo; experience.
The LinkBuds S boast both noise cancellation and high-resolution audio capabilities. These headphones allow users to stay connected to their surroundings with the LinkBuds&amp;rsquo; ambient sound feature or minimize distractions with high-quality noise cancellation, letting them fully enjoy their preferred content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-linkbuds-s-from-sony-provide-an-immersive-audio-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sony introduces new smartphones and audio-visual solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</guid><description>Sony Mobile Communications (Sony Mobile) has introduced new consumer experiences centered around innovation.
“Xperia Touch represents a groundbreaking interface,&amp;quot; stated Hiroki Totoki, President and CEO of Sony Mobile Communications. &amp;ldquo;A year after revealing our updated brand direction and vision for the future of communications, we are not only introducing the Xperia XZ Premium, packed with cutting-edge technologies to improve core smartphone features, but also creating entirely new interactive communication experiences with our Xperia Smart Products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-introduces-new-smartphones-and-audio-visual-solutions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>