<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payment on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payment/</link><description>Recent content in Payment on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 01:37:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instarem introduces a new mobile application for consumers in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 01:37:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instarem-introduces-a-new-mobile-application-for-consumers-in-singapore/</guid><description>Instarem, a digital platform for international payments, has updated its website and mobile app for users in Singapore. The company will also introduce a groundbreaking consumer debit card called Amaze later this year.
Instarem has revamped its brand and released a new app specifically designed for the Singapore market.
This rebranding goes beyond simply improving global consumer remittances. Instarem aims to simplify the complexities of international payments, providing its customers with an intuitive, transparent, and affordable way to manage their money.</description></item><item><title>Purchase online and make your payment at a nearby convenience store</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 01:47:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/purchase-online-and-make-your-payment-at-a-nearby-convenience-store/</guid><description>MOLPay, a Southeast Asian online payment provider, is partnering with 7-Eleven Malaysia to introduce a new e-commerce payment method.
This service, called MOLPay CASH, will launch first in select Klang Valley 7-Eleven stores, with 735 stores currently offering this option and plans for further expansion. By July 2014, all 1,569 Malaysian stores will provide this service.
MOLPay CASH allows merchants to accept cash payments from customers at their nearest 7-Eleven. After an online purchase, a barcode is generated for the customer to use for payment at a 7-Eleven location.</description></item><item><title>Australia has a high usage of digital payment methods</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 09:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-has-a-high-usage-of-digital-payment-methods/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard study shows Australians are steadily adopting digital payment methods, with over 80% using contactless payments weekly. In fact, a significant number of Australians get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer contactless payment options, and some even choose to shop elsewhere in such situations.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and gas stations are where Australians most frequently use contactless cards.
Garry Duursma, Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, points out that Australians find contactless payments convenient and efficient.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive benefits for Visa cardholders on their initial Deliveroo order</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 18:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-benefits-for-visa-cardholders-on-their-initial-deliveroo-order/</guid><description>Visa and Deliveroo have teamed up to give Singaporean Visa cardholders special deals on their initial order until December 31, 2016.
Ordering food will be easier, from browsing menus to paying with Visa.
Tristan Torres, Deliveroo Singapore&amp;rsquo;s General Manager, highlighted this partnership as a significant step in their expansion within Singapore. He emphasized their dedication to providing top-notch service and convenience, including flexible payment options.
Singapore leads the way in using cashless payments, such as Visa payWave, in-app transactions, and Visa Checkout.</description></item><item><title>Globebill is establishing a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globebill-is-establishing-a-payment-and-bank-card-settlement-system-in-saudi-arabia/</guid><description>Globebill, a global online payment company, has partnered with Saudi Arabia to establish cross-border trade settlement services. This initiative aligns with China&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;One Belt and One Road&amp;rdquo; project.
Through this partnership, Globebill will introduce a payment and bank card settlement system in Saudi Arabia. This system will issue credit cards to individuals and businesses, facilitating trade between China and Saudi Arabia through Globebill&amp;rsquo;s platform. Both entities will collaborate to promote Globebill&amp;rsquo;s payment and settlement services, including the issuance of personal and corporate credit cards across the Middle East and North Africa.</description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015).</description></item><item><title>Recharge your prepaid mobile accounts using du's mobile app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:59:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recharge-your-prepaid-mobile-accounts-using-du-s-mobile-app/</guid><description>For the first time in the UAE, du customers can now top up their prepaid mobile phones using mPay. This new service was unveiled today at GITEX Technology Week 2015.
Fahad Al Hassawi, Chief Commercial Officer at du, stated, &amp;ldquo;We are thrilled to be the first operator offering prepaid recharge via mPay, making it easier for our customers to top up their prepaid du lines conveniently. We believe this will be highly popular among our users.</description></item><item><title>Passengers from China can use Alipay to pay for Grab rides in Singapore and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 08:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/passengers-from-china-can-use-alipay-to-pay-for-grab-rides-in-singapore-and-thailand/</guid><description>Chinese visitors to Singapore and Thailand can now use Alipay to pay for Grab rides thanks to a new partnership between Grab, Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s ride-hailing leader, and Ant Financial Services Group, the force behind China&amp;rsquo;s largest third-party payment platform, Alipay. This collaboration offers a cross-border payment solution, allowing Alipay users to pay for Grab taxis and private cars directly through their Alipay accounts.
Previously, Chinese travelers had limited payment choices, relying on dual-currency credit cards or cash for Grab rides.</description></item><item><title>Ignoring preferred payment methods could result in travel companies losing customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</guid><description>Around 85% of Chinese consumers take at least one leisure trip per year.
Credit cards (36%) and debit cards (29%) are the top payment choices for travel worldwide. PayPal is also popular (17%) across various countries and age groups.
Electronic payments are prevalent in China, with 78% favoring Alipay.
Seven out of ten Chinese travelers report experiencing fraud.
A recent global survey* of 7,400 consumers by YouGov and ACI Worldwide, a provider of electronic payment solutions, found that over a third (36%) of respondents from Britain, America, China, France, and Germany are dissatisfied with limited online payment choices for booking vacations.</description></item><item><title>Obtain a prepaid virtual Visa account through Singtel Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 11:40:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/obtain-a-prepaid-virtual-visa-account-through-singtel-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one mobile payments app, Dash, now features Singapore&amp;rsquo;s first virtual Visa account. All Dash users, new and existing, will automatically receive a Dash Visa Virtual Account. This account can be used for mobile payments at over 50,000 merchant locations in Singapore.
To use the mobile payment feature, customers sign in to the Dash app, add funds to their Dash Visa accounts, and make purchases at Dash merchants and participating e-commerce websites like Qoo10, Zalora, and HungryGoWhere.</description></item><item><title>Consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more concerned about the security of their computer data than their mobile payment data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 11:58:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumers-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-more-concerned-about-the-security-of-their-computer-data-than-their-mobile-payment-data/</guid><description>New benchmark data from ACI Worldwide and the Aite Group reveals that consumers in the Asia Pacific region are more worried about the security of their financial and payment information on computers compared to mobile wallets. This conclusion comes from their Global Consumer Survey: Consumer Trust and Security Perceptions report.
The study, which surveyed over 6,000 consumers across 20 countries, found that only 46% of Asia Pacific consumers trust businesses, such as restaurants and retailers, to safeguard their financial data.</description></item><item><title>It is now easier for visitors to Mainland China to make payments using Weixin Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 13:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/it-is-now-easier-for-visitors-to-mainland-china-to-make-payments-using-weixin-pay/</guid><description>Tencent has simplified and strengthened the registration and payment processes for international visitors using WeChat and Weixin Pay. Overseas users can now register using non-Chinese mobile numbers and link international payment cards for transactions. This provides access to millions of merchants across China, with enhanced transaction limits for verified users.
The updated system allows for convenient payments up to a certain limit. Higher limits are available after a quick identity verification process, with passport verification taking seconds.</description></item><item><title>Simply smile to make your payment at this KFC restaurant in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/simply-smile-to-make-your-payment-at-this-kfc-restaurant-in-china/</guid><description>A new, digitally connected experience for professionals living in urban areas.
For the first time in the world, consumers can pay using facial recognition technology.
Yum China Holdings, which owns KFC, has launched a new restaurant concept, KPRO by KFC, in Hangzhou, China – the same city where Alibaba is headquartered. Designed for savvy diners who enjoy trying new things, KPRO offers a fresh and seasonal menu. Using digital technology, it provides an immersive dining experience.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks and Tencent collaborate to simplify gifting and payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-and-tencent-collaborate-to-simplify-gifting-and-payments/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Wong.
Starbucks Coffee Company and Tencent Holdings, a Chinese provider of online services, are collaborating. In early 2017, they plan to launch a new social gifting feature within WeChat, a popular mobile communications service in China. Additionally, Starbucks customers at nearly 2,500 stores across mainland China can now use WeChat Pay for their purchases.
This partnership makes Starbucks the first retailer in China to provide an integrated, locally relevant social gifting and digital payment experience within WeChat.</description></item><item><title>Adyen predicts that smartphones will soon surpass tablets as the primary device for mobile payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</guid><description>Source: Adyen. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Adyen, a global payments technology provider, recently released its quarterly Mobile Payments Index for Q3. This report analyzes mobile payment data from web-based transactions across Adyen&amp;rsquo;s customer base between July and September. Notably, the Index reveals that nearly half of online transactions using specific payment methods are now conducted on mobile devices.
The Index shows that 47% of payments made with JCB, a Japanese card, were completed on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay is expanding its presence in Turkey through partnerships with ZIRAAT BANK and Garanti Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-is-expanding-its-presence-in-turkey-through-partnerships-with-ziraat-bank-and-garanti-bank/</guid><description>Ziraat Bank in Turkey has partnered with UnionPay International to enable UnionPay card acceptance across all its ATMs and POS terminals within the year. This initiative aims to broaden the reach of UnionPay cards within Turkey and enhance the experience for visiting UnionPay cardholders.
UnionPay anticipates that this collaboration will increase the acceptance rate of UnionPay cards at Turkish ATMs from 50% to nearly 70% by year-end. Similarly, POS terminal acceptance is projected to rise from 80% to almost 90%.</description></item><item><title>Exchange your remaining loose change for digital currency at airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</guid><description>Source: TravelersBox. A kiosk at Singapore Changi Airport (airside).
Travelers passing through Singapore Changi Airport can now utilize their leftover foreign currency or remaining Singapore dollars more effectively. This is made possible by the new TravelersBox kiosks situated within the airport.
TravelersBox, a financial technology company, assists travelers in converting their remaining foreign currency, both bills and coins, into digital money. This digital money can be redeemed online with well-known brands.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay cardholders in Singapore can now enjoy exclusive visa privileges for travel to China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:35:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-cardholders-in-singapore-can-now-enjoy-exclusive-visa-privileges-for-travel-to-china/</guid><description>UnionPay International (UPI), a branch of China UnionPay, partnered with Chinese Visa Application Service Centre to offer special VIP treatment to UnionPay cardholders in Singapore applying for a Chinese visa. This express service features a dedicated VIP counter and a faster queue for UnionPay cardholders (card numbers starting with 62).
UnionPay is currently the only international card brand offering expedited Chinese visa applications at Chinese embassies, consulates, and participating visa processing centers.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is encouraging subscribers to use their phones for payment at the supermarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 01:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-encouraging-subscribers-to-use-their-phones-for-payment-at-the-supermarket/</guid><description>A picture of a Dash payment reader at a FairPrice checkout.
Starting November 17th, shoppers can use Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash mobile payment app at over 200 NTUC FairPrice locations, including their supermarkets, Xtra hypermarkets, and standalone Cheers stores.
Gan Siok Hoon, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of mCommerce, Consumer Singapore, stated that as a major fintech provider, they were excited to partner with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest retailer, FairPrice, to offer this fast and secure payment option to their over half a million daily shoppers.</description></item><item><title>Singtel's Dash is running a flash campaign offering mystery cashback for purchases made on Lazada.SG</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-dash-is-running-a-flash-campaign-offering-mystery-cashback-for-purchases-made-on-lazada-sg/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s mobile payment app, Dash, is holding a short promotional campaign with online store Lazada.SG. From October 2nd to 9th, 2015, shoppers can receive a surprise cashback reward of 15% to 50%*.
Each day of the campaign features a &amp;ldquo;Dash Happy Hour.&amp;rdquo; During this limited time frame, which lasts up to two hours, customers using Dash to pay for purchases on Lazada.SG can earn cashback. The specific cashback amount won&amp;rsquo;t be disclosed until the end of each day and will be added to customer accounts within three business days.</description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge.</description></item><item><title>Members of Emirates Skywards can utilize their miles to make payments at Dubai Duty Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/members-of-emirates-skywards-can-utilize-their-miles-to-make-payments-at-dubai-duty-free/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Dubai Duty Free focal display.
The Emirates frequent flyer program, Emirates Skywards, has teamed up with Dubai Duty Free to allow members to redeem miles instantly at participating airport shops. Members can now use their miles at Dubai Duty Free locations in both Dubai International Airport and Al Maktoum International at Dubai South.
Emirates passengers traveling through Dubai International Airport, whether departing, connecting, or in transit to over 150 destinations, can enjoy shopping across 34,000 square meters at Dubai Duty Free.</description></item><item><title>Apple Pay is now available for Dash users</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 22:28:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-pay-is-now-available-for-dash-users/</guid><description>Singtel Dash customers can now use Apple Pay to make purchases at millions of participating online and physical stores globally.
This was made possible through Singtel&amp;rsquo;s partnership with Wirecard, a digital financial technology company. Wirecard enabled Dash&amp;rsquo;s Visa Virtual Account to work with Apple Pay.
Brigitte Haeuser-Axtner, Wirecard&amp;rsquo;s Executive VP of Sales in Asia for Digital &amp;amp; Telecommunications, expressed pride in collaborating with Singtel to expand the reach of Dash to a wider customer base and connect consumers with merchants worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads.</description></item><item><title>UnionPay International introduces a new cross-border marketing campaign with global promotions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 11:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unionpay-international-introduces-a-new-cross-border-marketing-campaign-with-global-promotions/</guid><description>Source: UnionPay International. Ge Huayong, Chairman of China UnionPay (sixth from the right), Cai Jianbo, CEO of UnionPay International (fifth from the right), and representatives from initial partners were present at the ceremony.
UnionPay International, in collaboration with Bank of China, China Merchants Bank, CYTS, Ctrip, Spring Airlines, SaSa Hong Kong, Prince Jewellery &amp;amp; Watch, LUKFOOK JEWELLERY, and ISA, has introduced 优计划 (Youjihua), translating to &amp;lsquo;a beneficial strategy&amp;rsquo; and playing on the &amp;lsquo;you&amp;rsquo; in UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s Chinese name.</description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively.</description></item><item><title>The partnership between SMRT JV and Hailo Singapore will enable the use of electronic receipts for taxi rides</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 02:48:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-partnership-between-smrt-jv-and-hailo-singapore-will-enable-the-use-of-electronic-receipts-for-taxi-rides/</guid><description>SMRT Road Holdings (SMRT Roads) and London-based taxi app developer Hailo Network Holdings (Hailo) have partnered to launch Hailo Singapore. This joint venture will introduce a new taxi booking application in Singapore.
Benny Lim, Managing Director of SMRT Roads, believes this collaboration will improve the passenger experience. He stated that combining Hailo&amp;rsquo;s technology with SMRT&amp;rsquo;s operational knowledge will create a seamless booking process for both passengers and drivers.
Ron Zeghibe, Executive Chairman and Co-Founder of Hailo Network, emphasized Hailo&amp;rsquo;s goal of optimizing taxi services globally.</description></item><item><title>Visa premium credit and prepaid cards now feature NFC capabilities thanks to ABK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visa-premium-credit-and-prepaid-cards-now-feature-nfc-capabilities-thanks-to-abk/</guid><description>Source: ABK. ABK adds NFC capabilities to Visa premium credit and prepaid cards.
The Al Ahli Bank of Kuwait (ABK) recently introduced its new Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go service for holders of its Visa premium credit and prepaid cards. This service utilizes Visa payWave, a contactless technology that allows cardholders to simply wave or tap their card at a contactless terminal instead of swiping or inserting it.
Tap &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Go employs near field communication (NFC) technology, enabling customers to make small purchases swiftly, conveniently, and securely at any terminal equipped for Visa payWave.</description></item><item><title>Insurance is now available through Singtel's Dash</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insurance-is-now-available-through-singtel-s-dash/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Dash app is launching Dash EasyEarn, a new financial product offering a 2% annual return. This insurance savings plan is available exclusively through the Dash app and is backed by Etiqa Insurance.
Source: Singtel. Dash EasyEarn is a fully digital insurance product, allowing users to manage their plans entirely through the Singtel Dash app.
This innovative addition to the Dash app, which already provides various services like payments and mobile top-ups, aims to make saving simple and accessible.</description></item><item><title>The carnival at People's Park Complex will feature opera performances, games, and information on cashless services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carnival-at-people-s-park-complex-will-feature-opera-performances-games-and-information-on-cashless-services/</guid><description>Zhongguo Remittance and the management of People&amp;rsquo;s Park Complex in Singapore are collaborating on a free event at the mall from August 25th to 27th, 2017.
Attendees can enjoy daily Chinese opera performances at noon, participate in stage games and a shop hunt, and try their luck in lucky draws for prizes. Food sampling will be available, alongside retail booths and demonstrations of CCPay&amp;rsquo;s cashless services, including remittance options through Zhongguo Remittance.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks Indonesia has launched the Starbucks Mobile App</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:52:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-indonesia-has-launched-the-starbucks-mobile-app/</guid><description>Source: Starbucks. Use the mobile app to make purchases at Starbucks.
Starbucks Indonesia has launched its mobile app, offering customers a quick and easy way to pay at over 260 stores across the country.
Expanding upon the cashless Starbucks Card system introduced in 2013, the Starbucks Indonesia mobile app (available on iPhone and Android) allows customers to pay for purchases by scanning a barcode linked to their registered Starbucks Card.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean banks are getting their customers ready for Apple Pay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 09:25:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-banks-are-getting-their-customers-ready-for-apple-pay/</guid><description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s website in Singapore now features a dedicated page for Apple Pay, which includes a list of participating banks and retailers. Among the banks listed, DBS and POSB have almost identical images on their websites, and UOB also has a dedicated page. Standard Chartered currently does not have any information available. DBS clarifies that Apple Pay offers a fast and secure payment method compatible with a user&amp;rsquo;s preferred DBS card. Contactless payments are also supported for iPhone and Apple Watch users.</description></item><item><title>A virtual bank in Hong Kong has introduced a new cross-border QR payment solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-virtual-bank-in-hong-kong-has-introduced-a-new-cross-border-qr-payment-solution/</guid><description>livi, a Hong Kong-based virtual bank known for its lifestyle approach, has introduced livi QR Payment for customers traveling to mainland China. This new technology allows users to make purchases in mainland China, Japan, South Korea, and Thailand.
As the first Hong Kong virtual bank to offer a cross-border QR payment solution, livi QR Payment works seamlessly with UnionPay&amp;rsquo;s network of merchants and payment systems. Customers can make secure payments at any merchant displaying the UnionPay QR label by simply using their livi app.</description></item></channel></rss>