<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Domain Names on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domain-names/</link><description>Recent content in Domain Names on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:02:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/domain-names/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>With Hosting You Get Domains</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-hosting-you-get-domains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 03:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/with-hosting-you-get-domains/</guid><description>Looking for a website host? Consider this: 1&amp;amp;1 Web Hosting has a promotion running for summer 2009 that could potentially eliminate your hosting fees for three months. As if that weren&amp;rsquo;t enough, they&amp;rsquo;re also offering free domain names. Still not satisfied? They offer business hosting at $9.99 per month, developer hosting at $19.99 per month, and even include free software.
Curious about the free software? It&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;ll need to build and promote your website.</description></item><item><title>Website Reseller Hosting For One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-reseller-hosting-for-one/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 21:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/website-reseller-hosting-for-one/</guid><description>Many believe website reseller hosting is a simple way to start a hosting company with a private, ready-made operation. Web designers who create and maintain numerous small sites for local companies often utilize reseller hosting. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a third, important use for reseller accounts: highly adaptable hosting for personal use.
This approach is particularly beneficial if you own multiple domains. In the internet&amp;rsquo;s early days, domain names were costly, leading businesses to settle for a single domain.</description></item><item><title>Go Daddy CEO Elephant Debacle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-daddy-ceo-elephant-debacle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 22:51:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/go-daddy-ceo-elephant-debacle/</guid><description>GoDaddy, the tech company known for its Super Bowl commercials and accessible domain registration services, has unexpectedly found itself in hot water. CEO Bob Parsons posted a video of himself killing an elephant on a hunting trip, sparking outrage among animal rights activists and everyday people alike.
While hunting is a complex issue, the backlash centers around Parsons&amp;rsquo; seeming lack of remorse and the blatant celebration of killing an endangered animal.</description></item><item><title>Your Business Website is $7</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-business-website-is-7/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:21:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-business-website-is-7/</guid><description>Having a business website is essential in today&amp;rsquo;s digital world. However, the cost of building a website can be a barrier for many businesses. While custom websites can cost thousands of dollars, even basic websites can cost hundreds per year for hosting. But imagine having a professional website and domain for less than $7 annually.
This is not a dream. For $6.99 yearly, a major web hosting provider offers domain registration and a five-page website builder.</description></item></channel></rss>