<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>151RRBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/151rrbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 151RRBG4002 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/151rrbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Final Touches - AC Motor Calibration, Adjusting Platter and Sub-Chassis and Tracking Force</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 12:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration is nearly complete. After deep cleaning the aluminum panels and platter, I adjusted the sub-chassis and platter height, tonearm lowering limit, and tracking weight.
There are videos on my YouTube channel demonstrating platter bearing and sub-chassis adjustments, similar for the 4000 and 4002 models. Another video covers the crucial adjustment of lowering limits, essential because the 4002&amp;rsquo;s system can&amp;rsquo;t always prevent damage from photosensor failure. Proper adjustment acts as a safeguard, potentially saving an expensive cartridge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-final-touches-ac-motor-calibration-adjusting-platter-and-sub-chassis-and-tracking-force/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Restoration of RPM Trimmer Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</guid><description>Following the PCB rebuild of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, the author focused on restoring the RPM trimmer panel, which had been previously replaced due to a burned-out illumination bulb.
The first step involved re-soldering the connections where the original panel had been cut off and adding heat-shrink tubing for protection. LED replacement boards, specifically designed for the 550x series, were installed to provide similar resistance and current draw as the original bulbs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-restoration-of-rpm-trimmer-panel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacement of End Groove Detection Light Bulb with an LED</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 23:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4002 (5501) RPM trimmer panel, the focus shifted to the malfunctioning end groove detection mechanism. This ingenious mechanism utilizes a light bulb, a photoresistor, and an encoder wheel acting as a pulley to detect when the carriage accelerates after the record&amp;rsquo;s final track. By identifying this movement, the mechanism reduces the return time to the home position for records with extended end grooves, such as 12&amp;quot; singles or certain LPs with shorter playtimes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacement-of-end-groove-detection-light-bulb-with-an-led/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of a Strange Fault Caused by a Shorted Diode D6</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 22:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, a peculiar control system issue persisted even after replacing the reservoir capacitors.
Upon pressing START, the carriage would begin to move but halt after approximately 20 mm, coinciding with the lights turning off. A few seconds later, the lights would illuminate again, and the motor would operate at 45 RPM. In this state, the carriage could be moved using the &amp;raquo; &amp;laquo; buttons, but the arm lowering function was disabled...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-a-strange-fault-caused-by-a-shorted-diode-d6/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Aluminum Pulley for the Carriage Servo</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 05:26:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</guid><description>Recently, I completed the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable. The final piece I needed was a new aluminum pulley for the carriage servo. The original pulley was cracked and causing unwanted noise and vibration, particularly during rapid carriage movements like starting and stopping. This was not acceptable for a quality turntable.
A standard replacement pulley wasn&amp;rsquo;t compatible with this early 5501 model. These early models use a unique end groove detection system requiring a pulley with four holes that function as an optical chopper to monitor the carriage speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-aluminum-pulley-for-the-carriage-servo/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Installation of New Transport Lock Bushings and New Cabinet Guidance Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 05:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) restoration project is nearing completion. Following the keypad surface restoration, attention shifted to the transport locks and cabinet guiding washers. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to rebuild the transport lock bushings before adjusting the floating chassis for proper centering within the enclosure.
Resources like a video tutorial and the required bushings are available in my Shapeways store. The original bushings are often found in poor condition, requiring careful removal. Images illustrate their deteriorated state and the cleaning process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-installation-of-new-transport-lock-bushings-and-new-cabinet-guidance-washers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 06:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the repair of a peculiar control system problem, I proceeded with the comprehensive restoration process. This involved replacing all electrolytic capacitors, a crucial step given their tendency to dry out in these units. Notably, Ta type capacitors can become a fire hazard upon failure, making the upgrade to modern Aluminum 105C types a wise decision.
The main PCB in its original state is depicted here:
And here it is after capacitor replacement:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Sensor Arm Light Bulb Replacement - Final Version</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 15:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</guid><description>This post follows up on my previous writing about replacing incandescent sensor arm bulbs in Beogram 4002 turntables with LEDs. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that the LED PCB is best positioned 2.5 mm deep in the sensor compartment&amp;rsquo;s bulb cavity. This maximizes sensor response, likely because light bulb filaments sit slightly lower than the bulb&amp;rsquo;s rim.
For a consistent solution, I designed a 3D-printed wedge that affixes to the flexPCB with epoxy and positions the LED at the optimal depth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-sensor-arm-light-bulb-replacement-final-version/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Repair of 'Knocking' AC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</guid><description>I prefer to thoroughly test restored Beograms to ensure they&amp;rsquo;re free of intermittent issues. It&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for new problems to appear with regular use. This was the case with a recently restored AC motor Beogram 4002 (5501). After playing a few records, I detected a faint knocking sound coming from inside the turntable. Upon removing the aluminum plates, I discovered the knocking synchronized with the AC motor&amp;rsquo;s rotation. Adjusting the motor tilt provided temporary noise reduction, but the knocking always returned, intensifying with each record played until it was noticeable during quieter tracks—an unacceptable issue for a turntable!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-repair-of-knocking-ac-motor/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Sensor Arm Bulb with a SMD LED on a FlexPCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 13:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</guid><description>This post details the successful development of an LED-based replacement for the incandescent bulb in the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s sensor arm. This upgrade was particularly challenging due to the limited space within the arm and the need to replicate the look of the original incandescent light while effectively illuminating the B&amp;amp;O logo.
Initial attempts using high-brightness amber LEDs paired with a red LED proved unsatisfactory as the resulting light was too orange and the red LED&amp;rsquo;s output was weak...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-smd-led-on-a-flexpcb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Random Stop Issue Fixed - Defective Photo Resistor in the Spindle RPM Sensor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 05:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, previously restored, began experiencing a problem where the OFF function would randomly activate during playback as if the button was pressed.
Prior to delving into the solution, the circuit diagram is presented for reference.
Transistor TR17, within the &amp;lsquo;Electronic Switch&amp;rsquo; section, is responsible for initiating the turntable&amp;rsquo;s OFF function. When its base is grounded, the collector rises to approximately 18V, causing the arm to lift and return to its resting position...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-random-stop-issue-fixed-defective-photo-resistor-in-the-spindle-rpm-sensor/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>