<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Conferencing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/web-conferencing/</link><description>Recent content in Web Conferencing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/web-conferencing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Take a Conference, Save the Carbon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</guid><description>While conference calls have been a common business tool, they are often reserved for specific projects or occasional use. Similarly, web conferencing, its internet-based counterpart, allows for incorporating visuals like charts and graphs but remains irregularly utilized. So, when does integrating conferencing into daily operations become a more practical approach rather than just another tool?
Several factors suggest a potential shift. Firstly, technological advancements have made it possible. Computers and speakerphones are commonplace, with many conference rooms equipped with internet access and large display screens or projectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-conference-save-the-carbon/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>