<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regulation 604/2013 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-604/2013/</link><description>Recent content in Regulation 604/2013 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-604/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice.</description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR.</description></item><item><title>Is the Dublin Regulation coming to an end? Where should unaccompanied children seek asylum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Recent events have sparked debate concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin III Regulation, which dictates where asylum seekers must apply for asylum within the EU. A British court ruled that the UK is responsible for the asylum claims of unaccompanied children in France, particularly those in Calais, if they have family in the UK. Additionally, a press release suggested the Commission may soon propose significant changes to the Dublin rules.</description></item></channel></rss>