<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Small Office on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-office/</link><description>Recent content in Small Office on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/small-office/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ESET introduces security solutions for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>ESET, a company that provides proactive digital protection, has launched two new security products: ESET Multi-Device Security Home Office and ESET Small Office Security. These products are designed for small office/home office (SOHO) users.
&amp;ldquo;Cybercriminals often target small and home offices because they assume these businesses lack strong security measures,&amp;rdquo; said Andrew Lee, CEO of ESET North America. &amp;ldquo;There are 28 million businesses in this sector, and they need security solutions tailored to their unique needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-introduces-security-solutions-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Iomega Zips Into Network Storage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:07:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</guid><description>Do you recall the Zip drive? When floppy disks were the standard for backups, Zip drives offered a remarkable hundredfold increase in capacity using removable cartridges. While hard drives now boast hundreds of gigabytes and beyond, leaving floppies and even Zip disks in the past, Iomega, the company behind the Zip drive, has continued to innovate. Their product line has expanded beyond desktops and into the server room.
Iomega, now a part of EMC, a Fortune 500 company specializing in enterprise storage solutions, still caters to individuals and small offices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iomega-zips-into-network-storage/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>