<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Micro on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/micro/</link><description>Recent content in Micro on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/micro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Indian government and the World Bank have signed a loan agreement to provide support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 02:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</guid><description>The Indian government and the World Bank have partnered to improve the productivity of micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) in India. They have signed a $200 million loan agreement for expanding and upgrading Technology Centers across the country.
The manufacturing industry in India faces various obstacles, including limited access to markets, finance, and infrastructure. Additionally, MSMEs struggle to expand due to insufficient access to technology and skilled labor. Technology Centers, often located near industrial hubs, offer shared facilities for MSMEs to access technology, business advice, and training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-indian-government-and-the-world-bank-have-signed-a-loan-agreement-to-provide-support-for-micro-small-and-medium-enterprises-msmes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Kickstarter spotlight: An innovative USB cable that charges smartphones at double the speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</guid><description>Minsoo and Emily Seo have developed a USB charging cable, DouBBleTime, that significantly reduces charging times for iPhones and Samsung Galaxy phones compared to standard cables.
As explained on their Kickstarter page, typical USB cables attempt to communicate with the connected device while delivering limited power. In contrast, the DouBBleTime cable features a switch that prioritizes charging, effectively decreasing charging time.
Source: Kickstarter.
The Seos state on their Kickstarter page that a unique chip within the switch communicates with the connected computer, signaling that it only requires charging energy and not data syncing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kickstarter-spotlight-an-innovative-usb-cable-that-charges-smartphones-at-double-the-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India will receive the India Inclusive Innovation Fund</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</guid><description>The Indian Cabinet has approved a proposal from the Ministry of Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises (MSME) to establish a dedicated fund. This fund will focus on promoting grassroots innovations that generate social benefits alongside reasonable economic returns. Union Minister Shri Kalraj Mishra shared this information in a written response to a question in Lok Sabha.
The fund, named &amp;ldquo;India Inclusive Innovation Fund,&amp;rdquo; aims to support businesses developing solutions for citizens at the lower end of India&amp;rsquo;s economic spectrum...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-receive-the-india-inclusive-innovation-fund/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exchange your remaining loose change for digital currency at airports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</guid><description>Source: TravelersBox. A kiosk at Singapore Changi Airport (airside).
Travelers passing through Singapore Changi Airport can now utilize their leftover foreign currency or remaining Singapore dollars more effectively. This is made possible by the new TravelersBox kiosks situated within the airport.
TravelersBox, a financial technology company, assists travelers in converting their remaining foreign currency, both bills and coins, into digital money. This digital money can be redeemed online with well-known brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exchange-your-remaining-loose-change-for-digital-currency-at-airports/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accounting solution in the cloud specifically created for individuals without accounting expertise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 03:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</guid><description>Asian Business Software Solutions (ABSS) has introduced Financio, a cloud-based accounting software designed for micro and small businesses in Singapore. This secure solution simplifies financial tracking without requiring accounting expertise.
Developed by ABSS and utilizing Microsoft Azure, Financio allows users to easily monitor sales, purchases, and other transactions through a user-friendly dashboard. It automates tasks like generating financial reports, tax records, and sending invoices, and enables seamless collaboration and document sharing through Financio Connect...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accounting-solution-in-the-cloud-specifically-created-for-individuals-without-accounting-expertise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Singaporean financial technology company is striving to provide improved lending terms for business-to-business transactions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</guid><description>A Singapore-based fintech startup, Cash-IN-Asia, has introduced a new business-to-business (B2B) lending platform. The company&amp;rsquo;s fully digital approach lets business owners secure financing directly from their mobile devices.
Cash-IN-Asia aims to support micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in Singapore. The company offers products designed to meet current needs and help these businesses thrive even after the current economic challenges.
Their ISO27001-certified platform leverages artificial intelligence (AI) and data analytics to deliver a comprehensive solution for MSMEs seeking transparent and flexible financing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-singaporean-financial-technology-company-is-striving-to-provide-improved-lending-terms-for-business-to-business-transactions/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>