<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Data Center on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-data-center/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Data Center on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-data-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Such a Stampede to The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is everywhere you turn. This raises the question: are businesses truly shifting from traditional data centers to cloud-based solutions? And if so, what motivates this transition and what are their objectives?
Unveiling the Hidden Potential of Cloud Technology
Cloud storage receives significant attention, but the vast server capacity offered by the cloud is equally compelling. One often overlooked application is Hosted PBX or Hosted VoIP, which replaces traditional phone systems.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Is The New T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-is-the-new-t1/</guid><description>The longstanding leading connectivity solution for businesses, T1 service, is frequently used for dedicated internet connections, point-to-point private lines, and PBX phone trunks. T1 connections are easily accessible, cost-effective, and very dependable. However, their main selling point—fixed bandwidth of 1.5 Mbps—is now a significant drawback.
While 1.5 Mbps still satisfies the needs of many small businesses and less tech-dependent companies, this is changing quickly. Professionals in fields like insurance, medicine, video production, and engineering all require strong connections.</description></item><item><title>When You Need Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 01:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-you-need-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While standard bandwidth offerings from telecom, cable, and fiber providers meet the needs of most businesses, some applications demand exceptionally high bandwidth. This article explores the realm of massive bandwidth options.
How Massive Are We Talking? Over the past few decades, WAN bandwidth demands have skyrocketed, mirroring the internet&amp;rsquo;s growth. We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from basic T1 lines at 1.5 Mbps to common expectations of 1 Gbps or more. While easily handled by most providers in well-connected areas, limitations arise in rural or underserved locations.</description></item></channel></rss>