<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Transport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-transport/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Transport on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-transport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ENLAN Spans The Nation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</guid><description>The concept of unifying all your company locations under a single extended LAN is gaining momentum. Instead of grappling with the complexities of managing countless connections for numerous branch offices or retail locations, a single managed network can streamline this process.
TW Telecom offers a service called ENLAN, which stands for Extended Native LAN. This service provides users with a high-speed, dependable, and secure network that extends the reach of what is typically considered the WAN or Wide Area Network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enlan-spans-the-nation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Virtual Concatenation for Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Many businesses are choosing Carrier Ethernet services for their wide area and metropolitan area networks. Ethernet is directly compatible with local area networks and offers greater bandwidth than traditional telecom services like T1 (1.5 Mbps) and DS3 (45 Mbps). The demand for bandwidth is rising as more content shifts from emails and simple websites to videos and high-resolution images. Ethernet (10 Mbps), Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), and Gigabit Ethernet (1,000 Mbps) often provide the most cost-effective solutions for bandwidth expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/virtual-concatenation-for-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Many Flavors of Ethernet Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 05:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</guid><description>Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular for Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) and Wide Area Network (WAN) transport. This surge in popularity is driven by IT and telecommunications managers seeking the highest data speeds at the most affordable prices, as well as the simplified management that Ethernet offers. By using Ethernet, multiple locations can be unified into a single, large network.
Ideally, businesses would benefit from a direct fiber optic connection from a competitive carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP) directly to their premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-many-flavors-of-ethernet-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is VPLS Bringing to MPLS Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous branches have embraced MPLS networks for their affordability and high performance in connecting multiple locations. However, they may be overlooking a superior connectivity solution: Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS).
Essentially, VPLS is an Ethernet transport service operating over existing MPLS networks, enhancing rather than replacing them.
What sets VPLS apart is its ability to unify all your individual LANs into a single, company-wide network. This network transcends geographical limitations, enabling international connections for globally distributed businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>