<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Protein on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protein/</link><description>Recent content in Protein on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 18:22:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/protein/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Plant-based protein is the latest trend in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plant-based-protein-is-the-latest-trend-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 18:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plant-based-protein-is-the-latest-trend-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>The alternative protein market, encompassing meat, eggs, dairy, and seafood, is poised for substantial growth, projected to reach a minimum of US$290 billion by 2035. This surge is driven by consumers embracing plant-based, microorganism-derived, and animal-cell-based alternatives, as highlighted in a report by Boston Consulting Group (BCG) and Blue Horizon Corporation (BHC).
Titled Food for Thought: The Protein Transformation, the report projects the alternative protein market to expand from 13 million metric tons annually to 97 million metric tons by 2035, constituting 11% of the global protein market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plant-based-protein-is-the-latest-trend-in-the-food-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plant-based-protein-is-the-latest-trend-in-the-food-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Consuming a balanced amount of protein helps dieters maintain muscle mass at a slower rate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</guid><description>Source: Nestlé.
Nestlé Research Center collaborated with global scientists and found that consistent protein intake throughout the day might reduce muscle loss during weight loss attempts.
Published in the American Journal of Physiology - Endocrinology and Metabolism, the study explored ways to promote weight loss in obese older men while preventing muscle loss. Muscle loss can hinder weight loss, decrease strength and functional capacity, and heighten the risk of disability and mortality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consuming-a-balanced-amount-of-protein-helps-dieters-maintain-muscle-mass-at-a-slower-rate/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>