<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Social Media on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-media/</link><description>Recent content in Social Media on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:27:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The first product on Unified Inbox's roadmap, Outbox Pro, has been launched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 06:27:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/</guid><description>Source: Unified Inbox website.
Unified Inbox, a company specializing in unified communications as a service, recently launched its first product: Outbox Pro, a cloud-based platform. Outbox Pro simplifies and accelerates the process of creating and distributing posts across various social media platforms. This web browser extension, currently compatible with Chrome, empowers users to generate, share, review, modify, approve, schedule, publish, and monitor both original and curated online content. Multiple authors can collaborate on this content, which can be shared across Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-first-product-on-unified-inbox-s-roadmap-outbox-pro-has-been-launched/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starting from December 21, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM for Japan will be available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 19:55:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</guid><description>Source: Plus One Marketing.
Plus One Marketing, a Japanese company known for its FREETEL brand of mobile devices, is launching a prepaid data SIM card specifically for travelers in Japan. Starting December 21, 2015, the FREETEL Prepaid Data SIM will be available for purchase.
The SIM card is designed with tourists in mind, allowing unlimited access to popular social media platforms like Facebook, Kakao Talk, WeChat, LINE, and WhatsApp for seven days...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starting-from-december-21-the-freetel-prepaid-data-sim-for-japan-will-be-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Identifying gender through Facebook posts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</guid><description>A 2013 study featured in the research journal Plos One reveals that language use in social media can indicate a user&amp;rsquo;s gender and age. The study, &amp;ldquo;Personality, Gender, and Age in the Language of Social Media: The Open-Vocabulary Approach,&amp;rdquo; found that men and women choose distinct words and phrases online. Location and age also factor into language choices.
Singapore bank DBS&amp;rsquo; lucky red packets
The study&amp;rsquo;s authors, from the University of Pennsylvania and University of Cambridge, noted that women tend to express emotions using words like &amp;ldquo;love,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;wonderful,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;excited...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor's third hotel in Bengaluru is #bangalorelovin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</guid><description>Accor&amp;rsquo;s Ibis brand has opened its third hotel in Bengaluru, India, accompanied by a &amp;ldquo;#bangalorelovin&amp;rdquo; campaign designed to highlight the city&amp;rsquo;s appeal.
Source: Accor.
JB Singh, President &amp;amp; CEO of InterGlobe Hotels, emphasized Bengaluru&amp;rsquo;s cosmopolitan nature, stating that the new Ibis hotel caters to both business and leisure travelers seeking affordable luxury. He expressed enthusiasm for providing memorable guest experiences.
Firoz Jangaria, General Manager of Ibis Bengaluru City Centre, highlighted the hotel&amp;rsquo;s strategic location and commitment to quality accommodations at economical prices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-s-third-hotel-in-bengaluru-is-bangalorelovin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Down In The Face of Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</guid><description>At the end of 2011, major companies like GoDaddy and Verizon Wireless faced significant public backlash that caused them to reverse recently announced decisions. GoDaddy quickly backpedaled on their support for SOPA after online outrage, while Verizon abandoned their plan to charge a $2 payment fee due to public outcry and potential FCC involvement. These incidents, while seemingly isolated, point to a larger pattern found in other events from the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poken Around For Business Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</guid><description>Modern business networking goes beyond the traditional handshake and business card by utilizing technology to manage contacts. Poken offers a fresh approach to this concept.
Poken, encompassing both a device and a method, modernizes the conventional business card. While physical cards were sufficient in the past, today&amp;rsquo;s digitized world demands more. Although card readers exist, Poken offers a direct electronic solution.
The pokenPulse, resembling a USB flash drive, doubles as a 2 GB storage device and a wireless transponder...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-around-for-business-leads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going Rogue But Not Rouge With Samsung</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 17:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re a go-getter in need of a powerful cell phone that won&amp;rsquo;t let you down, the Samsung Rogue U960 Black for Verizon Wireless is a top contender among smartphones.
Does your current phone offer easy access to social media apps like Facebook and MySpace? How about web browsing, YouTube videos, and photo editing on a bright screen, even in sunlight? Can you stream music wirelessly, get directions, or message easily with a physical QWERTY keyboard?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-rogue-but-not-rouge-with-samsung/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Job Posting Tool Offers Free Trial</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 01:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/</guid><description>As the economy improves, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to start thinking about hiring again, but many companies dread the deluge of resumes and calls that come with advertising open positions. The cost of advertising and the staff time needed to screen applicants can be overwhelming. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to streamline and simplify your hiring process.
ZipRecruiter offers a web-based system designed to significantly reduce the workload for you and your staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-posting-tool-offers-free-trial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Travellers are pleased to engage with hotels on social media</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 02:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</guid><description>A 2014 study by Accorhotels called the Social Media Monitor showed that hotels have a significant opportunity to connect with travelers on social media. In the Asia Pacific region, almost half of travelers follow hotel brands, more than airlines or other travel-related businesses. This trend is especially strong among travelers from China and Indonesia, as well as those between 25 and 44 years old.
Interestingly, in countries with prominent airlines such as Malaysia, Australia, New Zealand, and Japan, airlines are followed most on social media...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/travellers-are-pleased-to-engage-with-hotels-on-social-media/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrating Social Media And Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</guid><description>We navigate two distinct realms: the digital sphere of communication, online activities, and social media, and the physical world of tangible experiences, relationships, and work. Although these realms overlap, their connection has been tenuous until recently.
Poken has emerged as a solution to bridge this gap between the digital and physical. As expected, it comprises both physical and virtual elements.
The tangible aspect is a device called Poken, resembling a digital avatar or a flash drive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>