<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Service on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-service/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Service on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Expansion With Multiple T1 Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 22:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-expansion-with-multiple-t1-lines/</guid><description>For many years, T1 lines have been a reliable network connection, especially when bandwidth demands are low. However, with increasing bandwidth requirements exceeding 1.5 Mbps, upgrading from the traditional T1 line becomes necessary.
One solution to increase bandwidth without abandoning existing T1 lines is &amp;ldquo;bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines the capacity of multiple T1 lines, effectively creating a single, faster connection. A managed router with multiple interface cards connects and manages the combined bandwidth from the T1 lines.</description></item></channel></rss>