<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AVMS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/avms/</link><description>Recent content in AVMS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:26:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/avms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Update of the Directive on Audiovisual Media Services – Platforms for Sharing Videos</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-of-the-directive-on-audiovisual-media-services-platforms-for-sharing-videos/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:26:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/update-of-the-directive-on-audiovisual-media-services-platforms-for-sharing-videos/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) has been undergoing revisions since 2016, sparking debate about how to update it for the digital age. While the Council and European Parliament generally agree that video-sharing platforms (VSPs) need some regulation, they differ significantly on the specifics. This disagreement is evident in the ongoing trilogue negotiations, where even accessing agreed-upon positions has proven difficult due to the influence of interest groups concerned about advertising regulations.</description></item><item><title>ERGA and the Audiovisual and Media Services Directive 2.0: A European Regulators Group without Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
In 2014, the European Commission created ERGA to help implement the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and support a unified European market. This built upon the existing High Level Group of Regulatory Authorities, established in 2003, which brought national enforcement bodies together twice a year. The goal was to improve collaboration between these authorities to ensure the AVMSD was applied consistently across Europe. This reflects a broader EU trend of forming networks, sometimes including member states, to promote harmonization.</description></item><item><title>Overview of the European Democracy Action Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The European Democracy Action Plan (EDAP) is one piece of a larger effort to regulate the online world. Unveiled as a key initiative by Commission President von der Leyen, it joins upcoming legislation like the Digital Services Act (DSA) and Digital Markets Act (DMA). These measures signal a change in how the EU approaches internet regulation and raise questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority in this space.</description></item></channel></rss>