<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>April Fools Day on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/april-fools-day/</link><description>Recent content in April Fools Day on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/april-fools-day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements.</description></item><item><title>Clod Computing Challenges The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clod-computing-challenges-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing is gaining popularity as a cost-effective alternative to traditional data centers. However, a new competitor called &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; computing is emerging, boasting even lower costs.
](http://www.sysnito.com/?crid=11591&amp;linkID=145&amp;refid=Telexplainer-Clod)Clod computing minimizes infrastructure expenses by utilizing readily available, discarded computers. Chip-On-A-Shingle, a clod computing startup, defines a &amp;ldquo;clod&amp;rdquo; as a network of interconnected old computers and devices that collectively provide impressive processing power.
This approach is viable due to the abundance of still functional computers being discarded simply because they are outdated.</description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays.</description></item><item><title>Economic Woes Drive Rural Telegraphy Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/economic-woes-drive-rural-telegraphy-initiative/</guid><description>The recent economic downturn has forced a reevaluation of strategies for providing digital communication to rural communities. Access to the internet and even cell phone service is notoriously limited in these areas. While the Rural Broadband Initiative, part of the economic stimulus plan, aimed to address this issue by funding fiber optic cable installation, those funds have unfortunately been redirected.
Robb M. Blihnd, a hedge fund manager, explained that the funds were considered more essential for urban and suburban areas.</description></item></channel></rss>