<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Document on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/document/</link><description>Recent content in Document on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/document/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KODAK CapturePro Software v5.0 has been released by Kodak Alaris</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 10:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</guid><description>Large businesses are constantly looking for ways to manage information more efficiently and productively. Extracting data from documents for business processes and getting information into digital storage can slow things down, impacting expenses and customer happiness.
Source: Kodak Alaris.
&amp;ldquo;As organizations rely more on online platforms for profit, it&amp;rsquo;s critical to manage remaining paper documents effectively,&amp;rdquo; says Harvey Spencer, President of leading capture software analyst firm Harvey Spencer Associates. &amp;ldquo;The best approach is quickly converting paper into usable electronic data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kodak-capturepro-software-v5-0-has-been-released-by-kodak-alaris/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dropbox and Microsoft collaborating more effectively</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 04:12:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</guid><description>Source: Microsoft.
Dropbox and Microsoft are joining forces to make it easier for their users to work together. This collaboration will allow users to seamlessly work with Dropbox and Microsoft Office on their phones, tablets, and computers. Given that over 1.2 billion people use Microsoft Office and 35 billion Office files are stored in Dropbox, this partnership has the potential to benefit a lot of users.
This integration will enable users to edit their Dropbox documents directly in the relevant Office application...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dropbox-and-microsoft-collaborating-more-effectively/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 now accepts e-signatures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 08:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</guid><description>Source: Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 website.
The Aloft Bangkok - Sukhumvit 11 has introduced a paperless check-in experience featuring electronic signatures. This system aims to eliminate the need for printed documents and expedite the arrival process for guests. Aloft Bangkok claims to be the first hotel within the Starwood brand to offer this service.
This innovative approach streamlines the check-in procedure by presenting all reservation details on a tablet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aloft-bangkok-sukhumvit-11-now-accepts-e-signatures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DocuWorks 9 is compatible with cloud and mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 19:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/</guid><description>Fuji Xerox Asia Pacific has introduced DocuWorks 9, a document management software now enhanced with cloud integration for seamless mobile workflows.
DocuWorks allows users to interact with electronic documents, such as office files and images, as if they were physical copies. The latest mobile features empower users to pick up their work anytime, anywhere.
A new feature called Task Space lets users gather work-related documents and sync them to Fuji Xerox&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based Working Folder with a simple click...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docuworks-9-is-compatible-with-cloud-and-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>