<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contact on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contact/</link><description>Recent content in Contact on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/contact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a Neutrik Gold Plated DIN5 Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</guid><description>A common improvement for the Beogram 4000 is replacing the DIN5 plug with a gold-plated version. The older plugs, often corroded, benefit from the upgrade. This particular Beogram 4000 was no exception.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a comparison of the old plug and the new, gleaming Neutrik plug (Newark 27B4483):
The old plug was removed, and the cable was prepped for the new plug. Stripping the outer insulation to this length works well:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-neutrik-gold-plated-din5-plug/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing a Broken MMC Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>The first issue to tackle on this Beogram 4000 restoration was a damaged cartridge mount, a common problem on these turntables. The existing mount had a broken plastic piece. This particular unit came with both a damaged 4002 arm and its original, detached 4000 arm. The goal was to remove the 4002 arm and install the original arm after fitting it with a functional MMC mount.
This project provided a perfect opportunity to use a recently designed 3D-printed replacement MMC mount...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-a-broken-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Broken Off MMC Cartridge Mount with 3D Printed Replacement Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 14:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 tonearm with a common issue: a broken MMC cartridge mounting tab due to the aging plastic. Fortunately, this tonearm had an older design allowing for easy disassembly.
The plastic piece meant to hold the cartridge was broken, leaving only the circuit board behind. The broken piece was glued in, requiring careful heating in boiling water to soften the glue before removal.
Thankfully, a crucial part with the grounding tab remained intact and was reusable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-broken-off-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-3d-printed-replacement-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: MMC Cartridge Mount Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 10:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 tonearm from Western Australia needed repair because its MMC cartridge mount had broken off, a common issue with these models. Unlike later models with soldered wiring, this older model has a plug-in tonearm, which complicates the mount replacement. The old mount, held by glue, had to be carefully removed.
Heating the arm softens the glue, allowing for the broken mount&amp;rsquo;s removal. This process was used for both the Australian tonearm and another one undergoing restoration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-mmc-cartridge-mount-restoration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Slow Slide Transport Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a problem was encountered where the tonearm carriage would continue moving after attempting to move it in reverse. This issue stemmed from a damaged keypad switch, specifically a bent contact terminal that prevented a clean shut-off connection. This damage was likely caused by a previous repair attempt.
To address this, the control panel and circuit board were removed to access and extract the switch terminals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-slow-slide-transport-function/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Assembly - Gold Plated Switch Terminals and Light Bulbs Replaced with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the repair of the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking systems, the next step was to focus on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control center: the keypad assembly. This unit houses an early digital control system that manages inputs from the keypad&amp;rsquo;s keys. The mechanical switches connected to these keys are a common source of problems and should be gold-plated to ensure reliable, long-term operation after restoration.
The keypad cluster was removed from the Beogram and opened, revealing a missing light bulb in the position indicator scale...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Keypad with a Worn Through Start Button</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 keypad, showing signs of wear, was recently sent from New Zealand. The start button&amp;rsquo;s coating was entirely worn down:
This is a common problem for Beogram keypads. The combination of skin acids and friction wears away the coating.
Fortunately, this is fixable. Here is the keypad after being restored:
It looks great! The coating will be left to harden further before being returned to New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of an 'Old Style' MMC Cartridge Mount with a New 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 01:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 restoration involved addressing a frequent problem: a broken MMC cartridge mount. This issue arises because the plastic used in older models becomes brittle over time. Thankfully, later models like the Beogram 4002 and 4004 utilized a more durable plastic, reducing this issue.
To begin the repair, the tonearm was removed to allow access to the cartridge mount assembly. Unlike later models where the mount is glued, this older version is bolted to the arm&amp;rsquo;s aluminum frame...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-an-old-style-mmc-cartridge-mount-with-a-new-3d-printed-assembly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>