<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Network Infrastructure on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-infrastructure/</link><description>Recent content in Network Infrastructure on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/network-infrastructure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Such a Stampede to The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 23:04:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is everywhere you turn. This raises the question: are businesses truly shifting from traditional data centers to cloud-based solutions? And if so, what motivates this transition and what are their objectives?
Unveiling the Hidden Potential of Cloud Technology
Cloud storage receives significant attention, but the vast server capacity offered by the cloud is equally compelling. One often overlooked application is Hosted PBX or Hosted VoIP, which replaces traditional phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-such-a-stampede-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cyber Security Threat Protection In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 21:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>In the past, castles relied on moats to provide extra security beyond their walls. This stopped attackers from directly reaching the castle. Similarly, today&amp;rsquo;s networks need more than just firewalls.
Firewalls are effective but can be overwhelmed. Cloud-based security acts as a modern moat, providing a barrier outside the network. MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s Unified Threat Management (UTM) uses this approach, offering cloud, on-site, or hybrid security solutions.
MegaPath&amp;rsquo;s UTM is a multi-layered Security as a Service (SaaS) solution that handles simple and complex threats, while also managing security alerts, logs, and compliance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cyber-security-threat-protection-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Amazon's CloudFront Moves In for Content Delivery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 09:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</guid><description>Amazon has expanded far beyond bookselling; it&amp;rsquo;s now a major player in network computing. Recognizing the value of their massive infrastructure, Amazon created Amazon Web Services (AWS) to offer cloud computing resources to businesses of all sizes.
AWS includes a range of services, such as Amazon EC2 for computing power, Amazon S3 for storage, and Amazon CloudFront for content delivery. Amazon&amp;rsquo;s global network, with numerous edge locations, makes it well-suited for content delivery...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-cloudfront-moves-in-for-content-delivery/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>