<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mercer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mercer/</link><description>Recent content in Mercer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mercer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem.</description></item><item><title>Asian financial institutions are expected to see an average pay increase of 4% in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-financial-institutions-are-expected-to-see-an-average-pay-increase-of-4-in-2016/</guid><description>Limits on variable pay are leading to an increase in guaranteed fixed pay. Asia and Latin America are projected to see average base pay increases of 4.3% in 2016, in contrast to 2% to 2.7% in Europe and North America. Overall, 2016 pay is expected to remain stable, with lower variable pay offset by increases in fixed pay.
Source: Mercer.
Mercer&amp;rsquo;s 11th annual Global Financial Services Executive Compensation Snapshot Survey reveals that in 2015, financial services companies worldwide continued to react to regulatory changes.</description></item><item><title>Financial services companies are placing a greater emphasis on developing a strong risk culture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:32:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/financial-services-companies-are-placing-a-greater-emphasis-on-developing-a-strong-risk-culture/</guid><description>A recent study by Mercer focusing on executive compensation in the global financial services industry found that a majority of firms are prioritizing the development of robust risk cultures within their organizations. Sixty-two percent of surveyed firms reported significant efforts to penalize misconduct and non-compliance, while 60% demonstrated clear leadership commitment to ethical behavior. Furthermore, 58% have established and communicated unambiguous objectives related to risk culture.
Vicki Elliott, Senior Partner and Financial Services Talent Leader at Mercer, highlighted the importance of senior leaders setting a positive example when it comes to risk management and compliance.</description></item><item><title>Singapore's CPF retirement savings system has fallen in the MMGPI rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 18:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-cpf-retirement-savings-system-has-fallen-in-the-mmgpi-rankings/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s retirement savings system, the Central Provident Fund (CPF), saw a slight decline in its index value, resulting in a drop from a B grade to a C+ grade in the 2015 Melbourne Mercer Global Pension Index (MMGPI). Singapore&amp;rsquo;s overall score decreased to 64.7 in 2015 from 65.9 in 2014, moving it further away from an &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; grade, which is awarded to pension systems scoring above 80. Denmark and the Netherlands are the only countries to have achieved an A grade in the index&amp;rsquo;s history.</description></item><item><title>Asian cities have been rearranged in Mercer's Cost of Living Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</guid><description>Five Asian cities—Hong Kong (ranked 2nd), Tokyo (3rd), Singapore (5th), Seoul (6th), and Shanghai (8th)—were named among the top 10 most expensive cities for expatriates in this year&amp;rsquo;s ranking.
Currency fluctuations played a significant role in shaping the rankings of most Asian cities.
While all mainland Chinese cities surveyed experienced a drop in ranking, Tianjin (12th) stood out as an exception, climbing 18 positions.
Mumbai, India made a remarkable jump of 25 places this year, attributed to robust economic growth, inflation, and a stable currency.</description></item></channel></rss>