<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vegetarian on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vegetarian/</link><description>Recent content in Vegetarian on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar.</description></item><item><title>Godrej Tyson Foods introduces the delectable Galouti Kabab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godrej-tyson-foods-introduces-the-delectable-galouti-kabab/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godrej-tyson-foods-introduces-the-delectable-galouti-kabab/</guid><description>Godrej Tyson Foods, a subsidiary of Godrej Agrovet, has introduced a Galouti Kabab under its rapidly expanding Godrej Yummiez brand. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that Godrej Yummiez primarily offers vegetarian products.
Godrej Yummiez already holds a strong position in the kabab market with its chicken seekh kabab and Hariyali kabab options. By adding Galouti Kabab to its offerings, Godrej Yummiez aims to bring this delicacy from the royal kitchens of Lucknow to dining tables across India.</description></item></channel></rss>