<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Inventory on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/inventory/</link><description>Recent content in Inventory on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 04:57:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/inventory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Leveraging eConnect for importing Inventory Adjustments with Multi-Bin functionality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leveraging-econnect-for-importing-inventory-adjustments-with-multi-bin-functionality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 04:57:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leveraging-econnect-for-importing-inventory-adjustments-with-multi-bin-functionality/</guid><description>I recently addressed a question on the Dynamics GP Developer forum about an eConnect issue. The problem involved importing inventory adjustments with multiple bins.
The developer successfully imported positive adjustments, but negative adjustments resulted in a &amp;ldquo;The QTY entered has to be &amp;gt; 0&amp;rdquo; error.
Exploring the GP Item Transaction Entry window revealed the root of the problem.
This window is unusual in GP because it allows negative quantities. While enjoyable, this feature isn&amp;rsquo;t consistent throughout GP.</description></item><item><title>The World Order That Isn't So New - Variances in Costs and Dynamics GP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-order-that-isn-t-so-new-variances-in-costs-and-dynamics-gp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-order-that-isn-t-so-new-variances-in-costs-and-dynamics-gp/</guid><description>In the past, Dynamics GP calculated cost variances for FIFO/LIFO perpetual valuation method items during purchase order processing, sales order processing, or inventory control. These variances were not always posted to the general ledger. Users were frequently reminded of the significance of reviewing the Cost Variance Journal. However, this changed with the release of Dynamics GP 9.0.
While articles about cost variances exist, many seem outdated or inaccurate, especially regarding changes introduced in version 9.</description></item><item><title>Setting up the item: Where it all begins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/setting-up-the-item-where-it-all-begins/</guid><description>My recent focus on Sure Step training reminded me how crucial item setup is. Many Sales Order Processing (SOP) and Purchase Order Processing (POP) problems stem from those initial item setup choices. Users might misunderstand how the system works, not realizing their settings are dictating the behavior – settings that are often easy to change. This happens because setup and transaction entry are often done by different people, or so much time has passed that the reasoning behind setup decisions is forgotten (hence the need for good documentation, though I doubt my coworkers would be thrilled to hear that again).</description></item><item><title>Modifying PO Distributions in Summary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:13:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/modifying-po-distributions-in-summary/</guid><description>Since the release of service packs GP 10 (SP2 and later) and GP 9 (SP3 and later), users can no longer make changes to summary distributions in Receivings Transaction Entry and Purchasing Invoice Entry. Instead, they must access the Item Detail expansion and adjust the account assigned to the line item.
While this change makes sense from an inventory management perspective, as reconciling inventory with the general ledger was difficult when summary distributions could be modified, it has made the process more complex for clients who use the POP module without inventory.</description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs: Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 08:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-2/</guid><description>This post continues the discussion about landed costs. We&amp;rsquo;ll cover the three main ways landed costs are used, building on the previous example of setting up insurance costs to connect insurance invoices with product shipments.
Three Ways to Use Landed Costs 1. Landed Costs by Line Item Assign a landed cost group to each line item upon receipt. This can be done by default (from item setup or the purchase order) or manually.</description></item><item><title>In Support of Classifications (Inventory)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 16:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-support-of-classifications-inventory/</guid><description>During a recent phone support session, I encountered a case that highlighted the often-overlooked advantages of using classes in Dynamics GP. While classes are generally known for providing default values, enabling changes to cascade down to records, and facilitating the grouping of records for tasks like reporting, their practical benefits go beyond these commonly recognized uses.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate this with an example from inventory management. When a new item is created manually (Cards&amp;raquo;Inventory&amp;raquo;Item), the option to maintain history is not enabled by default.</description></item><item><title>Kits, Bills of Materials, and Components - Oh, the Possibilities!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kits-bills-of-materials-and-components-oh-the-possibilities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 04:29:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kits-bills-of-materials-and-components-oh-the-possibilities/</guid><description>When examining the core functions of Kits and Bills of Materials (BOMs) in Dynamics GP, the differences appear straightforward: Kits combine items at the point of sale, while BOMs group items during the production of a finished good. Essentially, Kits are sales-focused, while BOMs are inventory-focused. Kits are assembled upon sale, whereas BOMs are created before the item is even available for sale.
While this seems simple, deciding between Kits and BOMs often sparks debate, even among experienced professionals.</description></item><item><title>The Land of Landed Costs - Part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 14:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-land-of-landed-costs-part-1/</guid><description>Landed cost represents the total expense of getting an item to your location. This includes the item price plus charges like shipping, customs fees, and processing. More companies are focusing on landed costs as they increasingly source products from global suppliers and manufacturers. Using landed costs provides a more accurate view of the &amp;ldquo;total&amp;rdquo; cost, reflecting it in inventory value as an asset, rather than treating additional expenses separately.
Let&amp;rsquo;s illustrate with an example: you buy 100 widgets from a European supplier at $20 per widget.</description></item></channel></rss>