<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Money on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/money/</link><description>Recent content in Money on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/money/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cash For Clunker Cell Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-for-clunker-cell-phones/</guid><description>While the government&amp;rsquo;s Cash for Clunkers program for cars might be ending, there&amp;rsquo;s a similar concept for old electronics. You can get cash for your unwanted devices, including cell phones, laptops, and more!
You might not have heard about this, but it&amp;rsquo;s a great way to earn money from your unused gadgets. From cell phones and laptops to gaming consoles and cameras, many devices have value. Don&amp;rsquo;t let them sit around collecting dust – see how much they&amp;rsquo;re worth!</description></item><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck.</description></item><item><title>The UAE Central Bank has introduced raised marks on certain currency notes to assist individuals with visual impairments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-central-bank-has-introduced-raised-marks-on-certain-currency-notes-to-assist-individuals-with-visual-impairments/</guid><description>The Central Bank of the United Arab Emirates has introduced new AED1,000, AED20, and AED10 banknotes featuring raised tactile marks designed to assist people with visual impairments, according to the Emirates News Agency, WAM.
These new banknotes incorporate tactile elements created using the intaglio printing method on their widths. The AED1,000 note now includes two sets of four horizontal lines, evenly spaced, on both the left and right edges.
Similarly, the AED20 denomination features three distinct horizontal lines in the same position, while the AED10 denomination has two.</description></item><item><title>Western Union has extended its contract to provide its services at Hong Leong Bank branches in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 12:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/western-union-has-extended-its-contract-to-provide-its-services-at-hong-leong-bank-branches-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Western Union, a company specializing in money transfers, has extended its partnership with Hong Leong Bank (HLBB) for another three years. This agreement allows Western Union to continue providing its services across all 283 HLBB branches in Malaysia.
Chew Mei Ling, Western Union&amp;rsquo;s Country Director for Malaysia, highlighted the increasing demand for both inbound and outbound remittances in the country. She emphasized that the renewed partnership with HLBB will support this growth by offering customers fast, reliable, and convenient money transfer services.</description></item><item><title>Xpress Money introduces a daily raffle for customers sending money in 11 countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xpress-money-introduces-a-daily-raffle-for-customers-sending-money-in-11-countries/</guid><description>Xpress Money, a money transfer company, has introduced a 49-day promotion called &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday.&amp;rdquo; This program is open to customers sending money from Malaysia and ten other countries, including several in the Middle East.
Source: Xpress Money website.
The World Bank reported that in 2012, individuals sent $2.3 billion from Malaysia to other countries. Xpress Money anticipates a 15% increase in money transfers during Ramadan. Sudhesh Giriyan, Xpress Money&amp;rsquo;s Vice President and Business Head, stated that the &amp;ldquo;Win Everyday&amp;rdquo; program is a gesture of goodwill towards customers during Ramadan.</description></item><item><title>India no longer accepts high denomination notes in the current series</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-no-longer-accepts-high-denomination-notes-in-the-current-series/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Reserve Bank (RBI) has decided to discontinue the use of 500 and 1,000 rupee notes. These notes ceased to be legal tender as of November 9, 2016. Consequently, ATMs and other cash transaction machines were shut down on November 9 and 10. However, bank branches and government treasuries remained open on November 10.
This move was prompted by the difficulty in differentiating real banknotes from counterfeit ones. The surge in fake currency was negatively impacting the Indian economy.</description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces loyalty card in partnership with Visa's walletplus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 07:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-loyalty-card-in-partnership-with-visa-s-walletplus/</guid><description>Source: Etihad Guest website.
Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; loyalty program, Etihad Guest, now allows members to use walletplus, a Visa-powered payment system, directly through their Etihad Guest cards. Members can add travel funds to their cards and exchange them for 11 different international currencies for use while traveling.
This prepaid card allows travelers to manage their money by securing favorable exchange rates in advance, eliminating the need for bank transfers or currency exchanges upon arrival.</description></item><item><title>Emirates Islamic has launched a forex counter at Al Maktoum International Airport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 03:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-islamic-has-launched-a-forex-counter-at-al-maktoum-international-airport/</guid><description>Source: Emirates Islamic. Emirates Islamic’s Foreign Exchange Counter at Al Maktoum International Airport at Dubai World Central.
Emirates Islamic announced the launch of a new currency exchange counter at Al Maktoum International Airport in Dubai World Central. Situated in the departure area, this counter will allow travelers and tourists to exchange up to 19 different currencies at competitive rates.
Emirates Islamic also manages another exchange counter at Port Rashid Cruise Terminal.</description></item><item><title>The inaugural Bitcoin conference in China will take place in May</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 17:36:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-bitcoin-conference-in-china-will-take-place-in-may/</guid><description>Bitfund.pe, a private equity firm focused on Bitcoin, and UBM China have jointly revealed plans for the first international Bitcoin conference in China. This event, the Global Bitcoin Summit 2014 (GBS), is scheduled for May 10-11 in Beijing.
Source: GBS
The summit will be structured around eight key themes, featuring conversations on Bitcoin trends both within China and globally. Additionally, there will be exploration of how to leverage Bitcoin for new business creation and expansion of existing ventures.</description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination.</description></item></channel></rss>