<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Qwest on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qwest/</link><description>Recent content in Qwest on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:25:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/qwest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Qwest Embraces Ethernet over Copper to Reach Rural Business Locations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 15:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</guid><description>Qwest Communications, a leading telecom provider in the US, boasts a nationwide fiber optic network capable of transmitting data at 40 Gbps, with plans to upgrade to 100 Gbps. While this caters to large enterprises requiring substantial bandwidth, what options are available for remotely located businesses?
Remote offices, even those belonging to large corporations, often face challenges justifying the cost of installing fiber optic cables due to their distance from carrier Points of Presence (POPs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-embraces-ethernet-over-copper-to-reach-rural-business-locations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Recovery Mirrors Your Servers and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 23:58:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</guid><description>Protecting valuable assets is crucial for any business, which is why backups are essential. However, backups alone can&amp;rsquo;t protect against major disasters that could damage physical infrastructure.
Having a backup located in the company safe won&amp;rsquo;t help if a catastrophic event destroys the entire building. Since many businesses heavily rely on computer systems, replicating the entire IT infrastructure is a wise decision.
You might be wondering about the cost of duplicating server rooms, applications, and data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-recovery-mirrors-your-servers-and-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Qwest Offers Synchronous Service Transport For Massive Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</guid><description>Need to move massive amounts of data quickly and reliably? Within a building or campus, fiber optic cables provide sufficient speed and capacity. However, for longer distances, you need robust carrier services. Quest&amp;rsquo;s Synchronous Service Transport (SST) offers a solution.
SST utilizes fiber optics and SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) to provide high-speed, point-to-point data transfer. SONET, a dependable carrier service based on Time Division Multiplexing (TDM), was initially designed for telephone companies and later adopted by large organizations requiring extensive bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qwest-offers-synchronous-service-transport-for-massive-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>