<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud Networking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-networking/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud Networking on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cloud-networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telephony In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>When we think about cloud networking, we often picture data networks moving information between locations. However, many businesses are also transitioning their phone systems to the cloud. This shift brings both benefits and hurdles.
The traditional phone network is essentially a large cloud network. This system is designed for reliability and high-quality service, handling countless users at once. Users connect to this cloud through a direct line to their nearest local central office, unconcerned with the complexities of the system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephony-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Covad Offers A Nationwide MPLS VPN Network For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</guid><description>Companies with numerous offices across the country have access to a new secure networking solution. Covad&amp;rsquo;s recently launched Intelligent Network Platform offers expanded WAN networking capabilities at a lower cost than traditional options.
Covad&amp;rsquo;s MPLS VPNs are designed for small to medium-sized businesses and larger dispersed companies needing to connect multiple locations, such as franchises, remote offices, warehouses, retail stores, factories, and hotels. Multi-location networking presents two key challenges: establishing secure and reliable connections between all sites and doing so cost-effectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/covad-offers-a-nationwide-mpls-vpn-network-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone’s Converged IP Cloud Expanding To Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:37:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</guid><description>Smoothstone IP Communications, a pioneering company in cloud-based unified communications, is expanding its services to include European locations. This expansion begs the question: is this the beginning of a global cloud network?
The answer is a resounding yes. International MPLS connectivity makes it possible to extend any IP service to any location worldwide. The power of MPLS networks lies in their ability to transport data seamlessly to users regardless of their location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-s-converged-ip-cloud-expanding-to-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Comes To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s professionals juggle multiple devices like smartphones, tablets, and laptops in addition to their office setups, which often include desktop computers, LAN connections, and speakerphones. This begs the question: how can we unify these devices for a seamless workflow?
This multifaceted connectivity issue has plagued corporate IT departments for years as communication devices multiply faster than solutions for integrating them. Often, the simplest answer is printing business cards with separate numbers for each device...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Advantage of Colocation Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</guid><description>Companies frequently grapple with the decision of whether to handle a product or service internally or outsource it to a specialized vendor. This dilemma extends to telephone and computer services, demanding a careful evaluation of the most advantageous approach.
The optimal choice concerning technical services hinges significantly on your specific circumstances at any given moment. It is advisable to reassess these decisions periodically, perhaps annually. While the merits of internally managing your telephone and computer systems might be clear, it&amp;rsquo;s equally crucial to understand the upsides of outsourcing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantage-of-colocation-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Meshed MPLS Forms a Cloud of Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 21:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</guid><description>Modern MPLS networks are replacing outdated Frame Relay networks for connecting multiple business sites. Their ability to handle almost any protocol with high quality and reliability has driven their popularity. A long-standing desire has been the ability to use multiple carriers across locations seamlessly within a managed MPLS network. This desire has finally been fulfilled.
AireSpring, a rapidly growing and innovative carrier, now offers a &amp;ldquo;Meshed MPLS Network.&amp;rdquo; But what exactly does this entail and how does it differ from the inherent mesh capabilities of any MPLS network?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/meshed-mpls-forms-a-cloud-of-clouds/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>