<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>High Speed Internet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/high-speed-internet/</link><description>Recent content in High Speed Internet on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/high-speed-internet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CLEAR Sailing for 4G Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re hearing a lot about 4G wireless technology, but did you know that CLEAR is already rolling out its 4G WiMAX network? If you happen to live in an area where CLEAR WiMAX is currently offered, you can experience internet speeds comparable to DSL or Cable, all without the need for physical wires. They have a range of plans to suit your needs, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for your home, mobile device, or both...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clear-sailing-for-4g-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Alternative Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 08:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>For those living and working in rural areas, limited internet options can be a major problem. While major providers often only service cities, there are ways to stay connected without spending a fortune or waiting years for expanded infrastructure.
Forget DSL or cable – those are rare finds outside city limits. While universal telephone service guarantees basic phone lines (and thus, very slow dial-up internet), there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for fast, affordable internet: the existing cell phone network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/alternative-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Plus Copper Equals High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 03:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Our appetite for bandwidth is insatiable, growing daily. Businesses and consumers alike are hampered by insufficient bandwidth, preventing them from fully utilizing the latest technologies. Content providers and productivity vendors face similar hurdles, unable to deliver their full potential due to inadequate transport and last-mile bandwidth.
This scenario mirrors the early days of personal computers. For decades, limitations in processor speed, RAM, and hard disk capacity were constant challenges. While advancements in these areas have significantly minimized these bottlenecks, they haven&amp;rsquo;t entirely vanished...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-plus-copper-equals-high-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 09:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband offers a wider selection compared to residential options. While it&amp;rsquo;s true that some business internet services come with a higher price tag due to their advanced features, there are also affordable choices comparable to residential broadband, suitable for specific needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the various high-speed business internet services available and how to determine the best fit for your location.
Business Cable Broadband
Among the most budget-friendly options is cable broadband, technically referred to as DOCSIS 3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>High Speed Internet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</guid><description>In recent years, high-speed internet access has become widely available and affordable for businesses. Numerous broadband options exist, even in remote areas. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore a variety of high-speed internet connections, categorized by low, medium, and high bandwidth.
While businesses might desire high bandwidth, most don&amp;rsquo;t require extremely high speeds. Generally, higher bandwidth means higher cost. However, prices within bandwidth categories can vary. Shared service options are less expensive than dedicated services but offer less stable bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/high-speed-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>