<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Batteries on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/batteries/</link><description>Recent content in Batteries on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 06:16:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/batteries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GP Batteries has created a unique powerbank for the SEA Games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-batteries-has-created-a-unique-powerbank-for-the-sea-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-batteries-has-created-a-unique-powerbank-for-the-sea-games/</guid><description>Source: GP Batteries.
As the official battery partner for the SEA Games, GP Batteries has launched a limited-edition lithium-ion power bank to commemorate the upcoming games. This special power bank features a printed design of the 28th SEA Games Nila Logo and is officially recognized as an &amp;ldquo;Official Battery Partner&amp;rdquo; product.
This power bank boasts a 10,400mAH capacity, making it perfect for charging smartphones and tablets. With two output ports, users can charge two devices concurrently while LED indicators display the remaining battery life.</description></item><item><title>Every Home And Business Is A Battery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 15:43:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-home-and-business-is-a-battery/</guid><description>This week&amp;rsquo;s blog posts are dedicated to Blog Action Day 2009&amp;rsquo;s theme: global warming, climate change, and alternative energy. We already established that alternative energy is a viable option, as solar and wind power are readily available. However, skeptics often question how to ensure a consistent energy supply when natural resources like sunlight and wind are inconsistent.
This is a valid concern since traditional power plants fueled by coal, nuclear, or natural gas have built-in energy storage within their fuel sources and steam boilers.</description></item></channel></rss>