<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Troubleshooting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/troubleshooting/</link><description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:05:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Visible Means of IT Support</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visible-means-of-it-support/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/visible-means-of-it-support/</guid><description>When technology troubles strike, large companies have IT departments on speed dial, but what about independent professionals and smaller businesses? Managing computer issues isn&amp;rsquo;t as simple without a dedicated tech team.
Many individuals and small businesses handle their own computer maintenance, often with limited expertise. While tech-savvy users might possess deep system knowledge and meticulously update their software, others only react when problems arise. This often leads to confusion and frantic trips to the computer store.</description></item><item><title>Computer Tech Support Online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-tech-support-online/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/computer-tech-support-online/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there: your computer starts acting up out of nowhere. You try to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s wrong, but nothing seems obvious. You could buy a huge manual or take it to a store and wait forever for a diagnosis, but who wants to do that? There&amp;rsquo;s a better way.
Consider online tech support. Most computer issues aren&amp;rsquo;t serious hardware malfunctions; they&amp;rsquo;re often configuration errors or viruses. These problems can be fixed remotely by skilled technicians using special software.</description></item><item><title>Tips and Tricks for Troubleshooting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 19:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-and-tricks-for-troubleshooting/</guid><description>I often find myself surprised at how effective simple troubleshooting steps can be in resolving problems. When I&amp;rsquo;m stuck on an issue, these five steps are my go-to solutions:
Does the issue affect everyone? This helps determine if the problem originates from a specific workstation or user. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to test both as a regular user and as &amp;lsquo;sa&amp;rsquo;. Does it impact all companies? This helps isolate whether the issue stems from the data or affects the entire system.</description></item><item><title>Buyer (or Surfer) Be Cautious!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 21:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyer-or-surfer-be-cautious/</guid><description>Over the past week, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a few situations that highlight the internet&amp;rsquo;s potential, both good and bad, for software troubleshooting and learning, especially with Microsoft Dynamics GP.
For instance, I came across a Summit Group Software Blog post about recent changes to US Payroll for form 941. This was perfect timing, as I had just seen an internal email chain about it. The blog had valuable information from a reliable source that I could share, which was a great find.</description></item></channel></rss>