<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technavio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/technavio/</link><description>Recent content in Technavio on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/technavio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce.</description></item><item><title>Switch to organic bath and shower products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:31:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-organic-bath-and-shower-products/</guid><description>According to research firm Technavio, consumers are increasingly interested in bath and shower products that offer both organic ingredients and convenience. The company&amp;rsquo;s report on the global bath and shower products market highlights that rising living standards and disposable income are driving consumers towards higher-priced, aesthetically pleasing products with unique fragrances and effective ingredients. This trend is projected to propel the market to a value of at least US$15 billion by 2019, reflecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of approximately 4% from 2015 to 2019.</description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available.</description></item><item><title>More than half of the worldwide facial aesthetics market is made up of Botox</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/more-than-half-of-the-worldwide-facial-aesthetics-market-is-made-up-of-botox/</guid><description>The global demand for facial aesthetic procedures is growing, driven by consumers who are increasingly interested in their appearance and prefer less invasive treatments, according to a report on the Facial Aesthetics Market from 2016-2020 by Technavio.
Technavio&amp;rsquo;s research shows that Botox holds the largest share of the facial aesthetics market, making up roughly 52% of the total. They attribute this dominance to changing cultural perceptions of beauty, higher disposable incomes, and the growing popularity of the brand.</description></item><item><title>We are all increasing the frequency of washing our hair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</guid><description>The increasing prevalence of hair problems and pollution has led people to shampoo their hair more often, either daily or every other day. This trend has fueled the growth of the shampoo industry, as noted in Technavio&amp;rsquo;s report on the global hair shampoo market from 2015 to 2019. The report highlights that shampoos held over 40% of the global hair care market share in 2014.
Source: Technavio.
The global shampoo market is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 4.</description></item><item><title>Instant coffee is becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-coffee-is-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>Instant coffee is becoming more popular, particularly among younger generations, due to its affordability and convenience, according to research firm Technavio. This growing trend is driving positive projections for the global instant coffee market, as highlighted in their latest report.
Technavio further notes an increase in coffee consumption and a growing acceptance of café culture worldwide, leading coffee producers to introduce new blends and varieties. However, fluctuating prices for raw coffee beans introduce some unpredictability to the market.</description></item><item><title>Handbags will be the focus in India and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</guid><description>A new report from Technavio predicts the handbag market in Brazil, Russia, India, and China will experience significant growth between 2014 and 2019. This growth is projected to be over 7.41% in revenue and 7.02% in volume.
Technavio attributes this anticipated growth to the increasing association of handbags with social status among consumers. The introduction of stylish and functional designs, along with attractive colors, finishes, and textures, are making handbags more desirable.</description></item><item><title>Childcare centers are emerging in Chinese workplaces</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 20:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/childcare-centers-are-emerging-in-chinese-workplaces/</guid><description>Government policy changes are fueling the growth of the preschool or childcare market in China. Technavio forecasts a CAGR exceeding 6% for this market between 2016 and 2020. This growth is largely attributed to recent policy adjustments, notably the 2015 amendment to the one-child policy, now permitting couples to have two children. This shift aims to balance population development and, coupled with rising disposable incomes among middle-class families, is driving increased preschool enrollment.</description></item><item><title>The popularity of home remedies for teeth whitening is increasing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 05:27:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-popularity-of-home-remedies-for-teeth-whitening-is-increasing/</guid><description>Technavio, a research company specializing in technology, found that self-applied teeth whitening products have significantly changed the global oral care market. Consumers are increasingly choosing at-home treatments over professional ones. The firm attributes this shift to the affordability and convenience of oral care products like whitening strips, pens, and trays, which have become popular alternatives to professional whitening procedures.
According to a new Technavio report on the global teeth whitening product market, the industry is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 4% between 2015 and 2019.</description></item></channel></rss>