<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Medical Imaging on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/medical-imaging/</link><description>Recent content in Medical Imaging on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/medical-imaging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IP WAN over MPLS Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</guid><description>The internet is often the first thing that comes to mind when considering IP wide area networks. Although it boasts near-universal accessibility and relatively low access costs, it presents significant drawbacks for business use. Factors like bandwidth, latency, jitter, and packet loss lack guarantees and predictability. Additionally, security on the internet is unreliable. However, are alternative methods for interconnecting business locations excessively expensive or difficult to manage?
It&amp;rsquo;s feasible to establish a private IP network that enables the use of your existing IP addressing system, eliminating the need for encryption, firewalls, tunnels, or supplementary hardware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-wan-over-mpls-advantages/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your Pipes Fat Enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 09:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</guid><description>Higher resolution data demands more bandwidth, and WAN connections can become bottlenecks. Imagine a kink in a garden hose - the data is the water, and bandwidth is the pressure. Just as a kink restricts water flow, limited bandwidth slows data transfer, even with efficient network engineering. A larger pipe is needed for faster flow, just as a fatter data pipe is necessary for faster data transfer.
The increasing size and resolution of electronic business data necessitate these &amp;ldquo;fatter pipes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-pipes-fat-enough/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Gig E WAN Comes To The Enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</guid><description>It may seem surprising, but businesses can now access 10 Gigabit Ethernet connections for their wide area networks. What&amp;rsquo;s even more surprising is how many businesses can actually utilize this bandwidth.
Gigabit Ethernet is becoming increasingly popular among large corporations and tech companies that need to manage and deliver massive amounts of data quickly. What kinds of companies are we talking about?
For those involved in video production or editing, Gigabit per second connections are essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gig-e-wan-comes-to-the-enterprise/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Router Included With Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 18:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</guid><description>Considering upgrading your voice or data bandwidth? DS3 service offers 45 Mbps for both uploads and downloads, suitable for demanding tasks like video transfer, medical imaging, or call centers. But finding the right DS3 router for your network can feel like an added burden.
Rest assured, DS3 is a well-established technology with readily available equipment and decreasing prices. As more companies switch from T1 lines to DS3 bandwidth, implementation is becoming increasingly straightforward...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-router-included-with-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Options for Healthcare Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s healthcare landscape, broadband connectivity is crucial, driven by the increasing use of electronic health records, medical imaging, and telemedicine. When establishing an effective EHR environment, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to consider both private lines and public internet bandwidth services.
While both serve a purpose, private lines offer secure internal communication channels ideal for organizations managing sensitive electronic data. Essentially, these lines act as an extension of your network, ensuring restricted access to authorized users only...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-options-for-healthcare-providers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>