<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Intellectual Property on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intellectual-property/</link><description>Recent content in Intellectual Property on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/intellectual-property/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Seminar on Intellectual Property and Legal Issues by the RHT Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 04:02:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</guid><description>RHT Academy and RHTLaw Taylor Wessing are holding a half-day seminar titled &amp;ldquo;Commercial Contracts: Latest Case Law Developments, Negotiation Strategies and Intellectual Property&amp;rdquo; on March 4, 2015, at the Suntec Convention &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre in Singapore.
Designed for legal professionals, business development executives, company secretaries, and compliance officers, this seminar aims to:
Offer a practical, business-focused overview of recent key case law developments related to commercial contracts in Singapore and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seminar-on-intellectual-property-and-legal-issues-by-the-rht-academy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is enhancing its intellectual property infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 17:40:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</guid><description>The Indian government has decided to continue its efforts to improve its intellectual property (IP) offices. This initiative, part of the 12th Plan (2012-2017), will cost Rs309.6 crore, with Rs258 crore allocated for the 12th Plan and Rs51.6 crore for the 13th Plan.
This decision recognizes the increasing importance of IP in a globalized economy, India&amp;rsquo;s recent membership in the Madrid Protocol (April 2013), and the Controller General of Patents, Designs, and Trademarks (CGPDTM) office&amp;rsquo;s new role as an International Searching and Preliminary Examining Authority (ISA/IPEA) under the Patent Cooperation Treaty (starting October 2013)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-enhancing-its-intellectual-property-infrastructure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU General Court has declared Adidas' three-stripe trademark to be invalid.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</guid><description>Alexandros Antoniou, a legal expert from the University of Essex, analyzes a June 19, 2019, ruling by the EU General Court (GC) that invalidated Adidas&amp;rsquo;s trademark of three parallel stripes. The court upheld the EU Intellectual Property Office&amp;rsquo;s decision, which found the trademark too simplistic and lacking distinctiveness, both inherently and through use.
Adidas&amp;rsquo;s trademark, registered on May 21, 2014, for apparel, footwear, and headgear, was challenged by Shoe Branding Europe BVBA in December 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-has-declared-adidas-three-stripe-trademark-to-be-invalid/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice (CJEU) provides clarification on the patentability of stem cells in Europe.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther; all views are the author&amp;rsquo;s own
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently clarified its stance on biotechnology patents in the International Stem Cell Corporation case, modifying its earlier decision in Brüstle. The court now emphasizes the &amp;ldquo;inherent capacity&amp;rdquo; of a non-fertilized human egg stimulated by parthenogenesis to become a human being as the defining factor for it to be considered a &amp;ldquo;human embryo&amp;rdquo; and thus ineligible for patenting under the Biotechnology Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-patentability-of-stem-cells-in-europe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore has modified its regulations for the protection of designs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Law (MinLaw) has introduced the Registered Designs (Amendment) Bill to Parliament for its first reading. The bill aims to modernize Singapore&amp;rsquo;s design protection laws by reflecting current design and technology developments. It seeks to foster growth in the design sector by streamlining the process for designers to safeguard their creations.
This bill stems from a joint review of Singapore’s registered designs system by MinLaw and the Intellectual Property Office of Singapore (IPOS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-modified-its-regulations-for-the-protection-of-designs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Government support for research and development in Singapore SMEs and startups has been increased</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</guid><description>The Singapore government is increasing its support for research, development, and commercialization (R&amp;amp;D&amp;amp;C) activities undertaken by small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) and startups. This support encompasses financial assistance through grants, participation in business incubator programs, and favorable tax structures, as highlighted by Lim Chuan Poh, Chairman of the Agency for Science, Technology and Research (A*STAR), during his guest speaker appearance at the Developer and Global Entrepreneur Day, part of IBM&amp;rsquo;s XCite event in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-support-for-research-and-development-in-singapore-smes-and-startups-has-been-increased/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Has UKIP completely lost its sense of humor? Another satirical story...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:21:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
Introduction
In September 2014, Mike Dicks created a Twitter account called ‘UKIP Trumpton’. The account bio stated ‘After the recent defection of the Mayor of Trumpton and Mr Troop the town clerk this is the new home of UKIP tweets from Trumptonshire’ and used the official UKIP logo. Dicks later explained that the account was meant to gently mock UKIP, drawing a parallel between the party&amp;rsquo;s vision and the classic children&amp;rsquo;s show &amp;ldquo;Trumpton,&amp;rdquo; which lacked diversity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-ukip-completely-lost-its-sense-of-humor-another-satirical-story/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AG Kokott dismisses challenges to the legality of the Tobacco Products Directive - what does this mean for standardized packaging laws in Member States?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:13:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</guid><description>Jonathan Griffiths, Reader in Intellectual Property Law, Queen Mary University of London
The Tobacco Products Directive (Directive 2014/40/EU, revising Directive 2001/37/EC) implements strict rules for selling tobacco products. This includes requiring larger image and text health warnings on cigarettes and rolling tobacco, tighter marketing regulations for tobacco products (including e-cigarettes), and a ban on marketing tobacco products with &amp;ldquo;characterizing flavors,&amp;rdquo; such as menthol cigarettes.
On December 23rd, Advocate General Kokott presented her Opinions on three cases regarding the validity of specific parts of the Directive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ag-kokott-dismisses-challenges-to-the-legality-of-the-tobacco-products-directive-what-does-this-mean-for-standardized-packaging-laws-in-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We have the freedom to laugh at anything, but not everyone can appreciate it!" Examining the boundaries of freedom of expression through parody: the ruling of the CJEU in the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 04:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception
at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
The Advocate-General recently issued an opinion on parody, sparking significant interest in the topic. This opinion, while not yet available in English, has been the subject of discussion in legal circles. Further amplifying this attention, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has now released its own judgment on the matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The ECJ clarifies EU's authority over copyright law in the Marrakesh Treaty ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</guid><description>Gesa Kübek, PhD candidate at the law faculty of the University of Passau.
In its February 14, 2017 Opinion 3/15, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) determined that the European Union (EU) possesses exclusive competence to enter into the Marrakesh Treaty to Facilitate Access to Published Works for Persons Who Are Blind, Visually Impaired, or Otherwise Print Disabled (hereafter: Marrakesh Treaty). This decision aligns with Advocate General (AG) Wahl’s prior Opinion, which similarly argued for exclusive EU competence in this domain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it reasonable to expect consumers to be fluent in foreign languages? This was the question addressed by the CJEU in the Golden Balls case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 02:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/</guid><description>Anna Dannreuther, Trainee, Research Department of the CJEU (All views author’s own)
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a judgment on November 20th in the case of Intra-Presse SAS v OHIM (the &amp;lsquo;Golden Balls&amp;rsquo; case), which did not resolve the seven-year trademark dispute between the UK company Golden Balls Ltd. and Intra-Presse, the French organizers of FIFA’s Ballon d’Or award. The case revolves around the registration of the word mark ‘Golden Balls&amp;rsquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-reasonable-to-expect-consumers-to-be-fluent-in-foreign-languages-this-was-the-question-addressed-by-the-cjeu-in-the-golden-balls-case/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>