<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electronic Business Cards on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-business-cards/</link><description>Recent content in Electronic Business Cards on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-business-cards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Poken Enhances Face to Face Social Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 20:45:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</guid><description>Is jotting down contact information on scraps of paper your go-to method? Do you find yourself hoping your hand-written notes survive the journey home? Perhaps you rely on traditional business cards?
Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, those methods are outdated.
Just like Facebook, MySpace, LinkedIn, and Twitter revolutionized online networking, Poken is ushering in a new era for in-person connections with a device aptly named &amp;ldquo;Poken.&amp;rdquo; Think of it as a modern-day amulet, powered by cutting-edge technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-enhances-face-to-face-social-networking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Poken Pulse Business Networking Gadget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 01:27:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</guid><description>Traditional business networking relies heavily on exchanging physical business cards, a practice that persists despite the rise of smartphones and online networking. Poken offers a modern alternative by digitizing the process.
The Poken device, a small gadget shaped like a four-fingered hand, allows users to exchange contact information wirelessly. When two Poken devices touch, they transfer unique codes linked to the users&amp;rsquo; online profiles.
Unlike traditional business cards, Poken stores contact data in an online portal, making it easier to manage and search...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/poken-pulse-business-networking-gadget/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>