<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2018 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2018/</link><description>Recent content in 2018 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The future was examined at the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-was-examined-at-the-great-festival-of-innovation-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>The second day of the GREAT Festival of Innovation in Hong Kong brought together over 50 prominent figures from various industries to discuss the future of living. The event, which ran until March 24th, featured experts, business leaders, and creatives sharing their insights with attendees from around the world.
With a focus on the prediction that 70% of the global population will reside in urban areas by 2050, the festival examined the implications for how we live, eat, travel, and interact with the natural world through panels and demonstrations.</description></item><item><title>Orchard Road in Singapore is adorned with Christmas lights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/orchard-road-in-singapore-is-adorned-with-christmas-lights/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road is aglow with Disney magic this holiday season. The &amp;ldquo;Disney Magical Moments — Christmas on A Great Street!&amp;rdquo; celebration features illuminated displays of beloved characters. The lights were officially switched on the evening of November 10.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the Toy Story-themed lights outside Plaza Singapura from the opening night.
The lights are arranged in four color-themed zones:
- Orange: Pixar’s Toy Story characters, including Woody, Buzz Lightyear, and their friends.</description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>WAKE UP CALL is coming to Bali in October</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 16:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wake-up-call-is-coming-to-bali-in-october/</guid><description>Source: WAKE UP CALL website. W Hotels is putting on a unique music festival at three locations in 2018, with a Dubai edition planned for 2019.
W Hotels presents WAKE UP CALL, a distinctive music festival hosted at three W Hotels, including the W Bali, alongside venues in the US and Europe.
Merging their love for music with their signature Whatever/Whenever approach, WAKE UP CALL brings the festival experience directly to the hotel.</description></item><item><title>The flag-carrier airline of Dubai is the most popular brand among women in the UAE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-flag-carrier-airline-of-dubai-is-the-most-popular-brand-among-women-in-the-uae/</guid><description>Source: YouGov. 2019 Women&amp;rsquo;s Choice Rankings, top 10 for the UAE.
For the third consecutive year, Emirates secured the top spot in the UAE YouGov BrandIndex Women&amp;rsquo;s Rankings. The airline achieved the highest positive &amp;ldquo;Impression&amp;rdquo; score, reaching +70.0 among women in the UAE. WhatsApp maintained its second-place position, while Carrefour climbed to third place, surpassing Apple, which descended to fourth.
These rankings were determined using data from YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex, a daily brand tracker.</description></item><item><title>ARTWALK Little India combines elements of the past with modern influences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/artwalk-little-india-combines-elements-of-the-past-with-modern-influences/</guid><description>Source: ARTWALK Little India. Izzad Radzali Shah, Festival, ARTWALK Little India 2018, LASALLE College of the Arts, 2018. Photo: Ng Wu Gang. The multidisciplinary arts festival ARTWALK Little India is a collaboration between LASALLE College of the Arts (LASALLE) and the Singapore Tourism Board (STB), with support from the Little India Shopkeepers and Heritage Association. It returns for its fourth year in January 2018 as a featured event in Singapore Art Week.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the end of the year with eco-friendly festivities at East, Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 10:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-end-of-the-year-with-eco-friendly-festivities-at-east-hong-kong/</guid><description>The environmentally conscious EAST, Hong Kong hotel is ready to celebrate the holiday season this year with special decorations and exciting events.
Continuing a tradition that began in 2014, EAST&amp;rsquo;s Christmas Village highlights creative recycling. This year, the EAST team gathered fallen logs left behind by Typhoon Mangkhut from the city streets to create unique Christmas decorations. Students from Jockey Club Sarah Roe School (JCSRS), the only school in Hong Kong offering an English curriculum for students with additional learning needs, collaborated with the EAST team on this project.</description></item><item><title>The Philippines' economic outlook has improved according to the World Bank</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 06:22:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-philippines-economic-outlook-has-improved-according-to-the-world-bank/</guid><description>The World Bank has improved its economic forecast for the Philippines from 2016 to 2018.
They now predict the Philippine economy will grow by 6.8% in 2016, up from their previous prediction of 6.4% made in October (World Bank Philippines Economic Update October 2016). This adjustment is based on stronger than expected growth in the third quarter of 2016, fueled by increased investment and private consumption. This follows robust economic performance in the first half of 2016, driven by the government’s pre-election spending.</description></item><item><title>Numerous innovations showcased at Food&amp;HotelAsia 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 13:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/numerous-innovations-showcased-at-food-hotelasia-2018/</guid><description>Display at the Suntec venue.
The Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) and ProWine Asia (PWA) trade shows are predicted to draw tens of thousands of attendees during their joint four-day run in Singapore, from April 24th to 27th.
This year marks the largest event yet. Visitors can explore exhibits from over 3,500 international food, beverage, and hospitality exhibitors throughout 120,000 sq m at FHA. In addition, PWA 2018 features 300 international wine and spirits exhibitors across 7,500 sq m.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air reveals its summer 2018 schedule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air. Plane in Gulf Air livery.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has launched its Summer 2018 schedule, increasing both flight frequency and passenger capacity to popular destinations for the peak travel season between mid-June and mid-September 2018.
Flights to Amman, Jordan, will increase to three times daily, while flights to Beirut, Lebanon, will increase to twice daily. Istanbul, Turkey, a popular summer destination, will have 12 weekly flights during peak season, and flights to Baghdad, Iraq, will permanently increase to five times per week.</description></item><item><title>Jane's Walk Singapore offers a blend of classic and innovative walking tours</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jane-s-walk-singapore-offers-a-blend-of-classic-and-innovative-walking-tours/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Peatix page.
Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk logo.
The annual Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk Singapore, a series of free walking tours led by community members, will take place from May 4th to 6th. Inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, these walks encourage participants to share local stories, discover the city, and connect with their neighbors.
While many tours are already at capacity, new spots may open up, so interested individuals are encouraged to check back.</description></item><item><title>Dell presents key features for IT Show 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-presents-key-features-for-it-show-2018/</guid><description>Dell is featuring special deals on select products at IT Show 2018, happening in Suntec Singapore now through March 18th.
The XPS 13, available in a new rose gold color, starts at S$2,899. This 13&amp;quot; device is touted as the most powerful in its class and the smallest 13&amp;quot; available. It boasts an 8th Gen Intel Quad Core processor, a 4K Ultra HD InfinityEdge display, and introduces Dell Cinema, featuring CinemaColor, CinemaStream with wireless channels, and CinemaSound with Waves MaxxAudio Pro.</description></item><item><title>Eko Nugroho is currently showcasing his street art exhibition through digital prints produced by HP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2024 22:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eko-nugroho-is-currently-showcasing-his-street-art-exhibition-through-digital-prints-produced-by-hp/</guid><description>This image, from HP Inc., showcases embroidered artwork by Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho. It features his signature masked characters and intricate designs reminiscent of Japanese woodcuts.
HP Inc is the Innovation Sponsor for the &amp;ldquo;Art from the Streets&amp;rdquo; exhibition at the ArtScience Museum in Singapore. For the exhibition, HP created nine large-scale prints of significant artworks. They are also using their digital printing technology to showcase the work of Indonesian artist Eko Nugroho in fresh and unexpected ways, demonstrating that street art can be displayed anywhere and on any medium.</description></item><item><title>The winners of the FinTech Awards have been announced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:57:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-winners-of-the-fintech-awards-have-been-announced/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and The Association of Banks in Singapore (ABS) awarded S$1.2 million to 12 fintech companies at the FinTech Awards, held during the third annual Singapore FinTech Festival.
This year&amp;rsquo;s winning solutions focused on financial inclusion and represented a broader range of ASEAN countries. These solutions addressed various business areas, including credit scoring, mobile security, anti-money laundering, and digital investment.
Here are the 12 award recipients:</description></item><item><title>The inaugural India-ASEAN Writers Festival premieres in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-india-asean-writers-festival-premieres-in-singapore/</guid><description>The High Commission of India in Singapore is hosting the first India-ASEAN Writers Festival in Singapore.
This festival is one of many events celebrating 25 years of friendship between India and ASEAN, coinciding with the ASEAN India Pravasi Bharatiya Divas (Overseas Indians Day). The events are scheduled for January 6-7 at the Marina Bay Sands.
The PBD Writers Festival, a key event organized by Singapore-based publishing house Kitaab International on behalf of the High Commission, aims to &amp;ldquo;celebrate the literary ties between India and the ASEAN nations,&amp;rdquo; said Zafar Anjum, Kitaab&amp;rsquo;s founder and CEO.</description></item><item><title>"Credit Suisse identifies three major trends for 2018"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 04:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-identifies-three-major-trends-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Cavalli.
The sixth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference 2018, held in Singapore, focused on three significant trends: technology designed to benefit humanity, including AI and robotics; a future shaped by Millennials; and the expanding silver economy.
Benjamin Cavalli, Head of Private Banking Southeast Asia and Singapore CEO of Credit Suisse, explained in his opening remarks that these megatrends represent investment themes based on Credit Suisse&amp;rsquo;s expert insights.</description></item><item><title>The 5th annual PCCW Global Charity Run will be held in Singapore this June</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 01:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5th-annual-pccw-global-charity-run-will-be-held-in-singapore-this-june/</guid><description>Source: PCCW Global Charity Run web page. A picture from the same event in 2017.
The 5th yearly PCCW Global Charity Run will happen this June, and both PCCW employees and the general public can participate.
This run is organized by PCCW Global, a telecommunications company operating in Asia, Africa, Latin America, and the Middle East.
All funds raised from this year&amp;rsquo;s run will be donated to Make-A-Wish Singapore, an organization that grants wishes for children facing life-threatening illnesses.</description></item><item><title>The true desires of Millennials</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:41:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-desires-of-millennials/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Yak, Szpitalak, Sun, and Huterstein, with Dan Murphy from _CNBC _moderating.
Millennials don&amp;rsquo;t stay with one company throughout their careers. They crave consistent feedback and embrace failure as a learning opportunity on the path to success. They&amp;rsquo;re comfortable investing in startups and don&amp;rsquo;t conform to the traditional 9-to-5 office schedule.
These characteristics and perspectives of Millennials were openly discussed at the 2018 Credit Suisse Global Megatrends conference, yielding some unexpected insights.</description></item><item><title>The impact of GDPR will be remembered in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</guid><description>The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) heavily influenced how we addressed online privacy in 2018. While it primarily protects residents of the European Union, the GDPR&amp;rsquo;s global reach impacts any company conducting business with EU residents. This broad scope has shifted GDPR from a regional concern to a worldwide one.
Several industry leaders have shared their perspectives on GDPR&amp;rsquo;s significant effects:
Source: Sage. Wherrett.
Arlene Wherrett, VP and MD of Sage Asia, observed that GDPR was a major catalyst for change in business operations.</description></item><item><title>Ignoring preferred payment methods could result in travel companies losing customers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:18:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ignoring-preferred-payment-methods-could-result-in-travel-companies-losing-customers/</guid><description>Around 85% of Chinese consumers take at least one leisure trip per year.
Credit cards (36%) and debit cards (29%) are the top payment choices for travel worldwide. PayPal is also popular (17%) across various countries and age groups.
Electronic payments are prevalent in China, with 78% favoring Alipay.
Seven out of ten Chinese travelers report experiencing fraud.
A recent global survey* of 7,400 consumers by YouGov and ACI Worldwide, a provider of electronic payment solutions, found that over a third (36%) of respondents from Britain, America, China, France, and Germany are dissatisfied with limited online payment choices for booking vacations.</description></item><item><title>The True Colours Festival includes a number of groundbreaking inclusive initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 19:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-true-colours-festival-includes-a-number-of-groundbreaking-inclusive-initiatives/</guid><description>Source: True Colours Festival website. Some of the featured performers.
This coming March, twenty artists and groups will come together in Singapore for the first and largest event in the Asia Pacific region to showcase performers with disabilities. From March 22-25, 2018, Singapore will host True Colours Festival – the Asia Pacific Celebration of Artistes with Disabilities. True Colours is presented by UNESCO and The Nippon Foundation (TNF), two global organizations that advocate for the rights of people with disabilities (PWDs).</description></item><item><title>Exploring the history of Bukit Panjang, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:05:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-history-of-bukit-panjang-singapore/</guid><description>Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a global movement of free walking tours inspired by urbanist Jane Jacobs, continues to thrive in Singapore, with tours often fully booked within hours of being announced. This enthusiastic response highlights the movement&amp;rsquo;s ability to connect people with their communities and explore urban landscapes.
This year, on May 5th, a sold-out walk titled &amp;ldquo;At the Crossroads: Bukit Panjang&amp;rdquo; offered participants a unique opportunity to delve into the neighborhood&amp;rsquo;s rich history.</description></item><item><title>Bloem marks 4th anniversary with introduction of new services and partnerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bloem-marks-4th-anniversary-with-introduction-of-new-services-and-partnerships/</guid><description>Pictured from left to right: Sukri Kadola and Ivy Tan cut a cake during Bloem&amp;rsquo;s anniversary celebration.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s custom floral design company, Bloem, recently commemorated its fourth anniversary. The company marked this occasion by announcing new partnerships and the launch of its Concierge service.
&amp;ldquo;While many believe the economy has presented difficulties for businesses, success is subjective,&amp;rdquo; says Sukri Kadola, Bloem&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO. Eighty percent of Bloem&amp;rsquo;s revenue is generated through corporate projects.</description></item><item><title>Watching 100 trends in the MENA region for 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 07:22:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watching-100-trends-in-the-mena-region-for-2018/</guid><description>Source: JWT website. Cover for the report.
J. Walter Thompson&amp;rsquo;s Middle East and Africa Innovation Group recently published their sixth yearly consumer trends report, focusing on the MENA region for 2018. Future 100 Trends and Change to Watch in MENA highlights the significant themes that are changing how consumers in Egypt, North Africa, Lebanon, Jordan, the Gulf, and Saudi Arabia live and consume.
A key takeaway from the Future 100 MENA Report is that Middle Eastern consumers are seeing themselves more as global citizens.</description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself for the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-for-the-2018-international-champions-cup-in-singapore/</guid><description>Get ready for football fever this July as Arsenal, Atlético de Madrid, and Paris Saint-Germain head to Singapore for the 2018 International Champions Cup. This renowned annual tournament showcases top European football clubs competing across North America, Europe, and Asia.
Source: Sports Hub website. Three football clubs will be playing against each other at the 2018 International Champions Cup in Singapore on July 26, 28 and 30.
Beyond the three matches at the National Stadium on July 26th, 28th, and 30th, fans can immerse themselves in the excitement at the House of Football pop-up in Clarke Quay, Singapore’s vibrant nightlife and dining hub.</description></item><item><title>Indonesia has the highest number of brand advocates for Garuda</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-has-the-highest-number-of-brand-advocates-for-garuda/</guid><description>Garuda Indonesia, the national airline, has earned the highest level of brand advocacy among Indonesian consumers, according to a YouGov BrandIndex analysis.
With a score of 87.5, Garuda secured the top position, surpassing Singapore Airlines (77.2) and Bank Central Asia (76.5).
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s rankings utilize a net promoter score methodology to determine which brands have the highest percentage of current and former customers who would recommend them to family or friends. The top 10 list includes several automotive brands, with Toyota ranking 4th (75.</description></item><item><title>CEOs express optimism about the global economy, according to PwC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 01:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ceos-express-optimism-about-the-global-economy-according-to-pwc/</guid><description>Global business leaders are feeling positive about the economic climate in the near future, according to the 21st annual survey of CEOs conducted by PwC. The survey, which included approximately 1,300 CEOs from around the world, was released at the World Economic Forum Annual Meeting in Davos, Switzerland.
A significant majority (57%) of CEOs believe that global economic growth will improve in the next year. This represents a substantial increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 29% and marks the largest surge in positive sentiment since PwC began tracking global growth projections in 2012.</description></item><item><title>Follow the light from day to night on 28 July in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:20:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/follow-the-light-from-day-to-night-on-28-july-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Canon. The Canon PhotoMarathon XVI will include assignments that extend from day into night.
Returning for its 16th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon XVI is scheduled for July 28th in Singapore. This year, Canon is expanding the event by incorporating community support and introducing new competition elements.
Building upon Canon’s ongoing support of local sports, Canon recently announced a partnership with Olympian Joseph Schooling. In line with the Canon PhotoMarathon’s goal to inspire and connect the photography community, Schooling will reveal one of the competition themes at the event.</description></item><item><title>Experience the passion and joy of BMW at the BMW World in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-passion-and-joy-of-bmw-at-the-bmw-world-in-singapore/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is hosting BMW World of Passion and Joy at the Suntec Singapore International Convention and Exhibition Centre on August 25th and 26th, 2018.
This event offers visitors a chance to experience the latest BMW and MINI models, explore classic BMW heritage cars, and immerse themselves in The MINI Story. Performances and interactive activities will be available throughout the event.
Christopher Wehner, Managing Director of BMW Group Asia, emphasized that the event bridges BMW&amp;rsquo;s past, present, and future.</description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the limits of art in the 1950s paved the way for the contemporary art scene we see today</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-limits-of-art-in-the-1950s-paved-the-way-for-the-contemporary-art-scene-we-see-today/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Minimalism: Space. Light. Object.&amp;rdquo; a groundbreaking exhibition for Southeast Asia, showcases the evolution of Minimalism, an art form that challenges conventions.
Presented in Singapore through a partnership between the National Gallery Singapore and ArtScience Museum, Singapore, this exhibition presents significant Minimalist works from the 1950s to today. Visitors can experience over 100 pieces by 70 artists, including prominent names like Donald Judd, Mark Rothko, Mona Hatoum, Anish Kapoor, Ai Weiwei, Olafur Eliasson, and Haegue Yang.</description></item><item><title>The Pantone color of the year for 2018 is Ultra Violet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:29:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-pantone-color-of-the-year-for-2018-is-ultra-violet/</guid><description>Source: Pantone. PANTONE Ultra Violet 18-3838.
Pantone, a subsidiary of X-Rite and a leading authority on color systems and technology, declared PANTONE 18-3838, Ultra Violet, as its highly anticipated Color of the Year for 2018. According to Pantone, this shade embodies originality, creativity, and forward-thinking.
For nearly two decades, Pantone&amp;rsquo;s Color of the Year has significantly shaped product development and purchasing choices across diverse industries, including fashion, home furnishings, industrial design, packaging, and graphic design.</description></item><item><title>Pesta Raya by Esplanade is back in July</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pesta-raya-by-esplanade-is-back-in-july/</guid><description>The Esplanade – Theatres on the Bay’s 17th annual Pesta Raya – Malay Festival of Arts will take place from July 12th to 15th, 2018. The festival coincides with Hari Raya Aidilfitri, a celebration that lasts until mid-July.
This year, the festival focuses on the history of the Nusantara. Fezhah Maznan, a programmer with The Esplanade Company, stated that Pesta Raya has always celebrated the rich Malay heritage through arts and culture from the region.</description></item><item><title>The second year of the 3-in-1 Singapore Festival of Fun promises even more excitement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 22:46:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-second-year-of-the-3-in-1-singapore-festival-of-fun-promises-even-more-excitement/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay. Banner for the Singapore Festival of Fun.
Now in its second year, the massive three-part Festival of Fun combines the Magners International Comedy Festival, Nickelodeon Fiesta, and Clarke Quay StreetFest this March. The festival welcomes street performers from Covent Garden in the UK, beloved Nickelodeon characters, and award-winning comedians from around the globe.
Attendees can join in the festivities while also enjoying the diverse food and drink options at Clarke Quay&amp;rsquo;s many establishments.</description></item><item><title>Enterprise Singapore is backing F&amp;B and food manufacturers with innovative digital projects</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 10:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-singapore-is-backing-f-b-and-food-manufacturers-with-innovative-digital-projects/</guid><description>RESTAURANT 3.0: Embracing Technology in the Food Industry Enterprise Singapore showcased new digital solutions at Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) 2018. These solutions aim to help Singaporean food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and food manufacturing companies expand internationally and enhance their operational efficiency.
The showcased digital initiatives include a B2B online platform for food manufacturers and the RESTAURANT 3.0 exhibition for F&amp;amp;B businesses.
Enterprise Singapore, in collaboration with the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF), launched the &amp;ldquo;SMF SMART App&amp;rdquo; at the Singapore Pavilion during FHA.</description></item><item><title>The uptrend in online hiring in Singapore is being led by the IT, BFSI, and advertising industries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 06:17:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uptrend-in-online-hiring-in-singapore-is-being-led-by-the-it-bfsi-and-advertising-industries/</guid><description>Singapore saw an increase in online recruitment in November 2018, with a 5% rise in job postings compared to the same period in 2017, as reported by the Monster Employment Index (MEI). This represents a significant jump from the 1% growth recorded in October 2018.
The IT, telecom, BPO/ITES sector experienced the most substantial growth, surging by 22% year-on-year, marking its highest point since March 2018. BFSI and advertising also demonstrated positive trends, rising by 16% and 15% respectively compared to the previous year.</description></item><item><title>Cirque de Cuisine: The Festive Edition returns to Atlantis, The Palm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cirque-de-cuisine-the-festive-edition-returns-to-atlantis-the-palm/</guid><description>Source: Atlantis, The Palm. Cirque de Cuisine.
The Cirque de Cuisine event will launch Dubai&amp;rsquo;s holiday season with a Winter Wonderland theme. Held on December 6th at The Avenues in Atlantis, The Palm, this all-you-can-eat-and-drink event offers early bird tickets starting at AED495 for four hours of holiday festivities.
Cirque de Cuisine gives diners the opportunity to sample signature dishes, live cooking stations, buffets, drinks, and live entertainment at a variety of restaurants.</description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be expanding in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:09:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-expanding-in-2020/</guid><description>A Nestle Sjora mural was a key feature at the Nestle booth during Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia 2018.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), the largest biennial trade show in the region for food and hospitality, will be split into two separate shows starting in 2020. FHA-HoReCa will take place in early March, and FHA-Food &amp;amp; Beverage will follow at the end of March.
This cake was on display at the Qingdao Kesong Food Company (KFI) booth.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the holiday season at the Westin Singapore in 2017!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-holiday-season-at-the-westin-singapore-in-2017/</guid><description>Source: The Westin Singapore website. The apple glazed turkey at Seasonal Tastes.
Celebrate this holiday season at the Westin Singapore with their Christmas offerings. Enjoy delicious yule log cakes, savory roasts, thoughtful Christmas hampers, and gourmet selections at Seasonal Tastes and Cook &amp;amp; Brew.
Christmas Eve and Christmas Day
The Christmas Eve lunch buffet at Seasonal Tastes includes tempting dishes like lobster bisque, grilled Aussie tomahawk, maple and miso glazed salmon, and panettone bread pudding with vanilla Anglaise (a delicate pouring custard).</description></item><item><title>The Bay Hotel is now offering a Ramadhan buffet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 21:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-bay-hotel-is-now-offering-a-ramadhan-buffet/</guid><description>Rumah Rasa, a restaurant located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Bay Hotel, is known for its &amp;ldquo;home-style with a twist&amp;rdquo; Indonesian cooking, using herbs freshly picked from its own garden. During the month of Ramadan, Rumah Rasa offers a special &amp;ldquo;Ramadan Iftar Menu&amp;rdquo; featuring unique and less common Indonesian dishes.
Indonesian-born Chef Esa Hassim, the mastermind behind these culinary creations, shared that he sources these distinctive dishes by inquiring about Indonesian delicacies that are not readily available in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Participate in the Singapore Mother's Day contest for a chance to win a Huawei P20 in Pink Gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 21:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/participate-in-the-singapore-mother-s-day-contest-for-a-chance-to-win-a-huawei-p20-in-pink-gold/</guid><description>Source: Huawei Mobile Singapore
Facebook page. Watch the video
In Singapore, Huawei&amp;rsquo;s Consumer Business Group is holding a contest in celebration of Mother&amp;rsquo;s Day (May 13th), ending on May 24th.
To participate, Singaporean residents simply need to comment on the contest video found on the Huawei Mobile Singapore Facebook page. The comment should answer the question: &amp;ldquo;What lengths would your mother go to for you?&amp;rdquo; and include the hashtag #SeeMooore.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Green Building Week has officially begun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 01:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-green-building-week-has-officially-begun/</guid><description>The DVUCA city management system dashboard uses data from Singapore and other cities to quickly compare water and power consumption. It can even provide granular insights, such as indicating if someone is at their desk.
Singapore Green Building Week has commenced, featuring Build Eco Xpo (BEX) Asia, a Southeast Asian trade show for the region&amp;rsquo;s green building market, and Mostra Convegno Expocomfort (MCE) Asia, a regional exhibition for HVAC-R*, water, and energy solutions.</description></item><item><title>Asian destinations emerge victorious in the inaugural KAYAK Travel Awards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 10:36:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-destinations-emerge-victorious-in-the-inaugural-kayak-travel-awards/</guid><description>Source: KAYAK. Winners from the first-ever KAYAK Travel Awards.
The travel search engine KAYAK has revealed the winners of its first KAYAK Travel Awards. Sixteen categories, including airlines, airports, hotels, and destinations, were awarded based on public votes collected over 19 days from June 12th to June 30th, 2018.
Singaporean brands dominated the awards. Singapore Airlines received top honors in four categories: Favourite Airline (Short-haul), Favourite Airline (Long-haul), Favourite Airline Crew, and Favourite In-flight F&amp;amp;B.</description></item><item><title>Amazon is sharing the best-selling Christmas items from Prime Now Singapore orders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:53:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazon-is-sharing-the-best-selling-christmas-items-from-prime-now-singapore-orders/</guid><description>Amazon has revealed the top-selling items purchased by Prime Now users in Singapore during a record-breaking holiday season worldwide. Customers took advantage of Prime Now&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ultra-Fast Delivery&amp;rdquo; option throughout the holiday period, with tens of thousands of products delivered, even in the final hours. The last Prime Now order was delivered at 10:23 p.m. on December 24th.
&amp;ldquo;The volume of shoppers in Singapore using Prime Now leading up to Christmas was remarkable, as was the number who signed up for a free Prime trial or initiated a paid membership,&amp;rdquo; shared Kourosh Kaghazian, Country Manager for Amazon Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Sony has introduced the Picture This Festival for the Planet competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-has-introduced-the-picture-this-festival-for-the-planet-competition/</guid><description>Sony Pictures Television Networks (SPTN), working with the United Nations Foundation, has launched the Picture This Festival for the Planet. The short-film competition encourages emerging filmmakers, storytellers, and changemakers globally to share their visions for a positive future for the planet.
Representing over 70 countries, participants are invited to submit videos inspired by the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The SDGs are a collection of global goals adopted by the United Nations to address poverty, protect the planet, and promote prosperity for everyone.</description></item><item><title>Salary growth is expected in Southeast Asia as there is a high demand for IT skillsets in key sectors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:33:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/salary-growth-is-expected-in-southeast-asia-as-there-is-a-high-demand-for-it-skillsets-in-key-sectors/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s IT sector is expected to experience high demand for skilled professionals and contract workers in 2018, particularly in fintech, healthcare, and technology.
Specialized skills will be highly sought after in 2018 across accounting and finance, human resources, sales and marketing, and technology sectors.
According to the 2018 Salary Survey by Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, the economic outlook for the coming year is positive. The survey anticipates that continued digitalization and market expansion in Southeast Asia will fuel salary growth.</description></item><item><title>Examining culture and heritage using technology as a tool</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 00:20:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-culture-and-heritage-using-technology-as-a-tool/</guid><description>The National Museum of Singapore&amp;rsquo;s new exhibit, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents,&amp;rdquo; opens on August 4th and features technologically innovative projects that combine history, art, and technology.
Developed collaboratively with designers, artists, and tech companies, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; offers visitors new ways to experience culture and heritage. This includes immersive virtual and augmented reality exhibits, artificial intelligence-powered conversations, and much more.
Part of a larger initiative to promote digital innovation within the cultural sector, &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Presents&amp;rdquo; showcases seven prototypes from the &amp;ldquo;DigiMuse Open Call&amp;rdquo; for digital art and innovation, which concluded in April.</description></item><item><title>The demand for HR and admin professionals is increasing in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 16:34:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-hr-and-admin-professionals-is-increasing-in-malaysia/</guid><description>For the first time since March 2018, HR and administrative (admin) jobs in Malaysia experienced a 2% year-over-year increase in December.
This job category also saw recent positive short-term growth, with a 4% rise month-over-month and a 2% increase over three months. The Philippines echoed this positive trend, with online hiring demand for HR and admin professionals surging by 22% year-on-year.
Demand for HR and admin interns remained strong in Malaysia and the Philippines, representing the highest demand among all surveyed occupations at 13% and 5%, respectively.</description></item><item><title>The 2023 goals of Singapore's Digital Government Blueprint are outlined</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 22:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2023-goals-of-singapore-s-digital-government-blueprint-are-outlined/</guid><description>Source: GovTech Singapore website.
Infographic, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s _Digital
Government Blueprint. _
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy Prime Minister, Teo Chee Hean, who also oversees National Security, recently introduced the Digital Government Blueprint (DGB) at the Smart Nation Innovations Week Opening Symposium. This blueprint outlines the government&amp;rsquo;s goal to utilize data and emerging technologies to enhance services for citizens, businesses, and public officials. It also aims to foster a digital economy and society, aligning with Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation vision.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2018 Budget is on technology, innovation, and building capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Budget 2018 site. View of Singapore skyline.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Trade and Industry (MTI) anticipates more broad-based economic growth across sectors in 2018, albeit at a moderated pace compared to the heights of 2017, according to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Financial Minister Heng Swee Keat during his Budget 2018 speech.
Minister Heng emphasized the need for Singapore to adapt to three major shifts in the coming decade:
Asia&amp;rsquo;s increasing global economic influence.</description></item><item><title>Positioning your company in the southwest corner of the office could enhance its success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/positioning-your-company-in-the-southwest-corner-of-the-office-could-enhance-its-success/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:52:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/positioning-your-company-in-the-southwest-corner-of-the-office-could-enhance-its-success/</guid><description>Source: Joey Yap Private Limited.
Infographic on the impact of directions in 2018.
Dato’ Joey Yap, a prominent speaker, author, and Chief Consultant at Joey Yap Private Limited, a consultancy specializing in fengshui and Chinese astrology, has put together a list of 2018 fengshui direction predictions for a prosperous year of the earth dog.
In fengshui, different directions are believed to influence different aspects of a person&amp;rsquo;s life, and these influences shift each lunar year.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has seen the launch of four new BMW models</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-seen-the-launch-of-four-new-bmw-models/</guid><description>BMW Group Asia is launching four new car models simultaneously for the first time in Singapore.
The First-Ever BMW i8 Roadster The BMW i8 Roadster features upward-opening doors.
This groundbreaking convertible plug-in hybrid, dubbed a &amp;ldquo;gentleman&amp;rsquo;s racer,&amp;rdquo; can accelerate from 0 to 100 km/h in 4.6 seconds. CS Liew, a director at an agricultural science company, owns the first edition in Singapore, which is already on the road. Initially preferring hardtop convertibles, Liew was captivated by the i8 Roadster&amp;rsquo;s design.</description></item><item><title>CulinaryOn Singapore is offering Lunar New Year dinner experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/culinaryon-singapore-is-offering-lunar-new-year-dinner-experiences/</guid><description>Source: Culinaryon Singapore. Yusheng with salmon sashimi.
For this Lunar New Year, CulinaryOn Singapore is offering special dinners starting on December 26th, 2017. These dinners feature premium six-to-eight course meals and include a taste of their cooking classes with a noodle-making activity. Guests can also choose to create their own desserts.
The eight-course premium menu features dishes such as yusheng with salmon sashimi, shiitake mushrooms with broccoli, crayfish braised longevity noodles, golden shrimp with honeydew mayo, and mango ice cream with pomelo.</description></item><item><title>Joey Yap provides predictions for the 12 animal signs in the year 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-provides-predictions-for-the-12-animal-signs-in-the-year-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 19:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-provides-predictions-for-the-12-animal-signs-in-the-year-2018/</guid><description>Source: Joey Yap Private Limited.
Infographic for the 12 animal signs in 2018.
Chinese culture places significance on the lunar year, believing it brings new fortunes. Each of the 12 animal signs in the Chinese zodiac is thought to face unique opportunities and obstacles.
Within the Chinese zodiac, each year aligns with one of 12 animals and one of five elements. Although the year of the fire rooster (January 28, 2017, to February 15, 2018) is still ongoing, a shift is anticipated on February 16, 2018, as the year of the earth dog commences.</description></item><item><title>Join us in Asia at the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group to celebrate the holiday season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 10:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-us-in-asia-at-the-mandarin-oriental-hotel-group-to-celebrate-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>To celebrate the holiday season, the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group is offering special packages at several of its Asian properties.
Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong
Source: Mandarin Oriental, Hong Kong website. Mother with daughter in a Christmas setting.
The hotel will be adorned with festive decorations, and guests will be treated to classic Christmas treats.
Starting from HKD4,200 per night, the Winter Getaway package, available from December 1, 2018, to January 6, 2019, includes accommodations, daily breakfast for two, and special holiday amenities.</description></item><item><title>40% of Singaporeans have experienced a data breach within the last year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:58:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/40-of-singaporeans-have-experienced-a-data-breach-within-the-last-year/</guid><description>Parvinder Walia, during his presentation, revealed that 72% of consumers react negatively to news of a company suffering a cyberattack or data breach.
ESET, a cybersecurity software company, conducted a survey to examine consumer online behavior and perspectives on cybersecurity in light of recent data breaches.
The ESET 2018 APAC Consumer Behaviour Survey found that 42% of Singaporeans had experienced some form of data breach in the preceding year. These breaches included theft and misuse of personal information, bank account fraud, social media account compromise, and attacks from malware and viruses.</description></item><item><title>Shoppers are interested in clothes, cosmetics, and baby products on 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 22:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoppers-are-interested-in-clothes-cosmetics-and-baby-products-on-11-11/</guid><description>Source: Alizila blog. The 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival logo is illuminated in neon.
Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 2018 11.11 Global Shopping Festival is surpassing the sales of the previous year. Alizila reports show that it took a mere 1 minute and 25 seconds for the festival to reach over US$1 billion in total gross merchandise volume (GMV).
By 1:15 p.m., Tmall Global had already exceeded its total GMV from the entire 2017 11.</description></item><item><title>Pre-registered delegates can access a report on industry innovations through Food&amp;HotelAsia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 06:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pre-registered-delegates-can-access-a-report-on-industry-innovations-through-food-hotelasia/</guid><description>To commemorate its 40th anniversary, Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA) has partnered with Euromonitor International to release a new white paper.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Smart Innovations Transforming the Food and Hospitality Landscape by 2020,&amp;rdquo; the 20-page report examines significant disruptions influencing the industry. Based on research conducted by UBM and Euromonitor, the white paper incorporates insights from a survey of over 1,000 suppliers and manufacturers across key food, hotel, and food service equipment sectors in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Take a look at the lineup for YouTube FanFest Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-look-at-the-lineup-for-youtube-fanfest-hong-kong/</guid><description>Source: YouTube. Poster for YouTube FanFest Hong
Kong 2018.
The Manulife-sponsored YouTube FanFest returns to Hong Kong on August 3 at the Kowloonbay International Trade &amp;amp; Exhibition Centre (KITEC).
This live event bridges the gap between prominent YouTube creators from Hong Kong and around the globe, offering a platform for fan engagement. YouTube FanFest Hong Kong will feature:
- Matt Steffanina, a US-based dancer, YouTuber, and social media figure known for his dance-centric content</description></item><item><title>Every night in Sydney, it's Lights On for Vivid Sydney!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Destination NSW. Vivid Sydney in action.
The tenth anniversary of Vivid Sydney, the world’s largest festival of light, music and ideas, has begun. As Australia’s largest event, Vivid Sydney transforms the city into a captivating display of illumination, sound, and creativity.
The festival commenced with the symbolic &amp;lsquo;Lights On&amp;rsquo; moment, with all eyes on the Sydney Opera House for the &amp;lsquo;Lighting of the Sails&amp;rsquo;. This year&amp;rsquo;s display, created by Australian artist Jonathan Zawada, featured dynamic digital sculptures of commonplace objects and elements from nature, morphing and changing before the viewers&amp;rsquo; eyes.</description></item><item><title>Celebrate the year of the dog in a stylish manner at Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 14:51:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-the-year-of-the-dog-in-a-stylish-manner-at-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Starting January 22, 2018, ring in the Year of the Earth Dog and usher in new beginnings at the Pan Pacific Singapore.
Hai Tien Lo
Executive Chef Lai Tong Ping of Hai Tien Lo (海天楼) has crafted eight special reunion set menus, including a vegetarian option, to commemorate this Chinese New Year. From January 22nd to March 2nd, 2018, indulge in highlights like double-boiled fish maw with sea conch soup, bamboo pith, and Chinese cabbage, or savor the stewed classic whole abalone with sea cucumber in conpoy sauce.</description></item></channel></rss>