<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sugar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sugar/</link><description>Recent content in Sugar on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sugar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Australians are worried about the amount of sugar in fizzy drinks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</guid><description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s carbonated soft drink (CSD) market is experiencing ongoing challenges due to consumer worries about sugar content, as reported by Mintel, a global market intelligence firm.
Mintel predicts that the total sales volume of CSDs in Australia will likely decrease by 2.3% in 2017, following a 4.7% drop from 2014 to 2016.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research suggests that growing awareness of sugar&amp;rsquo;s negative effects has prompted many Australians to reevaluate their sugar consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A recent Euromonitor survey reveals sugar as a new culprit in the food industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has observed a growing global trend of consumers turning against sugar. This shift in attitude stems from heightened awareness of its health implications.
Consumers are actively trying to decrease or eliminate sugar from their diets, with a significant 42% actively looking for food labels indicating low or no added sugar, according to Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Global Consumer Trends Survey.
&amp;ldquo;Sugar is now widely perceived as a health risk, with some even equating it to tobacco in terms of toxicity,&amp;rdquo; says Gina Westbrook, Director of Strategy Briefings at Euromonitor International...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-recent-euromonitor-survey-reveals-sugar-as-a-new-culprit-in-the-food-industry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improving heart health with cranberry juice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</guid><description>Drinking cranberry juice every day could potentially lead to healthier blood sugar and cholesterol levels, according to recent research.
In a study involving overweight but otherwise healthy participants, those who drank two glasses (450ml) of a cranberry-based beverage daily for two weeks showed improvements in blood sugar stability, reducing spikes and dips often associated with cravings and fatigue. These benefits continued when the two-glass intake was maintained.
After eight weeks of daily consumption, the same cranberry beverage was also linked to higher levels of &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo; HDL cholesterol, known for promoting artery health by removing &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; cholesterol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improving-heart-health-with-cranberry-juice/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>