<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2015 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2015/</link><description>Recent content in 2015 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2015 Singapore Christmas Gift Guide: The Joyful Edition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:48:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2015-singapore-christmas-gift-guide-the-joyful-edition/</guid><description>The holiday season is here, and with it comes the need for corporate gift ideas. Fortunately, there are many options to choose from this year.
Source: Kaizer Leather website.
Kaizer Leather offers a variety of leather business gifts, ranging from handcrafted luggage to smaller leather accessories. One notable option is the Cavalry Business Bag (shown above), crafted from high-quality Italian calf leather and featuring a detachable, adjustable shoulder strap.
~ o ~</description></item><item><title>There will be an increase in cyberattacks in the Asia Pacific region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 04:40:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-will-be-an-increase-in-cyberattacks-in-the-asia-pacific-region-in-2015/</guid><description>A new cybersecurity report from Trend Micro predicts that criminals will increasingly target retail and financial institutions outside the United States in 2015.
The report, Trend Micro Security Predictions for 2015 and Beyond: The Invisible Becomes Visible, anticipates a rise in targeted attacks, specifically in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region. These attacks focus on infiltrating a specific organization to obtain valuable data.
High-profile attacks in the US and China demonstrate that cybercriminals favor these targeted attacks to gather intelligence, including financial data, personal information, classified government data, and intellectual property like blueprints.</description></item><item><title>I can travel with my laptop, Internet, and headset</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 19:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-can-travel-with-my-laptop-internet-and-headset/</guid><description>Jabra, a company that produces headsets, headphones, speakers, and speakerphones, predicts that working from anywhere at any time will be commonplace by 2015.
Mark Leigh, the President of Jabra Asia Pacific, states that currently, 35% of employees are mobile, and this number is projected to increase to 75% by 2017. He explains that the traditional office environment is being replaced by laptops, internet connections, and headsets, allowing employees to work from anywhere with internet access.</description></item><item><title>Bank Mandiri is seeking submissions for the Young Entrepreneur award 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-mandiri-is-seeking-submissions-for-the-young-entrepreneur-award-2015/</guid><description>Bank Mandiri, a prominent bank in Indonesia, launched its yearly competition called Mandiri Young Entrepreneur (WMM) in 2015.
Kartika Wirjoatmodjo, the Director of Finance &amp;amp; Strategy at Bank Mandiri, stated that this competition aims to discover young individuals with entrepreneurial potential who can contribute to Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s growth. Kartika added that the competition also intends to inspire a passion for entrepreneurship and innovation among students and graduates, encouraging more young entrepreneurs to emerge.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is invited to a new year countdown at Clarke Quay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 08:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-invited-to-a-new-year-countdown-at-clarke-quay/</guid><description>Source: Clarke Quay.
Clarke Quay invites everyone in Singapore to celebrate the end of the year with exciting festivities. Popular radio DJs Glenn Ong from Class95FM and Sonia Chew from 987FM will host the New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve countdown. The event will feature live music by the band Goodfellas, a vibrant street parade with a glow theme, and roving percussionists.
The entire event at Clarke Quay will be broadcasted live on 987FM.</description></item><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions.</description></item><item><title>Sofitel SO Bangkok announces the chef lineup for So Amazing Chefs 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sofitel-so-bangkok-announces-the-chef-lineup-for-so-amazing-chefs-2015/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel SO Bangkok. The Sofitel SO Bangkok has announced that 12 world-renowned chefs will be in Thailand for the 4th So Amazing Chefs event, happening from October 6th to 11th, 2015.
Yves Mudry, General Manager of Sofitel SO Bangkok shared, &amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s food festival is our most prestigious yet, featuring an incredible lineup of chefs with a combined seven Michelin stars. This event highlights Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s status as a culinary destination and fosters the exchange of culinary ideas and inspiration.</description></item><item><title>Hoi An has the highest number of top hotels according to TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 02:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hoi-an-has-the-highest-number-of-top-hotels-according-to-tripadvisor/</guid><description>Hanoi and Hoi An are home to Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s highest-rated hotels. In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized ten top hotels in Vietnam, with three located in Hanoi and three in Hoi An. An additional two hotels in the top 25 are also situated in Hoi An.
The top ten hotels are:
Source: TripAdvisor. The Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel.
Hanoi Elegance Diamond Hotel: Garnering 1,832 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; ratings out of 2,064 total reviews.</description></item><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>Experience a unique twist on French-inspired dining this holiday season at Sofitel So Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 23:17:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-a-unique-twist-on-french-inspired-dining-this-holiday-season-at-sofitel-so-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Sofitel So Singapore. Paulo.
At Sofitel So Singapore, Xperience restaurant&amp;rsquo;s head chef, Trevor Paulo, is celebrating his first Christmas season at the hotel with a special four-course Christmas Eve dinner.
The dinner starts with a small bite of blinis topped with dill yogurt and herring roe. The first course is a visually appealing dish of house-cured Salmon Gravlax arranged to look like a miniature garden with edible truffle &amp;ldquo;soil&amp;rdquo; and pickled shallots.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>Smaato emphasizes the importance of emerging markets in the mobile advertising industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smaato-emphasizes-the-importance-of-emerging-markets-in-the-mobile-advertising-industry/</guid><description>Source: Smaato.
Smaato, a platform that connects mobile publishers and app developers with advertisers in real-time, has published its Q3 2015 Global Trends in Mobile Programmatic Report. The report is based on data from billions of mobile ad impressions processed through Smaato&amp;rsquo;s exchange during that quarter. It reveals significant growth in the Asia Pacific region, particularly in Indonesia, where the market expanded by 84%. This highlights Indonesia as an emerging opportunity for both publishers and advertisers in the region.</description></item><item><title>The new executive board of the EU-ASEAN Business Council has been elected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 05:29:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-executive-board-of-the-eu-asean-business-council-has-been-elected/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (EU-ABC), the leading advocate for European companies in the ASEAN region, recently selected its Executive Board for the next two years. The election took place at their annual general meeting in Hanoi, Vietnam, on June 1st.
The new board members are:
François Guibert, Executive Vice-President, President, Greater China and South Asia Region, STMicroelectronics (Chairman) Donald Kanak, Chairman, Prudential Corporation Asia (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Theodoor Bakker, Partner, ABNR Law, Indonesia; Executive Board Member, European Chamber of Commerce, Indonesia (Chamber Representative &amp;amp; Vice Chairman) Martin Hayes, President, Robert Bosch SEA (MNC Representative &amp;amp; Treasurer), and Jan B.</description></item><item><title>EY identifies obstacles that are impeding the effectiveness of the AEC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ey-identifies-obstacles-that-are-impeding-the-effectiveness-of-the-aec/</guid><description>Political, legal, and organizational difficulties, regulatory burdens, and a lack of standardized trade regulations among ASEAN nations are hindering the progress of the 2007 ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) Blueprint. This plan aims to achieve regional economic integration by 2015, according to EY.
A recent EY report, &amp;ldquo;Trade Secrets: ASEAN economic community and inward investment,&amp;rdquo; examines the AEC&amp;rsquo;s development from a business standpoint, specifically focusing on obstacles to conducting business within ASEAN.</description></item><item><title>Business confidence in China continues to be weak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 18:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-confidence-in-china-continues-to-be-weak/</guid><description>While overall business confidence in China showed a slight improvement, activity declined in December as large companies continued to face weak demand and an uncertain business climate. According to MNI Indicators, a provider of economic data and analysis, businesses don&amp;rsquo;t anticipate significant improvement in early 2016. This is reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator, which remains close to the previous month&amp;rsquo;s low point.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator, a measure of current business sentiment, rose 5.</description></item><item><title>Canon Singapore will be hosting the Photo Marathon again in August 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-singapore-will-be-hosting-the-photo-marathon-again-in-august-2015/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM.
Canon Singapore has announced the details for their 13th annual Photo Marathon, taking place on August 22nd from 7 am to 8 pm at the Marina Bay Sands Expo and Convention Centre, Level 1, Hall C.
The competition revolves around three photography themes that are revealed on the day of the event. Participants are tasked with capturing these themes in their photographs and submitting them by the given deadline.</description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development.</description></item><item><title>ASEAN releases strategic plan for the development of small and medium enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asean-releases-strategic-plan-for-the-development-of-small-and-medium-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The ASEAN Strategic Action Plan for SME Development (SAPSMED) 2016-2025 acknowledges the significant role of micro, small, and medium-sized enterprises (MSMEs) in ASEAN&amp;rsquo;s economic growth, job creation, and women&amp;rsquo;s empowerment. The plan seeks to enhance MSME participation in an increasingly competitive market and support their expansion and progress.
This plan outlines an implementation roadmap utilizing country representatives, leveraging available resources, including those from ASEAN Dialogue Partners, and incorporating regular monitoring and evaluation.</description></item><item><title>Project management is expected to face challenges in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:35:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/project-management-is-expected-to-face-challenges-in-2015/</guid><description>ESI International, a company that provides project management training, believes that in the coming year, project managers (PMs) will experience several changes. These include dealing with combined in-person and remote work environments, needing stronger talent management skills, and aligning project results with company goals.
Raed Haddad, Managing Director for Asia Pacific at ESI International, noted that strategy and execution are often discussed separately. He anticipates a stronger emphasis on connecting these two aspects, as more companies start seeing strategic execution as a crucial skill.</description></item><item><title>Finding good people is still a challenge, according to ManpowerGroup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</guid><description>Source: ManpowerGroup infographic.
Around the world, the most difficult positions to fill are in skilled trades (particularly chefs, bakers, butchers, mechanics, and electricians), sales, engineering (mechanical, electrical, and civil), technician roles, and drivers (especially heavy vehicle operators), according to workforce experts ManpowerGroup.
The situation in Singapore is somewhat different. While engineers are among the top five hardest roles to fill, as elsewhere, the other four are accounting and finance professionals, sales representatives, secretaries (including receptionists and administrative assistants), and marketing, public relations, and communications specialists.</description></item><item><title>Hawksford has released the latest data on new business formations in Singapore for the fourth quarter of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 09:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hawksford-has-released-the-latest-data-on-new-business-formations-in-singapore-for-the-fourth-quarter-of-2015/</guid><description>Source: Hawksford report. Data represents the shareholder&amp;rsquo;s country of origin. Although the final quarter of 2015 saw a decrease in new Singaporean company formations compared to the previous quarter and the same period last year, international investors continue to set up companies and subsidiaries in Singapore, according to Hawksford, a provider of corporate, private client, and fund administration services.
Hawksford notes this decline is typical for the fourth quarter. Private limited companies made up the largest portion of new formations at 48.</description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget provides a significant boost to the commercial sector in various ways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</guid><description>In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Budget, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized exploring new ideas and diversity to help Hong Kong citizens achieve their goals.
He stated his commitment to utilizing resources generated by the community, supporting those in need, and promoting sustainable development to ensure that people from all sectors of society and future generations can benefit from economic growth.
The Budget outlines measures for the cultural and creative sector:
An extra HK$400 million will be allocated to the CreateSmart Initiative.</description></item><item><title>Dubai Islamic Bank has been included in LinkedIn's Most In-Demand Employers 2015 list for the MENA region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 10:33:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-islamic-bank-has-been-included-in-linkedin-s-most-in-demand-employers-2015-list-for-the-mena-region/</guid><description>Source: DIB.
Dubai Islamic Bank (DIB), the leading Islamic bank in the UAE, has been acknowledged by LinkedIn as one of the most desirable employers in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. DIB secured the 16th position on LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Most In-Demand Employers&amp;rdquo; 2015 list for the MENA region, placing it among the top 10 local brands and making it the only bank to achieve this distinction.
LinkedIn annually publishes a list of top employers globally based on extensive data gathered from billions of member interactions.</description></item><item><title>Bhaya Cruises has been awarded the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence for five consecutive years</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhaya-cruises-has-been-awarded-the-tripadvisor-certificate-of-excellence-for-five-consecutive-years/</guid><description>Source: Bhaya Cruises website.
The luxury cruise company Bhaya Cruises, which operates in Vietnam&amp;rsquo;s Halong Bay, has received TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Certificate of Excellence award for 2015. This recognition was given to three of their brands: Bhaya Classic, The Au Co, and Legend Halong. This marks the fifth year in a row that Bhaya Cruises has been acknowledged for its exceptional service.
The Certificate of Excellence is a prestigious award within the hospitality industry.</description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness.</description></item><item><title>SUVs are driving the sales of cars, according to Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:10:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/suvs-are-driving-the-sales-of-cars-according-to-euromonitor/</guid><description>According to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, worldwide light vehicle sales increased by 1.7% from 2014 to 2015. This growth was primarily fueled by the rising popularity of sports utility vehicles (SUVs), which saw a 22% surge in sales since 2015.
In 2015, SUVs became the leading automotive segment globally, surpassing lower medium cars and representing 22.9% of all light vehicle sales. SUV sales have significantly increased from 5 million units in 2000 to 20 million in 2015, with projections indicating a further rise to 42 million units by 2031.</description></item><item><title>GP Batteries has created a unique powerbank for the SEA Games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-batteries-has-created-a-unique-powerbank-for-the-sea-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 06:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gp-batteries-has-created-a-unique-powerbank-for-the-sea-games/</guid><description>Source: GP Batteries.
As the official battery partner for the SEA Games, GP Batteries has launched a limited-edition lithium-ion power bank to commemorate the upcoming games. This special power bank features a printed design of the 28th SEA Games Nila Logo and is officially recognized as an &amp;ldquo;Official Battery Partner&amp;rdquo; product.
This power bank boasts a 10,400mAH capacity, making it perfect for charging smartphones and tablets. With two output ports, users can charge two devices concurrently while LED indicators display the remaining battery life.</description></item><item><title>Come to Singapore Gifts Show 2015 for a wide selection of corporate gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</guid><description>The upcoming Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015 is the ideal event to discover this year&amp;rsquo;s corporate gift trends. Taking place from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, Halls 401 to 403, this international trade event offers free admission. It showcases innovative gifts, premiums, and lifestyle products and services, catering to trade buyers and corporate attendees.
Celebrating its 10th anniversary, SGS 2015 will host 160 booths featuring exhibitors from the Philippines, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Adyen predicts that smartphones will soon surpass tablets as the primary device for mobile payments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 22:09:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adyen-predicts-that-smartphones-will-soon-surpass-tablets-as-the-primary-device-for-mobile-payments/</guid><description>Source: Adyen. Click on the image to view a larger version.
Adyen, a global payments technology provider, recently released its quarterly Mobile Payments Index for Q3. This report analyzes mobile payment data from web-based transactions across Adyen&amp;rsquo;s customer base between July and September. Notably, the Index reveals that nearly half of online transactions using specific payment methods are now conducted on mobile devices.
The Index shows that 47% of payments made with JCB, a Japanese card, were completed on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>The 6th Directors' Conference of the Singapore Institute of Directors will prioritize innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-6th-directors-conference-of-the-singapore-institute-of-directors-will-prioritize-innovation/</guid><description>Source: SID brochure.
The critical importance of boards in driving innovation will be the central theme at the Singapore Institute of Directors (SID) sixth annual Directors&amp;rsquo; Conference. Taking place on September 16, 2015, at the Marina Bay Sands, Singapore, this yearly event is designed to cultivate leadership skills for Singaporean businesses and is anticipated to draw over 800 attendees.
Organized by SID, the conference will be inaugurated by guest-of-honor S Iswaran, Minister in the Prime Minister’s Office; Second Minister for Home Affairs; and Second Minister for Trade and Industry.</description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India.</description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Hilton Worldwide was ranked as the top company to work for in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 04:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-hilton-worldwide-was-ranked-as-the-top-company-to-work-for-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Hilton Worldwide has been recognized as the best employer in Greater China for 2015 by the Great Place to Work Institute, a global organization known for identifying and ranking exceptional workplaces. This accolade is based on a 2015 survey conducted by Great Place to Work, which gathered insights from 200,000 employees.
A total of 112 companies from Hong Kong, Mainland China, and Taiwan participated in the comprehensive assessment. This process involved evaluating the workplace environments of these companies by asking employees about their experiences and perceptions of company policies and management practices.</description></item><item><title>Kuwait is anticipated to experience slight growth in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kuwait-is-anticipated-to-experience-slight-growth-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: KFH Research website.
According to KFH Research, Kuwait&amp;rsquo;s economy is projected to experience stable growth in 2015. In their late December 2014 publication, &amp;ldquo;Kuwait Focus 2015: Positive Adjustments,&amp;rdquo; the firm predicts a 3.8% growth in real GDP for 2015, slightly lower than the estimated 4.1% for 2014.
This prediction aligns with the anticipated moderate GDP growth of 4.5% in the overall Gulf Cooperative Council region from 2014 to 2015.</description></item><item><title>The top 10 global consumer trends for 2015 focus on multitasking and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-global-consumer-trends-for-2015-focus-on-multitasking-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor.
Market research firm Euromonitor International recently published their findings on the top 10 global consumer trends for 2015.
Euromonitor&amp;rsquo;s Top 10 Global Consumer Trends 2015 report states that consumers, pressed for time, are seeking convenience, diverse options, global product availability, and instant satisfaction. They aim to get the most out of their time and money, looking for products and services that meet multiple needs. As an illustration, a Swedish taxi service provides in-car therapists for their stressed and busy clients at a rate of US$165 per hour.</description></item><item><title>Registration for delegates is now open for EmTech Singapore 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/registration-for-delegates-is-now-open-for-emtech-singapore-2015/</guid><description>The MIT Technology Review&amp;rsquo;s EmTech Singapore event focuses on the intersection of technology, business, and society. It showcases significant technologies and explores their potential to transform businesses and shape the global economy. Scheduled for January 27-28, 2015, at the Sands Expo and Convention Center, the event is now open for registration.
The main themes for EmTech Singapore 2015 are:
Digital Life
Discussions will cover the Internet of Things (IoT) as a revolutionary advancement, along with new computing platforms and eras.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring worldwide travel patterns with Euromonitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-worldwide-travel-patterns-with-euromonitor/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Euromonitor International, a market research provider, has published its annual World Travel Market Global Trends Report. This 2014 edition, like the previous nine, identifies emerging patterns in the travel industry.
For the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions, the report highlights these key trends:
The Middle East is using design tourism to reshape its image. By integrating design into tourist attractions and experiences, the region hopes to attract more visitors and creative professionals.</description></item><item><title>United has made changes to the MileagePlus rules</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/united-has-made-changes-to-the-mileageplus-rules/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 02:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/united-has-made-changes-to-the-mileageplus-rules/</guid><description>Starting March 1, 2015, United Airlines will transition its MileagePlus program to a revenue-based model. Instead of earning miles based on flight distance, members will earn miles based on ticket price and MileagePlus status.
[Image of the United Airlines logo]
The new system calculates earned miles using the base fare, carrier-imposed surcharges, and the member&amp;rsquo;s MileagePlus status. Standard members will earn five miles per dollar spent. MileagePlus Premier members will earn based on the following structure:</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Facebook highlighted the things that caught the world's interest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
Facebook recently unveiled its &amp;ldquo;Year in Review&amp;rdquo; for 2015, featuring a dedicated website and video.
The company highlighted major global conversations, with the US presidential election taking the lead. This was followed by discussions surrounding the November 13 Paris attacks, the Syrian civil war and resulting refugee crisis, the Nepal earthquakes, and the Greek debt crisis.
On the entertainment front, &amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo; reigned supreme as the most popular TV show, while &amp;ldquo;Star Wars: The Force Awakens&amp;rdquo; dominated movie discussions globally.</description></item><item><title>Get in shape for the beach at Kata Rocks in Phuket with New Year workouts in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 05:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-in-shape-for-the-beach-at-kata-rocks-in-phuket-with-new-year-workouts-in-2015/</guid><description>Kata Rocks, a luxurious and modern resort in Phuket, has introduced a New Year&amp;rsquo;s fitness program designed to help guests achieve their &amp;ldquo;beach body&amp;rdquo; goals.
The program, which costs THB10,000 (US$305) per day, takes place at one of Thailand&amp;rsquo;s most advanced fitness centers. It&amp;rsquo;s overseen by Callum McGregor, an accomplished personal trainer and former British special forces Commando. McGregor, who also boasts titles in strongman competitions and military powerlifting, specializes in strength training, fitness, weight loss, and toning.</description></item><item><title>Hong Kong offers a winter wonderland experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-offers-a-winter-wonderland-experience/</guid><description>Source: HKTB website.
With temperatures dipping below 15°C, December is an ideal time for a winter escape to Hong Kong. The ongoing 2015 Hong Kong WinterFest offers a variety of attractions and experiences for visitors.
A short walk from the Observation Wheel, where visitors can enjoy a 15-minute ride with panoramic views of Victoria Harbour and the Hong Kong skyline from luxurious gondolas, stands a dazzling, jewellery-inspired Serpenti light art installation in Statue Square, Central.</description></item><item><title>The intangible cultural heritage of North Korea includes the tradition of making kimchi and the rituals surrounding Arabic coffee</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-north-korea-includes-the-tradition-of-making-kimchi-and-the-rituals-surrounding-arabic-coffee/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 08:27:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-intangible-cultural-heritage-of-north-korea-includes-the-tradition-of-making-kimchi-and-the-rituals-surrounding-arabic-coffee/</guid><description>The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) committee dedicated to safeguarding intangible cultural heritage convened in Namibia and added 20 new elements to the prestigious Representative List of the Intangible Cultural Heritage of Humanity. This list showcases diverse forms of expression that embody intangible heritage and promotes broader awareness of their significance. Concluding this year&amp;rsquo;s nomination review, the committee inscribed 23 out of 35 proposed elements.
On December 2nd, the following entries from the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions were formally included on the list:</description></item><item><title>Guests staying at the Hyatt hotel can enjoy complimentary Wi-Fi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 09:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guests-staying-at-the-hyatt-hotel-can-enjoy-complimentary-wi-fi/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels Corporation is demonstrating its commitment to enhancing the guest experience by providing free Wi-Fi at all of its hotels globally starting in February 2015. This initiative aims to provide guests with convenient connectivity regardless of how they booked their stay or their loyalty program status.
Guests will have access to complimentary Wi-Fi on an unlimited number of devices, including laptops and mobile phones, in both guest rooms and common areas of Hyatt-branded hotels.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines has been ranked as the airline with the highest positive buzz in Singapore, according to YouGov</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-has-been-ranked-as-the-airline-with-the-highest-positive-buzz-in-singapore-according-to-yougov/</guid><description>Source: Yougov.
YouGov, a market research firm, has identified the leading brands in Singapore across various sectors based on their &amp;ldquo;buzz.&amp;rdquo; These rankings, reflecting average &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo; scores from January to December 2015, offer insights into brands that garnered the most positive attention from the general public.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of the top-ranking brands:
Ecommerce and mCommerce: Q0010 leads the pack, followed by Groupon and Carousell. Retail: Fashion: Uniqlo secures the top spot, with H&amp;amp;M and Robinsons trailing behind.</description></item><item><title>Brands that optimize their apps for mobile devices experience an increase in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brands-that-optimize-their-apps-for-mobile-devices-experience-an-increase-in-sales/</guid><description>Source: Criteo website, Q3 2015 State Of Mobile Commerce report
Criteo, a performance marketing technology company, has published its Q3 2015 State of Mobile Commerce report, providing marketers with valuable insights into consumer behavior and sales trends in the mobile commerce sector. The report, which analyzed 1.4 billion online transactions, found that half of all purchases globally now involve multiple devices.
Southeast Asia demonstrated a strong mobile commerce presence, with a 45% conversion rate on mobile devices, significantly increasing from 27% in the previous quarter.</description></item><item><title>In May 2015, Digi prepaid customers have the chance to win smartphones, tablets, and cars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-digi-prepaid-customers-have-the-chance-to-win-smartphones-tablets-and-cars/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Thrane.
Digi Telecommunication (Digi) is celebrating its 20th anniversary by giving back to its prepaid customers. Throughout May, Digi will be offering prizes like smartphones, tablets, and even cars.
From May 1st to May 31st, customers who top-up their prepaid credit are eligible to win prizes. Every day, 20 smartphones will be given away, with 200 tablets awarded weekly. Two lucky winners will even drive home a Ford Ranger.</description></item><item><title>Direct your attention to the ASEAN approach: Prime Minister of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 06:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/direct-your-attention-to-the-asean-approach-prime-minister-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
During his opening speech at the 27th ASEAN Summit and other related meetings in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysian Prime Minister Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Mohd Najib Tun Abdul Razak urged members to embrace the &amp;ldquo;ASEAN way.&amp;rdquo;
He emphasized the importance of prioritizing community and collaborative solutions over individual pursuits and self-serving goals. This approach, he stated, favors non-violent resolutions, moderation over extreme viewpoints, and respect for all, including adversaries. He stressed that true strength lies in pursuing peace and building bridges instead of fueling conflicts.</description></item><item><title>Strong job market in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>A new report by recruitment firm REED indicates that 78% of employees in Hong Kong received a pay raise in the last year. The report, titled REED 2015 Salary Survey and Market Insight, covers 14 countries across Asia, Australia, Europe, and the Middle East.
REED predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s thriving job market will continue to grow in 2015, driven by substantial foreign investments. The financial, digital marketing, e-commerce, and sales &amp;amp; marketing industries are expected to be particularly strong.</description></item><item><title>Take advantage of the week-long Vietjet promotion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-advantage-of-the-week-long-vietjet-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Vietjet website.
Vietjet Aviation Joint Stock Company (Vietjet), an airline with 32 domestic and international routes, is offering a limited-time promotion with 500,000 discounted tickets. This offer is valid for one week, ending on Wednesday, July 29th, 2015.
The promotion applies to all of Vietjet&amp;rsquo;s current domestic and international routes for travel between September 7th, 2015 and December 31st, 2015. Discounted fares will be displayed in a separate column during booking.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, ASEAN received the highest amount of foreign direct investment (FDI) among developing countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 17:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-asean-received-the-highest-amount-of-foreign-direct-investment-fdi-among-developing-countries/</guid><description>Source: ASEAN Secretariat.
The latest ASEAN Investment Report examines the growth of foreign direct investment (FDI) into the ASEAN region, particularly the influence of corporations on infrastructure expansion and regional integration.
In 2014, ASEAN emerged as the top recipient of FDI among developing nations. FDI inflows to the region experienced a third consecutive year of growth, reaching US$136.2 billion, a rise from US$117.7 billion in 2013. This achievement occurred despite a 16% global decline in FDI and inconsistent global economic progress.</description></item><item><title>Harbour City ranked as the most searched location on Google mobile in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 19:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/harbour-city-ranked-as-the-most-searched-location-on-google-mobile-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Harbour City.
Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s largest shopping center, Harbour City, earned the title of most popular mobile search for local destinations in Google&amp;rsquo;s 2015 Year in Search. Situated in Tsim Sha Tsui, a bustling tourist hub in Hong Kong, the mall also secured the sixth position on the list of trending mobile search keywords.
Encompassing over 2 million square feet, Harbour City offers a blend of shopping, dining, entertainment, and sightseeing opportunities.</description></item><item><title>The Fall/Winter 2015 Collections have been launched by CH Carolina Herrera</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fall-winter-2015-collections-have-been-launched-by-ch-carolina-herrera/</guid><description>CH, a subsidiary brand under the Carolina Herrera fashion house, has launched their Fall/Winter 2015 collections for both men and women. The Women’s Collection uses vibrant pops of color like reds, sky blues, and fuchsias, which stand out against a darker color scheme with white and ivory accents.
Formal evening wear is designed using luxurious fabrics like silks, lace, and jacquard. The feminine looks are completed with signature CH Carolina Herrera details like bows and ruffles.</description></item><item><title>The top five consumer trends for 2015 according to Canadean</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 08:33:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-five-consumer-trends-for-2015-according-to-canadean/</guid><description>In 2015, market research company Canadean predicts five key trends will shape consumer behavior in the fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) industry:
From Mass Production to Personalization
Canadean anticipates a growing consumer preference for artisanal and handcrafted products. Consumers are seeking out products made on a smaller scale, believing this signifies higher quality and a stronger connection to the brand. Brands can capitalize on this trend by highlighting a product&amp;rsquo;s exclusivity and the care taken in its creation, appealing to consumers moving away from mass-produced FMCG items.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai Food Festival guarantees a February full of foodie fun</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 21:55:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-food-festival-guarantees-a-february-full-of-foodie-fun/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Food Festival website.
The second Dubai Food Festival (DFF) will showcase celebrity chefs and new events in addition to popular experiences from the previous year, according to the Dubai Festivals and Retails Establishment (DFRE), a branch of Dubai Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
New additions include Dubai Food &amp;amp; Film, the first foodie film event in the area, and Fatafeat Kitchen, a new program for 2015 and a first in the Middle East, featuring nine consecutive celebrity chef cooking events.</description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt provides insights on Malaysia's perspective in the Total Compensation Measurement study</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-provides-insights-on-malaysia-s-perspective-in-the-total-compensation-measurement-study/</guid><description>Aon Hewitt, a global human resource consulting firm, has published their Total Compensation Measurement (TCM) 2015 Study. This comprehensive report analyzes compensation data from 25,000 positions in 180 countries.
Salary increase by industry sector in Malaysia
While the global GDP is projected to grow from 3.1% in 2015 to 3.6% in 2016, regional economic conditions play a vital role in employee compensation decisions. In Southeast Asia, the Philippines and Vietnam led in 2015 with 6% and 6.</description></item><item><title>Lateefa AlWaalan has been awarded the title of Saudi Arabia's EY Entrepreneur Of The Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:20:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lateefa-alwaalan-has-been-awarded-the-title-of-saudi-arabia-s-ey-entrepreneur-of-the-year/</guid><description>Lateefa AlWaalan, the driving force behind the Arabic coffee startup Yatooq, has been crowned Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s EY Entrepreneur Of The Year (EOY) for 2015.
A panel of independent judges selected AlWaalan from a pool of eleven finalists representing ten different companies. Her entrepreneurial spirit, robust financial performance, strategic thinking, and positive social impact distinguished her as a leader. Fahad Altoaimi, EY&amp;rsquo;s Office Managing Partner in Riyadh and the Entrepreneur Of The Year Leader, emphasized that this award recognizes AlWaalan&amp;rsquo;s significant business accomplishments, innovative spirit, and contributions to her community.</description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes.</description></item><item><title>Langkawi hotels are prominently featured in the top 10 Travelers' Choice awards on TripAdvisor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 05:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/langkawi-hotels-are-prominently-featured-in-the-top-10-travelers-choice-awards-on-tripadvisor/</guid><description>In 2015, TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards recognized four Langkawi hotels in their top 10 for Malaysia. Additionally, Shangri-La properties secured two spots within the top 10, with a third ranking 11th.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Danna Langkawi Malaysia.
Here are the top 10 hotels:
The Danna Langkawi Malaysia, Pantai Kok, holds a 5 out of 5 rating from 1,777 reviews. It received an &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; rating from 1,508 reviewers, and &amp;ldquo;very good&amp;rdquo; from 203 reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Aon Hewitt reveals top employers for Singapore and the region in 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 04:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-reveals-top-employers-for-singapore-and-the-region-in-2015/</guid><description>Source: Best Employers website.
Aon Hewitt, a global human resources solutions firm, unveiled its list of top employers in Singapore for 2015 on February 27th. Launched in Asia in 2001, Aon Hewitt’s Best Employers study is currently the most thorough of its kind in the Asia Pacific region. Recognition as an Aon Hewitt Best Employer signifies that a company:
1. Cultivates strong employee commitment and top-tier performance;
2. Achieves strong business results through effective human resources strategies; and, 3.</description></item><item><title>The focus in the Philippines is on its beautiful beaches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-in-the-philippines-is-on-its-beautiful-beaches/</guid><description>Source: TripAdvisor website. The Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete.
TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s Travelers&amp;rsquo; Choice Awards for accommodations in the Philippines in 2015 were distributed relatively evenly between hotels located in Manila and seaside resorts. The top ten awardees are as follows:
Atlantis Dive Resorts Dumaguete in Dauin, Philippines, received 189 out of 235 &amp;ldquo;excellent&amp;rdquo; reviews. Amanpulo, Palawan Island El Nido Resorts Pangulasian Island Fairmont Makati, Manila Shangri-La&amp;rsquo;s Boracay Resort &amp;amp; Spa Raffles Makati Makati Shangri-La Manila Huma Island Resort and Spa, Coron, Palawan Island Radisson Blu Cebu Manila Marriott Hotel, Pasay View the TripAdvisor Top 25 hotels for the Philippines: http://www.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines is the top-ranked brand in terms of recognition in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 02:01:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-is-the-top-ranked-brand-in-terms-of-recognition-in-singapore/</guid><description>YouGov, a polling and research company, has released its mid-year rankings of the best brands in Singapore for 2015. Singapore Airlines secured the top spot, while Apple appeared twice on the list. Technology brands dominated the top 10, with WhatsApp, e-marketplace Qoo10, Facebook, and Google all making appearances.
Source: YouGov.
YouGov&amp;rsquo;s BrandIndex is a daily metric of public brand perception that monitors numerous brands across various sectors. The company compiles its data every six months and publishes the Best Brand Rankings globally.</description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Join Jane's Walk for free guided tours around Singapore from May 1 to 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:42:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/join-jane-s-walk-for-free-guided-tours-around-singapore-from-may-1-to-3/</guid><description>Source: Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk website.
Gather your coworkers and spend the first weekend of May discovering Singapore with Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk, a worldwide initiative of free walking tours led by locals and inspired by Jane Jacobs. The walks encourage people to share their community stories, explore their cities, and connect with their neighbors.
&amp;ldquo;Jane Jacobs, an advocate for walkability, vibrant communities, and citizen involvement in urban development, would be proud! She believed understanding a city requires observation, inquiry, and exploration, and we&amp;rsquo;re excited to do just that during the weekend of May 1-3,&amp;rdquo; stated Mai Tatoy, Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk City Organizer in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Come to Vivid Sydney and immerse yourself in the biggest festival of light, music, and ideas in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</guid><description>Source: Vivid Sydney/Destination NSW.
Vivid Sydney, a global festival celebrating light, music, and ideas, will illuminate Sydney until June 8th. Last year, the festival drew in 1.43 million attendees.
Stuart Ayres, the NSW Minister for Trade, Tourism and Major Events, highlighted the festival&amp;rsquo;s ability to transform Sydney for 18 days and nights with creativity and vibrant light displays. He emphasized it as a must-see event for showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s pride.</description></item><item><title>The AirAsia Foundation is investigating the concept of social enterprise</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 13:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-airasia-foundation-is-investigating-the-concept-of-social-enterprise/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia Foundation website.
The AirAsia Foundation is hosting a conference and marketplace focused on social enterprise on November 7th at Nexus Bangsar South in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. This event, Destination: Good – ASEAN Social Enterprise 2015, is the first public event organized by the AirAsia Foundation, the philanthropic branch of the AirAsia Group. Its goal is to initiate a discussion on the role large companies and social enterprises can play in fostering fair, sustainable, and inclusive economies.</description></item><item><title>The top 10 workplaces in Singapore have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 08:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>A recent study by the research and consulting firm Great Place to Work Institute Singapore reveals a strong connection between high levels of trust and engagement among employees and a high-performing work environment.
In addition to the new report, Singapore Insights 2015, Great Place to Work Institute Singapore has unveiled its first-ever 10 Best Companies to Work For in Singapore List. Salesforce, the cloud computing giant, claims the top spot.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Wuhan and Changsha were recognized as the top sustainable cities in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 22:18:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-wuhan-and-changsha-were-recognized-as-the-top-sustainable-cities-in-china/</guid><description>The 2015 China Sustainable Cities Report: Measuring Ecological and Human Development reveals that 35 Chinese cities have shown progress in their sustainability performance since 2014, as indicated by their scores on the Urban Ecological Input Index (EUII). This report, which assesses the progress of Chinese cities towards sustainable development, was presented in Beijing at the 2015 International Forum on Sustainable Cities in China.
A collaboration between the United Nations Development Programme (UNDP), Xinhua Oriental Outlook Weekly, and a team of experts from Tongji University, this report marks the first of its kind in China since the UN&amp;rsquo;s 193 member states adopted the 17 Sustainable Development Goals in September 2015.</description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin.</description></item><item><title>Canon Middle East introduces new cameras for 2015, challenging the competition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 22:24:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/canon-middle-east-introduces-new-cameras-for-2015-challenging-the-competition/</guid><description>Canon Middle East&amp;rsquo;s 2015 camera lineup boasts the high quality and advanced technology expected from the brand, with the added convenience of single-tap sharing via NFC and Wi-Fi.
The compact PowerShot series includes the SX530 HS, featuring a 50x zoom lens, and the SX410 IS, equipped with a 40x optical zoom.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at the PowerShot SX530 HS:
50x zoom Wi-Fi with NFC Full HD video recording Creative modes and manual controls The PowerShot SX410 IS offers these notable features:</description></item><item><title>India will be implementing GST and has announced additional training and business initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Shri Arun Jaitley, announced in his Budget speech that a comprehensive goods and services tax (GST) system will be implemented by April 1, 2016. Additionally, corporate tax rates are expected to be reduced from 30% to 25% gradually over the next four years. These proposals were presented alongside initiatives aimed at enhancing human resource capabilities and fostering innovation nationwide.
Training and Development The Finance Minister stressed the importance of structured skills training, revealing the government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce a National Skills Mission.</description></item></channel></rss>