<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Increase Bandwidth Without Increasing Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:29:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-bandwidth-without-increasing-costs/</guid><description>Companies need more bandwidth, especially for their wide area networks (WANs), but it can be very expensive. While high speeds are affordable within a company&amp;rsquo;s LAN, connecting to the outside world traditionally comes with much higher costs.
This is because WAN connections were typically provided by telecom companies using technology initially meant for phone services. While more modern providers have entered the market with updated infrastructure, even traditional providers are adapting to the demand for data services.</description></item><item><title>Copper WAN Bandwidth Headed to 500 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 05:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-wan-bandwidth-headed-to-500-mbps/</guid><description>Ericsson has developed a new technology that could significantly boost data transmission speeds over existing copper wire infrastructure. This innovation allows for WAN connections over copper, achieving speeds up to 500 Mbps.
While Gigabit Ethernet is achievable with Cat-6 wiring for LAN connections, this technology focuses on connecting businesses to broadband providers using existing copper infrastructure. This is significant because many businesses require increased bandwidth for various purposes, including server farms, internet access, data transfer between locations, and the growing need for electronic medical record transfers.</description></item><item><title>Your Point to Point Ethernet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-point-to-point-ethernet-connection/</guid><description>Businesses with multiple locations often need to share data, traditionally relying on T1 lines for connectivity. While multiple T1 lines can increase bandwidth, this approach might not be the most cost-effective solution, especially in metropolitan areas.
Point-to-point Ethernet offers a compelling alternative, often at a lower cost per Mbps, particularly for higher bandwidth needs. Ethernet streamlines data transmission by maintaining its format throughout the network, potentially allowing locations to function as a single bridged LAN.</description></item><item><title>Do You Need a Content Delivery Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-content-delivery-network/</guid><description>The way we deliver content online is evolving rapidly. While you could once manage a website with just a computer and a few phone lines, today&amp;rsquo;s high-definition video and nationwide audiences demand far more resources. This is where content delivery networks (CDNs) come in.
Think of a CDN as a specialized web hosting service. Just as you can host your website on your own server or outsource it, you can also choose between managing your content distribution or relying on a CDN.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Gigabit Ethernet Network Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-gigabit-ethernet-network-connection/</guid><description>The demand for high-capacity internet connections has caught some businesses off guard. What started as a T1 line evolved into a DS3 connection and maybe even an OC3 fiber optic service, but there always seems to be a bottleneck. It might be time to upgrade to Gigabit Ethernet (GigE).
It&amp;rsquo;s important to understand that those older telecom services you&amp;rsquo;ve been using are based on telephone technology. While they&amp;rsquo;re dependable, they weren&amp;rsquo;t designed for today&amp;rsquo;s network needs.</description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth for Cloud and On-Premises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:41:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-cloud-and-on-premises/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-performance Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is necessary for connectivity, regardless of whether your data center is on-premises or cloud-based. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available choices.
On-Premises Infrastructure
A significant advantage of managing your servers and data center equipment in-house is having control over the on-site network. Your Local Area Network (LAN) likely operates at a minimum speed of 100 to 1000 Mbps. Within the data center, connections might have even higher speeds to facilitate short-distance connections between storage, processing, security devices, and other components.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing and WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-and-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud computing in IT services has led to a rush towards all things cloud-related. However, the crucial role of WAN bandwidth in accessing the cloud often gets overlooked.
WAN, or Wide Area Network, typically refers to any connection outside of an office or corporate campus. While connections within a city might utilize a MAN (Metropolitan Area Network) limited to a smaller area, reaching distant locations or networks necessitates WAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>DS3 Over Copper Avoids Fiber Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-over-copper-avoids-fiber-installation/</guid><description>Businesses desire fiber optic connections for their high bandwidth capabilities, but the installation costs can be prohibitive, ranging from tens of thousands to even hundreds of thousands of dollars. However, there&amp;rsquo;s an alternative solution worth considering: DS3 over Copper.
Although DS3 is often associated with fiber optic lines, it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a 45 Mbps TDM protocol that can operate on various carriers. Originally, DS3 was delivered using T3 coaxial copper lines, waveguides, or microwave transmissions.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 14:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business moves online and companies shift their IT to the cloud, the demand for WAN bandwidth continues to rise. These days, even small businesses frequently require reliable dedicated internet and inter-office network bandwidth in the range of 100 Mbps to 1 Gbps. Larger companies, particularly those dealing with tech-heavy products, services, or medical imaging, can easily saturate Gigabit connections, making a transition to 10 Gigabit Ethernet WAN a worthwhile consideration.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Ethernet WAN Bandwidth Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 11:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-ethernet-wan-bandwidth-advantages/</guid><description>Larger companies often need more internet bandwidth than what&amp;rsquo;s typically offered through standard copper wire connections. While fiber optic cables provide a solution with almost limitless bandwidth, finding a cost-effective option is key.
Businesses already utilizing fiber optic bandwidth might be leasing older SONET/SDH services like OC3, OC12, or OC48 for their wide area network needs. These traditional telecom services, originally designed for high-volume phone calls, have been adapted to handle today&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-bandwidth data connections.</description></item><item><title>Getting Cavalier About Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 18:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/getting-cavalier-about-ethernet/</guid><description>Is ignoring Ethernet an option for your business&amp;rsquo;s connection to the world? Can you afford to miss out on its benefits?
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about Cavalier Telephone, a competitive telecom provider, whose Ethernet services are now available on the GeoQuote (tm) search tool within our Shop for Ethernet service. While their name might imply a casual approach, Cavalier is serious about providing the bandwidth your growing business requires.
Cavalier Telephone is a regional Competitive Local Exchange Carrier (CLEC) serving 15 states in the Eastern and Southern US, including Washington D.</description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points.</description></item><item><title>The Gift of Bandwidth For Administrative Professionals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gift-of-bandwidth-for-administrative-professionals/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s Administrative Professionals Week, a time to show appreciation for those essential staff members who keep everything running smoothly. While thoughtful gestures like cards and lunches are always appreciated, let&amp;rsquo;s not forget about the practical tools that can truly empower administrative professionals to excel in their roles.
Beyond personal recognition, what administrative professionals truly benefit from are improved tools that enhance their productivity. These individuals are often models of efficiency, making the most of available resources.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly.</description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability.</description></item><item><title>A Graphical Introduction to Big Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 20:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-graphical-introduction-to-big-data/</guid><description>Confused about the hype surrounding Big Data? This infographic might help clear things up&amp;hellip;
Feeling limited by your current internet connection when dealing with large amounts of data, cloud services, backups, or file transfers? Upgrading might be more affordable than you expect. Get immediate pricing on cost-effective copper and fiber internet options for your business.
Credit to Wikibon Infographics for this infographic on Big Data.</description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Makes Big Push For 100 Gigabit Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 23:06:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-makes-big-push-for-100-gigabit-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Not long ago, the idea of businesses and government agencies needing 100 Gbps WAN bandwidth seemed outlandish. Providers primarily used 10 Gbps networks, occasionally upgrading to 40 Gbps to accommodate high traffic from multiple customers. Today, those same customers seek 40 Gbps and even 100 Gbps connectivity options from their providers.
The driving force behind this surge in bandwidth demand is &amp;ldquo;Big Data.&amp;rdquo; Big Data presents significant potential for enhancing business operations and data analysis, but it demands substantial processing power, storage capacity, and bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Broadband Available In A Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-broadband-available-in-a-day/</guid><description>Imagine this: your new store is ready to open, everything is in place, but you can&amp;rsquo;t start selling because your internet service isn&amp;rsquo;t working. This is where Accel Networks comes in, offering a wireless solution that can get you online in just a few days.
Why choose Accel Networks? Traditional broadband often involves time-consuming installations. Accel Networks bypasses this by using existing cell tower infrastructure. Their service is secure, meets payment industry standards, and covers most of the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.</description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Connections from USA to Paris, France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:48:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-connections-from-usa-to-paris-france/</guid><description>Many businesses operate globally, importing/exporting or managing offices and factories across continents. Maintaining seamless connectivity between their US locations and international branches is crucial, especially requiring the right kind of connection.
While Direct Internet Access (DIA) suffices for smaller companies needing basic internet functions, larger corporations might need to connect their local area networks (LANs) across locations to function as one entity. Others may require low latency connections to support real-time applications like video conferencing and financial trading.</description></item><item><title>Is 10 Gbps Internet the New Business Standard?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 13:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-10-gbps-internet-the-new-business-standard/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Since broadband&amp;rsquo;s debut over 20 years ago, internet speeds have steadily increased. However, just when you think your bandwidth is sufficient, websites and cloud applications become sluggish, impacting productivity and necessitating an upgrade. The good news is that upgrading your internet service is no longer a daunting task if done correctly.
The Demand for High Bandwidth
The need for increased bandwidth is primarily driven by data-intensive applications. While the early internet was mostly text-based, the evolution to images, databases, and especially video streaming significantly increased bandwidth consumption.</description></item><item><title>The How and Why of 10 Gbps WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 03:33:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-how-and-why-of-10-gbps-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The volume of data continues to expand. HD video is on the verge of being replaced by 4K and eventually 8K video. As applications transition to the cloud, IT data centers are progressively shutting down. The question arises: where will the bandwidth originate to accommodate the increasing bit rates required in the MAN and WAN?
This bandwidth is being supplied by fiber optic carriers who understand that every organization must increase its data capacity to remain competitive.</description></item><item><title>Managed Security Moves To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud services are expanding beyond the familiar Infrastructure, Platform, and Software as a Service to include Security as a Service. Integra, for example, now offers a suite of Cloud Security Services, including a Cloud Firewall Service.
Many companies find managed security appealing because it removes the need for dedicated IT staff or investments in security hardware. Traditionally, this involved a monthly service fee and an on-premises security device. Cloud-based security takes it further, eliminating the need for physical hardware altogether.</description></item><item><title>What Type of Data Center Connectivity Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-type-of-data-center-connectivity-do-you-need/</guid><description>When thinking about moving to a colocation center or building a data center or private cloud off-site, you&amp;rsquo;ll face both opportunities and difficulties in setting up your network connections. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the key factors and uncover potential cost-saving opportunities.
The main difference between on-site and remote data centers, including colocation facilities, lies in how you manage network connections. On-site, you have full control over your local wiring. Off-site, you lease connections through service providers.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Connection Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:24:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-connection-services/</guid><description>For extremely high WAN bandwidth requirements, Gigabit connections are the solution. While this level of bandwidth is available, access is limited to areas with existing fiber optic infrastructure, typically major metropolitan areas near carrier Points of Presence (POPs). In such locations, even medium-sized businesses may find 1,000 Mbps connectivity affordable.
So, who needs Gigabit bandwidth? Telecom providers with nationwide fiber optic networks, for one. Their customers, including large medical centers, video production companies, Software as a Service providers, data centers, research organizations, large engineering firms, and Cable MSOs, drive the demand.</description></item><item><title>XO Communications Ups the Ante on Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xo-communications-ups-the-ante-on-ethernet/</guid><description>A major telecommunications provider is expanding its Metro Ethernet services, offering businesses more options for high-bandwidth connectivity. This provider leverages its vast fiber optic network, numerous points of presence, and advanced Ethernet over Copper technology to make Ethernet an even more attractive option for Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.
Why is Ethernet so important? It&amp;rsquo;s essentially a natural progression for network technology that businesses of all sizes already rely on. This means Metro Ethernet provides a nearly effortless solution for connecting various locations, effectively unifying them under a single network.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Multiplication to the Rescue</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-multiplication-to-the-rescue/</guid><description>Service providers are facing a challenge with the increasing demand for bandwidth, particularly with the rise of video streaming. Just when they thought their network capacity was sufficient, applications like video streaming emerged, consuming enormous amounts of bandwidth. To address this, providers like Comcast are partnering with companies like Cisco to enhance their existing infrastructure.
Comcast and Cisco are testing a system that uses Dense Wavelength Division Multiplexing (DWDM) to boost capacity on Comcast&amp;rsquo;s existing fiber optic network between Philadelphia and McLean, Virginia.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Beefs Up Last Mile Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:38:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-beefs-up-last-mile-access/</guid><description>The main obstacle for companies aiming to boost their WAN (Wide Area Network) bandwidth is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; access problem. Although network bandwidth has become more affordable and easier to access, the final connection between a business and the carrier&amp;rsquo;s network often poses a significant challenge.
Think of it this way: a superhighway might be close to your company, but if the only route to your facility is a rough, narrow road, transportation will be slow and limited.</description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate.</description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables.</description></item><item><title>10 Gigabit Ethernet For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 07:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gigabit-ethernet-for-business/</guid><description>Is Gigabit Bandwidth Enough? Maybe Not Anymore. Think Gigabit internet is enough for your business? Think again. The huge growth in video content and cloud computing is changing everything we thought we knew about internet needs. Today, 10 GigE connections are becoming the new normal.
Just a few years ago, 10 Gigabit bandwidth was reserved for the core of network infrastructure. Now we&amp;rsquo;re talking about 100 Gbps and even 40 Gbps is getting left behind.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Service Providers Offer Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 11:29:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-service-providers-offer-cost-savings/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is happening with the change from circuit-switched to packet-switched WAN protocols, noticeable when businesses seek bandwidth upgrades. Instead of familiar T1 lines, they&amp;rsquo;re encountering Ethernet over Copper. This shift is fueled by the telecom industry&amp;rsquo;s move towards all-IP networks. Devices like computers, servers, and smartphones generate traffic surpassing traditional telephony, pushing the need to connect LANs and access the internet.
Traditional telephone technologies like T-Carrier and SONET are being replaced with a more unified approach.</description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area.</description></item><item><title>You Mean There's Ethernet in My Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-mean-theres-ethernet-in-my-building/</guid><description>Frustrated with your business broadband and ready to take drastic measures? Before you do, let&amp;rsquo;s explore reliable and affordable dedicated Internet options.
The issue likely isn&amp;rsquo;t your internal network; it&amp;rsquo;s the unreliable connection to the broader Internet. While the Internet itself is robust, your chosen connection method might be the problem.
DSL or Cable Modem services, while offering substantial bandwidth at low costs for residential users, often lack guaranteed bandwidth allocation.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Internet Access Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 02:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-internet-access-via-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses of all sizes now have near-universal access to broadband internet. However, are you utilizing the optimal internet connection for your needs? It might be time to consider Ethernet.
Metro Ethernet Networks are rapidly expanding and provide significant benefits to businesses. Cost savings are a key advantage, potentially cutting your internet bandwidth expenses by half or more compared to your current solution. This significant cost reduction comes without compromising reliability or dedicated bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>GigE Ethernet Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-ethernet-private-lines/</guid><description>SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) services have been the traditional choice for high bandwidth fiber optic connections. However, GigE (Gigabit Ethernet) has emerged as a strong competitor, offering high bandwidth, low latency, and cost advantages.
GigE MAN and WAN services provide bandwidth comparable to many company LANs, ensuring seamless connections between business locations and the internet. While cost was once a limiting factor for high-speed data transfer beyond the LAN, GigE&amp;rsquo;s affordability now makes it feasible to have WAN bandwidth matching LAN bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines, a technology dating back to the telegraph, have evolved to offer businesses speeds ranging from 1.5 Mbps to 100 Gbps. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the characteristics of leased lines and how they stand apart from conventional broadband.
What is a Leased Line?
Similar to leasing a property, leased lines involve an agreement and regular payments that grant you exclusive access to a dedicated communication line.
In its simplest form, a leased line consists of a pair of copper wires, linking your location to your provider, often through a local telephone company (ILEC).</description></item><item><title>Ethernet From Coast To Coast</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-from-coast-to-coast/</guid><description>Imagine your current office Ethernet network expanding beyond the building, connecting your locations across the city and the country. This vision of a unified, nationwide network is now a reality with Carrier Ethernet.
Carrier Ethernet is essentially the same Ethernet used in local networks, but enhanced and standardized for use in metropolitan and long-distance networks.
To get Carrier Ethernet, businesses need to partner with a network provider offering this service. These providers typically have built extensive, nationwide fiber optic networks with service points in major cities.</description></item><item><title>From Megabit Copper to Gigabit Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 09:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/from-megabit-copper-to-gigabit-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that upgrading your WAN bandwidth is necessary due to two significant factors. Firstly, network traffic is consistently growing. Secondly, traditional copper-based services are being phased out by providers. This makes it an opportune time to transition to gigabit fiber.
Reasons to Upgrade
The IT landscape has transformed significantly. In the past, computing resources were mainly on-site, requiring minimal external connections. However, the paradigm has shifted. Now, most computing relies on cloud-based resources, demanding extensive connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Services to 400 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:06:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-services-to-400-gbps/</guid><description>Bandwidth requirements are clearly increasing. Small companies are upgrading from 1.5 Mbps T1 lines to 10 Mbps Ethernet over Copper, while medium-sized companies are moving towards 50 or 100 Mbps connections. Large companies are continuously seeking even faster Gigabit connections.
While bandwidth typically peaks at 5 or 10 Gbps, some providers offer up to 40 Gbps as they transition to 100 Gbps. However, one provider is setting a new standard with 400 Gbps availability.</description></item><item><title>Transparent LAN Service for WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transparent-lan-service-for-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>With the increasing trend of businesses expanding beyond a single location, the demand for reliable wide-area connectivity is on the rise. This is particularly relevant for companies with branches across the country and medical facilities spread over large regions. While traditional telecommunications services have connected multiple locations, newer solutions now allow your local area network (LAN) to cover an entire metropolitan area or even span multiple states.
One such solution is known as transparent LAN service, which effectively combines multiple separate LANs into a single, unified network.</description></item><item><title>T1 Bonding Buys Breathing Room</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-bonding-buys-breathing-room/</guid><description>Businesses often face the challenge of needing more resources, like network bandwidth, without the budget to acquire them. This is particularly true for WAN bandwidth. Companies often start with a modest plan, assuming they can upgrade when demand (and revenue) increase. However, in times of economic uncertainty, business activity might grow while revenue lags. So how can businesses meet their needs without overspending?
One solution is incrementalism, specifically &amp;ldquo;just in time&amp;rdquo; incrementalism.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations.</description></item><item><title>Your 50 Mbps WAN Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-50-mbps-wan-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The need for 50 Mbps bandwidth has increased due to businesses needing to use cloud services, access remote data centers, transfer large data files, run e-commerce platforms, send high-resolution images, and distribute video content. There are various ways to get 50 Mbps bandwidth connectivity, each with its own benefits and drawbacks.
DS3 &amp;amp; T3
DS3, or T3, is a traditional telecom service designed for transmitting many calls simultaneously between switching centers.</description></item></channel></rss>