<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Video Games on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-games/</link><description>Recent content in Video Games on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:25:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/video-games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recycle Video Games and Gaming Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/</guid><description>Think about all the video games and gaming systems you have in your home, even the ones tucked away. You probably have quite a collection!
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to turn those unused games and consoles into cash? Instead of letting them gather dust, you could use the money to buy whatever you want, including the newest games and systems.
Selling your old gaming stuff can be a hassle, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recycle-video-games-and-gaming-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cash In Old Gadgets To Buy New Gadgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 03:39:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</guid><description>The holiday shopping season is here, and with it comes the temptation of new electronics and gadgets. However, it&amp;rsquo;s also a time to be mindful of spending. One smart solution is to turn your old electronics into cash to fund those new purchases.
It&amp;rsquo;s common to have unused electronics lying around. We hesitate to discard them because they still hold value. This unused tech represents a potential savings account that can help you afford those tempting new gadgets...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cash-in-old-gadgets-to-buy-new-gadgets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is That A Game Or A Netbook?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 18:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</guid><description>For years, the distinction between computers and video games has been blurry. This is because modern gaming consoles are essentially powerful computers that run games as applications. So it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that Nintendo&amp;rsquo;s latest handheld gaming system, the DSi, boasts netbook-like features such as secure WiFi connectivity, a web browser, and expandable memory.
Let&amp;rsquo;s be clear: the Nintendo DSi is designed for gamers. It&amp;rsquo;s a handheld console, powered by a battery, and runs Nintendo DS game cartridges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-that-a-game-or-a-netbook/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Fun and Games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 05:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/</guid><description>Need a break from work? How about a quick game of Guitar Hero? Right on your BlackBerry! You don&amp;rsquo;t need your console for this. Choose your favorite guitar, character, and venue, and start rocking!
Yeah, you read that right – Guitar Hero on your BlackBerry. Not exactly ideal for a serious meeting, but perfect for when you&amp;rsquo;re off the clock. It&amp;rsquo;s your phone, customize it with whatever helps you unwind!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-fun-and-games/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>