<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IPTV on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iptv/</link><description>Recent content in IPTV on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/iptv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will Video Kill The Internet Star?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-video-kill-the-internet-star/</guid><description>The considerable growth of online video streaming and downloads has positioned them as the primary bandwidth consumers on the internet today. This begs the question: will the rapid proliferation of video packets lead to internet congestion, similar to traffic jams on physical highways?
Video content follows the same trajectory as previous &amp;ldquo;killer apps&amp;rdquo; such as email, web browsing, instant messaging, blogging, and social networking. These applications all began with a small user base, expanded quickly, and eventually became mainstream.</description></item><item><title>1.5 and 3.0 Gbps Uncompressed HD Video Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</guid><description>Analog television with its standard-definition video signals is a thing of the past. While older 4:3 aspect ratio televisions still exist, they are sustained by cable and satellite receivers. However, high-definition (HD) channels are becoming more prevalent, and standard-definition channels are being phased out as viewers switch to flat-screen HD TVs. The future of television is internet protocol television (IPTV) in high definition, with 3D technology on the horizon.
For broadcasters, distributors, and content providers, traditional video transport methods are no longer adequate.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Speeds Come to Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-speeds-come-to-cable/</guid><description>Cablevision Systems Corp. is pushing the boundaries of broadband speed by offering internet speeds exceeding 100 Mbps over its existing cable TV infrastructure. This new high-speed internet service, launching on May 11th, provides download speeds up to 101 Mbps and upload speeds up to 15 Mbps for approximately $100 per month.
One might wonder how cable TV lines, which traditionally use coaxial cables, can achieve such high speeds, usually associated with fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>Why Content Delivery Networks Need More Capacity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 02:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-content-delivery-networks-need-more-capacity/</guid><description>A significant media shift is underway, marked by a technological revolution since the days of broadcast dominance. Concerns about antenna reception have been replaced by anxieties over 3G and 4G coverage for accessing videos on mobile devices. Cable and satellite TV, which succeeded over-the-air broadcasting, now face competition from the internet as the preferred medium for audio and video content. As over-the-air delivery declines, Content Delivery Networks (CDNs) are emerging as its replacement.</description></item></channel></rss>