<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CAGR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cagr/</link><description>Recent content in CAGR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cagr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Euromonitor: Technology is increasingly influencing the growth of the toys and games industry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 18:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-technology-is-increasingly-influencing-the-growth-of-the-toys-and-games-industry/</guid><description>The worldwide toys and games market is expected to grow, driven by positive population trends in developing countries and a strong lineup of blockbuster movies. This combination is projected to result in a 4.5% compound annual growth rate (CAGR) until 2020.
Euromonitor International, a global market research firm, revealed that global toy and game sales hit US$179.7 billion in 2015. In-game purchases and construction toys made up 30% of total sales, highlighting their significance within the industry.</description></item><item><title>There is increasing interest in cold pressed juices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:41:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-increasing-interest-in-cold-pressed-juices/</guid><description>Source: Techsci Research.
A TechSci Research report projects the global cold-pressed juice market to experience a significant growth rate, exceeding 10% annually, between 2016 and 2022. This anticipated growth is attributed to several factors, including increased disposable incomes, heightened consumer awareness, effective marketing campaigns by industry leaders, widespread product availability, and a strong global distribution network.
Global GDP per capita, adjusted for purchasing power parity, rose from US$14,020.31 in 2012 to US$15,470.</description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives.</description></item><item><title>TechSci Research believes that the organic dairy market has significant potential</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 06:02:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/techsci-research-believes-that-the-organic-dairy-market-has-significant-potential/</guid><description>A recent report by TechSci Research, a global management consulting firm, predicts significant growth in the global organic dairy products market. Driven by factors like increased health consciousness, a growing urban population, and rising spending on organic foods, the market is expected to achieve a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of over 11% between 2016 and 2021.
The report, titled Global Organic Dairy Products Market By Product Type, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, identifies expanding product lines, readily available organic dairy products, strong distribution networks, increasing internet access, and proactive marketing strategies from key players as contributing factors to this projected growth.</description></item><item><title>Technavio provides an overview of the e-retail market for fashion in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 17:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-provides-an-overview-of-the-e-retail-market-for-fashion-in-india/</guid><description>Men&amp;rsquo;s clothing currently holds the largest portion of India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail market. Major companies in this market include Amazon, Flipkart, Snapdeal, Jabong, and Yepme.
Analysts at Technavio anticipate substantial growth in India&amp;rsquo;s online fashion retail sector, projecting a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of nearly 17% from 2016 to 2020. This surge is attributed to the convenience and affordability of online shopping, with diverse payment choices and a wider selection of products readily available.</description></item><item><title>The ideal location for candy in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ideal-location-for-candy-in-indonesia/</guid><description>Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT is a dominant player in the Indonesian confectionery market, particularly recognized for its Mentos brand.
According to a report on the Indonesian confectionery sector by market research firm Euromonitor, the wide array of inexpensive sugary treats, combined with robust marketing campaigns from prominent manufacturers, has propelled sales in this category within Indonesia.
Holding a commanding 23% market share in 2016, Perfetti Van Melle Indonesia PT remains the leader in the sugar confectionery sector.</description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018.</description></item><item><title>The Dubai consumer electronics market is projected to exceed a value of US$3 billion by the year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 11:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-consumer-electronics-market-is-projected-to-exceed-a-value-of-us-3-billion-by-the-year-2020/</guid><description>A Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry (DCCI) analysis, presented at GITEX Technology Week 2016, projects that the Dubai consumer electronics market will expand by 4.7% over the next four years, surpassing US$3 billion by 2020.
The analysis emphasizes Dubai&amp;rsquo;s robust retail sales growth despite challenges from low oil prices and global economic uncertainties. This strength is credited to strong underlying factors, including a growing population, increasing incomes, and a consistent influx of tourists.</description></item></channel></rss>