<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CJEU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cjeu/</link><description>Recent content in CJEU on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cjeu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Deceptive Client: The case that confused the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
John Grisham&amp;rsquo;s novels often feature a recurring theme: a determined but outmatched lawyer battling a powerful corporation that exploits the legal system, a vulnerable client harmed by the corporation, a polished corporate law firm doing the company&amp;rsquo;s bidding, and an eccentric judge striving for courtroom order. This formula has been a mainstay of his books for over two decades. However, the settings rarely venture beyond the Southern United States, except for occasional plot-driven trips to Caribbean islands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deceptive-client-the-case-that-confused-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU has restricted access to evidence through secretive means, pushing the boundaries of justice and cooperation within the European judicial system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi &amp;amp; Christina Eckes*
*Assistant professor of European law, Maastricht University and professor of European law, University of Amsterdam, respectively.
Beyond a &amp;lsquo;Procedural&amp;rsquo; Adjustment
The European Union has encountered substantial political and economic turmoil in recent years. For the first time in its 60-year existence, it faces a Member State seeking to withdraw, confronts hostility and trade conflicts with its former transatlantic partner, and grapples with rising populist movements across Europe that challenge the EU&amp;rsquo;s core principles, such as the rule of law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Putting an end to Brexit? Explaining the Wightman case on reversing the Article 50 notification independently.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</guid><description>Alan S. Reid, Senior Lecturer in Law, Sheffield Hallam University. The author welcomes comments on the blog at a.s.reid@shu.ac.uk
As the deadline for Brexit approaches and Theresa May&amp;rsquo;s conflicting negotiating goals become clearer, there are increasing demands for transparency regarding the Brexit process.
In late 2017, seven Scottish politicians from different parties and legislative bodies in Scotland (the Scottish Parliament, the UK Parliament, and the European Parliament) initiated a legal case in the Scottish Court of Session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-brexit-explaining-the-wightman-case-on-reversing-the-article-50-notification-independently/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do not bring up the additional judges!" The transformation of CJEU reform into a mockery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ongoing debate surrounding the reform of the Court of Justice (CJEU) is becoming increasingly chaotic, reminiscent of an episode of the British comedy &amp;ldquo;Fawlty Towers.&amp;rdquo; The show&amp;rsquo;s humor stems from Basil Fawlty&amp;rsquo;s futile attempts to manage unpredictable situations in his hotel, often venting his frustrations on his staff. While no one would endorse his management style, the current CJEU reform debate mirrors this comedic chaos.
To recap, following several unsuccessful attempts to reform the EU judicial structure, the CJEU proposed that the General Court, the lower EU court, should double its number of judges to two per Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The request for a preliminary ruling from the Polish Supreme Court on 2 August 2018 and its implications for the rule of law in Poland: A commentary on the CJEU's involvement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</guid><description>Alicja Sikora, Chair EU Law, Jagiellonian University
As the playwright Eugene Ionesco once said, predictions are only possible after events have occurred.
Last Thursday, the Polish Supreme Court presented the European Court of Justice with a request for a preliminary ruling. This type of request, outlined in Article 267 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union, is used to clarify questions regarding EU law. In doing so, the Polish court also paused the enforcement of a Polish law mandating early retirement for Supreme Court justices over 65...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-request-for-a-preliminary-ruling-from-the-polish-supreme-court-on-2-august-2018-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-poland-a-commentary-on-the-cjeu-s-involvement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU is currently hearing important cases regarding the European Arrest Warrant, questioning whether mutual trust should be blind or general with exceptions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:32:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</guid><description>Henning Bang Fuglsang Madsen Sørensen, Associate Professor, Department of Law, University of Southern Denmark
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing on February 15th, 2016, concerning two cases, Aranyosi and Caldararu, both addressing whether surrender under a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) should be refused if there are concerns about potential inhumane prison conditions in the requesting state. These cases, originating from the same German court, delve into the balance between the principle of mutual recognition in EU criminal law and the protection of fundamental rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>At the oral hearing on the PNR directive at the Court of Justice of the European Union, the focus was on flights, rock concerts, and finding a needle in a haystack.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</guid><description>Christian Thönnes, Research Associate at the Max Planck Institute for the Study of Crime, Security and Law in Freiburg, Department of Public Law.
July 13, 2021, marked a crucial moment for the future of privacy and security in the European Union. On this day, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing regarding its preliminary ruling procedure C-817/19. This procedure was initiated after the Constitutional Court of Belgium submitted ten questions to the CJEU, prompted by a legal challenge from the Belgian NGO Ligue des Droits Humains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement: Analysis 1 Overview</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</guid><description>Analysis of the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement - October 2019 Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction While the approval of the Brexit withdrawal agreement is uncertain at present, the UK Parliament&amp;rsquo;s upcoming vote necessitates an updated analysis of the revised agreement. This updated version includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship.
This post aims to provide a simplified explanation of the agreement for non-lawyers, outlining its structure and key content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-1-overview/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revised Brexit Withdrawal Agreement Analysis 2: Transition Period</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 12:59:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Now that a revised Brexit withdrawal agreement is available, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time to revisit my prior analyses of the initial agreement. This post, updating my spring 2018 analysis, focuses on the transition period outlined in the agreement. (The revised agreement includes changes to the Irish border protocol and the political declaration on the future relationship.) This post will provide context for the transition period and then break down the text...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revised-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-analysis-2-transition-period/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Opinion of AG de la Tour in C-621/21: Is it a helpful clarification or an unnecessary hindrance to women seeking international protection from gender-based violence?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 08:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</guid><description>Dr. Maja Grundler, a Lecturer in Law at the Department of Law and Criminology, Royal Holloway, University of London, examines a recent legal opinion concerning refugee and subsidiary protection eligibility for women at risk of violence within their families.
Advocate General (AG) de la Tour&amp;rsquo;s Opinion in case C-621/21 tackles the scope of the refugee definition within Article 2(d) of the Qualification Directive and the definition of subsidiary protection beneficiaries in Article 2(g) concerning women facing potential violence within a family setting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-ag-de-la-tour-in-c-621-21-is-it-a-helpful-clarification-or-an-unnecessary-hindrance-to-women-seeking-international-protection-from-gender-based-violence/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial stances on the status of UK and EU citizens in the Brexit negotiations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:47:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers*
Introduction
A crucial Brexit issue with potentially significant consequences for many is the fate of UK citizens in the EU and EU citizens in the UK post-Brexit. Addressed early in Brexit negotiations, both sides have established positions: the EU through a Council decision outlining the mandate for Commission negotiators on May 22, and the UK through a government proposal on June 26. Despite claims to the contrary, the UK&amp;rsquo;s proposal didn&amp;rsquo;t precede the EU&amp;rsquo;s stance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-stances-on-the-status-of-uk-and-eu-citizens-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speeches on the UK's future relationship with the EU by Theresa May and Boris Johnson: Lions vs. Unicorns</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 15:04:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Speeches delivered last week by Theresa May and Boris Johnson regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s future relationship with the EU present a study in contrasts. May&amp;rsquo;s approach was measured and pragmatic, advocating for close ties, while Johnson&amp;rsquo;s came across as dismissive and lacking depth, favoring distance from the EU.
While the EU27 has begun drafting treaty texts for Brexit, the UK has not. To illustrate potential outcomes, this post includes draft treaties based on Johnson&amp;rsquo;s and May&amp;rsquo;s security proposals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speeches-on-the-uk-s-future-relationship-with-the-eu-by-theresa-may-and-boris-johnson-lions-vs-unicorns/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reforming the EU's Court System: The path to progress lies in creating a more accountable court, not simply a larger one.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</guid><description>Alberto Alemanno, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Law &amp;amp; Risk Regulation, HEC Paris
Laurent Pech, Jean Monnet Professor of EU Public Law, Middlesex University London
1. Setting the Stage
Recent media attention on the EU Court of Justice highlights a departure from its previous low profile. Surprisingly, this attention is not focused on a specific court decision but rather on internal disputes regarding a proposal to address the court&amp;rsquo;s efficiency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reforming-the-eu-s-court-system-the-path-to-progress-lies-in-creating-a-more-accountable-court-not-simply-a-larger-one/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discussing the future relationship between the UK and EU: the suggested EU negotiating mandate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Formal negotiations for the future UK-EU relationship commenced last week. The EU published its proposed negotiating strategy, while the UK government released a parliamentary statement. Notably, Prime Minister Boris Johnson&amp;rsquo;s speech on the matter, aimed at a domestic audience, lacked substance concerning trade policy. It is crucial to clarify that the existing withdrawal agreement doesn&amp;rsquo;t govern trade between the UK (excluding Northern Ireland) and the EU post-transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discussing-the-future-relationship-between-the-uk-and-eu-the-suggested-eu-negotiating-mandate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resolving conflicts and the agreement for the UK's exit from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A key point of contention in the Brexit withdrawal agreement is how disputes will be settled. Specifically, there&amp;rsquo;s debate about whether the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) maintains authority over the UK. This post provides an overview of this issue and a detailed analysis of the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s provisions concerning dispute resolution and the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s role.
This post is the third in a series examining the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Role of Non-Legal Stability Factors in Ensuring Legal Certainty in the Preliminary Reference Procedure (Elgar 2022)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-role-of-non-legal-stability-factors-in-ensuring-legal-certainty-in-the-preliminary-reference-procedure-elgar-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 04:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-role-of-non-legal-stability-factors-in-ensuring-legal-certainty-in-the-preliminary-reference-procedure-elgar-2022/</guid><description>John Cotter, Lecturer in Law, School of Law, Keele University
A common saying, often credited to Benjamin Franklin, states that only death and taxes are inevitable. If we interpret &amp;ldquo;certainty&amp;rdquo; literally, legal professionals trying to anticipate the results of a case might concur. Predicting court outcomes involves significant challenges. Some stem from ambiguity within legal rules themselves, stemming from the limits of language in conveying meaning (&amp;ldquo;legal obstacles&amp;rdquo;). Others arise from external factors that influence how rules are selected, interpreted, and applied to a case (&amp;ldquo;extra-legal obstacles&amp;rdquo;)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-role-of-non-legal-stability-factors-in-ensuring-legal-certainty-in-the-preliminary-reference-procedure-elgar-2022/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-role-of-non-legal-stability-factors-in-ensuring-legal-certainty-in-the-preliminary-reference-procedure-elgar-2022/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union alters its stance on anonymity in cases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-alters-its-stance-on-anonymity-in-cases/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-alters-its-stance-on-anonymity-in-cases/</guid><description>Peter Oliver, Honorary Professor at the Université Libre de Bruxelles
Photo credit: Isaac Castillejos
In June 2018, the Court of Justice announced its decision to alter its handling of personal data in preliminary ruling requests. Citing the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the Court stated its commitment to safeguarding the data of individuals involved in these cases while upholding transparency and public access to court proceedings.
Starting July 2018, the names of individuals in all public documents related to preliminary rulings would be replaced with initials, not their actual ones, alongside a brief description of the case subject matter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-alters-its-stance-on-anonymity-in-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-alters-its-stance-on-anonymity-in-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is a Title Sufficient to Override Constitutional Rules and Fundamental Rule-of-Law Principles? A Paper on Enforcement Priorities for Article 102 TFEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</guid><description>Konstantinos Sidiropoulos
DPhil Candidate at University of Oxford – Prof Steve Weatherill
Foundation for Education and European culture scholar
Introduction
The best way to regulate abuse of dominance in the EU has been a subject of much discussion. In the early 2000s, aiming to address criticisms of its approach to unilateral conduct control, the European Commission started reviewing the relevant law, including how it was being applied (see the EAGCP Report and the Discussion Paper)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-title-sufficient-to-override-constitutional-rules-and-fundamental-rule-of-law-principles-a-paper-on-enforcement-priorities-for-article-102-tfeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is privacy prioritized over transparency in CJEU cases?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 20:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</guid><description>Peter Oliver, Barrister, Monckton Chambers; Visiting Professor, Université Libre de Bruxelles
Having a name is essential, as not having one can lead to problems. This is why courts in Strasbourg and Luxembourg have acknowledged a person’s fundamental right to use their own name.
The Court of Justice has traditionally used initials to protect the identities of vulnerable individuals like asylum seekers and children involved in sensitive litigation. However, in a recent announcement, the Court stated its intention to partially overturn this long-standing practice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-privacy-prioritized-over-transparency-in-cjeu-cases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guide for Law Students: Understanding EU Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge*
EU law is a captivating field of study that offers something for everyone, particularly those interested in politics, visionary thinking, and pragmatic solutions. Even if these aren&amp;rsquo;t your primary interests, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to study EU law due to its mandatory nature. However, it&amp;rsquo;s unlike any other legal system you may have encountered, defying categorization and fitting into no single box.
Before diving in, it&amp;rsquo;s helpful to reflect on your existing political perspectives on the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Politicians 1, Architects 0: Constructing the EU Judicial System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 18:07:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently suggested that the EU should double the number of judges on the General Court and eliminate the EU Civil Service Tribunal. This piece examines the reasons behind this significant proposition for restructuring the EU judicial system and evaluates its merits.
Background
The EU judicial system has consistently expanded to accommodate a growing caseload. The Single European Act of 1987 allowed for the establishment of the Court of First Instance (renamed the General Court by the Lisbon Treaty) to support the Court of Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/politicians-1-architects-0-constructing-the-eu-judicial-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3 of the updated Brexit Withdrawal Agreement focuses on dispute resolution.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 10:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
This post examines the dispute settlement mechanisms outlined in the revised Brexit withdrawal agreement, specifically addressing the role of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). It is part of a series analyzing the updated agreement, which includes a revised Protocol on the Irish border and a revised political declaration on the future relationship. Previous posts have provided an overview of the agreement and examined the transition period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-focuses-on-dispute-resolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell Address to the CJEU by EU Judge Dehousse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 14:34:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/</guid><description>Introduction by Professors Alemanno &amp;amp; Pech
This blog post presents the English translation of a farewell address by Judge Franklin Dehousse, who served on the EU General Court from 2003 to 2016.
Unusually, no public ceremony was held for the departing EU judges, including Judge Dehousse. This is likely due to Dehousse&amp;rsquo;s vocal criticism of the EU court system reform, a reform he extensively analyzed in several research papers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-address-to-the-cjeu-by-eu-judge-dehousse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In the case of Schipani v Italy, under what circumstances is it necessary for national courts to seek guidance from the CJEU as per the ECHR?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 11:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The European Court of Human Rights&amp;rsquo; (ECHR) judgment in the Schipani vs. Italy case, issued on July 21, 2015, revisited a topic of significant interest to EU legal experts: the violation of the ECHR by a national court due to its failure to request a preliminary ruling. This judgment, released just before the summer break, might have slipped under the radar for some...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-case-of-schipani-v-italy-under-what-circumstances-is-it-necessary-for-national-courts-to-seek-guidance-from-the-cjeu-as-per-the-echr/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dispute resolution between the EU and UK after Brexit in the context of the White Paper.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:09:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Emilija Leinarte*
*Professor of EU law, University of Cambridge and PhD student, University of Cambridge. This research has received support from the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe programme.
A recent publication by UK in a Changing Europe examined various governing structures that could be used to manage the UK-EU relationship following Brexit. The released White Paper offers a glimpse into the institutional structure that the UK envisions for its future dealings with the EU after withdrawal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dispute-resolution-between-the-eu-and-uk-after-brexit-in-the-context-of-the-white-paper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How can the issue of Suella be resolved? Exploring the legal implications of breaching and terminating the withdrawal agreement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent news suggests the UK may plan to violate the Brexit withdrawal agreement, with new Attorney-General Suella Braverman potentially seeking legal justification. This makes examining the repercussions of such a breach crucial. While the dispute resolution mechanisms within the agreement and the UK&amp;rsquo;s Withdrawal Agreement Act have been analyzed separately, this piece aims to provide a comprehensive overview, encompassing international law perspectives. This blog post summarizes the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution clauses and the international law principles concerning treaty termination, exploring their interplay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-the-issue-of-suella-be-resolved-exploring-the-legal-implications-of-breaching-and-terminating-the-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>