<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deoxit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/deoxit/</link><description>Recent content in Deoxit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 11:27:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/deoxit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bemaster 6000 (2702) restoration: the FM preset board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 11:27:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bemaster-6000-2702-restoration-the-fm-preset-board/</guid><description>As part of the equipment restoration, cleaning is essential. After over four decades, units accumulate a substantial amount of dust, as depicted in an earlier post. The FM preset board was no exception, exhibiting both dust and corroded trimmer contacts. These open trimmers are situated beneath the front panel, where gaps allow dust infiltration.
[Image]
To remove and clean the trimmers, desoldering their three contacts is necessary. They can then be slid out of the main black plastic housing.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Cleaning the Carriage Position Switches and Fixing a Bent Output Switch Contact Tab</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-cleaning-the-carriage-position-switches-and-fixing-a-bent-output-switch-contact-tab/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000, a process known as &amp;ldquo;switch day&amp;rdquo; involves cleaning the contacts of the many open switches. While some recommend desoldering the switches for thorough cleaning, it&amp;rsquo;s generally sufficient to clean the contact areas directly. This minimizes the risk of damaging the delicate contact tabs.
Effective switch functionality hinges on clean contact points, not the overall appearance of the switch. The contact tabs should be straight and have adequate spring to ensure proper contact.</description></item></channel></rss>