<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frontex on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frontex/</link><description>Recent content in Frontex on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/frontex/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges.</description></item><item><title>EU leaders are avoiding taking significant action to address the migrant crisis.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 18:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-leaders-are-avoiding-taking-significant-action-to-address-the-migrant-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU leaders convened yesterday and agreed on a policy to handle the escalating migrant death toll in the Mediterranean Sea. This new policy expands on the recently implemented 10-point plan established by ministers. Notably, some significant last-minute revisions to the initial draft highlight the leaders&amp;rsquo; priorities.
Detailed comments
The leaders&amp;rsquo; statement appears to demonstrate more empathy than the prior 10-point plan. It acknowledges the immense loss of life as a tragedy and prioritizes the prevention of further deaths at sea.</description></item><item><title>Accountability of Frontex: a challenging journey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</guid><description>Laura Salzano, PhD student in Constitutional Law, Barcelona University
Since its establishment in 2004, Frontex&amp;rsquo;s role and duties have been heavily scrutinized by the EU and human rights advocates. This attention stems from various concerns, including allegations of power abuse, opacity, and lack of cooperation. These concerns have been raised by diverse voices, such as policy experts, legal professionals, academics, activists, and NGOs.
Critiques of Frontex originate from both within and outside the EU.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's reaction to migrant fatalities focused on safeguarding and stopping them, or is it merely a way to disguise policy laundering?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-reaction-to-migrant-fatalities-focused-on-safeguarding-and-stopping-them-or-is-it-merely-a-way-to-disguise-policy-laundering/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU foreign and interior ministers recently agreed on a ten-point plan to address the tragic loss of migrant lives in the Mediterranean. While a summit and a new strategy are forthcoming, this initial plan is disappointing. It lacks crucial specifics and prioritizes border control and restrictive measures over aiding migrants facing perilous journeys and seeking safety.
This analysis will examine each of the plan&amp;rsquo;s ten points, followed by a look at the suggested &amp;ldquo;Australian solution&amp;rdquo; and the controversial &amp;ldquo;Christians only&amp;rdquo; approach.</description></item><item><title>Responsibility in Joint Returns after WS and Others v Frontex: Letting the Active By-Stander Off the Hook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</guid><description>A Missed Opportunity for Accountability: Examining the General Court&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in WS and others v Frontex This analysis delves into the General Court&amp;rsquo;s September 6, 2023, decision in the case of WS and others v Frontex, where a Syrian refugee family&amp;rsquo;s claim for damages against Frontex was dismissed. The family, seeking refuge in the EU during the Syrian war, was returned to Turkey under questionable circumstances involving a joint return operation between Greece and Frontex.</description></item><item><title>European Union Migration Agencies: Frontex, EASO, and Europol's Operations and Collaborations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</guid><description>Dr. David Fernández-Rojo, Universidad de Deusto - davidfrojo@deusto.es
The recent surge in migration, often called the “refugee crisis,” highlighted the urgent need to strengthen both the Schengen area and the Common European Asylum System (CEAS). It also underscored the need to support EU member states dealing with large numbers of migrants and to consistently apply EU policies on migration, asylum, and border control. EU agencies such as Frontex, EASO, and Europol have become central to these efforts.</description></item><item><title>The EU General Court's ruling in the WS and Others v Frontex case: Failure to hold accountable human rights violations at EU external borders.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 14:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-general-court-s-ruling-in-the-ws-and-others-v-frontex-case-failure-to-hold-accountable-human-rights-violations-at-eu-external-borders/</guid><description>Francesca Romana Partipilo, PhD candidate in International Law at Sant&amp;rsquo;Anna School of Advanced Studies (Pisa)
Photo credit: Rock Cohen, via Wikimedia commons
(see also critique of the judgment, by Melanie Fink and Jorrit Rijpma)
On September 6th, the EU General Court dismissed a case brought by a Syrian family claiming material and emotional damages from Frontex. They alleged experiencing anguish, fear, and suffering due to Frontex&amp;rsquo;s actions during a return operation conducted jointly with Greece on October 20th, 2016.</description></item></channel></rss>