<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Convergence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convergence/</link><description>Recent content in Convergence on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/convergence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Buy Convergence By The Byte</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buy-convergence-by-the-byte/</guid><description>XO Communications is revolutionizing telecommunications by offering IP Network services priced by bandwidth usage instead of traditional lines or channels. This shift to an IP-based network and the use of Session Initiation Protocol (SIP) for telephone trunking are rendering traditional telephony services obsolete. By utilizing a packet-switched network and transmitting everything in packet protocol, voice, and data traffic can easily share a single circuit.
The concept of convergence, using one network for voice, video, and data, has gained traction with IT departments aiming to simplify network management and executives seeking cost reductions.</description></item><item><title>On Monday, we will be converging in Atlanta.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-monday-we-will-be-converging-in-atlanta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 00:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/on-monday-we-will-be-converging-in-atlanta/</guid><description>Yesterday was a great start to Convergence 2011 in Atlanta! We balanced successful lab work and managing a Sure Step study hall with a fun evening exploring the Georgia Aquarium and the World of Coca-Cola.
Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the labs, especially for GP – they&amp;rsquo;re impressive! There are some excellent demos for the upcoming GP 2010 R2 release, as well as self-guided and recorded labs covering SQL Reporting Services, Management Reporter, and various other analytical and customization tools for Dynamics GP.</description></item><item><title>Returned from Convergence 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returned-from-convergence-2012/</guid><description>Looking forward to Convergence 2013 in New Orleans! I enjoyed New Orleans, though San Diego remains my top pick. It was a successful event, even though it seemed to fly by. As always, the hands-on labs were a highlight, and I appreciated connecting with attendees, partners, and familiar faces. We had better access to the product teams this year, which provided valuable opportunities to interact with those who consistently support us.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet VPLS Extends Your LAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</guid><description>Traditional methods of connecting multiple business locations, such as Frame Relay, VSAT satellite terminals, internet-based VPNs, and dedicated T1 lines, have been around for a while. However, a new technology called Ethernet VPLS offers superior performance and cost advantages, making it a compelling option for businesses with multiple locations, including branch offices, retail franchises, and medical clinics.
Ethernet VPLS, which stands for Virtual Private LAN service, essentially functions as a carrier-managed local area network that can span across cities, states, or even the entire country.</description></item><item><title>Heading to New Orleans!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heading-to-new-orleans/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 22:48:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heading-to-new-orleans/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m really excited about attending conferences, especially ones focused on Dynamics like Convergence. I love learning new things and sharing knowledge with others, and Convergence offers a fantastic opportunity to connect with customers, former students, fellow consultants, and Microsoft representatives in a relaxed setting. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to head south this weekend for a week of learning and networking.
I&amp;rsquo;ll be in the community and learning center labs as a technical learning guide.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications Merges Everything</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-merges-everything/</guid><description>The convergence of enterprise networks typically focuses on incorporating phone systems into the existing corporate network using VoIP. However, the ultimate goal of unified communications is to integrate all forms of electronic communication. This includes traditional phone lines, voice messages, video conferencing, data networks, network security, VPNs, and wireless access.
Cisco Systems already offers a platform designed to handle all of these functions for smaller businesses: the Cisco Unified Communications 500 Series.</description></item><item><title>Benefits Of An MPLS Mesh Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</guid><description>When your company grows to have multiple locations like branches, data centers, or factories, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a way to connect them all on the same network. The best way to do this is with an MPLS Mesh Network.
Smaller companies with only two locations usually start by connecting the locations with a point-to-point T1 or Ethernet line. While this works, using an MPLS network might be more cost-effective depending on the distance between locations and the availability of T1 or Ethernet services.</description></item><item><title>HP Inc. provides innovative computing solutions and designs that empower individuals to live their best life</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hp-inc-provides-innovative-computing-solutions-and-designs-that-empower-individuals-to-live-their-best-life/</guid><description>HP is changing mobile computing with new devices designed for the &amp;ldquo;One Life&amp;rdquo; experience – a blend of work and personal life. HP recognizes that work happens everywhere with an internet connection, requiring increased collaboration.
Lionel Chng, Managing Director of HP Inc. Singapore, emphasizes that millennials desire devices that are both stylish and functional, enabling creativity and secure collaboration. HP focuses on design, productivity, security, and entertainment to enhance the computing experience for both work and leisure.</description></item><item><title>A New Edge On Private IP Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-edge-on-private-ip-networks/</guid><description>With the increase in businesses operating from multiple locations, IP network solutions have become more affordable and accessible. New Edge Networks, a key player in this domain, specializes in private IP-based WANs, offering enhanced quality and performance for connecting multiple business sites by bypassing the public internet.
While the internet has revolutionized global communication, its ubiquity and open nature pose limitations for businesses. Network neutrality principles treat all data equally, regardless of its importance.</description></item></channel></rss>