<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Region on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/region/</link><description>Recent content in Region on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/region/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Box Zones provides customers with increased flexibility in choosing the locations for storing their data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</guid><description>The enterprise content management platform Box has introduced Box Zones, enabling companies to store their data regionally in Europe and Asia. Utilizing Amazon Web Services (AWS) and IBM Cloud, Box Zones will allow content to be stored in Germany, Ireland, Singapore, and Japan, based on customer requirements.
Box CEO and co-founder Aaron Levie highlighted that businesses are increasingly interconnected, collaborative, and global due to cloud technology. However, local regulations often compel companies to make technological compromises that hinder their growth and reduce employee productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/box-zones-provides-customers-with-increased-flexibility-in-choosing-the-locations-for-storing-their-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Commonwealth has adopted the Living Lands Charter and has launched the Blue Charter project incubator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</guid><description>Commonwealth leaders have formally agreed to the Living Lands Charter: A Commonwealth Call to action on Living Lands (CALL). This charter represents a commitment from all 54 member countries to protect global land resources and collaborate on climate change, biodiversity loss, and sustainable land management.
This non-binding agreement, announced at the close of the 2022 Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in Kigali, Rwanda, is the result of almost two years of discussions and negotiations with member countries, United Nations Rio Conventions, and other involved parties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-commonwealth-has-adopted-the-living-lands-charter-and-has-launched-the-blue-charter-project-incubator/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>