<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online Shopping on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-shopping/</link><description>Recent content in Online Shopping on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:23:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-shopping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bricks and Mortar Apocolypse, Now?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bricks-and-mortar-apocolypse-now/</guid><description>The physical world is struggling while the virtual world thrives. We may be approaching a point where the internet becomes dominant, and traditional businesses may suffer for unexpected reasons.
Retail has been declining, but recently, there&amp;rsquo;s been a sharp downturn due to rising gas prices. This discourages driving, which leads to less shopping. Shopping is crucial for the economy; a decline in shopping could lead to an economic depression.
Our society relies heavily on driving.</description></item><item><title>Marco, it's Polo on Your Mobile</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 02:26:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/marco-its-polo-on-your-mobile/</guid><description>Fashion giant Ralph Lauren is taking shopping to the next level by moving beyond online stores and embracing mobile shopping via cell phones. This shift, known as mobile or m-commerce, is poised to become as significant as e-commerce has been in recent times. Its success relies on internet-enabled smartphones and mobile-friendly websites designed for smaller screens, along with advancements like barcode scanning software and web-connected vending machines.
Why the focus on cell phone shopping?</description></item><item><title>How to Get a Web Presence For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 10:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-a-web-presence-for-your-business/</guid><description>Starting a new business or moving an existing one online can feel overwhelming with all the options available. Is it really worth the effort?
Absolutely! Many business owners will attest to the value of establishing an online presence. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be complicated. You can simplify the process by seeking guidance from experienced professionals. Take a look at this engaging introductory video from Network Solutions to see what I mean&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>