<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>287VVBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/287vvbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 287VVBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/287vvbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 02:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms on a Beogram 4002 turntable, the subsequent task involves refurbishing the printed circuit boards (PCBs) and replacing the reservoir capacitor.
The initial focus is on the main PCB. It was in its original state, showing signs of age and use. A detailed view highlights the RPM control section, which was particularly important for speed stability.
All electrolytic capacitors on the board were replaced with new, high-quality Japanese components rated for 105 degrees Celsius.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of RPM Trimmer Panel Bulbs with LED Assemblies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:35:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-rpm-trimmer-panel-bulbs-with-led-assemblies/</guid><description>Following the electronic restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the next step was to upgrade the light bulbs in the RPM adjustment panel with LED assemblies. This change was made because LEDs offer greater longevity and produce less heat compared to incandescent bulbs. Reduced heat generation is particularly beneficial as it improves the stability of the DC motor responsible for driving the platter. The original RPM control panel, in a disassembled state, is depicted below.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:34:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My first step when restoring a Beogram 4002 turntable is to focus on the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms. The arm lowering mechanism often requires attention because hardened lubricants can hinder the solenoid and damper assemblies. To address this, I disassemble the mechanism.
Once the solenoid and linkages are removed, I take the parts to my workbench for cleaning and re-lubrication.
Next, I address the linkage connecting the damper plunger to the tonearm, as it can cause delays in arm lowering, particularly after storage.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's Liquid Love</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-liquid-love/</guid><description>Following the installation of the Beolover 4002 Commander remote control and internal RIAA pre-amplifier, it was time for final adjustments before testing the turntable. The first step was tracking feedback adjustment. A blue trimmer on the tracking sensor LED light source simplified the fine-tuning of the feedback after the coarse mechanical adjustment of the sensor housing.
Next, the subclasses and platter height were adjusted, followed by the arm lowering limit. The lowering limit ensures the needle can descend below the record surface without hitting the platter ribs if the record detection fails.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Sensor Arm Bulb with an LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 11:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-sensor-arm-bulb-with-an-led-assembly/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable, the light bulb in the sensor arm, crucial for record detection, was replaced with a longer-lasting LED.
To ensure compatibility with the turntable&amp;rsquo;s bulb detection circuit, which disables record detection if a bulb failure is detected, the LED assembly was designed to mimic the current draw of the original bulb. LEDs inherently use less current, so a parallel current path was added to the LED board to compensate.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of a Cracked Hood - Another Process Improvement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:26:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-a-cracked-hood-another-process-improvement/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on has a cracked hood around the hinge attachments. The left side was entirely detached, and the right side had a crack extending around one of the holes.
The right side had a crack going all the way around one of the attachment holes:
To begin, I glued the broken pieces back together using Weld-On #4 acrylic solvent. This low-viscosity solvent is ideal for injecting into cracks, as capillary action draws it in.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of the DC Motor - Oil Infusion of the Oilite Bearings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 21:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-the-dc-motor-oil-infusion-of-the-oilite-bearings/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the DC motor required attention. The bearings were making noise, indicating a need for lubrication. This is a common issue in Beogram DC motors of this age, often requiring oil replenishment for stable performance.
The motor was removed from the turntable for servicing.
The bearings, identified as two ring-shaped components, were taken out of the motor.
To lubricate them, the bearings were submerged in motor oil, and a vacuum was applied to remove trapped air.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacement of Degraded Transport Lock Bushings and Missing Cabinet Guiding Washers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacement-of-degraded-transport-lock-bushings-and-missing-cabinet-guiding-washers/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 restoration involved addressing the common issue of fragile orange transport lock bushings and missing cabinet guiding washers. Many Beograms used plastic washers, which are prone to cracking and falling apart. This was evident in the restoration project, as some washers were missing entirely.
To rectify this, five new 3D-printed washers were installed. For aesthetic purposes, using a black washer for the front-center position is recommended to avoid visibility through the gap between the aluminum panel and the plinth.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of Beolover Commander MkII Remote and Internal RIAA Pre-Amp Board</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 09:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-beolover-commander-mkii-remote-and-internal-riaa-pre-amp-board/</guid><description>The owner of the Beogram 4002 (5513) requested the installation of a 4002 Commander remote control and an internal RIAA pre-amplifier module. The Commander enables complete control of the 4002 using an Apple remote, while the RIAA provides a strong output signal, allowing direct connection to modern amplifiers via CD/DVD/AUX inputs.
The first image displays the RIAA board and its mounting adapter, which elevates it above the output PCB headers.</description></item></channel></rss>