<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Central Bank on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-central-bank/</link><description>Recent content in European Central Bank on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-central-bank/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Government bailouts, borrowed institutions, and the role of judicial review in the case of Ledra Advertising.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 05:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective
A key aspect of the euro area crisis response has been the use of intergovernmental agreements that minimize judicial and parliamentary oversight at the EU level. A prime example is the European Stability Mechanism (ESM), established by euro area nations to offer conditional financial aid to struggling countries. The ESM, formed outside the EU framework through an international agreement (the ESM Treaty), relies on existing EU institutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/government-bailouts-borrowed-institutions-and-the-role-of-judicial-review-in-the-case-of-ledra-advertising/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Battle of the Legal Giants: Can the Euro endure?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 11:52:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The German Federal Constitutional Court (BVerfG) has finally submitted a legal question to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) on a critically important issue: the legality of the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) policy. This policy is widely credited with saving the EU&amp;rsquo;s single currency. If either court finds the policy unlawful, the euro&amp;rsquo;s continued existence could be in jeopardy.
In simple terms, the OMT is a 2012 commitment by the ECB to buy government bonds from struggling eurozone countries on secondary markets (from banks and financial institutions)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/battle-of-the-legal-giants-can-the-euro-endure/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The UK has emerged victorious in a battle with the financial services industry and the European Central Bank, but the question remains: can it secure victory in the overall war?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Until recently, the EU courts seemed to consistently rule against the UK in cases related to financial services and opt-outs from EU law. However, a recent General Court judgment regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s challenge to the European Central Bank (ECB) policy on securities clearing systems has defied these trends. This begs the questions: what does this mean for the UK&amp;rsquo;s financial services sector, and for the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-has-emerged-victorious-in-a-battle-with-the-financial-services-industry-and-the-european-central-bank-but-the-question-remains-can-it-secure-victory-in-the-overall-war/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Looking beyond austerity: the future of employment law in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Catherine Barnard, Trinity College Cambridge
Contrary to critics, the EU social model (ESM) is not dead, argues Professor Barnard. Although facing significant challenges, the ESM has historically demonstrated a capacity for renewal. This post explores potential future directions for the model.
While some believe a Social Union is necessary for Europe, this post focuses on a potentially more agreeable agenda for the EU-28, particularly in the area of employment law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-beyond-austerity-the-future-of-employment-law-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Judicial review of monetary policy and banking supervision by the European Central Bank.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</guid><description>Introduction
The European Union has experienced widespread political and economic consequences due to the financial crisis. These effects extend to the legal realm, leading to the European Central Bank (ECB) not only creating debatable new methods for involvement in monetary policy but also acquiring new authority in banking supervision. Additionally, the ECB, alongside the European Commission and the International Monetary Fund (forming the &amp;lsquo;Troika&amp;rsquo;), has become engaged in austerity measures within Member States requiring financial support...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/judicial-review-of-monetary-policy-and-banking-supervision-by-the-european-central-bank/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What lies ahead for Greece and the Eurozone: catharsis or catastrophe?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 13:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The recent victory of the anti-austerity party Syriza in the Greek elections raises questions about its potential effects on the EU&amp;rsquo;s economic and monetary union. Syriza&amp;rsquo;s objective is not to withdraw from the EU or the single currency but to renegotiate Greece&amp;rsquo;s debt and austerity measures. Their goal is to secure debt forgiveness and renegotiate terms, including the removal of austerity demands associated with previous bailouts.
However, this program might encounter legal obstacles due to limitations on debt forgiveness and ending austerity outlined in EU Treaties and Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-lies-ahead-for-greece-and-the-eurozone-catharsis-or-catastrophe/</a></p></description></item><item><title>After the Steinhoff case, the ECB has an increased responsibility to uphold and advocate for the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:25:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Diane Fromage, Maastricht University*
* I am grateful to Menelaos Markakis for his insightful feedback.
On March 12, 2020, the Court of Justice dismissed an appeal concerning the Steinhoff case (T-107/17), previously decided by the General Court in May 2019. This case, though not widely discussed, holds significant weight as it clarifies and broadens the European Central Bank (ECB)&amp;rsquo;s obligation to &amp;lsquo;respect the rights [of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (ECFR)], [to] observe the principles and [to] promote the application thereof&amp;rsquo; as stated in Article 51 ECFR, specifically concerning its advisory role...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/after-the-steinhoff-case-the-ecb-has-an-increased-responsibility-to-uphold-and-advocate-for-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What implications does the climate case against ING have for monetary policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</guid><description>Annelieke Mooij, Assistant Professor, Tilburg University
Photo credit: Sandro Halank, via Wikimedia Commons
The Dutch environmental organization “milieudefensie” threatened legal action against ING bank in the Netherlands. On February 14, 2024, ING declared it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t yield to the organization&amp;rsquo;s demands, making a lawsuit highly probable. While seemingly a domestic issue, this case could have significant European implications, particularly for the Monetary Union and the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) independence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the legality of the ECB's OMT program in question? The Advocate-General's opinion in Gauweiler suggests so.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 01:25:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</guid><description>Alicia Hinarejos, Downing College, University of Cambridge; author of The Euro Area Crisis in Constitutional Perspective (OUP)
On January 14th, Advocate General Cruz Villalon presented his legal opinion on the Gauweiler case (C-62/14), which concerns the legality of the European Central Bank (ECB) Outright Monetary Transactions (OMT) program. He believes the OMT program generally complies with EU treaties, provided certain conditions are met if it&amp;rsquo;s activated in the future. This case has significant implications for the European Monetary Union&amp;rsquo;s (EMU) constitutional framework, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s role, and the relationship between the German Constitutional Court (Bundesverfassungsgericht) and the Court of Justice of the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-legality-of-the-ecb-s-omt-program-in-question-the-advocate-general-s-opinion-in-gauweiler-suggests-so/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenging the legality of ECB restrictions on Greek bank accounts – and ways you can support the cause</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many citizens across the EU have observed the plight of Greeks limited to €60 withdrawals per day with sympathy and apprehension. This situation stems from the European Central Bank (ECB) restricting emergency funds for Greek banks.
Beyond the human cost, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s actions raise serious legal, political, and economic concerns. A core function of any central bank is acting as a last-resort lender for banks, a role the ECB is demonstrably failing to fulfill in this case...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>