<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Exclusion Clause on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exclusion-clause/</link><description>Recent content in Exclusion Clause on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/exclusion-clause/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The ECJ shows no sympathy for expelling war criminals who are EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 21:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-shows-no-sympathy-for-expelling-war-criminals-who-are-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently clarified the circumstances under which an EU citizen or their family member can be expelled from a Member State after being denied refugee status. This landmark judgment sheds light on the intersection of EU (and international) refugee law and EU free movement law, a relationship previously unaddressed in the Court&amp;rsquo;s case law.
This lack of legal precedent stems from EU law&amp;rsquo;s attempt to separate these two areas.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice has clarified that foreign fighters' accomplices are not eligible for refugee status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-has-clarified-that-foreign-fighters-accomplices-are-not-eligible-for-refugee-status/</guid><description>When can someone be refused asylum for terrorism? Professor Steve Peers
What happens when a person seeking refuge is suspected of terrorism or aiding terrorists? Can they still be considered a refugee? If not, how do we legally define &amp;ldquo;terrorism&amp;rdquo; to justify denying their claim? The recent EU Court of Justice judgment in the Lounani case clarifies some aspects of this complex issue but leaves some challenging questions unanswered.
Legal Framework The UN Refugee Convention (Geneva Convention) outlines an &amp;rsquo;exclusion&amp;rsquo; clause in Article 1.</description></item></channel></rss>