<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2019 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2019/</link><description>Recent content in 2019 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The LASALLE Show will begin in April 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 08:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lasalle-show-will-begin-in-april-2019/</guid><description>From the beginning of April to the end of May, the public and industry professionals are invited to view almost 900 graduating student projects at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s LASALLE College of the Arts yearly graduation showcase.
The projects featured at The LASALLE Show are developed throughout the students&amp;rsquo; final year and embody the culmination of their artistic growth and the realization of their aspirations. The LASALLE Show also provides insights into current trends in contemporary arts and design and highlights the emerging work of young artists.</description></item><item><title>Sony Singapore's year-end promotions are valid until the beginning of January 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 02:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sony-singapore-s-year-end-promotions-are-valid-until-the-beginning-of-january-2020/</guid><description>Are you looking for some of Sony&amp;rsquo;s top products from 2019? Here are a few:
Digital imaging
Sony A7 III
Source: Sony. The α7 III.
The A7 III boasts five-axis stabilization, 4D Focus for reliable focusing in low light (down to EV-3), and the capability to record 4K HDR videos.
Promotional price: S$2,699 (usual price S$2,899)
Sony α7 III with 35mm full-frame image sensor (ILCE7M3K) Sony RX100 VII
The compact RX100 VII features an extensive zoom range and remarkable speed.</description></item><item><title>LG will be showcasing its newest Ultra monitors at CES</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-will-be-showcasing-its-newest-ultra-monitors-at-ces/</guid><description>At CES, LG Electronics (LG) will showcase its newest Ultra monitors, featuring UltraWide models for productivity and UltraGear monitors designed for gaming.
2019 LG UltraWide Monitor
Source: LG. The new 49&amp;quot; UltraWide monitor.
Known for its innovation in the UltraWide monitor market, LG&amp;rsquo;s latest 49-inch model (49WL95) offers a 32:9 aspect ratio curved screen designed to enhance productivity. Its size is equivalent to two 27-inch Quad High Definition displays combined, with a resolution of 5,120 x 1,440 and 108 pixels per inch for clarity.</description></item><item><title>According to the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, Singaporean small and medium-sized businesses are leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</guid><description>Source: Cisco ebook. This Cisco report, the APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, evaluates digital maturity based on four key aspects.
· Singaporean SMBs achieved the highest ranking on the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index.
· Cybersecurity is the primary technology that Singaporean SMBs are investing in, followed by cloud computing and analytics.
· The most significant challenges cited by SMBs across Singapore are a shortage of digital skills and talent within their organizations and a lack of understanding of operational and customer data.</description></item><item><title>Collagen, probiotics, and plant-based protein were popular subjects at Vitafoods Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 20:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/collagen-probiotics-and-plant-based-protein-were-popular-subjects-at-vitafoods-asia/</guid><description>Vitafoods Asia, a nutraceutical event showcasing the newest ingredients, product advancements, and technology driving innovation in the industry, revealed emerging trends.
Chris Lee, MD, Global Health &amp;amp; Nutrition Network Europe, Informa Markets, stated, &amp;ldquo;Nutraceuticals are a booming industry in Asia, and Informa Markets aims to support its growth in the region by providing a knowledge base and platform.&amp;rdquo;
First-time attendee Rikhia Mazumdar, Global Senior Brand Manager for Reckitt Benckiser, expressed her intention to return the following year.</description></item><item><title>Red Letter Sale by KEEPERS to feature Singaporean designer brands</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 05:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/red-letter-sale-by-keepers-to-feature-singaporean-designer-brands/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s largest designer sale is back and bigger in 2019, featuring over 50 designers offering discounts up to 90%.
The second annual KEEPERS Red Letter Sale will showcase a variety of brands, including accessory makers, publishers, home and décor companies, fashion and shoe brands, and even food and drink vendors to keep shoppers energized. Attendees can:
Discover local stories at Epigram Books Craft personalized scents with local perfumers Artisan of Sense, The LAB Fragrances, and SIX Explore environmentally friendly and natural skincare brands like Alcheme Skincare, offering free consultations for custom blends; Frank Skincare, a luxury brand handmade in Singapore; and RE:ERTH, featuring unique, naturally-derived ingredients like Japanese white turmeric.</description></item><item><title>Register for a Jane's Walk (if possible)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 16:32:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/register-for-a-jane-s-walk-if-possible/</guid><description>](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjjjftL3eBnpoP9-lZPIx2FBUIjixQblEemCMYjK1fsqWMFAnV2mbG6iaAU305MtXqwpzxONmNTYc8Z02crj7dnUv-D5-CAAuQb0naLfJdJRIYhUsM2hARYEEShQ8L3TaCSNH0-kREbc6cU/s1600/20180505_150031.jpg)
This image showcases an overseas Chinese support organization, 武裕平民互助会, with Lee Huat Motoring located just beyond the tree.
As expected, spots for Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walks are quickly filling up. Jane&amp;rsquo;s Walk is a yearly event featuring free walks led by volunteers. These walks pay tribute to Jane Jacobs (May 4, 1916 - April 25, 2006), an urbanist, writer, and activist who tirelessly advocated for community involvement in urban design.
This coming May marks the 7th anniversary of Jane’s Walk Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor has released a list of the top 10 workplaces in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</guid><description>The job and recruiting website Glassdoor has revealed the winners of its annual Employees’ Choice Awards, which included a category for Singapore for the first time.
These awards recognize the Best Places to Work in 2020 across nine countries, including Singapore. The rankings are determined by the input of employees who anonymously share their experiences through company reviews on Glassdoor. This feedback encompasses their job, work environment, and employer over the past year.</description></item><item><title>In 2018, Dubai drew in more than 1,000 residents with a net worth of over a million dollars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2018-dubai-drew-in-more-than-1-000-residents-with-a-net-worth-of-over-a-million-dollars/</guid><description>Hamdan bin Mohammed: &amp;ldquo;The UAE&amp;rsquo;s forward-looking leadership has made it a top global destination for living and business.&amp;rdquo;
Over 1,000 millionaires relocated to Dubai in 2018.
Crown Prince of Dubai, Sheikh Hamdan bin Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, credits the UAE&amp;rsquo;s robust investment and economic landscape to its leadership&amp;rsquo;s visionary approach. He highlights their commitment to the well-being of residents, visitors, and investors, along with fostering innovation, as key factors in establishing the UAE as a premier lifestyle and business hub.</description></item><item><title>The deadline for submissions to the Sony World Photography Awards 2019 is January 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deadline-for-submissions-to-the-sony-world-photography-awards-2019-is-january-2019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-deadline-for-submissions-to-the-sony-world-photography-awards-2019-is-january-2019/</guid><description>Global photographers have less than a month to submit their entries to the 12th annual Sony World Photography Awards’ Professional, Open and Youth competitions. Considered a major event in the photography world, the awards acknowledge the finest contemporary photography from the past year across a diverse range of photographic genres.
Scott Gray, the CEO and founder of the World Photography Organisation, remarked that each year, the Sony World Photography Awards brings new photographic talents to light and provides established artists with a global stage for their work.</description></item><item><title>The recipients of the MRM Business Award and MRM Business Innovation Award have been revealed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-recipients-of-the-mrm-business-award-and-mrm-business-innovation-award-have-been-revealed/</guid><description>Source: Dubai Chamber. HH Sheikh Ahmed Al Maktoum acknowledged the recipients of the 10th Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum (MRM) Business Award and the 2nd MRM Business Innovation Award in Dubai, UAE.
Sheikh Ahmed bin Saeed Al Maktoum, President of Dubai Civil Aviation Authority, as well as Chairman &amp;amp; Chief Executive of the Emirates Airline &amp;amp; Group, presided over the ceremony, which was held under the patronage of Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, Vice-President and Prime Minister of the UAE and Ruler of Dubai, and organized by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is ranked third in the Asia-Pacific region for promoting the growth of women entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-ranked-third-in-the-asia-pacific-region-for-promoting-the-growth-of-women-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Dell. Post-it notes show challenges facing women
in the workplace.
• Out of the top cities in the Asia Pacific region, Singapore ranks third behind Sydney and Melbourne, Australia, in Dell&amp;rsquo;s yearly Women Entrepreneur Cities (WE Cities) Index, which analyzes cities&amp;rsquo; ability to support women entrepreneurs.
• Since 2017, all 50 cities included in the study have demonstrated year-over-year progress in the majority of the evaluated areas. Cities in the Asia Pacific region are keeping pace with global improvements, demonstrating the most significant growth in the Talent area.</description></item><item><title>Preparations for Vivid Sydney start two weeks before Lights On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</guid><description>Sydney is getting ready for Vivid Sydney, a major festival celebrating light, music, and ideas in the Southern Hemisphere. Over 50 light installations and projections will illuminate the city starting May 24th.
Source: Vivid Sydney. An artist&amp;rsquo;s impression by Andrew Thomas Huang &amp;amp; Bemo on the Austral Floral Ballet, part of Vivid Light 2019. For 23 days, Vivid Sydney will transform the city into a captivating display of color with stunning light sculptures and large-scale projections.</description></item><item><title>Singapore to host a coffee consumer festival driven by heritage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-to-host-a-coffee-consumer-festival-driven-by-heritage/</guid><description>Source: La Kopi.
The first-ever La Kopi festival, launched in 2019, is a joyous weekend event celebrating Singapore&amp;rsquo;s coffee and bakery culture. Supported by the Singapore Coffee Association, the festival aims to raise awareness and appreciation for these local staples.
This unique coffee festival will take place at the Singapore Expo Hall from January 25th to 27th, 2019. Spanning 4,000 square meters, the event features nearly 70 vendors from various countries, including Japan, Taiwan, Malaysia, and Hong Kong.</description></item><item><title>We are all increasing the frequency of washing our hair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 06:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-are-all-increasing-the-frequency-of-washing-our-hair/</guid><description>The increasing prevalence of hair problems and pollution has led people to shampoo their hair more often, either daily or every other day. This trend has fueled the growth of the shampoo industry, as noted in Technavio&amp;rsquo;s report on the global hair shampoo market from 2015 to 2019. The report highlights that shampoos held over 40% of the global hair care market share in 2014.
Source: Technavio.
The global shampoo market is projected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 4.</description></item><item><title>Ericsson has unveiled its 10 top consumer trends for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-has-unveiled-its-10-top-consumer-trends-for-2019/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson website. Infographic summarizing the 10 hot consumer trends for 2019.
· Consumers anticipate that smart speakers will participate in family disagreements, much like human family members do.
· Users of virtual assistants believe that devices capable of understanding human emotions will be commonplace within the next three years.
· Users of augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) express a desire for interactive, virtual assistance with practical tasks such as cooking or completing repairs.</description></item><item><title>VistaJet World introduces end-of-year travel experiences</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:07:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vistajet-world-introduces-end-of-year-travel-experiences/</guid><description>VistaJet World offers a selection of highly exclusive and luxurious travel experiences designed to fulfill every Christmas wish.
Unconventional and unique trips for the Asia Pacific region include: The Great Maharajas | India Source: VistaJet. Enjoy India on the Maharajas trip.
Experience the life of Indian royalty as you travel from palace to palace, hosted by maharajas, with luxurious overnight stays at various Taj Hotels.
Spend time with maharajas in their palaces</description></item><item><title>Dato' Joey Yap reveals his forecasts for the Year of the Earth Boar, 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dato-joey-yap-reveals-his-forecasts-for-the-year-of-the-earth-boar-2019/</guid><description>Over 5,000 attendees were present at Dato&amp;rsquo; Joey Yap&amp;rsquo;s yearly Feng Shui &amp;amp; Astrology seminar in January 2019.
During the seminar, Dato&amp;rsquo; Yap provided insights into the Year of the Earth Boar, covering both the year&amp;rsquo;s forecasts and the projected global economic climate.
He specifically highlighted February 8th, 11th, and 12th as auspicious dates to resume work in 2019.
A notable collaboration with EZ-Link resulted in the launch of special edition EZ-Link cards.</description></item><item><title>In March, Clarke Quay will be hosting the largest Singapore Festival of Fun ever</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:28:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-clarke-quay-will-be-hosting-the-largest-singapore-festival-of-fun-ever/</guid><description>- This image features carnival performers and comedians
- This ten-day festival includes the Clarke Quay Streetfest, the Magners International Comedy Festival and the Nickelodeon Fiesta.
The third annual Singapore Festival of Fun returns this March with its signature entertainment. From March 14-24, 2019, Clarke Quay will become a carnival showcasing street performers, standup comedy, and games. This ten-day event combines international and local carnival acts featuring acrobatics, juggling, and daring feats with standup comedic talent and distinctive Nickelodeon games celebrating Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The future of work revolves around extracting valuable business insights from data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 01:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-future-of-work-revolves-around-extracting-valuable-business-insights-from-data/</guid><description>The rise of robotics and artificial intelligence (AI) is a significant development for the workforce. The shortage of skilled professionals across industries has made automation increasingly appealing to employers. It is evident that automation and AI have the potential to replace a considerable portion of tasks currently performed by humans.
Reactions to this trend are varied, ranging from optimism to apprehension. An Oracle study reveals that 93% of individuals would readily follow instructions from robots in the workplace, demonstrating a high level of trust in automation.</description></item><item><title>Joey Yap's advice for the 12 zodiac signs in 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-s-advice-for-the-12-zodiac-signs-in-2019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 23:38:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/joey-yap-s-advice-for-the-12-zodiac-signs-in-2019/</guid><description>Joey Yap, a renowned author, speaker, and expert in Chinese metaphysics, has provided his forecasts for the 12 zodiac signs, along with a flying stars chart, based on traditional Chinese metaphysical principles. These predictions cover the year of the earth boar, spanning from February 5, 2019, to January 24, 2020.
Dog Birth years: 1934, 1946, 1958, 1970, 1982, 1994, 2006, 2018
Overall: This year brings excellent financial prospects for Dogs, presenting opportunities to enhance wealth through carefully chosen investments and assistance from others.</description></item><item><title>Dubai hotels are at the top of the list of top meeting hotels according to Cvent</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 03:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-hotels-are-at-the-top-of-the-list-of-top-meeting-hotels-according-to-cvent/</guid><description>Dubai, UAE, boasts seven out of the top 10 hotels in the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region for Meetings, Incentives, Conferences, and Exhibitions (MICE), according to a new ranking. The list was released by Cvent, a leading technology provider for meetings, events, and hospitality.
These rankings are based on data from the Cvent Supplier Network (CSN), a comprehensive database with information on over 260,000 hotels, resorts, and event spaces in more than 175 countries.</description></item><item><title>CEE is ready to showcase gadgets and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 02:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cee-is-ready-to-showcase-gadgets-and-games/</guid><description>The 4th Consumer Electronics Exhibition (CEE) will be held from May 23rd to 26th, 2019, at Suntec Singapore Convention Centre. The event is organized by Exhibits Inc., a subsidiary of Sphere Exhibits, which is the events and exhibitions branch of Singapore Press Holdings.
Some of the featured events include:
Singapore Robo Fight 2019 (Level 4, Gamex Booth 8601)
Attendees can use smartphones to control miniature battle robots and engage in virtual combat.</description></item><item><title>Prepare yourself to taste delicious food from various regions at RWS Street Eats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 00:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prepare-yourself-to-taste-delicious-food-from-various-regions-at-rws-street-eats/</guid><description>Resorts World Sentosa (RWS) is bringing back its popular food event, RWS Street Eats, after it attracted over 100,000 attendees last year. The event will run from May 3rd to 12th, 2019, and showcase new dishes from across Southeast Asia.
Taking place at the Malaysian Food Street in RWS, this 10-day event will feature hidden culinary gems from Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, Vietnam, and Taiwan. These vendors are local favorites, often known only to the savviest eaters in their respective countries.</description></item><item><title>The KPMG index assesses the capacity of 140 countries to adapt to change</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 19:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-kpmg-index-assesses-the-capacity-of-140-countries-to-adapt-to-change/</guid><description>According to the 2019 KPMG Change Readiness Index (CRI), countries in the Asia Pacific region are generally showing improvement in their approaches to climate change. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose two spots to number 2, while Taiwan jumped 18 places.
Published twice a year, the CRI is now in its fourth year. It ranks 140 countries* based on their preparedness for and response to major change events. This edition focuses on the capabilities countries need to effectively combat climate change and minimize related risks.</description></item><item><title>Asia is leading in the Henley Passport Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-leading-in-the-henley-passport-index/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 17:13:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-is-leading-in-the-henley-passport-index/</guid><description>Asian nations are leading the Henley Passport Index, a ranking of all passports based on how many destinations their holders can visit without a pre-arranged visa. This index uses exclusive data from the International Air Transport Association (IATA). For the third year in a row, Japan holds the top spot with a visa-free/visa-on-arrival score of 191, meaning Japanese citizens can travel to 191 destinations without needing a visa beforehand.
Singapore holds second place, while South Korea ties with Germany for third place.</description></item><item><title>The Private Museum is taking a new approach to printmaking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 20:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-private-museum-is-taking-a-new-approach-to-printmaking/</guid><description>The Private Museum (TPM) in Singapore is hosting an exhibition curated by Zaki Razak, titled Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing. The exhibition runs from May 17th to July 7th, 2019, and features printmaking works by seven artists: Miguel Chew, Weixin Chong, Mona Choo, Urich Lau, Nadia Oh, Shin-Young Park, and Shih Yun Yeo.
Source: Eventbrite page. Poster for Repeat, Repeat, Repeat; revising the phenomenon of printing.
This is the second exhibition in TPM&amp;rsquo;s Guest Curator series, which aims to promote independent curatorial practices and diverse perspectives.</description></item><item><title>Women in Saudi Arabia prefer Apple over Almarai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/women-in-saudi-arabia-prefer-apple-over-almarai/</guid><description>In 2019, Apple surpassed Almarai to secure the top position in YouGov MENA&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Women’s Choice Brand Rankings&amp;rdquo; for Saudi Arabia. YouGov attributes Apple&amp;rsquo;s success to the buzz surrounding their new iPhones and Apple Watches, which resonated strongly with women.
Almarai&amp;rsquo;s decision to increase milk prices last year sparked consumer backlash, including calls for boycotts on social media. This negatively impacted the brand&amp;rsquo;s perception among women in Saudi Arabia, causing them to drop from first to fifth place in the rankings.</description></item><item><title>Should you consider investing in cryptocurrency?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 19:45:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-you-consider-investing-in-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: Statista. Bitcoin price index from November 2016 to November 2018 (US$).
Cryptocurrencies experienced substantial growth in 2017, followed by a less impressive 2018. This raises the question: Are we witnessing a classic boom and bust cycle? Several experts in the field share their insights.
Source: Dash. Taylor.
“The total market value of all cryptocurrencies combined is currently at the same level as in September 2017. However, what often gets overlooked is the continued growth in actual usage and the constant innovation happening in the sector.</description></item><item><title>In March, The Island Exchange provides business insights</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-march-the-island-exchange-provides-business-insights/</guid><description>Source: HSBC Women&amp;rsquo;s World Championship. Heng.
The Island Exchange is a brand-new festival geared towards ambitious individuals, launching at Sentosa, Singapore, on March 2nd.
Running concurrently with the HSBC Women&amp;rsquo;s World Championship, The Island Exchange is a one-day event featuring a mix of local and international speakers who will be sharing their insights and experiences on cultivating a successful and fulfilling career.
Notable speakers include Nadya Hutagalung, TV personality and UN Environmental Goodwill Ambassador, and Rachel Lim, founder of Love Bonito.</description></item><item><title>The most popular videos on YouTube in Hong Kong for 2019</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:03:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-most-popular-videos-on-youtube-in-hong-kong-for-2019/</guid><description>Content related to local news, tutorials, and parodies were the most popular on YouTube in Hong Kong this year.
A wider variety of music genres are gaining traction.
YouTube Hong Kong Rewind 2019 highlights this year&amp;rsquo;s trending videos, showcasing categories like the Top 10 Trending Videos, Top 10 Trending Local Music Videos, Top 10 Trending International Music Videos, and Top 10 Emerging Channels.
Music, in various forms like music videos, live shows, remixes, and covers, remains a favorite among Hong Kong viewers.</description></item><item><title>TikTok has introduced the #NDP2019 challenge to celebrate Singapore's National Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tiktok-has-introduced-the-ndp2019-challenge-to-celebrate-singapore-s-national-day/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 14:03:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tiktok-has-introduced-the-ndp2019-challenge-to-celebrate-singapore-s-national-day/</guid><description>To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 54th birthday, TikTok, the short-form video app, is launching a special hashtag challenge just for Singapore: #NDP2019.
TikTok users in Singapore are invited to express their national pride using the country&amp;rsquo;s colors, red and white, in their videos. They can use special NDP stickers and add the #NDP2019 hashtag to their posts. Ten lucky users who participate will have the chance to win limited-edition National Day TikTok merchandise.</description></item><item><title>The 2019 Year in Review by Yahoo highlights Singapore's obsession with celebrity, wealth, and the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 05:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2019-year-in-review-by-yahoo-highlights-singapore-s-obsession-with-celebrity-wealth-and-the-future/</guid><description>Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Year in Review (YIR) reveals that Singapore&amp;rsquo;s internet users were captivated by stories surrounding Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s former PM Najib Razak, NUS student Monica Baey, and the Hong Kong protests.
The YIR, which analyzes search trends on Yahoo&amp;rsquo;s platforms, highlighted Najib Razak&amp;rsquo;s connection to the 1MDB scandal as a topic of significant interest. The Orchard Towers murder case, particularly Natalie Siow&amp;rsquo;s involvement, also drew considerable attention.
Actor Aloysius Pang&amp;rsquo;s passing during reservist training prompted searches related to training safety, while his girlfriend, actress Jayley Woo, also became a top search.</description></item><item><title>The award ceremony for the Zayed Sustainability Prize 2019 took place</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 02:25:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-award-ceremony-for-the-zayed-sustainability-prize-2019-took-place/</guid><description>Source: PRNewsfoto/Zayed Sustainability Prize. The 2019 Zayed Sustainability Prize ceremony took place during Abu Dhabi Sustainability Week (ADSW). His Highness Sheikh Mohamed presented awards to 10 winners across categories such as Health, Food, Energy, Water, and Global High Schools. The ceremony was attended by prominent figures including HH Sheikh Hazza bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of Abu Dhabi Executive Council; HH Lt General Sheikh Saif bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Prime Minister and Minister of the Interior; HH Sheikh Mansour bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy PM and Minister of Presidential Affairs; HH Sheikh Hamed bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Chief of the Abu Dhabi Crown Prince&amp;rsquo;s Court; and HH Sheikh Omar bin Zayed Al Nahyan, Deputy Chairman of the Board of Trustees of Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan Charitable and Humanitarian Foundation; Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan, Minister of Tolerance; and other high-ranking ministers and officials.</description></item></channel></rss>