<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-networks/</link><description>Recent content in IP Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Your Telecom Lines Should Be Switched Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 02:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-your-telecom-lines-should-be-switched-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A significant shift is occurring in the telecom industry as traditional circuit-switched networks are being replaced with packet-switched networks. This change brings with it the widespread availability of Ethernet connections, extending from individual locations to the internet. However, some organizations are hesitant to move on from their reliable T1 lines and SONET fiber optic services. This begs the questions: why should they consider transitioning, and to what?</description></item><item><title>Is Voice Over MPLS The New PSTN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</guid><description>Packet-switched networks are undeniably replacing circuit-switched networks, so much so that the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) might be phased out by the FCC. This signals the potential end of the century-old telephone system, raising the question of what will replace it. VoIP is a strong contender, but not in its current form.
VoIP&amp;rsquo;s strengths lie in its established standards for coding, signaling, and its compatibility with Ethernet data networks. However, its widespread adoption is hampered by incompatible implementations, concerns from wireless carriers about network overload, and inconsistent voice quality on the internet.</description></item><item><title>What Is Lowering Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Pricing?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-lowering-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-pricing/</guid><description>The cost of Gigabit Ethernet bandwidth has decreased significantly in recent years, offering a welcome change for companies needing robust bandwidth for cloud computing, e-commerce, medical imaging, video streaming, and other high-demand applications. This price drop extends across various bandwidth services, including T1 lines, DS3 connections, OCx SONET/SDH fiber optic bandwidth, and Ethernet options ranging from Fast Ethernet to 10 GigE. Notably, Ethernet services often show the most substantial cost reductions per Mbps.</description></item><item><title>WAN Connection Strategies</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 04:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-connection-strategies/</guid><description>When you need to connect your business to the outside world, the variety of telecommunication options can be overwhelming. Understanding the basic technologies can help you make the right choice.
There are two main types of networks: Time Division Multiplexing (TDM) and Internet Protocol (IP). TDM is older and relies on dedicated circuits, while IP uses packet switching for more flexible data transfer. Interestingly, both types can carry the other&amp;rsquo;s traffic, blurring the lines.</description></item><item><title>Profit From The Bandwidth Price Wars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/profit-from-the-bandwidth-price-wars/</guid><description>A price war is currently happening in the commercial bandwidth industry. This battle between carriers presents a unique opportunity for consumers to benefit.
The telecommunications industry was once considered stable and resistant to change. However, the breakup of the Bell System in 1984 brought about significant competition. Companies like Sprint, MCI, and more recently, others like Opex and PNG, began offering competitive long-distance services. This gave both businesses and consumers the option to save money on long-distance calls while keeping their local phone service.</description></item><item><title>LAN to WAN Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 19:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lan-to-wan-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>Ethernet is the standard protocol for local area networks (LANs), but connecting beyond a single location requires a way to bridge the gap to wide area network (WAN) technologies. Traditionally, this meant converting between protocols, which was inefficient. However, Metro and Carrier Ethernet connections now offer a seamless way to link LANs and WANs.
Packet-based networks, especially those using IP, benefit significantly from using the same technology across the entire network.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper Optical Carrier Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-optical-carrier-services/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:35:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-optical-carrier-services/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on digital operations, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth is skyrocketing. However, the perceived cost of these services often deters companies from upgrading. Many assume they cannot afford faster networks, but this assumption is often outdated.
The cost per Mbps for carrier services has plummeted since the dot-com bubble burst in the late 1990s. While bandwidth was once prohibitively expensive, the subsequent oversupply led to a dramatic price drop.</description></item><item><title>Finding An Ethernet Internet Provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</guid><description>Looking for a better alternative to traditional internet services like T1 lines? Ethernet Internet might be the answer. But finding the right provider can be tricky. That’s where the Ethernet Internet Finder comes in.
This free tool, powered by Telarus, a leading telecom brokerage firm, helps businesses easily find and compare Ethernet Internet providers. Just enter your basic business contact information, preferably your main business phone number, and let the system do the rest.</description></item><item><title>600 Mbps Ethernet vs OC12 SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-mbps-ethernet-vs-oc12-sonet/</guid><description>Companies that need bandwidth in the fractional Gigabit range have often relied on OC12 SONET fiber optic service. While it remains a solid high-speed choice, it&amp;rsquo;s worth considering 600 Mbps Ethernet as well. Comparing these two options might yield some surprising results.
OC-12 (622 Mbps) is the next tier up from OC-3 (155 Mbps) in the SONET optical carrier hierarchy. This service is widely available in Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) and as a dedicated internet access connection for mid-sized internet service providers.</description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area.</description></item><item><title>Find The Ethernet Internet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</guid><description>Looking for increased bandwidth for your business without the high price tag? An Ethernet Internet connection might be the solution you need.
Ethernet Internet connections are a newer offering. While we’ve utilized Ethernet in our local area networks for years and the internet itself aligns with LAN Ethernet, connecting the two has involved specialized telecom services.
You likely currently have T1 or DS3 service, which require specific equipment and software for protocol conversion and signal interfacing with standard network Ethernet ports.</description></item></channel></rss>