<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Streaming on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/streaming/</link><description>Recent content in Streaming on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/streaming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Guvera introduces support for Apple TV and updates its product</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 09:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guvera-introduces-support-for-apple-tv-and-updates-its-product/</guid><description>Source: Guvera.
Guvera, a music streaming service supported by brand funding, has announced significant upgrades to its product and compatibility with Apple TV.
The updated Guvera 3.0 app introduces music channels and a variety of new editorial features. These include artist interviews, news articles, reviews, photo galleries, brand competitions, and product promotions.
Hazel Savage, Head of Marketing and Operations for Guvera Asia, stated that the company recognizes that music is more than just individual tracks; it represents a whole culture and way of life.</description></item><item><title>Celcom users have the opportunity to participate in the Hear Forever promotion on Yonder Music and have a chance to win cash prizes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celcom-users-have-the-opportunity-to-participate-in-the-hear-forever-promotion-on-yonder-music-and-have-a-chance-to-win-cash-prizes/</guid><description>Source: Yonder Music. Graphic for the Hear Forever campaign.
Until August 18, 2016, Yonder Music Malaysia is running a promotion, awarding RM500 daily to the Celcom subscriber who uses the Yonder Music app most actively. The user with the highest daily engagement wins the cash prize.
Daphne Lourdes, Yonder Music’s Country Manager for Malaysia, stated that Yonder Music consistently seeks new ways to interact with users and provide them with constant access to all their favorite music.</description></item><item><title>Singtel introduces Malaysia's tonton to its CAST app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 16:54:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-malaysia-s-tonton-to-its-cast-app/</guid><description>Singtel has added Media Prima&amp;rsquo;s tonton, a popular Malaysian streaming platform, to its CAST video streaming app. This partnership, along with existing offerings on Singtel TV, makes Singtel a leading provider of Malay entertainment content in Singapore.
This is the first time tonton is available outside of Malaysia. Through CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus pack, subscribers will have access to over 23,000 hours of Malay entertainment, including content from TV3, TV9, and tonton originals.</description></item><item><title>The Aneka Plus pack on Singtel CAST now features Tribe from Astro</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 14:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-aneka-plus-pack-on-singtel-cast-now-features-tribe-from-astro/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The show &amp;ldquo;Qadr&amp;rdquo; from Tribe is now available through CAST.
Singtel&amp;rsquo;s CAST platform now includes Tribe, a regional video service by Astro. Showcasing content from Astro&amp;rsquo;s Malay channels, like Astro Ria and Astro Prima, Tribe will be part of CAST&amp;rsquo;s Aneka Plus package.
For the first time in Singapore, viewers can access Astro&amp;rsquo;s premium on-demand Malay programs anywhere. Tribe offers complete seasons of drama series, variety shows, movies, and award shows.</description></item><item><title>Singtel Music is excited to announce the addition of TIDAL to its portfolio</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-music-is-excited-to-announce-the-addition-of-tidal-to-its-portfolio/</guid><description>Singtel Music now offers its customers access to the global music and entertainment platform, TIDAL.
TIDAL differentiates itself as the sole music app providing high-fidelity, lossless audio quality and exclusive content from top global artists. Singtel Music users can enjoy both TIDAL Premium and TIDAL HIFI without impacting their data plans.
Diana Chen, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s VP of Mobile Marketing, Consumer Singapore, expressed the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to expanding its music streaming options. Following the addition of Saavn in October, TIDAL further solidifies Singtel Music&amp;rsquo;s goal of providing the best music streaming experience with diverse content, attractive pricing, and no data charges.</description></item><item><title>Spotify users in Singapore have collectively spent 11.4 billion minutes on the platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:27:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-users-in-singapore-have-collectively-spent-11-4-billion-minutes-on-the-platform/</guid><description>Forty percent of Singaporeans with Internet access use Spotify for their streaming needs.
The music streaming service is celebrating its third successful year in Singapore. Since its launch, Spotify has become a favorite way for Singaporeans to enjoy music, according to Sunita Kaur, Spotify Asia&amp;rsquo;s Managing Director. She believes that Spotify is the ideal music streaming service for Singapore, offering the best local and international music and features.
Since Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Singapore launch, users have spent 11.</description></item><item><title>Exclusive Global Jay Chou content available on Spotify from December 16th to 18th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 09:28:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exclusive-global-jay-chou-content-available-on-spotify-from-december-16th-to-18th/</guid><description>Source: Spotify website.
Music streaming platform, Spotify, released Asian pop star Jay Chou&amp;rsquo;s latest single, &amp;ldquo;What Kind of Man are You?&amp;rdquo; today.
Spotify is offering fans an early preview of one of the year&amp;rsquo;s most anticipated albums, with the release of Jay Chou&amp;rsquo;s latest album, &amp;ldquo;Aiyo, Not Bad,&amp;rdquo; planned for December 26th, days before its official release.
Recently ranked the most streamed Asian artist on Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Year in Music charts, Jay Chou is celebrating his return to the pop charts with this new album after a two-year hiatus.</description></item><item><title>Prioritizing mobile can lead to success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 03:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prioritizing-mobile-can-lead-to-success/</guid><description>Source: Spotify. Kaur.
Spotify&amp;rsquo;s Asian launch prioritized mobile support, recognizing the region&amp;rsquo;s growing mobile-centric market, according to Sunita Kaur, Managing Director, Asia, Spotify, speaking at CommunicAsia2015.
This mobile-first, freemium approach has significantly expanded Spotify&amp;rsquo;s user base, leading to a surge in premium subscribers with an average conversion rate of approximately 20%, Kaur explained.
&amp;ldquo;We are fully committed to the freemium mobile model,&amp;rdquo; Kaur stated. &amp;ldquo;We share the music labels&amp;rsquo; view that subscribers are vital to revitalizing the industry.</description></item></channel></rss>