<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Connection Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connection-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Connection Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/connection-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dual Core, Quad Core, Up to 64 Core Managed Dedicated Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</guid><description>The race for faster processors has shifted its focus. Instead of increasing clock speeds, the industry is now prioritizing multi-core and multi-processor designs to improve performance.
The good news is that there are affordable options for powerful processing, including managed dedicated servers with excellent support.
Entry-level systems typically feature dual-core processors. For increased power, users can opt for quad-core or hexa-core (6 cores) configurations. For even greater performance, dual or quad-processor dedicated servers are available.</description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e.</description></item></channel></rss>