<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Devices on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-devices/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Devices on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-devices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Solstice Before The Solstice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solstice-before-the-solstice/</guid><description>You don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait for the winter solstice to experience the Samsung Solstice, a touchscreen phone designed for social networking. This sleek phone boasts a vibrant 3-inch color touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable app widgets for easy access to platforms like Facebook and MySpace.
Staying connected is effortless with the Solstice&amp;rsquo;s virtual keyboard and high-resolution screen, perfect for messaging. Its slim, half-inch profile, achieved through advanced virtual technology, surpasses bulkier models with slide-out keyboards.</description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system.</description></item><item><title>Will a Refurbished Smartphone Meet Your Needs?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-a-refurbished-smartphone-meet-your-needs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-a-refurbished-smartphone-meet-your-needs/</guid><description>Placing your phone on top of your car alongside your coffee is never advisable. Distractions happen, like thinking about a meeting, and before you know it, you&amp;rsquo;ve driven off, leaving your belongings behind. The sound of your phone hitting the pavement as it falls off the car might be audible or not. Meanwhile, your coffee has stained your car window. Losing your phone is a financial headache.
Why? Because now you&amp;rsquo;re paying for an expensive service plan with no device to use it.</description></item><item><title>Laptop Too Big? Try a Tablet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 18:33:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/laptop-too-big-try-a-tablet/</guid><description>Carrying a laptop everywhere would be great if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t so heavy and cumbersome. While internet-enabled phones address the size issue, their small buttons and screens can be limiting. Ideally, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground—something portable yet equipped for easy internet browsing. This is where internet media tablets come in.
The Archos 7, for example, is a top-tier ultra-mobile computer resembling a larger iPhone, with a 7-inch touchscreen offering an 800x480 pixel resolution.</description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker.</description></item></channel></rss>