<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Association Agreements on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/association-agreements/</link><description>Recent content in Association Agreements on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:37:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/association-agreements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Claimants of benefits who are not part of the European Union and the impact on the European Union's relationship with Switzerland.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 05:37:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/claimants-of-benefits-who-are-not-part-of-the-european-union-and-the-impact-on-the-european-union-s-relationship-with-switzerland/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While it&amp;rsquo;s unlikely to grab sensationalist headlines, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling on social security rules for Swiss citizens raises important questions about extending such rules to non-EU countries and the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Switzerland.
Background
This ruling marks the second instance where the UK has challenged the legal basis of Council Decisions concerning the extension of revised EU social security coordination rules to specific non-EU countries.</description></item><item><title>What potential issues could arise with the EU, Turkey, and the Refugee Crisis?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 06:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-potential-issues-could-arise-with-the-eu-turkey-and-the-refugee-crisis/</guid><description>Steve Peers* and Emanuela Roman, University of Palermo and Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam**
*Emanuela Roman wrote the sections on ‘safe third country’, ‘super-safe third country’ and ‘first country of asylum’. Steve Peers wrote the rest of the main text and the annexes.
Turkey plays a pivotal role in the EU&amp;rsquo;s current refugee crisis, hosting over two million Syrian refugees and serving as a transit point for many asylum seekers. A growing number of these individuals travel from Turkey to the Greek islands, contributing to a notable increase in asylum seekers within the EU in recent times.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice resolves the issue of posting third-country workers within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Amedeo Arena, Assistant Professor of European Law - University of Naples &amp;ldquo;Federico II&amp;rdquo; School of Law
Judgment of the court (Second Chamber) of 11 September 2014, Essent Energie Productie BV v. Minister van SocialeZaken en Werkgelegenheid, Case C-91/13.
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) has consistently maintained that, in contrast to workers from EU Member States, Turkish nationals do not possess the right to freedom of movement within the European Union.</description></item></channel></rss>