<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Day on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/day/</link><description>Recent content in Day on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Butchers Club Burger offers National Day dishes in celebration of Singapore's 51st anniversary</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 01:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-butchers-club-burger-offers-national-day-dishes-in-celebration-of-singapore-s-51st-anniversary/</guid><description>The Butchers Club Burger in Singapore is launching a special menu item for National Day: The Little Red Dot Burger.
Starting July 29th and lasting for two weekends, The Little Red Dot Burger will be featured as part of a National Day Set Menu at The Butchers Club Burger Singapore. This marks the restaurant&amp;rsquo;s first National Day celebration in Singapore, and the burger itself is a tribute to a beloved local dish: satay ayam (chicken satay).</description></item><item><title>Celebrate National Day with Amara Sanctuary Singapore's special promotion!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 07:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/celebrate-national-day-with-amara-sanctuary-singapore-s-special-promotion/</guid><description>Source: Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa. Singapore laksa.
To commemorate Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 53rd birthday, the 5-star Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa is offering a National Day special at their Shutters restaurant.
During this National Day celebration, Shutters&amp;rsquo; dinner guests will enjoy a discounted Singapura buffet, priced at S$53++ per adult, down from the usual S$75++. This offer is valid from 6:30 pm to 10:00 pm. The buffet features local favorites like Nyonya laksa, barbequed stingray, and charcoal-grilled satay.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor has discovered that India and China have lower-than-average per capita calorie purchases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</guid><description>A new study by Euromonitor International reveals how many nutrients people consume daily from packaged foods and beverages. This data, found in their Passport: Nutrition database, tracks the consumption of calories, fats, saturated fats, carbohydrates, sugars, salt, protein, and fiber across 54 countries.
Globally, we buy enough packaged food and soft drinks to consume 1.5 trillion calories per day, averaging 765 calories per person. While a healthy daily intake is around 2,000 calories, North America and Western Europe exceed 1,500 calories, contrasting with India&amp;rsquo;s 150 and China&amp;rsquo;s 510.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race.</description></item><item><title>The Global Day of Discovery at Renaissance Hotels worldwide is celebrated on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Renaissance Hotels is hosting its third annual Global Day of Discovery on June 26th at over 150 locations. On this day, almost every hotel will offer guests and community members the opportunity to explore something new. These events, designed by hotel Navigators, include musical performances, culinary experiences, art displays, cultural activities, and unique local excursions.
This day marks the start of the Renaissance Hotels&amp;rsquo; Summer of Discovery calendar, a summer-long series of exclusive events at all 157 hotels worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Solarwinds is advocating for the recognition of IT personnel on September 15th as IT Professionals Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/solarwinds-is-advocating-for-the-recognition-of-it-personnel-on-september-15th-as-it-professionals-day/</guid><description>SolarWinds, a company that provides software for managing hybrid IT infrastructures, has declared the third Tuesday of September (starting on September 15, 2015) as IT Professionals Day. This day is meant to show appreciation for IT professionals, recognizing their often-unsung contributions to modern businesses.
To mark IT Professionals Day, SolarWinds published the findings of their IT Pro Value Survey. This research highlights the significant contributions of Singaporean IT professionals. It examines how much end-users value IT departments and explores how valued IT professionals feel within their organizations.</description></item></channel></rss>