<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Copper Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/copper-line/</link><description>Recent content in Copper Line on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/copper-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Wireless Is The New Copper… But Not The New Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 09:21:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A couple of weeks ago, a portion of the world experienced a communication blackout. This disruption wasn&amp;rsquo;t caused by governments or hackers, but by a powerful typhoon named Haiyan, which devastated the Philippines, resulting in thousands of casualties, millions displaced, and communication infrastructure crippled.
Natural disasters often obliterate infrastructure, including buildings, roads, radio towers, power lines, and telephone wires. Rebuilding these systems, which took years to develop, is a long and arduous process...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-wireless-is-the-new-copper-but-not-the-new-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>