<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>World Edition on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world-edition/</link><description>Recent content in World Edition on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/world-edition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BlackBerry 8830 is World Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</guid><description>Verizon Wireless has engineered a BlackBerry that functions domestically and internationally. This is notable because Verizon uses the CDMA network in the US, while the rest of the world primarily uses GSM.
Previously, this difference prevented Verizon phones from roaming internationally. To solve this, Verizon created a device with both CDMA and GSM capabilities. In the US, the CDMA component accesses the 800 and 1900 MHz bands, including EV-DO broadband. Outside the US, the GSM component accesses the 900 and 1800 MHz bands, including GPRS broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your BlackBerry 8830 Before President Obama</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</guid><description>President Obama famously missed his BlackBerry 8830 after prioritizing security during his initial days in office. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s news that he might be reunited with his BlackBerry, equipped with specialized software for secure communication. You, however, can enjoy the RIM BlackBerry 8830 World Edition right away, even without the special government features. This standard model caters to both personal and business needs.
The BlackBerry 8830 World Edition eliminates the need for separate phones for domestic and international use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-blackberry-8830-before-president-obama/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>