<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nigel Farage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nigel-farage/</link><description>Recent content in Nigel Farage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nigel-farage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is Nigel Farage's claim that the EU's asylum policies will allow in half a million terrorists accurate?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-nigel-farage-s-claim-that-the-eu-s-asylum-policies-will-allow-in-half-a-million-terrorists-accurate/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, the UK Independence Party leader, recently asserted that the European Union&amp;rsquo;s response to the migrant crisis could unintentionally allow a large number of terrorists into the EU. He bases this on the threat by ISIS to use smuggling routes to infiltrate the EU and urges David Cameron to block the EU&amp;rsquo;s plans.
These claims lack merit. The EU&amp;rsquo;s approach essentially maintains the existing situation. The current maritime surveillance efforts, while being expanded, may not become full-scale rescue missions.</description></item><item><title>Is it against EU law to tolerate discrimination against women who are breastfeeding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, leader of the UK Independence Party, recently expressed that while he personally had no issue with public breastfeeding, businesses should set their own rules. He suggested businesses could ask breastfeeding women to move to a less conspicuous area, implying a discreet approach would be preferable.
His statement was prompted by incidents where a restaurant asked a woman to cover her baby while breastfeeding and another establishment suggested using the disabled restroom for this purpose.</description></item></channel></rss>