<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Gift on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gift/</link><description>Recent content in Gift on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HKTDC fairs for gifts, premiums, printing, and packaging draw in more than 60,000 buyers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:17:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hktdc-fairs-for-gifts-premiums-printing-and-packaging-draw-in-more-than-60-000-buyers/</guid><description>Source: HKTDC.
The 31st edition of the Hong Kong Gifts &amp;amp; Premium Fair and the 11th Hong Kong International Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair drew over 60,000 attendees from 134 countries and regions, according to the Hong Kong Trade Development Council (HKTDC). The Gifts Fair welcomed approximately 50,000 visitors, while the Printing &amp;amp; Packaging Fair saw over 14,000 attendees. Notably, there was increased participation from mainland China, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia.</description></item><item><title>2018 Singapore Last-Minute Christmas Gift Guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2018-singapore-last-minute-christmas-gift-guide/</guid><description>As the year comes to a close, many are preparing for holiday festivities. If you&amp;rsquo;re still searching for the perfect gifts or party essentials, look no further!
Party Accessories Creative Home Genuine Marble Stone, S$55.20
Source: Amazon. Creative home genuine marble stone.
This stylish marble disc serves as a sophisticated base for cheese platters, keeping your appetizers cool and visually appealing.
Source: Amazon. Nutcracker napkins.
Michel Design Works Paper Luncheon Napkin, Nutcracker, S$11.</description></item><item><title>Luxury Gift Guide for Christmas 2017 in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:46:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Hong Kong offers a plethora of high-end gift options. Make a lasting impression with these distinctive incentive or corporate gift suggestions:
For the Fashionable
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjTOBGQGtqMhlt_i0m3XHwBn1QjO906znU9xMy97VBPqWBHVy80nBxjOKm1Lgg1I_v5sIp6sxy7HGCTZRC2xSpXTAGFdVOIKDSwZQes3MFguk5NpzGOVFh1lp4vHGEYKbE_CzRPC6l2PblW/s1600/chandelier+earrings.JPG)
Source: The 5th C. My 5-Ways chandelier earrings.
The 5th C, a Hong Kong-based diamond consultancy and jewelry brand, presents My 5-Ways, a completely customizable pair of diamond earrings. At their core, My 5-Ways are elegant stud earrings. However, with a few simple adjustments, they transform into studs with drops, elegant dangle earrings, or eye-catching chandelier earrings.</description></item><item><title>The amount of money given as gifts for Chinese New Year in 2017 was calculated</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 08:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-amount-of-money-given-as-gifts-for-chinese-new-year-in-2017-was-calculated/</guid><description>Source: Gift Something blog post. Survey results for monetary gifts during Chinese New Year in Hong Kong. Values are in Hong Kong dollars.
Gift Something, a Hong Kong-based online retailer specializing in premium gifts, conducted a survey to understand the practice of giving red envelopes (known as angpow or red packets in Singapore, and lai see or red pockets in Hong Kong) during Chinese New Year. Traditionally, married couples give these envelopes to unmarried individuals during the first 15 days of the Lunar New Year to bring luck.</description></item><item><title>Starbucks Singapore is launching a special, limited edition alice + olivia design collection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-singapore-is-launching-a-special-limited-edition-alice-olivia-design-collection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 13:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-singapore-is-launching-a-special-limited-edition-alice-olivia-design-collection/</guid><description>Starting January 31, 2015, Starbucks Singapore is offering a limited-edition collection of merchandise designed by Stacey Bendet, the CEO and Creative Director of alice + olivia.
The collection incorporates the brand&amp;rsquo;s signature black-and-white color scheme and the famous ‘Stace Face’ logo, bringing a playful and whimsical touch to Starbucks merchandise. This special collection, which includes a ‘Stace Face’ mug, a reusable designer tote bag, and an alice + olivia Starbucks Rewards Card, is available at the Starbucks ION Orchard location.</description></item><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero.</description></item><item><title>During the festive season, you can find exclusive Ferrero Rocher pralines at Pasticceria Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>Celebrities Qi Yu Wu and Joanne Peh are pictured at the event.
Ferrero Rocher has opened its first Southeast Asia store, Pasticceria Ferrero, at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Wisma Atria on Orchard Road. This unique boutique is the only one in the world and will be open for the holiday season.
A sneak peek before the official opening.
The shop offers a unique experience, allowing customers to personalize chocolate boxes with limited-edition Ferrero pralines available only during this special time of year.</description></item><item><title>Come to Singapore Gifts Show 2015 for a wide selection of corporate gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</guid><description>The upcoming Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015 is the ideal event to discover this year&amp;rsquo;s corporate gift trends. Taking place from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, Halls 401 to 403, this international trade event offers free admission. It showcases innovative gifts, premiums, and lifestyle products and services, catering to trade buyers and corporate attendees.
Celebrating its 10th anniversary, SGS 2015 will host 160 booths featuring exhibitors from the Philippines, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Choose Knots &amp; Gifts for your online gifting needs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-knots-gifts-for-your-online-gifting-needs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:09:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/choose-knots-gifts-for-your-online-gifting-needs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Knots &amp;amp; Gifts is a newly established online platform offering a curated selection of gifts, including fresh pastries, cakes, and breads from Singapore&amp;rsquo;s best bakeries. The platform also features beverages crafted by mixologist Michael Chen, along with home spa services, flowers, and scents.
Source: Knots &amp;amp; Gifts. The Mini Tea Party Set, S$78. To order, choose Munchies from the menu at the top.
Singaporean entrepreneur Rubina Tiyu created this personalized service after adapting her wedding planning business, Inside the Knot, to the e-commerce landscape during the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>Signature Market offers Chinese New Year corporate gifts for Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signature-market-offers-chinese-new-year-corporate-gifts-for-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/signature-market-offers-chinese-new-year-corporate-gifts-for-malaysia/</guid><description>Signature Market is offering corporate gift bundles for the Lunar New Year, starting from RM30, with a focus on wellness.
The &amp;ldquo;Chinese New Year 2023 Collection&amp;rdquo; features festive packaging adorned with lucky symbols like the number eight, pistachio nuts, mandarin oranges, and spring flowers. Special edition sets come in an exclusive festive box sleeve. Signature Market can advise companies on creating gift packages and offers bulk discounts. They provide over 700 product options and custom packaging solutions.</description></item><item><title>2020 Christmas Gift Guide: Must-Have Gadgets for the Holiday Season</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-christmas-gift-guide-must-have-gadgets-for-the-holiday-season/</guid><description>As the year ends, it&amp;rsquo;s the perfect time to treat yourself. Check out these gadgets for relaxation and maybe even work:
OPPO Find X2 Pro smartphone
The OPPO Find X2 Pro blends technology and elegant design. Marketed as &amp;ldquo;a cinema in your hand,&amp;rdquo; it boasts a 120 Hz QHD+ Ultra Vision screen with exceptional resolution, color, refresh rate, and brightness. Enjoy immersive audio and video with its powerful dual speakers and Dolby Atmos.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Gadget Gift Guide for Christmas 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 22:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-gadget-gift-guide-for-christmas-2017/</guid><description>As 2017 comes to a close, treat yourself to a range of exciting new gadgets! WorkSmart Asia presents its top picks for this year, featuring:
Limited Edition Star Wars Shavers Source: Philips Singapore. Philips limited edition shavers, inspired by Star Wars. From left: the Poe Dameron-inspired Philips _Star Wars _Shaver SW6700/14; the BB-8-inspired SW5700/07 and the Stormtrooper-inspired SW170/04.
Philips introduces a new line of limited-edition shavers inspired by iconic Star Wars characters.</description></item><item><title>Watsons stores in Singapore are offering a variety of Christmas gift sets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:21:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/watsons-stores-in-singapore-are-offering-a-variety-of-christmas-gift-sets/</guid><description>Watsons Singapore offers a variety of boxed Christmas gift sets, ideal for office Secret Santa gift exchanges. These sets include toiletries, travel accessories, and even a coffee mug.
](https://blogger.googleusercontent.com/img/b/R29vZ2xl/AVvXsEjuFQqRo_4KdJEEAt15qa83slFSXiCLkOhVqNapfI1b4jkE6ukFQPhs1wRGbVAowuWpJ4UwAN_fCdEHchVu3DPtpFMtEedEO6vXFbR06xUcMG0stNQ2hbT_c0NaucfCCoJVqEoT4RiWifek/s1600/watsons+spaa+reviving+collection.JPG)
Source: Watsons. The Spaa Reviving Collection.
The Spaa Reviving Collection (S$15.90) allows you to create a spa experience at home. It includes aloe vera extract and pro vitamin B5 to calm both your senses and skin. The set contains a 150ml body wash, 100ml body lotion, 100ml body scrub, 50g bath fizzer, and a body puff.</description></item><item><title>There is a growing trend of adults purchasing toys and games</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:23:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-is-a-growing-trend-of-adults-purchasing-toys-and-games/</guid><description>In 2016, games and puzzles experienced an 8% surge in the global market, surpassing construction toys as the fastest-growing toy category, according to Euromonitor International, a global market research firm. This impressive growth also marks the highest for the category since 2002.
Although construction toys saw a growth of 7.8% in 2016, a dip compared to the double-digit growth of 2015, they still dominated the traditional toys and games market with a value of US$10 billion.</description></item><item><title>In India, Swarn Amrit produces sweets made with edible gold</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 02:28:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-india-swarn-amrit-produces-sweets-made-with-edible-gold/</guid><description>Swarn Amrit, a high-end confectionery brand, has introduced a first-of-its-kind product line in India: sweets made with real 24-karat gold. The company believes that gold symbolizes purity, prosperity, and good fortune, and even suggests it may promote longevity.
Swarn Kalash
The new collection features a variety of sweets with names like kalash, mukhi, madhu, yukti, and katak, representing both Indian and international flavors. For example, Swarn Mukhi layers cashews, almonds, pistachios, and gold, while Swarn Madhu combines Belgian chocolate with gold, and Swarn Katak adds a touch of gold to Turkish delight.</description></item><item><title>Support World Vision in the Philippines by using the Gift It app to make a contribution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 10:53:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/support-world-vision-in-the-philippines-by-using-the-gift-it-app-to-make-a-contribution/</guid><description>World Vision, a charitable organization, has teamed up with Gift It, a crowdgifting platform. Gift It allows users to create personalized campaigns to fund gifts from various stores or support charitable causes through foundation partners.
Jun Godornes, World Vision&amp;rsquo;s Director for National Resources and Development, highlights the app&amp;rsquo;s convenience, stating it simplifies giving while raising awareness for their programs that support children through education, disaster relief, and economic development. Gift It also features a social aspect, enabling friends to contribute collaboratively.</description></item><item><title>Haldiram's is promoting mithai in India that is free from adulteration at SwaadMarket</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 04:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/haldiram-s-is-promoting-mithai-in-india-that-is-free-from-adulteration-at-swaadmarket/</guid><description>Source: SwaadMarket.com website.
Haldiram&amp;rsquo;s, a leading brand in the Indian sweets market, is now available on SwaadMarket.com. SwaadMarket is an Indian online marketplace that guarantees authentic, hygienic, and pure sweets and other food products. Giving Indian sweets (mithai) as gifts is a long-standing tradition, but recently the mithai market has declined due to a lack of new ideas and concerns about hygiene and purity. This trend inspired both companies to start promoting unadulterated sweets within India.</description></item><item><title>Giftano improves the experience of giving gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/giftano-improves-the-experience-of-giving-gifts/</guid><description>Giftano, a Singapore-based online gifting platform, has expanded its offerings to include a complete online gifting solution. In addition to their existing digital gift card selection, Giftano now features &amp;ldquo;Giftano Gifts,&amp;rdquo; a curated marketplace for physical presents.
Giftano aims to provide a seamless and personalized online gifting experience, especially with the holiday season approaching. The company has improved its platform by adding a user-friendly search engine and features that allow for custom gift cards and various delivery choices.</description></item><item><title>Australian businesses have the option to utilize uChoose for their corporate rewards program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-businesses-have-the-option-to-utilize-uchoose-for-their-corporate-rewards-program/</guid><description>Source: uChoose website.
i2c, a company providing card processing and new financial service solutions, partnered with Corporate Prepaid Solutions (CPS), a prepaid program manager, to launch the first of several corporate prepaid programs. This launch features the uChoose corporate rewards gift card in Australia.
The uChoose card, enabled by i2c&amp;rsquo;s global processing platform, is a ready-made solution for companies wanting to provide a Visa-branded gift card. Businesses can personalize the card to match their branding.</description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts.</description></item></channel></rss>