<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Agencies on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/agencies/</link><description>Recent content in Agencies on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/agencies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Europol's Joint and Several Liability Regime Transforming Responsibility for EU Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 03:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Dr Joyce de Coninck, University of Ghent
Photo credit: Oseveno Introduction The Europol Regulation introduces a shared responsibility framework for the EU concerning unlawful data processing that violates Articles 7 and 8 of the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This developing system of liability is at the center of the Marián Kočner v Europol case, highlighting the need for clarity regarding joint responsibility for human rights violations when EU agencies and Member States collaborate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beware of the Accountability Gap in the EU's Financial Supervisory Authorities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</guid><description>Dr Marios Costa, Lecturer in Law, City Law School
The year 2010 saw the creation of three European Supervisory Authorities: the European Banking Authority, the European Insurance and Occupational Pensions Authority, and the European Securities and Markets Authority (ESMA). These authorities were established by the European Union in response to the then-unprecedented financial crisis. On January 22, 2014, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued a significant judgment (Case C-270/12, United Kingdom v Council &amp;amp; Parliament) concerning recent legislation granting ESMA the authority to impose legally binding measures on financial institutions in Member States when the proper functioning of financial markets or the stability of the EU financial system is threatened...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beware-of-the-accountability-gap-in-the-eu-s-financial-supervisory-authorities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling in Case C-632/20 P Spain v Commission (Kosovo) on Third Parties, Nations, and Other Entities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
Photo credit: Aljabakphoto, via Wikimedia commons - Šar Mountains National Park in Dragaš, Kosovo
On January 17th, 2023, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in Case C-632/20 P, Spain v Commission (Kosovo), deciding that Kosovo can participate in the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications (BEREC). This decision, reached despite the EU&amp;rsquo;s non-recognition of Kosovo as a state, clarifies that &amp;ldquo;third country&amp;rdquo; status, as defined by the EU, can include territories not recognized as sovereign states and that these entities are eligible for participation in EU agencies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Introducing the European Labour Authority: A New EU Agency Based in Bratislava</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 13:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</guid><description>Bartłomiej Bednarowicz, PhD Researcher at the Faculty of Law of the University of Antwerp
Background
Bratislava was chosen by the Council to host the headquarters of the newly established European Labour Authority (ELA). Initially proposed by President Juncker in 2017, the ELA&amp;rsquo;s primary goal is to simplify and enhance the fairness of EU labor mobility within the internal market. This initiative stemmed from the European Pillar of Social Rights (EPSR) and was introduced alongside other measures aimed at promoting social fairness within the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/introducing-the-european-labour-authority-a-new-eu-agency-based-in-bratislava/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Union Migration Agencies: Frontex, EASO, and Europol's Operations and Collaborations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</guid><description>Dr. David Fernández-Rojo, Universidad de Deusto - davidfrojo@deusto.es
The recent surge in migration, often called the “refugee crisis,” highlighted the urgent need to strengthen both the Schengen area and the Common European Asylum System (CEAS). It also underscored the need to support EU member states dealing with large numbers of migrants and to consistently apply EU policies on migration, asylum, and border control. EU agencies such as Frontex, EASO, and Europol have become central to these efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do Member States have the authority to make decisions that are above the law? Is it possible to challenge Member States' decisions regarding the locations of EU agencies?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-member-states-have-the-authority-to-make-decisions-that-are-above-the-law-is-it-possible-to-challenge-member-states-decisions-regarding-the-locations-of-eu-agencies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 12:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-member-states-have-the-authority-to-make-decisions-that-are-above-the-law-is-it-possible-to-challenge-member-states-decisions-regarding-the-locations-of-eu-agencies/</guid><description>Ezio Perillo, formerly a judge on the EU General Court and the EU civil service tribunal, argues that decisions made by EU Member States regarding the locations of European agencies may not be subject to judicial review by the EU Court. This is based on the Sharpston-Council orders (cases C-684/20P and C-685/20P), which deemed the former British Advocate General’s challenge against a new AG appointment inadmissible, and Advocate General Bobek&amp;rsquo;s opinion in joined cases concerning the European Medicines Agency (EMA) and the European Labour Authority (ELA) (cases C-59/18, C-182/18, and C-743/19, and in a parallel opinion in Cases C-106/19 and 232/19)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-member-states-have-the-authority-to-make-decisions-that-are-above-the-law-is-it-possible-to-challenge-member-states-decisions-regarding-the-locations-of-eu-agencies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-member-states-have-the-authority-to-make-decisions-that-are-above-the-law-is-it-possible-to-challenge-member-states-decisions-regarding-the-locations-of-eu-agencies/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>