<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bandwidth Connections on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-connections/</link><description>Recent content in Bandwidth Connections on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/bandwidth-connections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cheaper Connections To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-connections-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Businesses are often quick to celebrate the cost savings of cloud services compared to maintaining their own data centers. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a hidden cost that often catches them off guard: cloud connectivity.
The current cost of bandwidth depends on a company&amp;rsquo;s blend of LAN, MAN, and WAN traffic. Businesses with data centers located in the same building as their employees usually find most of their application traffic stays on the LAN.</description></item><item><title>Copper Bandwidth Connections Push 1 Gbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 12:16:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-bandwidth-connections-push-1-gbps/</guid><description>It seems impossible, but engineers continue to find ways to squeeze more speed out of traditional copper telephone lines, proving we haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limit yet. Imagine 1 Gbps speeds on copper lines for businesses!
While this technology isn&amp;rsquo;t widespread yet, it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly approaching. Huawei, a Chinese company specializing in networking and telecommunications, has developed a prototype Giga DSL system capable of delivering a combined speed of 1 Gbps within 100 meters of a remote terminal (RT) cabinet.</description></item><item><title>Why The Smart WAN Beats A Dumb Pipe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) are traditionally built using &amp;ldquo;dumb pipes,&amp;rdquo; which are simple bandwidth connections between two points. These connections are efficient at their primary function: transferring data packets. However, as IT requirements become more complex, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing need for more intelligent solutions. This can be achieved by either enhancing your internal IT capabilities or outsourcing these needs as a service.
Level 3 Communications, a leading provider of fiber network services, recognizes this shift from basic to high-performance networking demands.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Computing Appropriate For Small Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-computing-appropriate-for-small-business/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming extremely popular with medium and large businesses, with many moving from local data centers to cloud-based services. Smaller companies may be unsure if cloud computing is right for them or if it&amp;rsquo;s too much for their needs.
Actually, cloud computing might be even more beneficial for smaller businesses. Large corporations have large budgets that support extensive IT departments and on-site data centers, believing that managing everything internally results in lower costs, better security, and faster response times.</description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities.</description></item></channel></rss>