<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Screen Sharing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/screen-sharing/</link><description>Recent content in Screen Sharing on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:03:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/screen-sharing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Affordable Conference Calls For 1,000 Participants With StartMeeting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/affordable-conference-calls-for-1-000-participants-with-startmeeting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 12:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/affordable-conference-calls-for-1-000-participants-with-startmeeting/</guid><description>Business conference calls, especially those with screen sharing, can lead to significant cost savings compared to in-person meetings. While past conferencing solutions were often limited in participant capacity or became expensive at scale, StartMeeting offers an affordable option worth considering.
StartMeeting&amp;rsquo;s features are designed to enhance productivity and reduce expenses. Audio conferencing is central, with video as a supplementary tool. You can choose from dial-in long distance, toll-free numbers (landline and wireless compatible), or HD VoIP audio via a computer headset.</description></item><item><title>A Map to Unified Communications and Collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-map-to-unified-communications-and-collaboration/</guid><description>Infographic provided by Level 3 Communications
Modern workplaces rely on tools like web conferencing, screen sharing, presence technology, and teleconferencing to enhance employee productivity and knowledge sharing. Unsure if your business is utilizing these tools effectively? Learn more about the latest in Unified Communications and Collaboration solutions from industry leaders like Level 3 Communications.</description></item></channel></rss>