<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>140NTBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/140ntbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 140NTBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/140ntbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the RPM Indicator Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-rpm-indicator-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513), the incandescent bulbs in the RPM indicator panels were replaced with LED-based alternatives. This change aimed to enhance the stability of the DC motor control system by reducing heat generation, a common issue with traditional bulbs.
The new SMD LED circuits, designed for a seamless drop-in replacement, feature red and green LEDs calibrated to mimic the warm glow of incandescent lighting. This spectrum, especially the inclusion of red photons, ensures accurate illumination of the red plastic RPM indicators.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoring the Hood</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:11:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoring-the-hood/</guid><description>Restoring a Beogram often includes restoring its hood, as many have accumulated scratches over time. This particular Beogram 4002 (5513) had deep scratches on its hood.
The restoration started by sanding with 220-grit sandpaper, then progressively moved to finer grits (320-grit shown). This process, which took about 3 hours and involved around 10 polishing steps with Micro-Mesh up to 12000 level, returned the hood to a translucent and shiny condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Oil Infusion of DC Platter Motor Bearings and RPM Test</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 02:10:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-oil-infusion-of-dc-platter-motor-bearings-and-rpm-test/</guid><description>To fully rebuild the platter drive system of a Beogram 4002 DC motor, you must relubricate the motor bearings. Many DC motor Beograms have fluctuating RPMs because the oil in their porous brass bearings (called &amp;ldquo;Oilite&amp;rdquo;) depletes over time. These bearings can be &amp;lsquo;refilled&amp;rsquo; by using a vacuum to remove air and allow oil to replenish the pores. The challenge lies in extracting the bearings without causing damage. I documented this process in a recent video.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Final Adjustments and a Test Drive with Freddie Hubbard's "The Love Connection"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 06:23:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-final-adjustments-and-a-test-drive-with-freddie-hubbards-the-love-connection/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project is finished after some final tuning. I made adjustments to the platter height and sub-chassis alignment, documenting the process for my YouTube channel. While my videos feature a Beogram 4000, the method for adjusting the platter bearing and sub-chassis are quite similar for the 4002 model.
The arm lowering limit was the next step, a crucial adjustment to safeguard the cantilever if the record detection malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Arm Lowering and Tracking Mechanisms, and Installation of a New Carriage Pulley</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:13:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-mechanisms-and-installation-of-a-new-carriage-pulley/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, the arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, often problematic due to hardened lubricants, required attention. While the lowering damper section was functional, the damper-to-arm linkage was stuck and only moved because its pin had loosened.
The restoration process involved carefully disassembling the arm lowering mechanism, cleaning it, and applying fresh lubrication. The seized damper-to-arm linkage was removed, requiring a workbench procedure to press out its stuck pin.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New 3D Printed Transport Lock Bushings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:03:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-3d-printed-transport-lock-bushings/</guid><description>Prior to aligning the platter and sub-chassis, I had to swap out the worn transport lock bushings on the Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently refurbishing. These bushings are crucial for proper sub-chassis alignment. This particular Beogram had the orange type of bushings, which were showing signs of age. The gray bushings tend to hold up better, but these orange ones were beyond their prime. I took apart the transport lock plates, revealing one of the brittle bushings.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): End Groove Detection Not Working</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-end-groove-detection-not-working/</guid><description>Just when I thought I had finished refurbishing a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a problem surfaced during playback. The tonearm wouldn&amp;rsquo;t return after playing a record, instead getting stuck in the end groove, repeating the sound of the run-out.
Investigating further, I used an oscilloscope to examine the signal from the position sensor, which tells the control system the tonearm&amp;rsquo;s location. The signal was weak specifically in the end groove area, often indicating misalignment between the sensor&amp;rsquo;s IR diode and the light entry slit.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs and Restoring the 33 RPM Function</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs-and-restoring-the-33-rpm-function/</guid><description>Typically, my restoration process for Beogram 4002 turntables begins with the arm lowering and tracking systems. However, this particular Beogram 4002 (5513) required a different approach. The control system needed attention, so I opted to address the PCBs first.
Upon unpacking the turntable, I discovered that the platter motor would power on as soon as it was plugged in. This unusual behavior was caused by the seller connecting the motor to the standby LED header on the circuit board – a connection point rarely used on the 5513 boards.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Original Dual Main Capacitor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 02:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-original-dual-main-capacitor/</guid><description>While restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513), I had the chance to improve my design for a replacement part for the reservoir capacitor. This part lets me use two modern, high-temperature Japanese capacitors in place of the original dual-capacitor unit, which is no longer available. My previous design worked, but this new version is more robust and easier to 3D print. I&amp;rsquo;m getting better at designing for 3D printing; for instance, I learned to minimize overhangs.</description></item></channel></rss>