<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Android on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/android/</link><description>Recent content in Android on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/android/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Samsung Galaxy S III Supports Verizon 4G LTE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:47:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</guid><description>The Samsung Galaxy S III for Verizon Wireless is a top-of-the-line smartphone with cutting-edge technology for both features and speed. This model continues the Galaxy series&amp;rsquo; tradition of innovation.
This Android smartphone uses the Google Operating System 4.0 &amp;ldquo;Ice Cream Sandwich&amp;rdquo; and features a 4.8-inch HD Super AMOLED display. With 1280 x 720 pixels, the screen displays sharp, vibrant images and text. The curved design helps prevent scratches, even when the phone is face down...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-galaxy-s-iii-supports-verizon-4g-lte/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China's unicorn company has revealed the top 10 rankings in the Google Play store for its Wi-Fi crowdsourcing app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</guid><description>Source: Play Store.
The free app WiFi Master Key, which helps users find and connect to crowdsourced Wi-Fi hotspots, is gaining popularity in Southeast Asia. It helps people access the internet in a region where connectivity is rapidly expanding.
The app lets users share Wi-Fi hotspot information with the community. While this information allows others to connect for free, the app prioritizes privacy and security by encrypting and storing shared Wi-Fi passwords in its cloud database instead of revealing them directly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-s-unicorn-company-has-revealed-the-top-10-rankings-in-the-google-play-store-for-its-wi-fi-crowdsourcing-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phones become unresponsive due to Android vulnerability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 05:18:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</guid><description>Trend Micro has identified a weakness in the Android operating system that can cause a phone to seem non-functional. Affected phones exhibit symptoms like no ringing or notification sounds, an inability to make calls, and an unresponsive screen. Additionally, locked phones cannot be unlocked.
This vulnerability affects Android versions from 4.3 (Jelly Bean) to 5.1.1 (Lollipop), encompassing over half of all Android devices currently in use. Despite being reported to the Android Engineering Team in late May, no official fix has been released through the Android Open Source Project (AOSP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phones-become-unresponsive-due-to-android-vulnerability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In just minutes, Wondershare can transfer Blackberry data to other phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</guid><description>Switching from a Blackberry to a new phone? Wondershare might be the solution for you. Their updated MobileTrans software (Version 4.1) enables Blackberry users to move their data to other devices. This includes SMS messages, contact lists, call history, and other data.
Source: Wondershare website
Wondershare claims that MobileTrans is the first and only solution that can transfer Blackberry SMS messages to an iPhone.
With this software and a Blackberry desktop backup, users can transfer data without connecting both their old and new phones to a computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-just-minutes-wondershare-can-transfer-blackberry-data-to-other-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG G3s will be the first to receive the Lollipop upgrade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</guid><description>LG Electronics claims to be the first worldwide smartphone maker to launch the Lollipop update in 2014. According to LG, the updated Android operating system, Android 5.0 or &amp;ldquo;Lollipop,&amp;rdquo; will be available for its G3 smartphones starting in Poland the week of November 10, with other major markets following shortly after.
Source: LG.
This newest Android OS offers a variety of enhancements, including enhanced depth, shadows, and animations. With a fresh design and color scheme, notifications have been enhanced and will be visible on the new lock screen...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g3s-will-be-the-first-to-receive-the-lollipop-upgrade/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HandySpeech app, which converts handwriting to speech, is now available on Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</guid><description>iSpeak4U, a company known for developing mobile apps for individuals with speech and hearing impairments, has launched an Android version of their app HandySpeech. This app offers a simple and efficient communication tool for those with speech difficulties.
Source: iSpeak4U. HandySpeech running on various devices.
With HandySpeech, users can input text on a device screen using their finger or a stylus, and the device will then vocalize the written words. The app is designed to store frequently used phrases and adapt to the user&amp;rsquo;s handwriting style...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Send Fax From Email On Your Computer or Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</guid><description>Do you recall fax machines with thermal paper rolls? Those messages had a distinct look and tended to fade. To preserve them, you&amp;rsquo;d copy them onto regular paper using a laser printer, then diligently wash the strange residue off your hands.
Fax technology has significantly evolved. Thermal paper is out, and even traditional fax machines are becoming rare. Cloud-based electronic transmission and storage are the modern alternatives.
Sending and receiving faxes via email is the contemporary approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trend Micro demonstrates ways to enhance the security of Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 14:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</guid><description>In 2014, Android controlled the global smartphone market, shipping one billion units and representing 81% of all smartphones shipped, as reported by Strategy Analytics.
Trend Micro researcher, Paul Oliveria, points out that Android&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its affordability, efficient data storage, and availability across various brands and price points.
This widespread use makes Android a prime target for hackers. To combat this, Trend Micro proposes seven security measures for mobile users:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trend-micro-demonstrates-ways-to-enhance-the-security-of-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smartfren Android users will receive a smart start screen from Celltick</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</guid><description>Source: Android Play Store.
The MySmartfren app.
Celltick, a company that provides mobile marketing solutions, has teamed up with Indonesian telecommunications company Smartfren Telekom (Smartfren) to introduce a smart home screen for Android users.
Smartfren aims to give its 12 million subscribers quick access to their most-used apps and features, along with special deals. This will be achieved through a personalized version of Celltick&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Start&amp;rdquo; app, pre-installed on Smartfren Android devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smartfren-android-users-will-receive-a-smart-start-screen-from-celltick/</a></p></description></item><item><title>360 Security and iQIYI have secured the top positions in the App Annie download rankings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:57:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</guid><description>360 Security, an Android mobile antivirus and performance app, climbed to 6th place on Google Play&amp;rsquo;s download chart, making it the 6th most downloaded app worldwide in July, according to the App Annie Index. This achievement is attributed to increased consumer awareness of mobile security and recent campaigns in Korea and Japan.
360 Security provides users with virus protection, memory optimization, and power-saving features. The App Annie report indicates a global surge in popularity for security apps, including 360 Security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/360-security-and-iqiyi-have-secured-the-top-positions-in-the-app-annie-download-rankings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Mozilla has launched Firefox Focus on Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 06:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</guid><description>Source: Mozilla. Mozilla launches Firefox Focus for Android.
Mozilla, a strong advocate for an open and accessible internet, has released Firefox Focus for Android devices. This launch caters to the increasing number of mobile users seeking enhanced online privacy.
Firefox Focus allows users to browse the internet without being tracked by advertisements, which are infamous for slowing down mobile browsing. This announcement comes six months after the successful iPhone and iPad launch in November...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mozilla-has-launched-firefox-focus-on-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ESET updates Mobile Security app for Android</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:35:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</guid><description>ESET, a company known for its digital security solutions, has launched an improved version of ESET Mobile Security in the Asia Pacific region. This enhanced version, specifically its premium offering, boasts advanced anti-theft features designed to help Android users locate their lost or stolen devices.
[Image of ESET Mobile Security App]
Source: Play Store.
The app&amp;rsquo;s free version provides essential protection, such as comprehensive device scans, scans of downloaded applications, and basic anti-theft functions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eset-updates-mobile-security-app-for-android/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Incredible DROID INCREDIBLE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/</guid><description>Android phones are constantly improving, aiming to surpass the leading Apple iPhone. The newest contender in the Google versus Apple battle is the impressive DROID INCREDIBLE.
This HTC phone, available through Verizon Wireless, runs on the Android 2.1 operating system and offers customization with numerous apps and widgets from the Android marketplace. Its internal features are equally remarkable.
One standout feature is the 8-megapixel digital camera and camcorder, with resolution comparable to standalone digital cameras...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-incredible-droid-incredible/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Doing BACKFLIPs with MOTOBLUR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 10:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</guid><description>Would you do a backflip for your current cell phone? Probably not, but Motorola&amp;rsquo;s BACKFLIP might just change your mind.
This phone&amp;rsquo;s unique feature is its reverse hinge. Unlike most phones where the keyboard is hidden beneath the screen, the BACKFLIP&amp;rsquo;s keyboard is located on the exterior, flipping open to reveal a full-size touchscreen. This design eliminates the need for a smaller internal screen, offering a more spacious keyboard and a high-resolution touchscreen experience comparable to a small computer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doing-backflips-with-motoblur/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fascinated By The Samsung Fascinate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fascinated-by-the-samsung-fascinate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fascinated-by-the-samsung-fascinate/</guid><description>The Samsung Galaxy S series is a highly sought-after line of smartphones, offering a combination of style and advanced technology. The Samsung Fascinate, available through Verizon Wireless, is the newest member of this family.
The Fascinate lives up to its name with a vivid 4-inch Super AMOLED display that&amp;rsquo;s easily viewable indoors and out. Its 1 GHz Hummingbird processor ensures smooth handling of demanding multimedia applications. The phone also boasts a 5-megapixel camera with autofocus and HD video recording capabilities, complemented by a DivX video player and an MP3 music player...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fascinated-by-the-samsung-fascinate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fascinated-by-the-samsung-fascinate/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG G Watch R receives an enhanced connectivity feature through an Android Wear update</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 07:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</guid><description>LG has announced that their first smartwatch, the G Watch R, will now have Wi-Fi capability thanks to the latest Android Wear update. The G Watch R is one of three Android Wear devices from LG.
Source: LG.
Over the next several days, LG&amp;rsquo;s G Watch, G Watch R, and Watch Urbane devices will receive the firmware over-the-air (FOTA) update as it is gradually released globally.
All three LG devices will now support downloadable interactive watch faces from Google Play in addition to the G Watch R&amp;rsquo;s new Wi-Fi capabilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-g-watch-r-receives-an-enhanced-connectivity-feature-through-an-android-wear-update/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Free Learner's Dictionary provides limitless translations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-learner-s-dictionary-provides-limitless-translations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:41:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-learner-s-dictionary-provides-limitless-translations/</guid><description>Dictionary.com&amp;rsquo;s Android app, with over 80 million downloads, now features a free Learner&amp;rsquo;s Dictionary. This addition provides users with comprehensive tools for professional success, from job searching to business meetings.
English, as the dominant language in the business world, is used by approximately 565 million people online. According to a 2012 Harvard Business Review report, a growing number of companies, including major corporations like Airbus and Samsung, have adopted English as their official language...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-learner-s-dictionary-provides-limitless-translations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-free-learner-s-dictionary-provides-limitless-translations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Access PC or Mac applications from iOS and Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 21:20:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</guid><description>Source: Parallels website.
Parallels has launched an updated version of its Parallels Access app for iOS and Android. The app allows for remote access to both PCs and Macs, letting users access files and run applications while on the move.
With Parallels Access, mobile devices can remotely utilize applications, edit documents, and search through files on a connected computer. Users can connect to any computer through a web browser without needing additional plugins or extensions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-pc-or-mac-applications-from-ios-and-android-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Includes Android and iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 00:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</guid><description>Network convergence typically focuses on combining LAN, MAN, and WAN technologies to support various data types like voice and video. This convergence is key to the advantages offered by enterprise VoIP solutions, such as increased productivity and reduced costs. However, there&amp;rsquo;s often a missing link: mobile phones. This is where Fixed Mobile Convergence (FMC) comes in.
Smartphones have become so essential that excluding them from corporate communication systems creates a significant gap...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-includes-android-and-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC has released the Android-powered Nexus 9, with pre-orders starting on October 17th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 13:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/</guid><description>HTC teamed up with Google to create the Nexus 9, the first tablet to launch with Android Lollipop*. This premium tablet is designed for an exceptional user experience.
The Nexus 9 allows for extensive customization and features a suite of secure login functions for enhanced security. Multi-tasking is made easy with this device.
The tablet boasts an 8.9-inch display with a 4:3 aspect ratio, all within a sleek brushed aluminum frame...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-released-the-android-powered-nexus-9-with-pre-orders-starting-on-october-17th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC Aria Social Networking Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to stay connected, forget dogs – get FriendStream! This service lets you interact with friends through Facebook, Twitter, and Flickr, all from the HTC Aria, a cutting-edge Android smartphone.
The Aria boasts a sleek, seamless design crafted from a single piece of black aluminum. It&amp;rsquo;s compact enough for your pocket yet powerful enough for work and play. Its sizable 3.2-inch touchscreen features pinch-to-zoom functionality, automatically adjusting text size for comfortable website browsing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Watch Urbane 2nd edition also functions as a phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG claims its Watch Urbane 2nd Edition is the first Android Wear smartwatch to offer cellular connectivity. The watch will launch globally this month, starting with the US and Korea, followed by other major markets in the coming months.
The LG Watch Urbane 2nd Edition works with both Android and iOS smartphones, giving users the freedom to answer calls and check messages without relying on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The language learning app HelloTalk has reached 1 million downloads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:03:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</guid><description>Source: HelloTalk app page at the Play Store.
The mobile language learning app HelloTalk has reached over one million registered users globally, according to its developer, HelloTalk.
The HelloTalk app allows users to teach each other their native languages using their mobile devices. Users can communicate in real-time with native speakers through various features, helping them practice their target language.
Over one million HelloTalk users, representing over 200 countries, use the app to learn various languages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-language-learning-app-hellotalk-has-reached-1-million-downloads/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google is revealing how it plans to increase your productivity in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Google&amp;rsquo;s annual developer conference, I/O, brought a wave of announcements for Apps, Android, Chromebooks, and the Cloud Platform.
As highlighted on the official Google blog, Android now boasts a staggering one billion users who send an estimated 20 billion text messages and 93 million selfies daily. Key introductions include:
Android Wear
Expanding Android&amp;rsquo;s reach to wearable devices, Android Wear allows users to perform tasks or ask questions simply by saying &amp;ldquo;Ok Google...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>