<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FCC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fcc/</link><description>Recent content in FCC on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fcc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Side of Spectrum Renewal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</guid><description>Half a century ago, the government embraced urban renewal, demolishing and rebuilding deteriorated urban areas for housing projects or highways leading to suburbs. Similarly, today, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing &amp;ldquo;spectrum renewal,&amp;rdquo; where sections of the radio frequency spectrum are deemed too valuable for older technologies like analog TV and cell phone service, despite their widespread use.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by lack of public demand. Millions of analog TV sets and cell phones are still functional.</description></item><item><title>Do You Still Have Broadband?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 07:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-still-have-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet broadband speeds have increased significantly in recent times. While a few Mbps was initially considered sufficient, businesses are now rapidly adopting speeds of 100 Mbps and higher, with the FCC setting a 25 Mbps benchmark for broadband. This shift signifies escalating bandwidth demands driven by the increasing reliance on remote resources and the changing nature of online content.
What Does The New Standard Represent?
The updated broadband standards highlight the growing need for greater bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>E-Rate Discounted Broadband Internet for Schools and Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-discounted-broadband-internet-for-schools-and-libraries/</guid><description>Educational institutions and libraries are demanding high-speed internet, which has become essential for business, personal growth, and various types of learning. While most public resources have some internet access, there is increasing pressure to enhance speed for more users and advanced applications. The main obstacle is the cost.
Discounted Service is Available A government program offers discounts of 20% to 90% on broadband internet upgrades for most K-12 schools and libraries.</description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population.</description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Bill Shock Is So Easy To Avoid</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-bill-shock-is-so-easy-to-avoid/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission is looking into new regulations due to a high volume of complaints regarding unexpected cell phone charges. While this intervention is welcomed by those who have faced this issue, understanding how to avoid such situations is key.
&amp;ldquo;Bill shock&amp;rdquo; refers to the unpleasant surprise of discovering unexpectedly high charges on your cell phone bill, often leaving you in disbelief and frantically searching for errors. While billing mistakes can occur, these charges are typically accurate, stemming from a lack of awareness regarding contract details or exceeding usage limits, often unknowingly.</description></item><item><title>FCC Confiscates Remaining TV Channels For Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:29:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fcc-confiscates-remaining-tv-channels-for-twitter/</guid><description>The Federal Communications Commission (FCC), overwhelmed by the rapidly growing demand for wireless broadband, has seized control of all remaining broadcast television channels. This unexpected move aims to dedicate this valuable spectrum solely to Twitter.
FCC Chairman Lowon B. Andwidth explained that a recent study revealed Twitter&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth will soon consume all available bandwidth. He expressed concern not only for the impact on internet browsing, video streaming, texting, and email, but also for the potential chaos if Twitter users experience posting delays.</description></item></channel></rss>