<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Process on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/process/</link><description>Recent content in Process on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Halos are the key to achieving success in business, according to Cognizant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</guid><description>Cognizant Technology Solutions claims that the most successful businesses are using a new concept called &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; to gain a competitive advantage. This concept revolves around leveraging digital data, such as clicks, swipes, likes, purchases, comments, and searches, to understand individual preferences and behaviors.
Source: Cognizant. Roehrig.
Paul Roehrig, Global Managing Director of Cognizant’s Center for the Future of Work and co-author of Code Halos: How the Digital Lives of People, Things, and Organizations are Changing the Rules of Business, highlights how businesses can utilize this &amp;ldquo;Code Halo&amp;rdquo; thinking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/code-halos-are-the-key-to-achieving-success-in-business-according-to-cognizant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Airswift Holdings, a global recruiting company, operates in 57 locations worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 05:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Airswift Holdings. From left, Duncan Gregson, CEO of Air Energi; Janette Marx, COO, Airswift, Ian Langley, Chairman, Airswift; Peter Searle, CEO, Airswift; and Tobias Reed, CEO of Swift Worldwide Resources.
Air Energi Group and Swift Worldwide Resources combined to establish Airswift Holdings, a global staffing company. Airswift specializes in placing contract and permanent employees, providing resource consultation, assisting with global mobility, and developing managed solutions for companies in the energy, process, and infrastructure sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>