<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smart on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smart/</link><description>Recent content in Smart on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/smart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dubai Chamber has announced the launch of the Dubai Smartpreneur Competition for 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 23:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</guid><description>The Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry, working with the Smart Dubai Office, launched the second annual Dubai Smartpreneur Competition. This aligns with the vision of His Highness Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum, UAE Vice President and Prime Minister, and Ruler of Dubai, to make Dubai a leading smart city.
Source: Dubai Chamber. The event featured a panel discussion about the UAE government&amp;rsquo;s progress on smart city and innovation initiatives, and what will drive future sustainable growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dubai-chamber-has-announced-the-launch-of-the-dubai-smartpreneur-competition-for-2017/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Now, you have the ability to answer calls directly on your Apple Watch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</guid><description>Source: Apple. Apple Watch 3 includes phone capabilities.
Apple has launched the Apple Watch Series 3, a smartwatch with built-in cellular capabilities. With this new feature, users can make and receive calls and texts, and stay connected even when they don&amp;rsquo;t have their iPhone nearby.
This third-generation Apple Watch is designed for health and fitness, offering smart coaching features, water resistance up to 50 meters, and a new barometric altimeter for measuring elevation changes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/now-you-have-the-ability-to-answer-calls-directly-on-your-apple-watch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIM Global Education hosts information sessions on smart city design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:01:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</guid><description>SIM Global Education (SIM GE) is hosting informational meetings with industry experts for individuals interested in their Master in Design for Smart Cities program in Singapore, a collaborative offering with the Strate School of Design from France.
A series of online discussions will be held featuring: urban planning expert Yann Follain on October 2nd, Airbus&amp;rsquo;s Cyrille Schwob on October 24th, sustainable smart cities specialist Pablo Viejo on October 28th, and PSA Peugeot Citroen&amp;rsquo;s Gregory Blokkeel, focusing on smart city mobility, on November 8th...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sim-global-education-hosts-information-sessions-on-smart-city-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai has moved up one position in the Dubai Innovation Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</guid><description>• Dubai&amp;rsquo;s ranking rose to 15th out of 28 global cities in the innovation sector. • HE Buamim: The Index helps pinpoint areas needing improvement and provides suggestions for increased competitiveness.
Source: Dubai Chamber. Buamim.
The Dubai Innovation Index, recently published by the Dubai Chamber of Commerce and Industry during UAE Innovation Week, places Dubai in 15th position.
A study of 28 leading global innovation cities was conducted for the Index by the Chamber in partnership with PricewaterhouseCoopers (PwC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-has-moved-up-one-position-in-the-dubai-innovation-index/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MinuteCast by AccuWeather can be accessed on the Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:44:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</guid><description>AccuWeather, a leading provider of global weather information and digital media, announced today that its hyperlocal weather forecasting tool, AccuWeather MinuteCast, is now available on the new Garmin vivoactive HR smartwatch. MinuteCast was already available on other Garmin devices, such as the Forerunner and fēnix running and training watches.
The Garmin vivoactive HR is a GPS smartwatch with wrist heart rate technology that allows users to track the intensity of their activities, monitor their progress, and keep tabs on their activity throughout the day...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/minutecast-by-accuweather-can-be-accessed-on-the-garmin-vivoactive-hr-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson Singapore has released the new Moverio Pro smart glasses with augmented reality capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</guid><description>Epson, a global provider of projection technology and visual communication tools, has introduced the Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset. This binocular headset offers an augmented reality experience for applications such as inspections, training, and remote field service support for intricate repairs and troubleshooting.
Source: Epson Singapore. The new
Moverio Pro BT-2000 smart headset.
Augmented reality smart glasses have the potential to boost worker efficiency across various sectors, including warehousing, logistics, field service, automotive, manufacturing, construction, and retail...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-singapore-has-released-the-new-moverio-pro-smart-glasses-with-augmented-reality-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The eco-conscious GROHE smart water system is gaining traction in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 06:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: GROHE. The GROHE Blue system in action.
GROHE Blue, a smart water system, has become increasingly popular in Asia since a May 2014 study revealed its smaller carbon footprint compared to bottled mineral water.
The study estimated that the GROHE Blue system generates 17.96 g CO2-eq/liter, significantly less than the 70 to 600 g CO2-eq/liter produced by bottled mineral water. The variation in bottled water emissions is linked to packaging and origin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eco-conscious-grohe-smart-water-system-is-gaining-traction-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Intel Security has released a list of the holiday gifts that are most vulnerable to hacking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</guid><description>· A survey indicates that 80% of shoppers are anticipated to make purchases online this year.
· While 85% of consumers begin utilizing connected devices within a day of obtaining them, a mere 45% report taking the appropriate security precautions.
· Despite acknowledging the significance of device security, nearly half of consumers (46%) are unsure if they are implementing adequate protective measures.
Intel Security has released its second yearly McAfee Most Hackable Holiday Gifts list, aiming to spotlight potential security vulnerabilities linked to popular gift items this holiday season...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/intel-security-has-released-a-list-of-the-holiday-gifts-that-are-most-vulnerable-to-hacking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The BenQ interactive flat panel simplifies education and collaboration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 11:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</guid><description>BenQ, a well-known name in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, introduces the RP750K, a new interactive flat panel (IFP). This innovative IFP offers a comprehensive solution by combining a 4K Ultra HD whiteboard with annotation and collaboration tools.
The RP750K excels in dynamic classroom or corporate training settings. Its Germ-Resistant Screen, infused with a safe and robust nano-ionic silver coating, effectively eliminates most surface germs, reducing cross-infection risks. This antimicrobial protection persists even with regular cleaning and extended use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-benq-interactive-flat-panel-simplifies-education-and-collaboration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides eSIMs for the Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</guid><description>Source: Samsung website. This Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch functions on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE network.
Singtel has launched the Samsung Gear S3 frontier (LTE) on its 4G LTE network. Equipped with an eSIM, this smartwatch offers independent 4G LTE connectivity. This allows users to make and receive calls, send text messages, and browse the internet without needing their smartphones.
Singtel customers will also experience 4G ClearVoice, also known as VoLTE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The implementation of smart technologies is increasing revenues by up to 33%</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</guid><description>A global Avanade study, involving Australian executives, business unit leaders, and IT decision-makers, reveals that a majority of business leaders are already investing in and seeing positive results from incorporating smart technologies in their workplaces. A key motivator is the potential for increased revenue, with business and IT leaders projecting up to a 33% revenue boost from these technologies within the next five years. Furthermore, companies anticipate retraining existing employees, generating new roles, and restructuring their organizations as they predict the repurposing of up to 20% of current roles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-implementation-of-smart-technologies-is-increasing-revenues-by-up-to-33/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The latest Apple watches have the capability to contact someone in case of a fall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</guid><description>Apple has released the Apple Watch Series 4, a redesigned smartwatch focused on connectivity, activity tracking, and health management.
Maintaining its classic look, the fourth iteration boasts a 30% larger screen and a smaller, slimmer casing. This model introduces advanced fitness and communication features with watchOS 5, a new accelerometer and gyroscope for fall detection, and an electrical heart rate sensor that enables electrocardiograms (ECGs) through the new ECG app...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-latest-apple-watches-have-the-capability-to-contact-someone-in-case-of-a-fall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The TomTom Golfer 2 GPS Watch is created to assist golfers in enhancing their game</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 12:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</guid><description>TomTom has introduced the TomTom Golfer 2, a slim GPS watch designed for golfers. The watch uses automatic shot detection to provide detailed analysis after a round, aiming to improve users&amp;rsquo; games.
The TomTom Golfer 2 eliminates uncertainty on the course by measuring distances to greens and hazards. This automatic shot detection helps golfers understand their distance potential by displaying distances for drives and approach shots at a glance. After the game, golfers can analyze their strokes in detail using TomTom MySports...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tomtom-golfer-2-gps-watch-is-created-to-assist-golfers-in-enhancing-their-game/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's nol card set to become more advanced</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 02:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</guid><description>Source: RTA. The nol card.
Introduced in September 2009, the versatile nol card, accepted across various transportation modes, has facilitated 3.4 billion transactions thus far, according to HE Mattar Al Tayer, Director-General and Chairman of the Board of Executive Directors of Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Roads and Transport Authority (RTA).
These transactions encompass a wide range of activities, including passenger entries and exits at metro and tram stations, bus rides, taxi fares, water transit usage, fare payments, and card reloads...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-nol-card-set-to-become-more-advanced/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can use iSend from any location to recharge Smart and Sun mobile accounts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</guid><description>iSend, an international electronic payment platform that helps people financially support family members in other countries, has expanded its services. iSend customers globally can now send mobile phone credits to a combined 73 million subscribers of Smart Communications, Digitel Mobile Philippines (Digitel), and its mobile brand, Sun Cellular (Sun). These companies are all part of the Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), the largest telecommunications company in the Philippines.
Steve LaBella, iSend&amp;rsquo;s President and CEO, emphasized the reliability of this new service, stating that customers can be sure their purchased recharges for Smart and Sun prepaid mobile subscribers will be delivered reliably and with excellent service coordination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-use-isend-from-any-location-to-recharge-smart-and-sun-mobile-accounts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TomTom's latest Spark GPS fitness watches also have the capability to play music</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:28:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</guid><description>Source: TomTom. TomTom has introduced the Spark GPS fitness watch line. These new watches include a 3GB music player, making it simpler for fitness enthusiasts to enhance their workouts by listening to music directly from their wrist.
The TomTom Spark GPS fitness watch can stream music to a variety of Bluetooth headphones. It also includes a preloaded thirty-minute Running Trax curated by Ministry of Sound. Users can easily download playlists to the TomTom Spark from iTunes or Windows Media Player...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tomtom-s-latest-spark-gps-fitness-watches-also-have-the-capability-to-play-music/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Epson introduces the latest Moverio smart glasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</guid><description>Epson has introduced the third generation of its Moverio smart glasses, designed for augmented reality applications. The Moverio BT-300 utilizes Epson&amp;rsquo;s innovative silicon-based OLED display technology, providing a truly transparent mobile augmented reality (AR) experience for both businesses and consumers.
Epson highlights the Moverio BT-300 as the lightest binocular see-through smart glasses available, boasting a weight reduction of over 20% compared to its predecessor, the Moverio BT-200. These glasses are powered by a quad-core Intel Atom X5 processor and run on Android 5...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/epson-introduces-the-latest-moverio-smart-glasses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Huawei has launched the HUAWEI nova 3i</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 06:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</guid><description>Singapore is among the first countries globally to introduce the HUAWEI nova 3i, a midrange smartphone equipped with AI-powered front-facing dual cameras.
Huawei aims to make high-end technology and value accessible to budget-conscious consumers, according to Cheng Jiangfei, Managing Director of Huawei Singapore Consumer Business Group. He emphasized that the HUAWEI nova 3i combines stylish design with advanced AI features, offering exceptional quality and functionality at an affordable price.
Notable features of the HUAWEI nova 3i include:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/huawei-has-launched-the-huawei-nova-3i/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CIMB and PLDT's Smart and Voyager have partnered to provide digital financial solutions in the ASEAN region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. The image depicts the signing ceremony between CIMB Group, Philippine Long Distance Telephone Company (PLDT), and Smart Communications. Present are Tengku Dato’ Sri Zafrul Aziz, Group Chief Executive of CIMB Group (second from left) and Manuel Pangilinan, Chairman of PLDT, Smart Communications, and Voyager (center), along with Gurdip Singh Sidhu, Group Chief Strategy Officer of CIMB Group (second from right), Orlando Vea, President and CEO of Voyager Innovations (left), and Angelito Villanueva, Vice President &amp;amp; Head of Fintech, Digital Inclusion &amp;amp; Alliances at Voyager (right)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-and-pldt-s-smart-and-voyager-have-partnered-to-provide-digital-financial-solutions-in-the-asean-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Watch Urbane 2nd edition also functions as a phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</guid><description>Source: LG.
LG claims its Watch Urbane 2nd Edition is the first Android Wear smartwatch to offer cellular connectivity. The watch will launch globally this month, starting with the US and Korea, followed by other major markets in the coming months.
The LG Watch Urbane 2nd Edition works with both Android and iOS smartphones, giving users the freedom to answer calls and check messages without relying on their phones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-watch-urbane-2nd-edition-also-functions-as-a-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Singtel NumberShare service is compatible with the Apple Watch Series 3, which comes with built-in cellular capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</guid><description>Singtel is the first in Singapore to offer Apple Watch Series 3 (GPS + Cellular), allowing users to stay connected without their iPhones. The watch has been available in Singapore since September 2017 and works with compatible plans.
Apple Watch Series 3 with cellular enables users to stay in touch, make calls, and send and receive texts without needing their iPhones nearby, as long as their carrier provides a compatible plan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-numbershare-service-is-compatible-with-the-apple-watch-series-3-which-comes-with-built-in-cellular-capabilities/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>