<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mobile Video on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-video/</link><description>Recent content in Mobile Video on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:03:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mobile-video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Samsung Intercept Android Phone Goes NASCAR</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 13:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/samsung-intercept-android-phone-goes-nascar/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s both thrilling and fast-paced, almost too much to handle?
NASCAR is a fitting example, but so is the Samsung Intercept Android phone. And surprisingly, they&amp;rsquo;re connected!
The Samsung Intercept M910 for Sprint is a dual phone, offering both a large 3-inch touchscreen display and a slide-out QWERTY keyboard with spacious keys for efficient typing and texting.
As an Android 2.1 phone, it offers access to thousands of customizable apps from the Android market.</description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs.</description></item><item><title>iPhone Getting its Video in a Sling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 01:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/iphone-getting-its-video-in-a-sling/</guid><description>The mobile video landscape is seeing growth in various forms, including carrier-specific services like Verizon&amp;rsquo;s VCAST and Sprint TV, and dedicated channels such as MediaFLO. Sling Media&amp;rsquo;s introduction of a SlingPlayer for iPhone has the potential to disrupt the market by giving control of content back to the user.
Sling Media is known for its Slingbox, a device that connects to your television source (satellite receiver, DVR, or cable box) and a broadband connection.</description></item></channel></rss>