<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directorate-Generals on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directorate-generals/</link><description>Recent content in Directorate-Generals on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:40:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directorate-generals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do not bring up the additional judges!" The transformation of CJEU reform into a mockery</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-not-bring-up-the-additional-judges-the-transformation-of-cjeu-reform-into-a-mockery/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The ongoing debate surrounding the reform of the Court of Justice (CJEU) is becoming increasingly chaotic, reminiscent of an episode of the British comedy &amp;ldquo;Fawlty Towers.&amp;rdquo; The show&amp;rsquo;s humor stems from Basil Fawlty&amp;rsquo;s futile attempts to manage unpredictable situations in his hotel, often venting his frustrations on his staff. While no one would endorse his management style, the current CJEU reform debate mirrors this comedic chaos.
To recap, following several unsuccessful attempts to reform the EU judicial structure, the CJEU proposed that the General Court, the lower EU court, should double its number of judges to two per Member State.</description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous.</description></item></channel></rss>