<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EIU on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eiu/</link><description>Recent content in EIU on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eiu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CIMB discusses its regional strategies for participating in the ASEAN Economic Community</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 09:59:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</guid><description>Source: CIMB. Chairman of CIMB Group, YBhg Dato&amp;rsquo; Sri Nazir Razak (right) and Director, Southeast Asia of The Economist Intelligence Unit Justin Wood showcasing the special report Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia.
CIMB partnered with the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) to publish a report titled Re-drawing the ASEAN Map: How companies are crafting new strategies in Southeast Asia. This independent management brief, co-sponsored by CIMB and Baker McKenzie, aims to equip companies for the upcoming launch of the ASEAN Economic Community (AEC) on December 31, 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cimb-discusses-its-regional-strategies-for-participating-in-the-asean-economic-community/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Social media holds greater significance for customer experience than phone calls or email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</guid><description>Source: Genesys infographic.
A recent study by Genesys, a customer experience and contact center solutions provider, found that over one-third (37%) of Asia Pacific businesses now consider social media a critical channel for customer experience (CX).
While in-person interactions remain the top CX channel, the study highlights that social media has surpassed phone and email in importance.
Bruce Eidsvik, Genesys Asia Pacific Senior Vice President, states, “Consumers are embracing digital platforms more than ever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/social-media-holds-greater-significance-for-customer-experience-than-phone-calls-or-email/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>