<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet of Things on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-of-things/</link><description>Recent content in Internet of Things on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/internet-of-things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Time for IT and Users to Embrace Our IoT Overlords</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 05:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet of Things (IoT) is currently a popular topic in the tech world. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of discussion about connecting everything to the internet, but some are urging caution and calling for standards and bandwidth. While many believe we&amp;rsquo;re on the brink of a technological revolution, history suggests we should be cautious about assuming only positive outcomes. Could there be negative consequences to the rise of the IoT?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-for-it-and-users-to-embrace-our-iot-overlords/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accenture demonstrates a potential vision of the future of retail in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>A recent report from Accenture, &amp;ldquo;The future is now: understanding the new Asian consumer,&amp;rdquo; highlights that consumer packaged goods (CPG) companies need to embrace digital commerce fully or face being overtaken by newer players in the rapidly growing Asia Pacific market. This market is expected to grow by US$340 billion by 2020, with China leading the way.
Accenture emphasizes that CPG companies must adapt to a new generation of consumers who prefer digital engagement and trust social influence...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-demonstrates-a-potential-vision-of-the-future-of-retail-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The potential marketing opportunities presented by a customizable wearable device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</guid><description>Source: Broadcast Wear website. Control the shirt&amp;rsquo;s display with an app.
Broadcast Wear, an innovative company from Hyderabad, has introduced a programmable t-shirt with touch-sensitive technology, opening up exciting possibilities for marketing.
Their invention incorporates a flexible, washable LED screen directly into the fabric. Users can pair the shirt with the Broadcast Wear smartphone app to instantly show any text or image. A simple tap turns the screen on and another tap switches it off...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-potential-marketing-opportunities-presented-by-a-customizable-wearable-device/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big Data Needs Big Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Bandwidth is expanding at an incredible rate. Currently, a major infrastructural development is the shift towards 100 Gbps (100 GigE) wavelength services for national and international connections. It seems like only yesterday Gigabit Ethernet was a new concept, impractical for most businesses. These days, GigE is a basic requirement in some fields. What&amp;rsquo;s driving this huge need for more bandwidth?
Video Started It All
Video now makes up most of the world’s internet traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-data-needs-big-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AI Is Going to Eat Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 20:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Human communication might not dominate telecom usage for much longer. It started when computers began sharing data over phone lines and sped up when broadband internet connected almost every computer. Even though people currently use the internet for websites, messaging, social media, videos, backups, and work, machines will soon be the primary users, communicating amongst themselves.
The Rise of Artificial Intelligence
Artificial intelligence, or AI, has been subtly infiltrating our lives for decades, likely since computers emerged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ai-is-going-to-eat-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CloudEthernet Forum Ensures Ethernet Will Dominate</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</guid><description>Ethernet has dominated the network space for decades, outliving technologies like Token Ring and Token Bus. While alternatives like Fibre Channel and T-Carrier still exist, the rise of cloud computing presents a new challenge to Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance. This challenge led to the creation of the CloudEthernet Forum, a group aiming to adapt Ethernet for the demanding requirements of cloud services.
The enormous increase in networked devices, from traditional computers to virtual machines and the Internet of Things, is putting a strain on existing Ethernet infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloudethernet-forum-ensures-ethernet-will-dominate/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>