<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cbeyond on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cbeyond/</link><description>Recent content in Cbeyond on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cbeyond/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>T1 Line With Instant Wireless Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</guid><description>Losing business broadband during a crucial moment can be incredibly frustrating. This is why many companies choose dedicated T1 lines instead of standard DSL or cable internet, despite the higher reliability of T1, they can still experience outages. Issues like equipment malfunctions or accidents can unexpectedly cut your connection.
To prevent downtime, some companies opt for diverse T1 service, ordering two lines from separate providers. However, this solution isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof, as both lines often use the same physical infrastructure owned by the Incumbent Local Exchange Carrier (ILEC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>