<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Directive 2003/86 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2003/86/</link><description>Recent content in Directive 2003/86 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/directive-2003/86/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Integration requirements for family reunification: the CJEU restricts the autonomy of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In recent times, many EU member states have started requiring non-EU citizens to pass an integration test before they can be reunited with their families in the EU. The EU&amp;rsquo;s family reunification rules allow for this, stating that family members joining non-EU citizens &amp;ldquo;may be required to comply with integration measures.&amp;rdquo; However, for family members of refugees and highly skilled migrants with EU Blue Cards, these tests can only be applied after they arrive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's stance on the minimum age requirement for spouses in a family reunification application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently ruled in the Noorzia case concerning the age requirement for family reunification. The case revolved around whether a national law, requiring both the sponsor and their spouse to be 21 years old when applying for family reunification, aligns with European Union (EU) law. The CJEU determined that the national law was indeed consistent with EU Directive 2003/86/EC...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Just like the sun, hope shines bright: Court of Justice decision expands refugee minors' right to family reunification.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani (PhD) is a linguist agent working for the European Commission and a member of Amnesty International Belgique francophone’s Sexual Orientation and Gender Identity (OSIG) coordination group. The opinions and perspectives presented in this article are solely those of the author and do not necessarily represent the views, policies, or opinions of the European Commission or Amnesty International.
Photo credit: Enno Lenze, via Wikimedia Commons
As of this writing, the European Parliament recently voted to approve the EU’s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, despite concerns raised by over 50 civil society organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>