<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Converged Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/converged-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Converged Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/converged-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SMB Phone System Needs Only Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 08:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</guid><description>The simplicity of traditional phone systems, where plugging in a phone provided immediate dial tone, is making a comeback with cloud-based communication systems.
This modern approach, known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, shifts the responsibility of complex switching equipment to a service provider. This means the provider manages updates, maintenance, and scalability, leaving you with only the phones to handle.
These aren&amp;rsquo;t your typical phones; they are IP phones designed for computer networks, using different electrical signals and connectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smb-phone-system-needs-only-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Dynamic CoS Means to You</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 13:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Modern networks are typically converged, meaning they handle various traffic types like backups, file transfers, cloud access, VoIP calls, streaming, and web services. This begs the question: how can we ensure these networks maintain the integrity of each process with so much going on?
The Need for QoS
When we implement Quality of Service (QoS) controls, a network becomes more than just a passive conduit. But why is this necessary?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-dynamic-cos-means-to-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Voice over MPLS Expands Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Many medium and large businesses have switched from traditional phone lines and internet connections to VoIP technology over combined networks to increase productivity and reduce expenses. However, connecting to the outside world can present challenges and potentially negate the benefits of enterprise VoIP.
While a high-performing local area network (LAN) efficiently connects everything within a company&amp;rsquo;s premises, it often stops there. Communicating with other business sites requires routing voice and data traffic over standard telecom services, creating a disconnect between the internal network and the external transport service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-voice-over-mpls-expands-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Cloud Communications Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</guid><description>Cloud computing is becoming increasingly popular, and now cloud communications is emerging as a new trend. This means that phone services, data processing, and file storage are all moving to the cloud. A clear sign of this shift is the launch of enterprise-level cloud communication services by major providers like XO Communications.
While this seems new, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a return to the roots of telephony. Traditional phone systems operated on a cloud-based model, using the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) as the central hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-cloud-communications-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why NOT to Buy a New PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</guid><description>Traditionally, businesses dealing with outdated or inadequate phone systems have opted for a complete replacement, known as a “forklift upgrade.” While this provided enhanced performance and capacity, like a brand new car, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling alternative in today&amp;rsquo;s world: hosted PBX solutions.
Rather than investing heavily in another physical PBX system, consider a hosted PBX, also referred to as Hosted VoIP or PBX in the cloud. This service eliminates the need for a physical PBX on your premises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-not-to-buy-a-new-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Exchange For Miami, Dallas and Los Angeles</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:49:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</guid><description>Carrier Ethernet is emerging as a strong contender to replace the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), as evidenced by the increasing number of Ethernet Exchanges that facilitate traffic sharing among carriers. Telx, a prominent interconnection and colocation provider, recently expanded its Ethernet Exchange services to Miami, Dallas, and Los Angeles. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the significance of Ethernet Exchange and its impact on the future of international wide-area networking.
The PSTN&amp;rsquo;s global reach and interoperability have contributed to its longstanding success, enabling communication between any two phones worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-exchange-for-miami-dallas-and-los-angeles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Easy Convergence for Small Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 23:27:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>The convergence of voice and data networks is a cost-saving strategy employed by businesses of all sizes. Combining these networks into one is more cost-effective than running separate networks for internet and phone services.
While larger companies have readily adopted converged networks, smaller businesses can also benefit, especially with new installations. Integrated T1 service is a practical solution for smaller companies with 6 to 12 phone lines and broadband internet. This technology is relevant for various businesses, from dealerships and real estate offices to manufacturing facilities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-convergence-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>