<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telarus on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telarus/</link><description>Recent content in Telarus on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telarus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comprehensive Network Services From Telarus</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</guid><description>Creating and managing a network can be a significant challenge for businesses of all sizes. Small businesses find it distracting, while larger companies view it as a costly endeavor that can either help or hurt their efficiency. Integrating local and wide area networks seamlessly is a particularly difficult problem.
Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution: Telarus. Regardless of your size or technical expertise, Telarus provides a range of services to address your networking needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comprehensive-network-services-from-telarus/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Communications Services To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>A significant shift from traditional phone systems to cloud-based communication is happening right now. XO Communications, a leader in this field, predicts 60% of companies will move almost a third of their voice communications to the cloud in the coming years.
For a free consultation and quotes tailored to your company&amp;rsquo;s communication needs, our partners at Telarus offer fast and reliable service from expert product specialists. Contact them at http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Sales Support Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 15:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in earning money by selling business voice and data services, there&amp;rsquo;s a brokerage service that can simplify the process.
The VAR Network, managed by Telarus, Inc., connects telecom providers with VARs (Value Added Resellers). VARs typically represent manufacturers of business phone systems, network equipment, video conferencing tools, and similar products. They often handle both sales and service, providing clients with complete solutions and ongoing support.
Many VARs, focused on hardware and software, haven&amp;rsquo;t ventured into selling telephone lines or WAN services, which are crucial for a comprehensive business solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-sales-support-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Use a Telecom Broker Before You Go Broker</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/</guid><description>Are you getting the best deal on your telecom services? It&amp;rsquo;s hard to know when every provider claims to offer the best rates. Comparing plans and prices from multiple companies is time-consuming and challenging.
That&amp;rsquo;s where telecom brokers come in. Telecom brokers are independent experts who work on your behalf to find the best telecom deals. They are not affiliated with any specific provider, ensuring unbiased recommendations.
Similar to independent insurance agents, telecom brokers represent multiple carriers, giving you access to a wide range of options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/use-a-telecom-broker-before-you-go-broker/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free Help On Your Telecom Needs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 13:27:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/</guid><description>Want free, top-notch tech support for your phone and computer networks? No cost now or ever, even with today&amp;rsquo;s tight budgets.
Sounds too good to be true? It&amp;rsquo;s not. This is a telecom brokerage service with a team of experts in telephony, computer networking, international networks, wireless solutions, and more. They&amp;rsquo;re ready to help – just tell them what you need.
But how is this free? A third party – the service providers – foots the bill...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-help-on-your-telecom-needs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Adam Edwards Interview Part II</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</guid><description>I recently had a fascinating dinner conversation with Adam Edwards, the president of Telarus, Inc., and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to share what I learned.
In Part I of our interview, Adam discussed the philosophy behind Telarus&amp;rsquo;s remarkable success in the telecommunications industry. Launched just five years ago with its revolutionary GeoQuote (tm) instant pricing tool, Telarus has become a leading master agency, earning numerous accolades.
This audio report focuses on the comprehensive range of services Telarus provides and their significance to you, the customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adam-edwards-interview-part-ii/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Filling Coverage Gaps With High Quality Business Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses in big cities have it easy when it comes to internet and phone service. There are so many options! But what if your business isn&amp;rsquo;t in a big city? What if you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with slow internet and outdated phone lines? You&amp;rsquo;re not out of luck!
Look Up for Better Options
Stop looking for internet and phone service on the ground. Look up! Satellite service is a great option for businesses that need fast, reliable service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Gigabit Prices On Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 05:45:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</guid><description>Modern businesses are increasing their reliance on bandwidth-intensive applications like video and cloud-based solutions, putting a strain on their Wide Area Networks (WANs). While evaluating bandwidth needs and exploring the best deals seems logical, it can often feel complicated. However, new tools are emerging to simplify this process.
Traditionally, obtaining competitive telecom prices meant identifying local carriers, navigating through voicemail systems, enduring endless phone tag, and deciphering complex quotes to ensure accurate comparisons...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Telarus GeoScan Finds Better Network Deals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-telarus-geoscan-finds-better-network-deals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 10:34:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-telarus-geoscan-finds-better-network-deals/</guid><description>Telarus, a leading telecom brokerage service, introduces GeoScan, an innovative telecom carrier research tool, to enhance its suite of software-based services. This new tool allows Telarus consultants to refine carrier service offerings for clients through a more efficient search and evaluation process. By pinpointing the closest matching offers, Telarus agents can better serve their client&amp;rsquo;s specific needs.
GeoScan addresses the need to manage a rapidly expanding pool of carrier options. Telarus&amp;rsquo; existing GeoQuote process, known for finding and organizing services from various carriers, faced a welcome challenge: increased carrier participation and a transforming telecom landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-telarus-geoscan-finds-better-network-deals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-telarus-geoscan-finds-better-network-deals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Telarus, the New Face of Telecom Sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</guid><description>The telecommunications industry is undergoing a massive transformation thanks to disruptive technology. Wireless technology is shaking up the century-old wireline business, VoIP is changing the landscape of the digital voice trunking business, competitive fiber optic carriers are challenging the dominance of established phone companies, and Ethernet and IP networks are blurring the lines between local and wide area networks.
Despite these technological advancements, the sales and marketing processes for business telecommunications services have remained largely unchanged...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telarus-the-new-face-of-telecom-sales/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding An Ethernet Internet Provider</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 21:21:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</guid><description>Looking for a better alternative to traditional internet services like T1 lines? Ethernet Internet might be the answer. But finding the right provider can be tricky. That’s where the Ethernet Internet Finder comes in.
This free tool, powered by Telarus, a leading telecom brokerage firm, helps businesses easily find and compare Ethernet Internet providers. Just enter your basic business contact information, preferably your main business phone number, and let the system do the rest...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-an-ethernet-internet-provider/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How SD-WAN Hands-Off Seamlessly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 05:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It would be ideal if WAN network connections never failed, but unfortunately, that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. Even the most reliable copper, fiber, or wireless connections eventually experience downtime. This can interrupt phone calls, halt ongoing work, and lead to lost productivity and revenue. However, imagine a solution that ensures your connections remain virtually uninterrupted, experiencing only minor, momentary glitches regardless of the underlying issue.
This solution exists and is called SD-WAN, or Software-Defined Wide Area Networking...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding Lit Buildings and Near Net Fiber Buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic internet service is becoming increasingly essential for modern businesses, but not everyone has access to it. Some businesses don&amp;rsquo;t need the high speeds fiber offers and are content with slower options. Others might have outdated perceptions of fiber&amp;rsquo;s affordability. Many are unaware that fiber might already be available in their building or nearby.
Fiber optic internet isn&amp;rsquo;t the niche product it once was. Even consumers are demanding fiber to their homes for streaming and entertainment...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-lit-buildings-and-near-net-fiber-buildings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Audio Interview With Adam Edwards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 02:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</guid><description>Telarus, Inc. is considered a leading innovator in telecommunications marketing since the major telecom expansion of the 1990s. The company has transformed how businesses purchase services like T1, Ethernet, and other high-speed internet options.
I recently spoke with Adam Edwards, Telarus&amp;rsquo;s president, to understand the company&amp;rsquo;s success as a top master agency. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share an MP3 recording of our conversation so you can hear directly from Adam instead of reading a transcript...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/audio-interview-with-adam-edwards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two T1 Lines For The Price of One</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 11:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</guid><description>Companies are transmitting more data than ever before, putting a strain on their WAN connections. You might assume that increasing bandwidth in this economic climate would be difficult, but what if you could get double the capacity for the same price?
While it sounds unbelievable, many competing providers offer deals that effectively give you two T1 lines for the price of one. Skeptical? Compare current T1 prices to what you might have paid a few years ago on a multi-year contract, especially in major cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-t1-lines-for-the-price-of-one/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>