<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU Criminal Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-criminal-law/</link><description>Recent content in EU Criminal Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-criminal-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do crime victims now have additional rights under EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 07:46:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
*This analysis is taken from the upcoming 4th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Victims of crime are often disheartened not just by the crime itself but also by the criminal justice system&amp;rsquo;s indifference to their needs. To tackle this issue, the EU introduced a Directive on crime victims’ rights in 2012 that Member States were required to implement by November 16, 2015. This law supersedes an earlier Framework Decision on this matter from 2001...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-crime-victims-now-have-additional-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Arrest Warrant compatible with human rights? Can individuals be legally detained for more than 90 days before being surrendered?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 04:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD student, Utrecht University
The Amsterdam District Court, solely responsible for handling European Arrest Warrants (EAWs) in the Netherlands, faces a conflict between national and EU laws regarding detention and release. Dutch law mandates the release of a requested individual after 90 days if the court hasn&amp;rsquo;t made a decision on the EAW. However, a 2015 European Court of Justice (CJEU) ruling stated that national courts can extend detention beyond 90 days to ensure conditions for surrender are met...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-arrest-warrant-compatible-with-human-rights-can-individuals-be-legally-detained-for-more-than-90-days-before-being-surrendered/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU here to rescue legal aid, or to put it to rest? Evaluating discussions on the proposed Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</guid><description>by Claire Perinaud (FREE Group Trainee)
Access to legal aid is crucial for individuals facing criminal charges, enabling them to mount a proper defense. The EU is developing legislation to address this right, but its impact remains uncertain.
Progress of the Procedural Rights Roadmap
EU legislation concerning the procedural rights of suspects and accused individuals in criminal cases has been developing gradually since late 2009, following years of unsuccessful attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unexpected turn of events? Case C-128/18 Dorobantu: the conditions of detention and the ECHR's relevance in the EU legal system</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</guid><description>Ágoston Mohay, University of Pécs Faculty of Law
Introduction
The EU legal system is often viewed as a distinct entity, separate from both international and national law. Within this system, safeguarding fundamental rights is paramount. Article 6 of the Treaty on European Union (TEU) establishes a three-pronged approach to fundamental rights protection: 1) the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union, 2) the EU&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and 3) general principles of EU law derived from the ECHR and shared constitutional values of member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unexpected-turn-of-events-case-c-128-18-dorobantu-the-conditions-of-detention-and-the-echr-s-relevance-in-the-eu-legal-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the European Court of Justice reconsidering the European equivalent of the 'fifth amendment'? The CJEU makes a decision on the right to remain silent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</guid><description>Inês Pereira de Sousa, Lecturer and PhD candidate at Porto Faculty of Law, Universidade Católica Portuguesa; Researcher at CEID – Católica Research Centre for the Future of Law; Member of ANESC – Academic Network on the European Social Charter and Social Rights; Member of EUCRIM –European Criminal Law Associations’ Forum - isousa@porto.ucp.pt
On February 2, 2021, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) had the chance to reexamine the right to remain silent and the right against self-incrimination in a case originating from the Italian Constitutional Court...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-court-of-justice-reconsidering-the-european-equivalent-of-the-fifth-amendment-the-cjeu-makes-a-decision-on-the-right-to-remain-silent/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU is currently hearing important cases regarding the European Arrest Warrant, questioning whether mutual trust should be blind or general with exceptions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:32:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</guid><description>Henning Bang Fuglsang Madsen Sørensen, Associate Professor, Department of Law, University of Southern Denmark
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing on February 15th, 2016, concerning two cases, Aranyosi and Caldararu, both addressing whether surrender under a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) should be refused if there are concerns about potential inhumane prison conditions in the requesting state. These cases, originating from the same German court, delve into the balance between the principle of mutual recognition in EU criminal law and the protection of fundamental rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-is-currently-hearing-important-cases-regarding-the-european-arrest-warrant-questioning-whether-mutual-trust-should-be-blind-or-general-with-exceptions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for prosecutors from Belgium, France, and Sweden to issue European Arrest Warrants? The CJEU provides clarification on the necessity of independent public prosecutors.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 04:27:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</guid><description>Laure Baudrihaye-Gérard, Fair Trials The European Court of Justice (CJEU) has again clarified who can issue a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). This decision is significant for this key EU judicial cooperation tool, used countless times daily to extradite individuals between member states for investigations or to serve sentences.
Courts in Luxembourg and the Netherlands recently paused EAWs from prosecutors in Belgium, France, and Sweden to seek clarification from the CJEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-prosecutors-from-belgium-france-and-sweden-to-issue-european-arrest-warrants-the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-the-necessity-of-independent-public-prosecutors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pilate cleanses his hands. The CJEU's stance on pre-trial detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 02:07:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</guid><description>By Adriano Martufi (Assistant Professor, Leiden University) and Christina Peristeridou (Assistant Professor, Maastricht University)
Introduction
The recent judgment of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of DK (C-653/19 PPU, 28 November 2019) has validated two concerning observations about the state of European criminal law. Firstly, Directive 2016/343 on the presumption of innocence has limited practical application, particularly regarding pre-trial detention. Secondly, pre-trial detention is a contentious subject, with both the CJEU and the EU legislator hesitant to establish common standards despite their absence negatively impacting mutual trust between Member States&amp;rsquo; judicial systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pilate-cleanses-his-hands-the-cjeu-s-stance-on-pre-trial-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Day the Unicorns Cried: Understanding Phase 1 of the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
The recent joint report on the progress of Brexit negotiations, along with a related paper from the Commission, represents an informal agreement to move to the next stage of negotiations. Based on this report, the EU27 have agreed that &amp;ldquo;sufficient progress&amp;rdquo; has been made to move forward. This next phase will focus on a transition period and, potentially starting in March 2018, the framework for the post-Brexit relationship between the UK and the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-day-the-unicorns-cried-understanding-phase-1-of-the-brexit-negotiations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU missed an opportunity to address mass hacking and fundamental rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Hugo Partouche, a Paris Bar Attorney-at-law (avocat), and Chloé Berthélémy, a Senior Policy Advisor at EDRi, collaborated on this piece.
Photo credit: hacker-silhoutte, via Wikimedia commons
*This article initially appeared in French in Actualité Juridique (AJ) Pénal, Dalloz Revues. You can find it here.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on the ‘EncroChat’ case on April 30, 2024.
This case arose from large-scale European police operations targeting organized crime...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Review of the updated Brexit withdrawal agreement: examining the political declaration on the future relationship between the EU and UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
If Brexit proceeds based on the updated withdrawal agreement, what will the UK-EU relationship look like? The revised political declaration addresses this, outlining the future relationship. This declaration, revised during recent UK-EU negotiations, clarifies their post-Brexit partnership.
Although not legally binding as a treaty, the political declaration gains relevance domestically through the proposed withdrawal agreement bill. This bill mandates that Parliament&amp;rsquo;s agenda for the future relationship must align with the declaration...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-the-updated-brexit-withdrawal-agreement-examining-the-political-declaration-on-the-future-relationship-between-the-eu-and-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit has not resulted in any legal changes yet, as the Court of Justice of the European Union continues to rule on the execution of European Arrest Warrants issued by the UK before Brexit Day.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 09:25:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
While there are many legal discussions surrounding the impact of Brexit, the ultimate authority on these matters, at least for the EU, is the EU Court of Justice. The Court&amp;rsquo;s first ruling on Brexit, released today, clarifies the legal standing until Brexit Day and potentially influences the approach after that.
The judgment in the case of RO addressed whether Ireland remained obligated to enforce a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) issued by the UK considering its impending withdrawal from the EU after triggering Article 50 TEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-has-not-resulted-in-any-legal-changes-yet-as-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-continues-to-rule-on-the-execution-of-european-arrest-warrants-issued-by-the-uk-before-brexit-day/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it advisable for the EU to approve the Istanbul Convention on violence against women?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 09:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While conversations about the European Union (EU) and human rights often revolve around the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights and the EU&amp;rsquo;s potential membership in the European Convention on Human Rights, it&amp;rsquo;s also important to look at how the EU interacts with other international human rights agreements.
The EU can&amp;rsquo;t join older UN human rights treaties like those addressing sex and race discrimination because they are only open to individual countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-advisable-for-the-eu-to-approve-the-istanbul-convention-on-violence-against-women/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dillon Judgment, Exemption of Laws, and Article 2 of the Northern Ireland Protocol/Windsor Framework</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</guid><description>Anurag Deb, PhD researcher, Queens University Belfast, and Colin Murray, Professor of Law, Newcastle Law School
Photo credit: Aaronward, via Wikicommons media
In a landmark decision, a UK court has disapplied portions of a UK Act of Parliament for the first time since Brexit due to conflicts with the Withdrawal Agreement, specifically highlighting the ongoing connection between UK and EU legal systems. This unexpected development, though previously argued for, underscores the UK government&amp;rsquo;s consistent underestimation of Article 2&amp;rsquo;s impact on rights-related cases...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dillon-judgment-exemption-of-laws-and-article-2-of-the-northern-ireland-protocol-windsor-framework/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Challenges to Judicial Independence in the European Arrest Warrant System and Potential Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 14:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</guid><description>Dr Leandro Mancano, Senior Lecturer in EU Law, Edinburgh Law School
This blog post builds upon Leandro Mancano&amp;rsquo;s work, ‘You’ll never work alone: A systemic assessment of the European Arrest Warrant and judicial independence’, published in Common Market Law Review, Volume 58, Issue 3 (2021) pp. 683 – 718
Introduction
The European Arrest Warrant Framework Decision (EAW FD) has significantly altered cooperation between EU states on criminal justice matters (for its effects beyond the EU, see the Court of Justice’s judgments in Petruhhin – discussed here – and IN)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenges-to-judicial-independence-in-the-european-arrest-warrant-system-and-potential-solutions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Alice Gross case: Examining EU law implications of allowing murderers to freely move within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
British readers of this blog are likely aware of the case of missing teenager Alice Gross. A Latvian man, Arnis Zalkalns, is a person of interest in her disappearance. What makes this case more complex is that Mr. Zalkalns had a prior murder conviction in Latvia before relocating to the UK. He has since vanished, possibly returning to Latvia.
This raises several questions: how was a convicted murderer able to enter the UK undetected?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-alice-gross-case-examining-eu-law-implications-of-allowing-murderers-to-freely-move-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Investigation Order: A fresh perspective on mutual recognition in criminal affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 03:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</guid><description>Emilio De Capitani and Steve Peers
The enactment of Directive 2014/41/EU concerning the European Investigation Order (EIO) marks a significant development in criminal justice cooperation within the European Union, particularly after the Lisbon Treaty and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights came into effect. This piece will delve into the broader legal framework surrounding this new directive, examining its territorial reach considering various opt-outs and its key provisions on the interplay between human rights and mutual recognition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-investigation-order-a-fresh-perspective-on-mutual-recognition-in-criminal-affairs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Assessing the Commission's Proposal to Enhance Europol's Authority: A Review of the Amendment to Regulation (EU) 2016/784 (Europol Regulation)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</guid><description>Niovi Vavoula and Valsamis Mitsilegas, Queen Mary University
Introduction The European Union Agency for Law Enforcement Cooperation (Europol) plays a crucial role in supporting EU Member States&amp;rsquo; cross-border police cooperation, as defined by Regulation (EU) 2016/794 (Europol Regulation). Referred to as the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;criminal information hub,&amp;rsquo; Europol facilitates information exchange between Member States, Europol itself, other EU bodies, international organizations, and third countries. It also generates criminal intelligence using information from various sources, including Member States and partners...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Details of the upcoming referendum on Denmark's participation in EU Justice and Home Affairs Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:53:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Denmark&amp;rsquo;s involvement in international criminal law, exemplified by the TV show &amp;ldquo;The Bridge,&amp;rdquo; is facing uncertainty due to changing EU regulations. This situation will soon lead Denmark to vote on modifying its current near-total opt-out of EU Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) laws. While the general implications have been discussed, the specifics of this vote are now clearer.
To recap, Denmark negotiated opt-outs from the euro, defense, and parts of JHA law in 1992...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/details-of-the-upcoming-referendum-on-denmark-s-participation-in-eu-justice-and-home-affairs-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>European Arrest Warrants and the autonomy of public prosecutors as ruled by the CJEU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Julia Burchett, PhD candidate at the Université libre de Bruxelles and the University of Grenoble
Introduction
Widely recognized as a cornerstone of EU criminal law, the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) stands out as one of the most, if not the most, utilized tools for judicial cooperation in criminal matters among EU member states. This streamlined cross-border surrender procedure, designed for prosecution or execution of custodial sentences and detention orders, has replaced traditional systems relying on political involvement from individual member states...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-arrest-warrants-and-the-autonomy-of-public-prosecutors-as-ruled-by-the-cjeu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a need for additional anti-terrorist legislation in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 01:42:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Following the horrific attacks in Paris two days ago, the EU Commission wasted no time in announcing its intention to propose new anti-terrorism measures within a month. While the specifics of this legislation remain unclear, the very notion of enacting new laws is fundamentally flawed.
The EU institutions were right to express sympathy for the victims and emphasize their commitment to defending freedom of speech. Utilizing existing EU anti-terrorism laws, such as the European Arrest Warrant (EAW), to apprehend suspects who may have fled to another Member State, would also be appropriate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-need-for-additional-anti-terrorist-legislation-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Number of Human Trafficking Victims in the EU: A Statistical Puzzle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:21:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</guid><description>Dr. Vladislava Stoyanova
Postdoctoral Fellow, Faculty of Law, Lund University; Author of Human Trafficking and Slavery Reconsidered. Conceptual Limits and States’ Positive Obligations in Europe (Cambridge University Press, 2017)
In May 2016, the European Commission presented its initial findings on the progress made in combating human trafficking. This report, mandated by the 2011 EU Trafficking Directive, examines advancements in prosecuting traffickers, safeguarding victims, and preventative measures. It highlights trafficking patterns, incorporating statistical data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-number-of-human-trafficking-victims-in-the-eu-a-statistical-puzzle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Clarifications from the Court and reports from the Commission on Double Jeopardy and EU Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 10:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</guid><description>After a long wait, two judgments regarding the Schengen double jeopardy rules have been issued by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU), accompanied by two Commission reports examining the implementation of related EU laws. The judgments clarify these rules, while the reports highlight Member States&amp;rsquo; recurring delays in fulfilling their legal duties.
Background
Many national constitutions and the European Convention on Human Rights&amp;rsquo; Seventh Protocol forbid double jeopardy, but typically only within the same state...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clarifications-from-the-court-and-reports-from-the-commission-on-double-jeopardy-and-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Public Prosecutor’s Office and Fundamental Rights: A Disquieting Lack of Discussion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 01:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</guid><description>Michiel Luchtman, Jannemieke Ouwerkerk, Marloes van Noorloos, Pim Geelhoed, Jorrit Rijpma, and Louis Middelkoop are affiliated with the Meijers Committee (www.commissie-meijers.nl/en).
The EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed European Public Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office (EPPO) has sparked significant debate among Member States. The EPPO&amp;rsquo;s role would be to investigate and prosecute fraudulent use of EU funds, with discussions already underway to expand its jurisdiction to include terrorism and other serious crimes. Current political dialogue centers around the necessity of this supranational entity and the potential impact on national sovereignty, particularly within the sensitive realm of criminal justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-public-prosecutor-s-office-and-fundamental-rights-a-disquieting-lack-of-discussion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Arrest Warrant and the German Constitutional Court: A new development in the legal conversation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 21:33:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</guid><description>Daniel Sarmiento, Professor of EU Law at the University Complutense of Madrid*
The German Constitutional Court (GCC) has issued another impactful ruling, this time concerning fundamental rights. In an order published yesterday, the GCC exercised its authority to review the implementation of a European Arrest Warrant (EAW) from Italy to Germany. The subject, a US citizen convicted in Italy in absentia, argued that his conviction lacked due process and that Italian law provided no recourse for appeal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-arrest-warrant-and-the-german-constitutional-court-a-new-development-in-the-legal-conversation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU's groundbreaking Directive 2024/1385 on Violence Against Women is a significant step forward in promoting gender equality.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</guid><description>Dr. Ceren Kasım, Postdoctoral Research and Teaching Fellow, University of Hildesheim, Germany
Photo credit: MesserWoland, via Wikimedia Commons
INTRODUCTION
May 14, 2024, marked a pivotal moment for the European Union (EU) as it unveiled its first legally binding instrument to combat violence against women and domestic violence. This Directive, officially known as Directive 2024/1385, signifies the EU&amp;rsquo;s strong commitment to achieving genuine equality for women.
Gender-based violence is a pervasive issue across the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-s-groundbreaking-directive-2024-1385-on-violence-against-women-is-a-significant-step-forward-in-promoting-gender-equality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on conflicting EU and national law obligations regarding detention time limits. Is this a Prison Break?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 01:58:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</guid><description>Joske Graat, PhD candidate, Utrecht University
A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressed the conflict between EU and national laws regarding detention periods for individuals subject to a European Arrest Warrant (EAW). Specifically, the case considered whether a longer EU-mandated detention period overrides a shorter national one, and whether unclear national legislation on this matter violates the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR) and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-conflicting-eu-and-national-law-obligations-regarding-detention-time-limits-is-this-a-prison-break/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible to renegotiate the UK's membership of the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:14:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Can the UK renegotiate its EU membership terms? This question is easier to answer after analyzing David Cameron&amp;rsquo;s stated objectives for such a renegotiation.
The Telegraph summarized these objectives into seven key points, which we will examine individually.
Firstly, limiting the movement of people from countries joining the EU in the future. This wouldn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily require a Treaty amendment, as accession treaties require unanimous agreement. However, if the goal is to allow for potentially indefinite delays in free movement, a Treaty amendment might be needed, as this represents a permanent exception to a fundamental Treaty rule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-to-renegotiate-the-uk-s-membership-of-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The argument for the UK to remain in the European Arrest Warrant</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</guid><description>Maria Fletcher, Senior Lecturer in Law at the University of Glasgow, and Steve Peers, Professor of Law at the University of Essex, collaborated on this piece.
As of December 1, 2014, the UK government will have to decide which pre-December 2009 EU laws on criminal law and policing to potentially rejoin. One of the most contentious issues is whether to opt back into the European Arrest Warrant (EAW) framework. This article presents the argument for rejoining this legal framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-argument-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-european-arrest-warrant/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What's all the fuss about the draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</guid><description>Cian C. Murphy, The Dickson Poon School of Law, King’s College London
The transnational public sphere continues to be gradually suppressed. The European Union&amp;rsquo;s initial legislative response to recent killings by Islamic State militants in Europe and elsewhere is a draft EU Directive on Combating Terrorism, which was published last month. The Directive, which seeks to expand the scope of EU law in national criminal law regarding terrorism, will replace the Framework Decision on Combating Terrorism, which was initially approved in 2002 and revised in 2008...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-all-the-fuss-about-the-draft-eu-directive-on-combating-terrorism/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disappointing ruling by the CJEU on reverse discrimination against rape victims</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 20:50:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</guid><description>Steve Peers
National criminal justice systems are frequently criticized for overlooking the needs of crime victims. In contrast, the EU has been attentive to this matter since the initial stages of EU criminal law development. Early on, one of the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Framework Decisions&amp;rsquo; addressed victims&amp;rsquo; rights. This measure has since been superseded by a comprehensive Directive on this subject, which Member States are required to implement by October 2015...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disappointing-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-reverse-discrimination-against-rape-victims/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A.T. v Luxembourg: The Beginning of the EU-ECHR Narrative on Rights to Criminal Defense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 02:07:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</guid><description>Alex Tinsley, Legal &amp;amp; Policy Officer (Head of EU Office) at Fair Trials, based in Brussels. Twitter: @AlexLouisT In a judgment issued on April 9, 2015, the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) ruled in the case of A.T. v. Luxembourg. This ruling, which will become final unless reviewed by the Grand Chamber, determined that Luxembourg violated Article 6 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). The judgment expands upon the principles established in Salduz v...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-t-v-luxembourg-the-beginning-of-the-eu-echr-narrative-on-rights-to-criminal-defense/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>