<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ISDN on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isdn/</link><description>Recent content in ISDN on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/isdn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses.</description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out.</description></item><item><title>T1 PRI is More Than Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</guid><description>T1 lines are the most common way to link PBX phone systems to the telephone network. T1 PRI service is often the preferred choice because it can transmit Caller ID information to business phones or call centers. However, there are additional ways that T1 PRI can offer the most budget-friendly phone line trunking.
T1 PRI is a highly specialized telecom service. T1 lines have been in use for over half a century to carry phone calls, and more recently, for point-to-point data, dedicated internet service, and connections to private networks.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems.</description></item><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls.</description></item><item><title>What is ISDN and Why Do I Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</guid><description>You might have encountered the term ISDN in the context of phone services. What does it mean and how can it benefit you?
ISDN stands for Integrated Services Digital Network, a technical term for a digital phone service that adheres to specific standards.
The concept of ISDN emerged when dial-up modems using analog phone lines were the norm for internet access. ISDN aimed to combine phone and internet services on a single line with three channels.</description></item><item><title>ISDN's Primary Rate Interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</guid><description>The Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) is a digital telephone standard that provided widespread voice and data services before Enterprise VoIP and MPLS networks. Notably, ISDN&amp;rsquo;s Primary Rate Interface remains in high demand due to its seamless integration with existing telephone trunk lines, which are nearly ubiquitous.
The development of ISDN was driven by the increasing use of modems on analog telephone lines for long-distance data transmission. Analog telephone networks, designed for limited voice bandwidth, only allowed for data speeds up to 56 Kbps.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification.</description></item><item><title>PRI Phone Line Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 18:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</guid><description>Analog business phone lines are suitable for small offices and retail spaces that don&amp;rsquo;t need many outside lines. If you require more than six lines, an option like ISDN PRI might be a better fit.
ISDN PRI, which stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is a standard for transmitting calls digitally over regular phone lines. It&amp;rsquo;s the larger of two primary options, with the smaller being BRI (Basic Rate Interface).</description></item></channel></rss>