<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Outsourcing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/outsourcing/</link><description>Recent content in Outsourcing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/outsourcing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Office to Data Center Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 22:34:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While outsourcing IT applications to the cloud is increasingly popular, the importance of a strong cloud connection is often overlooked. People assume that since the data center has abundant connectivity, their connection doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter. But how you connect to the cloud significantly impacts performance.
The Difference Between LAN and WAN Think about your current in-house network. It&amp;rsquo;s likely fast and reliable because everything connects through the company LAN with standard Ethernet connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-office-to-data-center-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Ubiquitous Cloud of 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</guid><description>The year 2012 brings a shift in the business landscape, not towards a downturn, but rather a move towards cloud computing. This change benefits businesses facing uncertainty by offering flexibility and adaptability. Instead of struggling to predict the future, businesses can embrace the cloud and adjust their strategies as needed.
The current business environment is already in flux. While some businesses are stagnant, others experience constant change. This unpredictability leaves many longing for a more stable past...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ubiquitous-cloud-of-2012/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing In Lieu of Outsourcing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</guid><description>Over recent years, outsourcing has become increasingly popular as a way to meet business needs. However, since the Great Recession, crowdsourcing has emerged as a new and growing trend. This approach leverages the collective talent of a group to find solutions for specific tasks.
Crowdsourcing provides a decentralized approach to problem-solving, unlike traditional methods of assigning tasks to employees or contractors. Imagine needing a building sold – you&amp;rsquo;d hire a real estate agent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>