<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Economic Migration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-migration/</link><description>Recent content in Economic Migration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 16:35:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/economic-migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Will the new Blue Card proposal entice a greater number of highly skilled workers to the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-blue-card-proposal-entice-a-greater-number-of-highly-skilled-workers-to-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 16:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-blue-card-proposal-entice-a-greater-number-of-highly-skilled-workers-to-the-eu/</guid><description>Jean-Baptiste Farcy, Research Assistant, Universite Catholique de Louvain
Introduction
After a 2001 attempt to create a comprehensive EU law regarding entry and residency for non-EU workers failed, the EU&amp;rsquo;s approach to labor migration has been fragmented and industry-specific. Due to the sensitivity surrounding immigration and the importance of national sovereignty, the EU has focused on creating laws for a select few economic migrant categories.
Highly skilled workers are one such category.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: The future of the UK's free movement of people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-future-of-the-uk-s-free-movement-of-people/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard and Sarah Fraser Butlin*
*The authors are both at the University of Cambridge and funded by the ESRC’s UK in a Changing Europe program. They thank their colleagues, Graeme Ross, Steve Peers, Jonathan Portes and Madelaine Sumption.
Introduction
A primary reason many voted to exit the European Union on June 23, 2016, was concern over immigration. Many felt the UK had &amp;ldquo;lost control&amp;rdquo; of its borders and that leaving the EU would allow the UK government to regain control.</description></item><item><title>Quit this job and shove it: the updated EU legislation on non-EU migrant workers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quit-this-job-and-shove-it-the-updated-eu-legislation-on-non-eu-migrant-workers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
*Text updated Dec 22 2023, to add a link to the agreed text of the Directive, and April 12 2024, on its final adoption Photo credit: Lasse Fuss, via Wikimedia commons
While the recent agreement on asylum legislation has garnered significant attention, an equally important development occurred with the EU Member States and European Parliament reaching an agreement on amending the &amp;lsquo;single permit Directive,&amp;rsquo; a law governing non-EU migrant workers.</description></item><item><title>Will the new Directive on intra-corporate transferees improve the safeguarding of third-country nationals and bolster EU competitiveness?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</guid><description>Lucia Brieskova, PhD candidate at Oxford Brookes University
This post examines the new EU Intra-Corporate Transfers Directive (ICTD) concerning legal economic migration. This analysis is divided into three parts. First, it explains the background and motivation behind introducing this Directive and its connection to other EU directives on economic migration. Second, it outlines the key changes this Directive brings. Finally, it highlights potential issues that will be analyzed in future posts.</description></item></channel></rss>