<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unified on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified/</link><description>Recent content in Unified on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/unified/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ameyo introduces a new cloud-based omnichannel contact center solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 22:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ameyo-introduces-a-new-cloud-based-omnichannel-contact-center-solution/</guid><description>Ameyo, a company that provides contact center technology and service integrations, has introduced Ameyo Emerge, a cloud-based product designed to help businesses communicate smoothly across different channels. This platform tackles the difficulties new businesses and startups often encounter when trying to establish a streamlined and effective communication process to manage customer interactions.
Ameyo Emerge enables emerging businesses like local mobile app platforms, online marketplaces, and e-commerce websites to establish contact centers without needing to invest in physical equipment or complex coding.</description></item><item><title>Avaya IP Office enhances security for cloud-based installations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-ip-office-enhances-security-for-cloud-based-installations/</guid><description>Avaya has enhanced its unified communications (UC) solution, Avaya IP Office, with the release of version 10. This upgrade brings improvements to security, resilience, and user experience for small and midsize businesses (SMBs).
Avaya IP Office is a widely used UC solution, with over half a million systems deployed globally. A key feature of the updated platform is built-in media encryption for endpoints and UC clients. This feature enhances privacy and data integrity at no extra cost.</description></item></channel></rss>