<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>4G Network on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-network/</link><description>Recent content in 4G Network on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/4g-network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Plethora of Free Android Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-plethora-of-free-android-phones/</guid><description>This Christmas, give the gift of a cutting-edge Android phone without breaking the bank. Although these devices boast advanced technology and typically come with a high price tag (often $500-$600), it&amp;rsquo;s possible to get one for free.
Android smartphones are essentially pocket computers, running on 3G and 4G networks and offering similar functionality to desktops and laptops. They&amp;rsquo;re capable of web browsing, social networking, email, video streaming, and more. While $500-$600 might be reasonable for such a device, why pay when you can get one for free?</description></item><item><title>WiMAX 2 Will Challenge Fiber For Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:29:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wimax-2-will-challenge-fiber-for-speed/</guid><description>The idea that copper and wireless technologies are outdated in terms of bandwidth is circulating. While copper has found new life as a last-mile solution for Metro Ethernet services, and wireless stands out for its unmatched mobility, a new wireless technology is emerging that might surpass even fiber optic speeds.
It&amp;rsquo;s surprising to think that wireless could outpace fiber in terms of bandwidth.
While not all fiber optic services offer top speeds of 10 GigE, with many customers receiving 50 to 100 Mbps, especially in the case of Fiber To The Home (FTTH), the prospect of achieving 100 to 300 Mbps wirelessly anywhere in a city is enticing.</description></item></channel></rss>