<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Race Discrimination on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/race-discrimination/</link><description>Recent content in Race Discrimination on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/race-discrimination/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Story of Two Institutions: Regulation of Hate Speech in Europe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 02:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-story-of-two-institutions-regulation-of-hate-speech-in-europe/</guid><description>Clotilde Pégorier, Lecturer in Law, University of Essex
The regulation of hate speech has recently resurfaced as a crucial legal and political topic in Europe. While the complexity of this issue and the varying views on balancing legislation with rights protection are well-known, the contrasting approaches of the EU and the Council of Europe, two closely linked entities, is notable. This difference raises questions about its underlying reasons and broader legislative ramifications in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Is there more that the EU and its Member States can do to combat Holocaust denial and hate crime?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 11:27:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-more-that-the-eu-and-its-member-states-can-do-to-combat-holocaust-denial-and-hate-crime/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Coinciding with International Holocaust Remembrance Day, the European Commission has released its initial assessment of how EU member states are putting into action the EU Framework Decision. This legislation addresses combating racism and xenophobia through criminal law.
Putting EU Law into Practice
EU member states were obligated to incorporate this law, a carryover from the pre-Lisbon Treaty era, by December 2010. The Council was then expected to evaluate the member states&amp;rsquo; progress based on the Commission&amp;rsquo;s report by November 2013.</description></item><item><title>Revisiting Coleman: The Impact of Racial Discrimination on Collateral Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/</guid><description>Simon Cox
The Court of Justice of the European Union in Luxembourg recently heard arguments in a case regarding racial discrimination against Roma people. The case involves a non-Roma woman arguing that anyone negatively impacted by racially discriminatory actions deserves legal recourse under EU law. This case challenges the court&amp;rsquo;s prior decision in Coleman and seeks to clarify who can invoke EU discrimination law.
This case, originating from the Sofia Administrative Court, involves ten preliminary questions under the European Union Directive 2000/43 regarding racial discrimination.</description></item><item><title>We have the freedom to laugh at anything, but not everyone can appreciate it!" Examining the boundaries of freedom of expression through parody: the ruling of the CJEU in the Deckmyn case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 04:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-have-the-freedom-to-laugh-at-anything-but-not-everyone-can-appreciate-it-examining-the-boundaries-of-freedom-of-expression-through-parody-the-ruling-of-the-cjeu-in-the-deckmyn-case/</guid><description>By Sabine Jacques
PhD student focussing on the parody exception
at the School of Law, University of Nottingham (UK)
The Advocate-General recently issued an opinion on parody, sparking significant interest in the topic. This opinion, while not yet available in English, has been the subject of discussion in legal circles. Further amplifying this attention, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has now released its own judgment on the matter.</description></item><item><title>Is it against EU law to tolerate discrimination against women who are breastfeeding?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 21:59:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-against-eu-law-to-tolerate-discrimination-against-women-who-are-breastfeeding/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Nigel Farage, leader of the UK Independence Party, recently expressed that while he personally had no issue with public breastfeeding, businesses should set their own rules. He suggested businesses could ask breastfeeding women to move to a less conspicuous area, implying a discreet approach would be preferable.
His statement was prompted by incidents where a restaurant asked a woman to cover her baby while breastfeeding and another establishment suggested using the disabled restroom for this purpose.</description></item><item><title>Should there be increased use of majority voting in EU social policy decisions? Evaluating the Commission's suggestion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, PhD Candidate, University of Antwerp
In April 2019, the European Commission initiated a discussion on streamlining the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making in social policy. The goal was to enhance efficiency by utilizing &amp;ldquo;passerelle&amp;rdquo; clauses, which permit a shift from unanimous voting to qualified majority voting (QMV) and from special to ordinary legislative procedures. This change, while requiring unanimous approval from Member States, aims to bypass the complexities of Treaty revisions.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Appeal ruling in Benkharbouche and Janah: State immunity, remedies, and rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:57:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-appeal-ruling-in-benkharbouche-and-janah-state-immunity-remedies-and-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Benkharbouche v Sudan and Janah v Libya delves into significant aspects of public international law, the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), and the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, highlighting their interplay within the current British constitutional framework. The cases involved employment law claims brought by two domestic workers against the Sudanese and Libyan embassies, respectively. The embassies invoked state immunity under a UK law based on a Council of Europe Convention.</description></item></channel></rss>