<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Access to Documents on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-documents/</link><description>Recent content in Access to Documents on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/access-to-documents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU has restricted access to evidence through secretive means, pushing the boundaries of justice and cooperation within the European judicial system.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi &amp;amp; Christina Eckes*
*Assistant professor of European law, Maastricht University and professor of European law, University of Amsterdam, respectively.
Beyond a &amp;lsquo;Procedural&amp;rsquo; Adjustment
The European Union has encountered substantial political and economic turmoil in recent years. For the first time in its 60-year existence, it faces a Member State seeking to withdraw, confronts hostility and trade conflicts with its former transatlantic partner, and grapples with rising populist movements across Europe that challenge the EU&amp;rsquo;s core principles, such as the rule of law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-restricted-access-to-evidence-through-secretive-means-pushing-the-boundaries-of-justice-and-cooperation-within-the-european-judicial-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Access to documents: The Council may choose not to enforce a significant CJEU ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU is frequently criticized for its lack of transparency, particularly concerning its legislative processes. Ideally, these processes should be as open as those in national legislatures, allowing public access to draft legislation.
However, despite a 2001 regulation on public access to documents, EU transparency in this area remains an issue. Within the Council, some Member States prefer to keep their positions confidential during negotiations. This secrecy undermines the idea that citizens, through their national parliaments, can hold their governments accountable for actions taken within the Council...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it time for the EU to increase transparency in its legislative process, as condemned by the EU Court?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</guid><description>Massimo Frigo, Senior Legal Adviser of the International Commission of Jurist’s Europe Programme*
Occasionally, cases concerning seemingly insignificant administrative matters evolve into pivotal judgments, shaping the continuous development of our democratic legal frameworks. A prime example in the US is Marbury v. Madison, a case initially garnering limited public interest due to its focus on judicial appointment procedures. Nonetheless, it ultimately established the crucial precedent of constitutional review within the US legal system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In order to create more responsive rules, the EU-US transatlantic trade and partnership (TTIP) negotiations are crucial.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</guid><description>Dr. Elaine Fahey, Senior Lecturer, The City Law School, City University London
The script
The EU and US have concluded six rounds of discussions on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Agreement (TTIP). This agreement aims to reduce trade barriers and other obstacles, such as differing regulations and standards, across various industries. TTIP is promoted as potentially setting a global trade standard. Some argue it&amp;rsquo;s already irrelevant, but while this downplays its potential influence, skepticism is understandable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-order-to-create-more-responsive-rules-the-eu-us-transatlantic-trade-and-partnership-ttip-negotiations-are-crucial/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the European Parliament's Closed Reading Rooms: Shedding Light on Transparency in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Dr Vigjilenca Abazi
Assistant Professor of European Law
Maastricht University
Documents related to various topics, such as Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (TTIP) negotiations, EU Food Safety Authority oversight, and tax justice, share a common factor: accessing them requires select Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to participate in closed reading rooms. This blog post will examine how this departure from transparent parliamentary oversight is becoming increasingly common and question its potential impact on public access to documents requests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regarding knowledge as power: the transparency of procedures for making EU laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</guid><description>Päivi Leino (University of Helsinki)
A key promise made during the adoption of the Lisbon Treaty was increased transparency in EU law-making. However, this has not yet been realized. Access to documents related to EU legislative processes, especially &amp;ldquo;trilogues&amp;rdquo; (informal meetings between the European Parliament, the Council, and the Commission), has become a significant concern. This issue is highlighted in the new Interinstitutional Agreement (IIA) on Better Regulation, the European Ombudsman&amp;rsquo;s public consultation on trilogue transparency, and a legal appeal by a former LIBE Committee Secretariat head against the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s refusal to grant full access to legislative documents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there another accountability gap with the European Peace Facility?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 12:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</guid><description>Ellen Cantraine, PhD researcher, Ghent European Law Institute
Photo credit: Dietmar Rabich / Wikimedia Commons / “Münster, Stadtweinhaus, Beflaggung Ukraine und EU &amp;ndash; 2022 &amp;ndash; 0219” / CC BY-SA 4.0 / see also
Introduction
Following the 2021 coup attempt in Mali, the EU&amp;rsquo;s mission in Mali (EUTM) continued operating despite concerning reports of serious misconduct by EU-trained soldiers. Funded by the European Peace Facility (EPF), EUTM&amp;rsquo;s case exposed significant flaws in the EU&amp;rsquo;s external funding mechanisms...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-another-accountability-gap-with-the-european-peace-facility/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>