<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2065JMBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2065jmbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 2065JMBG4002 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/2065jmbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Functional Restoration and a Test Spin with Stanley Turrentine and Milt Jackson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</guid><description>This article details the restoration of a Beogram 4002 turntable from Kentucky. The unit, pictured below, was in excellent condition, making it ideal for a complete refurbishment.
As is typical with DC motor Beograms, the platter motor was the starting point. These motors commonly suffer from dried-out bearings, leading to speed instability. The extracted motor is shown here:
The motor was disassembled to access the bearings:
The bearings, visible as two small rings on the black pad, were then submerged in motor oil under a vacuum:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-functional-restoration-and-a-test-spin-with-stanley-turrentine-and-milt-jackson/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Kentucky</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable from Kentucky arrived safely thanks to its secure packaging. The turntable was in excellent cosmetic condition, with minimal scratching on the dust cover and un-cracked hinges.
Upon removing the cover, the aluminum surfaces appeared nearly flawless, showing only minor signs of wear. The keypad was also well-preserved, exhibiting only slight deterioration on the START key and a few insignificant marks. The pristine condition of the keypad made it an ideal candidate for the Beolover Commander remote control system, which protects such keypads from further wear...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-kentucky/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>