<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keypad on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/keypad/</link><description>Recent content in Keypad on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/keypad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival from California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 08:45:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-from-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (Type 5503; AC platter motor) turntable for restoration. The unit arrived in remarkably good shape. The dust cover is practically flawless, and the aluminum panels and platter are in fantastic condition.
However, there is a hole drilled into the top left corner of the aluminum plate surrounding the platter, meaning this part will need replacement. Thankfully, beneath the plates, the turntable appears to be in pristine, original condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 14:05:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002, model 5514, recently arrived in its original packaging, complete with styrofoam, which is remarkable! The platter was separately packaged in a vinyl box for added protection.
The turntable is in excellent cosmetic condition, requiring only cleaning. Even the keypad is in good shape, though using a 4002 Commander remote control could help prevent future wear.
The veneer corners are flawless, and the internal components appear untouched.
Initial testing showed the turntable powers on and the motor functions, but the arm doesn&amp;rsquo;t lower.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the Output Board, Installation of a Grounding Switch and Repair of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-output-board-installation-of-a-grounding-switch-and-repair-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is almost done. Today, I worked on Output PCB #8 and fixed a loose key on the keypad.
The Output PCB #8 was initially in this condition:
I prefer to replace the output relay as they tend to get stuck with age. Luckily, the relay is the same one used for platter RPM switching, so my custom replacement boards work here as well:
These replacement parts are available to anyone interested; feel free to email me.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad and RPM Panel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 02:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-and-rpm-panel/</guid><description>Slow response times from the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control panel buttons pointed to potential oxidation on the keypad contacts. This was confirmed upon opening the keypad assembly, revealing dull key contacts.
The contact pads were unsoldered and removed for a closer look. While they seemed okay, the leaf contacts engaged by the actuators showed signs of oxidation.
To address the oxidation, a fiberglass brush and Deoxit were used, restoring the contacts to a shiny and clean condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Restoration of Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-restoration-of-worn-keypad/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on restoring a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable and have reached the stage of addressing cosmetic details. A common issue with this model, as with approximately 90% of them, is a worn keypad. The original coating deteriorates over time due to exposure to skin oils and acids. This results in unsightly smudges, especially on units that have seen regular use. I recently acquired some refurbished keypads from a contact in Denmark to have on hand for my restoration projects.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from Germany En Route to California</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-en-route-to-california/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4000 turntable from Germany, intended for a customer in California. My task is to refurbish the unit and deliver it to its new owner.
The turntable was poorly packaged for shipment, resulting in the keypad plates becoming detached during transit. This led to minor damage to the plates themselves and some cosmetic imperfections on other internal surfaces.
The aluminum surfaces are in surprisingly good shape considering the loose keypad plates.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Stopover From Arizona on the Way to Portugal - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:59:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-stopover-from-arizona-on-the-way-to-portugal-a-first-look/</guid><description>Our company provides a service where we assist customers in buying vintage audio equipment from online marketplaces and other sellers. We arrange shipping to our facility, restore the unit, and then deliver it to the customer. It&amp;rsquo;s almost like taking a trip back in time to buy a brand new unit! This post documents the unboxing of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable purchased on eBay from an Arizona seller for a customer in Portugal.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable from Norway recently arrived for restoration. The packaging was excellent, using the original styrofoam inserts, and the only issue was two loose control pads, which were prevented from causing damage due to tape and foam inside. This highlights the importance of securing these pads with non-residue tape during shipping.
Fortunately, this is an easy repair. Cosmetically, the Beogram is in excellent condition.
The aluminum panels will gleam like new with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Rebuilding the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:17:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-rebuilding-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4002 (5513)&amp;rsquo;s arm lowering and tracking mechanisms, the next stage of restoration involved the electronics and platter drive. As usual, the process commenced with the replacement of all electrolytic capacitors on the printed circuit boards (PCBs) with new, high-quality Japanese capacitors rated for 105 degrees Celsius. To ensure the DC motor operates smoothly and without speed variations, the RPM relay was upgraded to a modern, enclosed unit, and 25-turn precision trimmers were installed for precise RPM adjustment.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Keypad Restoration and LEDs for the RPM Indicators</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 05:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-keypad-restoration-and-leds-for-the-rpm-indicators/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on had a significantly deteriorated keypad. The material used for these keypads tends to wear down over time due to the oils from fingerprints, making them a known weak point in this model.
My friend in Denmark, who sadly passed away recently, was an expert at restoring these keypads. In his memory, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to learn his techniques. A couple of months ago, I started practicing, and I managed to successfully restore one keypad.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing all Electrolytic Capacitors and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 19:12:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-all-electrolytic-capacitors-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, a humming sound and vibration from the solenoid were traced back to a faulty 30V power supply. The reservoir capacitance was depleted, causing instability in the solenoid&amp;rsquo;s power supply and preventing the arm lowering mechanism from functioning correctly.
To address this, the reservoir and motor capacitors were rebuilt. A custom-designed 3D printed part was used to house the new capacitors, ensuring a secure fit within the original capacitor bay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A Very Corroded New Arrival from Sweden</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 01:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-very-corroded-new-arrival-from-sweden/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the Beogram 4000 from Sweden is a mixed bag. Positively, the aluminum surfaces, platter, arm cover lettering, and panels are in good shape, though a thorough cleaning is needed to determine their true condition. The internal components appear original, and the red position indicator is intact. However, there are significant drawbacks.
The black enclosure parts have an unprecedented amount of corrosion, exceeding typical wear and tear. This corrosion is present even on the underside and has also affected the chassis&amp;rsquo;s leaf springs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Arrival from Arizona - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 21:48:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-arrival-from-arizona-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently received a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) from Arizona. It needed complete functional restoration. The unit arrived without its cover, shipped in a Beolover container, which is a great way to ensure safe transportation.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the unit as it looked when unpacked:
While a little dirty, it&amp;rsquo;s in decent condition except for the worn-out keypad:
Hopefully, these keypads can be professionally refurbished. On a positive note, the base is in good shape, with almost pristine corners:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival From West Virginia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-west-virginia/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable from West Virginia recently arrived for a complete restoration. The turntable was in good condition and shipped in a Beolover container.
Initial inspection revealed no significant damage to the dust cover or hinges. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, but the keypad has some wear. This will be addressed by installing a Beolover Commander remote control module, which allows for keypad-free operation.
The plinth is well-preserved, with minimal damage to the front corners, which are prone to wear.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 20:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-first-look/</guid><description>I recently began restoring a Beogram 4002 (5503) AC-motor turntable purchased from eBay. I had sent the seller specific packaging instructions and a sturdy double-boxed container, which they thankfully followed, resulting in the unit arriving undamaged. Initial observations are as follows:
The aluminum surfaces are generally in good shape, just needing a cleaning. The platter, in particular, has remarkably few imperfections.
The keypad shows typical signs of use, with fingerprints visible on the most frequently pressed keys.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Look (What a Packaging Mess!)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-look-what-a-packaging-mess-/</guid><description>I recently purchased a Beogram 4002 (5513) on eBay for a customer. Although the seller described it as being in very good cosmetic condition and included a new Soundsmith SMMC20 EN cartridge, the turntable arrived poorly packaged in a damaged box. Thankfully, the turntable itself was inside a second box with better protective materials.
Upon opening the inner box, I was relieved to find the Beogram 4002 in pristine condition, as advertised.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 12:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I recently began working on a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, which was exciting to receive in its original box and packaging. Upon opening it, I was greeted by a pleasant surprise—a pristine MMC20CL cartridge was mounted on the tonearm. Thankfully, it was protected by a cover and had been gently pressed against the styrofoam, keeping it safe during shipping.
Carefully, I removed the styrofoam and cartridge, relieved to find the cantilever was still centered and undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival and a First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 02:44:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-and-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, known for its unstable RPM, recently arrived for repair. The turntable was packaged well and arrived in excellent cosmetic condition with only minor blemishes.
The keypad appears barely used. However, the hood has some deep scratches, likely from improper storage. Internally, the turntable looks completely original.
Initial testing revealed the arm lowering mechanism is slow, and the automatic RPM switching from 33 to 45 is not functioning, although manual switching works.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 18:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>The recent arrival of a Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable from the UK marks the end of a summer break for one turntable enthusiast. This particular model is unique, showcasing transitional design elements between the Beogram 4000 and the later 4002 models.
ParcelHero, a shipping company offering swift and trackable service between the UK and US, delivered the turntable securely. Its efficient service, comparable in cost to standard international mail, is commendable.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: From German Ebay to Tampa via Hong Kong Poorly Packaged</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 01:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-from-german-ebay-to-tampa-via-hong-kong-poorly-packaged/</guid><description>I recently obtained a Beogram 4000 turntable that was poorly packaged during shipment from Germany to Hong Kong, resulting in significant damage. It&amp;rsquo;s unfortunate because the unit appeared to be in excellent condition before shipping, which is uncommon for Beogram 4000s these days. For tips on proper packaging of a 4000 turntable, please refer to our instructional video on our dedicated 4000 page.
The unsecured platter caused damage during transit, resulting in deep scratches on the underside of the plexiglass hood, potentially beyond repair.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival from Seattle en Route to Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-from-seattle-en-route-to-australia/</guid><description>An Australian customer purchased a Beogram 4002 on eBay from the US and sent it to me for restoration. Upon its arrival, I discovered it was in poor condition, likely due to storage in a basement or attic. The dust cover was particularly damaged, with scratches on the aluminum trim and the surface itself.
Despite the dust cover&amp;rsquo;s condition, the internal components appeared undamaged, including the hinges, suggesting a successful restoration is possible.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Keyboard Keys - Video About Removal and Installation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-keyboard-keys-video-about-removal-and-installation/</guid><description>After restoring a Beogram 4000, I shipped it to a customer, but two keypad keys came loose during transport. To secure them, I had used tape and foam, but the shipping stress was too much for the delicate leaf spring mechanism holding the keys.
To prevent this from happening again, I created special tools that make it easier to install the keys and shared a video demonstrating their use. These tools, designed to avoid damaging the aluminum, are available to other enthusiasts.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Restored Keypad and Plinth, a New Hood and Installation of the Beolover Commander Remote Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 06:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-restored-keypad-and-plinth-a-new-hood-and-installation-of-the-beolover-commander-remote-control/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I finished restoring the functionality of a Beogram 4002 (Type 5513), a project detailed in this post. Here&amp;rsquo;s how the unit appeared at that stage:
Although functionally restored, there were two noticeable cosmetic issues: a bleached area on the plinth and typical keypad wear from finger contact. It appears that skin oils negatively affect the keypad coating:
My client opted for a refurbished keypad. Additionally, the RPM panel&amp;rsquo;s plastic securing clamps were cracked, a common issue causing the panel to detach.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 19:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-first-look/</guid><description>This Beogram 4000, recently acquired in Germany, is about to undergo a complete restoration before being sent to its new home in the UK. A preliminary assessment reveals the aluminum surfaces to be in quite good condition.
The teak plinth is similarly well-preserved, with notably sharp corners.
While the original arm cover shows significant dirt accumulation, thorough cleaning is likely to improve its appearance. Sourcing a replacement would be challenging due to the unique labeling on this model – &amp;ldquo;tracking weight adjusting&amp;rdquo; instead of the &amp;ldquo;tracking force adjustment&amp;rdquo; found on the 4002.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Further Improvement of the RPM Stability Through Replacement of the RPM Trimmers and the RPM Relay</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:31:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-further-improvement-of-the-rpm-stability-through-replacement-of-the-rpm-trimmers-and-the-rpm-relay/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild, which significantly enhanced the RPM stability of the Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration project, the main RPM trimmers and relay were replaced. It was hoped this would further improve RPM stability and bring the Beogram back to the 0.05% specification outlined in the service manual. While accessing the main PCB, all electrolytic capacitors were exchanged with high-quality, 105C grade Japanese-manufactured equivalents. The board&amp;rsquo;s original and upgraded conditions are pictured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Colorado - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 08:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable arrived from Colorado for restoration, carefully packaged in a specialized box. The outer cover had several scratches but could potentially be polished to an acceptable condition. The hinges seemed fine, and the aluminum underneath the cover appeared to be in good shape. The control keypad showed only minor signs of wear.
The corners of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s base were almost pristine. However, upon inspection, the metal frames attached to the plinth were loosening, a common issue caused by deteriorating glue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A First Evaluation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:52:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-first-evaluation/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived for refurbishment, carefully packaged to prevent damage during shipping. The unit appears to be mostly original and in good cosmetic condition, with the exception of a worn keypad.
The keypad&amp;rsquo;s stamped metal sheet is not scratched, suggesting a straightforward restoration using a specialized technique. Interestingly, the STOP key shows more wear than the START key.
Further inspection revealed minor damage to the plinth corners and non-original screws securing the dust cover.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Some additions for a previous Beogram project from Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-some-additions-for-a-previous-beogram-project-from-houston/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 Type 5513 turntable I previously restored in 2018 was returned for a sensor lamp replacement. This turntable had also visited in 2020 for a broken tonearm cartridge mount.
During both prior repairs, the owner opted to retain some original, functioning components, including the sensor lamp, tracking sensor lamp, and output phono muting switch. Since the sensor lamp has now burned out, it will be replaced with a modern Beolover LED assembly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Restoration of the Worn Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-restoration-of-the-worn-keypad/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 Type 5523 I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on, like many others, required keypad restoration due to a common issue of a worn-out start key. The keypad&amp;rsquo;s condition upon arrival is shown in the first image.
The second picture showcases the keypad&amp;rsquo;s appearance after restoration.
To avoid damaging the keypad coating through contact with finger oils and friction, we suggest using a soft cloth for operation, regardless of whether it&amp;rsquo;s restored or original.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Another New Arrival - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:09:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-another-new-arrival-a-first-impression/</guid><description>I received another Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable that needs some care. After unboxing it, I was pleased to see the effective packing method, similar to what I demonstrate in my 4002 shipping video. The sturdy metal construction of the 4002 makes it relatively easy to ship safely with proper double boxing and precautions.
My initial assessment is positive. The aluminum surfaces are in great shape and will gleam with a thorough cleaning.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Keyboard Repair - Detached Backstops</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 11:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-keyboard-repair-detached-backstops/</guid><description>Following the AC motor hood restoration on a Beogram 4002 (5503), the next cosmetic issue addressed was the loose keypad backstops. Some keys were protruding and functioned erratically, requiring multiple presses.
Upon removing the keypad and its PCB, it was discovered that several plastic backstops had detached. A previous attempt to reattach them using double-sided tape proved unsuccessful, causing an uneven keypad surface.
The remaining backstops were easily removed, but precisely reattaching them posed a challenge.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): A New Arrival on Beolover's Bench - A First Impression</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench-a-first-impression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 13:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-a-new-arrival-on-beolovers-bench-a-first-impression/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable arrived yesterday, requiring some care. My initial assessment today was positive. The deck is quite clean with minimal cosmetic issues. The customer took great care in packaging, using a double box and securing the sub-platter with high-density foam. However, the tonearm transport support clamp detached during shipping. Thankfully, the arms were also protected with foam, preventing any damage.
The presence of orange fragments suggests that the transport lock bushings crumbled during shipment, a common problem with the 5513 model.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): First Contact and Two Dead Transistors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:08:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-first-contact-and-two-dead-transistors/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 that was already being repaired but needed further troubleshooting. The unit is in good cosmetic condition with minor wear. Upon inspection, the platter motor ran when turned on, but the carriage remained static.
Further investigation revealed that transistor TR20, responsible for the carriage motor control, was faulty. Replacing this component restored carriage movement.
However, the carriage would move only slightly before returning to its starting position.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Re-Attaching Keypad Segments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-re-attaching-keypad-segments/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:10:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-re-attaching-keypad-segments/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5513) restoration is moving along, and I&amp;rsquo;m currently focusing on aesthetics. The last step was to reattach two keypad sections that had become unglued. The image illustrates the problem:
I used a small amount of superglue gel and clamped the pads down with vise grips:
It&amp;rsquo;s important to use minimal glue to avoid damaging the delicate paint on the pad&amp;rsquo;s surface. Start with a small amount and add more if needed.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from California with a Bit of Shipping Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-california-with-a-bit-of-shipping-damage/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived needing some care, but unfortunately experienced additional damage during shipping. Upon opening the box, it was discovered that the carriage had detached from the pulley, which was stuck to tape residue. Thankfully, the tonearm was secured with tape, preventing it from ejecting through the platter opening and causing more severe damage. However, the tonearm did sustain some impact. This highlights the importance of securing the carriage during transport using foam and tape.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Some Final Touches - Replacing Plinth and Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-some-final-touches-replacing-plinth-and-keypad/</guid><description>Following the installation of the BeoloverRIAA internal preamplifier and the Commander remote control, this Beogram 4002 (5523) needed a few finishing touches.
The original plinth of the Beogram was damaged. A replacement plinth was sourced, but it also had minor damage, particularly to the corners. Inspired by a previous veneer repair on a Beomaster 8000, a similar approach was taken to address the plinth&amp;rsquo;s corners. Veneer was added and color-matched to the existing finish, significantly improving the appearance, although not completely perfect.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From New York</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 18:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-new-york/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently purchased on eBay was shipped using a specialized container to protect it in transit. Thankfully, the seller mostly followed the provided packing guidelines, resulting in no damage during shipping. Upon opening, the turntable was in good condition, with only minor issues.
While the blue tape used on the aluminum surfaces didn&amp;rsquo;t cause any damage to the lettering, there were a few scratches on the platter. These were likely caused by attempts to remove it improperly.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Rebuilding the Control System and RPM Stability Qualification with the BeoloverRPM Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-rebuilding-the-control-system-and-rpm-stability-qualification-with-the-beoloverrpm-device/</guid><description>After addressing the fundamental components, such as the tracking system and platter motor, in the Beogram 4002 (5523) restoration project, I turned my attention to enhancing the electronic control system. This involved replacing electrolytic capacitors, baseline RPM trimmers, and the RPM and output relays. Additionally, I incorporated a grounding switch to connect system and signal grounds, a measure often effective in mitigating ground loop/humming problems.
Here are some noteworthy observations:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Assembly - Gold Plated Switch Terminals and Light Bulbs Replaced with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the repair of the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking systems, the next step was to focus on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control center: the keypad assembly. This unit houses an early digital control system that manages inputs from the keypad&amp;rsquo;s keys. The mechanical switches connected to these keys are a common source of problems and should be gold-plated to ensure reliable, long-term operation after restoration.
The keypad cluster was removed from the Beogram and opened, revealing a missing light bulb in the position indicator scale.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Terminals in Control System Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 10:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-terminals-in-control-system-switches/</guid><description>A customer expressed interest in purchasing a Beogram 4000 I refurbished last year, prompting me to address the final restoration step: gold plating the contact terminals in the carriage position and keypad switches. These switches are critical for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control system, and even a single malfunction can lead to significant operational problems. Gold plating enhances their long-term reliability and performance.
Extracting the contact terminals is a meticulous process due to their spring-loaded solder connections to the PCBs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Worn Keypad Restoration - My Process Finally Appears Reproducible...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-worn-keypad-restoration-my-process-finally-appears-reproducible/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5501) I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a common issue: a worn-out keypad. The start button, in particular, was in rough shape due to frequent use.
After a multi-month endeavor, I successfully restored the keypad to an almost-new appearance. My refined restoration method finally produces consistent results, marking a significant step forward in the 4002&amp;rsquo;s rehabilitation.
During the process, I discovered another problem: a broken RPM panel clamp. This prevented the RPM panel from staying securely in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Exchanging all Electrolytic Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 13:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-exchanging-all-electrolytic-capacitors/</guid><description>After finishing most of the mechanical work, it was time to start repairing the electronics on a Beogram 4002 (5503) turntable. Replacing all electrolytic capacitors is recommended, as their internal fluid often leaks or dries up. I use high-quality Japanese capacitors to ensure my repairs last as long as possible. Tantalum capacitors, in particular, must be replaced because they can fail dramatically if a short circuit occurs, potentially damaging the circuit board.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival from the UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 01:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-the-uk/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable recently arrived from a UK seller for restoration. This report outlines its pre-restoration condition.
Upon arrival, the unit was quite dirty but in good overall shape. The dust cover showed typical scratches from storage, many deep enough to feel with a fingernail. However, it can be polished back to good condition. Positively, the dust cover features an aluminum strip instead of the less durable plastic type, and the hinges appear to be intact.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Michigan - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 20:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-michigan-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Michigan for restoration, carefully packaged according to instructions. The aluminum surfaces are in good condition, with one minor dent on the platter&amp;rsquo;s surrounding plate. The platter itself, keypads, and small aluminum plate are also in good shape. However, one corner of the plinth is damaged. Fortunately, replacement plinth panels were included, which will be installed.
The hood has noticeable scratches, primarily on the surface, and should polish well.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Light Bulbs in the Control Panel and Gold Plating of the Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-light-bulbs-in-the-control-panel-and-gold-plating-of-the-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>The next stage of restoring my Beogram 4000 involved working on the control panel. Typically, I swap out the old incandescent bulbs for LEDs and clean the keypad&amp;rsquo;s contacts. This particular unit had three out of four bulbs burnt out, highlighting the wisdom of switching to LEDs for their superior lifespan.
I had recently designed SMD LED boards to replace the position scale illumination bulbs (the top two) and had them professionally manufactured.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Restoration of a Keypad with a Worn Through Start Button</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:47:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-restoration-of-a-keypad-with-a-worn-through-start-button/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 keypad, showing signs of wear, was recently sent from New Zealand. The start button&amp;rsquo;s coating was entirely worn down:
This is a common problem for Beogram keypads. The combination of skin acids and friction wears away the coating.
Fortunately, this is fixable. Here is the keypad after being restored:
It looks great! The coating will be left to harden further before being returned to New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (Type 5513): Full Upgrade with SyncDrive Platter Motor, Commander Remote Control and Internal RIAA Pre-Amplifier</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-full-upgrade-with-syncdrive-platter-motor-commander-remote-control-and-internal-riaa-pre-amplifier/</guid><description>A customer from Kentucky requested a full upgrade for their Beogram 4002 turntable, including three modifications: a SyncDrive motor for enhanced speed stability, a Commander remote control system for convenient operation and keypad protection, and a Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier for direct connection to modern audio equipment.
All upgrades were installed without soldering. The SyncDrive replaced the original DC motor, connecting to existing mounting points and the main circuit board. The Beolover RIAA pre-amplifier replaced the output board, using compatible connectors for easy installation.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacing the Keypad Light Bulbs with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacing-the-keypad-light-bulbs-with-leds/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with replacing the control panel&amp;rsquo;s light bulbs with LEDs. This enhances the unit&amp;rsquo;s lifespan and prevents issues that incandescent bulbs, susceptible to vibration, can experience during shipping.
The top two bulbs illuminate the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s unique position indicator, while the vertical bulbs light the RPM trimmers. I recently designed SMD LED-based PCB replacements for the position indicator bulbs (available via email).
Standard red LEDs with current-limiting resistors can replace the RPM trimmer bulbs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival - A First Look</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-a-first-look/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable arrived in need of repair. The packaging was generally good, but the cartridge was not secured properly for transport. Thankfully, the delicate cantilever was undamaged. The first step was to safely store the cartridge in a specialized MMC cartridge box. These boxes are offered to customers who are shipping their Beograms for restoration and are also available for the MMC1-5 cartridges.
An initial assessment showed that the aluminum panels were in good condition.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Replacing the Electrolytic Capacitors, RPM Relay and Trimmers on the Main PCB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 09:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-replacing-the-electrolytic-capacitors-rpm-relay-and-trimmers-on-the-main-pcb/</guid><description>Following the DC motor rebuild on this Beogram 4002 (5513), the main PCB was addressed. All electrolytic capacitors were swapped with high-quality, Japanese-made, 105C-rated capacitors. The existing Tantalum capacitors, known for their tendency to fail dramatically, were preemptively replaced with modern equivalents to avoid any potential issues. Images illustrate the original board and the sections targeted for capacitor replacement.
The author designed a replacement for the original Siemens relay using a modern, fully encapsulated SMD relay.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): Rebuilding the DC Motor</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-rebuilding-the-dc-motor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:32:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-rebuilding-the-dc-motor/</guid><description>My initial assessment of the recently acquired Beogram 4002 turntable revealed a noisy DC motor. The sleeve bearings were dry, causing a high-pitched sound when spinning without the load of the belt and platter. To restore peace to my workspace and enjoy some vinyl, I decided to fix this first.
The motor was removed from its mounting plate by unscrewing two screws and carefully prying off the glued pulley. After opening the outer enclosure, the motor was extracted.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of Incandescent Light Bulbs in Control Panel with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-incandescent-light-bulbs-in-control-panel-with-leds/</guid><description>During the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable, all four incandescent bulbs in the control panel were found to be non-functional. This highlighted the fragility of these bulbs and emphasized the need for a more durable solution. To address this, the original bulbs were replaced with custom-designed LED replacements.
Specifically, the two position indicator bulbs were replaced with surface-mounted LED (SMD LED) units. The two bulbs responsible for illuminating the RPM trimmers were replaced with high-intensity red LEDs.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5521): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5521-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (5521) in visually appealing condition recently arrived for restoration. The turntable came with a known faulty tracking sensor, burned-out 33 RPM indicator lights, and was secured in a double box for safe transport. A previous video on packing a 4002/4 for shipping can be found here. This image shows the inner packaging:
Here is the unit unpacked: Foam pads secured the sub-platter, and importantly, the tonearm and RPM panel were protected with removable tape for shipping.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): A New Arrival - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:29:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-a-new-arrival-first-impressions/</guid><description>I recently acquired a Beogram 4002 (5503) for restoration. The 5503 is the North American version of the 5501/5502 models, evident in the non-functional voltage switch included to maintain a consistent appearance.
This Beogram is in excellent overall condition, featuring high-quality veneer on the plinth and a dust cover with typical scratches that can be polished to near-original clarity. Internally, it appears largely untouched, though there are indications of prior work, such as loose bolts in the tracking and tonearm mechanisms.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Cluster</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-cluster/</guid><description>Following the repair of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s electrolytic capacitors and AC motor, the focus shifted to restoring the keypad cluster. The circuitry underneath the keypad forms the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system, a pioneering digital system utilizing TTL logic chips. This system relies heavily on inputs from numerous mechanical switches within the turntable to make decisions. The keypad itself houses eight of these switches, allowing user interaction.
The keypad was held by a single screw, which was missing, hinting at previous tampering.</description></item></channel></rss>