<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Family on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family/</link><description>Recent content in Family on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:51:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happy Thanksgiving From Telexplainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 23:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/happy-thanksgiving-from-telexplainer/</guid><description>Wishing you a joyous and safe Thanksgiving filled with loved ones.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese New Year promotion by Digi highlights the importance of family and tradition</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-chinese-new-year-promotion-by-digi-highlights-the-importance-of-family-and-tradition/</guid><description>Source: Digi website.
For many Chinese individuals, the Chinese New Year signifies the only opportunity to reconnect with distant family members. Malaysian telecommunications company Digi is capitalizing on this tradition with a new promotional campaign designed for a global audience.
Recognizing that in today&amp;rsquo;s world, many individuals simply use titles like &amp;lsquo;aunt,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;uncle,&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;cousin&amp;rsquo; for relatives beyond their immediate family, Digi&amp;rsquo;s campaign encourages the use of more precise family titles within Chinese families.</description></item><item><title>Family-run businesses in Singapore are the least ready for succession planning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/family-run-businesses-in-singapore-are-the-least-ready-for-succession-planning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/family-run-businesses-in-singapore-are-the-least-ready-for-succession-planning/</guid><description>A new report by the Economist Intelligence Unit, commissioned by Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (IBFC), reveals that Singaporean family businesses are the least prepared in Southeast Asia for leadership transition.
Source: Labuan IBFC.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Building Legacies: Family Business Succession in Southeast Asia,&amp;rdquo; found that only 58% of Singaporean family businesses have a succession plan. While 35% utilize formal wealth management structures like private foundations, and 41% use trusts for intergenerational wealth transfer, these numbers fall short compared to similar businesses in Indonesia, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Thailand.</description></item></channel></rss>