<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Derogations on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/derogations/</link><description>Recent content in Derogations on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/derogations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The application of the EU Charter of Rights to derogations in the internal market of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 19:26:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-application-of-the-eu-charter-of-rights-to-derogations-in-the-internal-market-of-member-states/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Pfleger case confirmed a significant point about the reach of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights. However, it also indirectly raised some doubts about the Charter&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness in such situations.
This case revolved around Austria&amp;rsquo;s limitations on gambling machines. The CJEU has handled numerous cases concerning national gambling restrictions, a topic not comprehensively addressed by EU law but still generally falling under EU internal market rules.</description></item><item><title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Health Interventions in Cases of Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:18:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-health-interventions-in-cases-of-free-movement/</guid><description>Angus MacCulloch, Lancaster University Law School
Two recent rulings concerning the free movement of goods (Articles 34/36 TFEU) highlight the critical importance of strong evidence when governments attempt to justify public health interventions in the market. The first example, a judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in Case C-148/15 Deutsche Parkinson Vereinigung, addressed the legality of fixed prices for prescription medicines in Germany. The second, a ruling from the Inner House of the Court of Session in Scotland in Scotch Whisky Assoc v LA [2016] CSIH 77, upheld the Scottish Government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce minimum unit pricing (MUP) for alcohol, finding it compatible with Article 34.</description></item><item><title>Who should have control over the 'emergency brake' on benefits for EU citizens: the Commission or the Council?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 22:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-should-have-control-over-the-emergency-brake-on-benefits-for-eu-citizens-the-commission-or-the-council/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
During the UK&amp;rsquo;s negotiations to leave the European Union, a key point of contention arose: the process for enacting an &amp;ldquo;emergency brake&amp;rdquo; to restrict EU citizens&amp;rsquo; access to in-work benefits. Should a Member State have the authority to implement this measure independently, perhaps with a requirement to inform the Commission and Council? Or should it be required to submit a request, leaving the decision of authorization to the Commission and/or Council?</description></item></channel></rss>