<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sage on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sage/</link><description>Recent content in Sage on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:43:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The impact of GDPR will be remembered in 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 06:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-gdpr-will-be-remembered-in-2018/</guid><description>The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) heavily influenced how we addressed online privacy in 2018. While it primarily protects residents of the European Union, the GDPR&amp;rsquo;s global reach impacts any company conducting business with EU residents. This broad scope has shifted GDPR from a regional concern to a worldwide one.
Several industry leaders have shared their perspectives on GDPR&amp;rsquo;s significant effects:
Source: Sage. Wherrett.
Arlene Wherrett, VP and MD of Sage Asia, observed that GDPR was a major catalyst for change in business operations.</description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality.</description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality introduces the new Sage Hotel brand, catering specifically to upscale business travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</guid><description>SilverNeedle Hospitality, headquartered in Singapore, has introduced a new upscale hotel brand, Sage Hotel, tailored for business travelers. The first Sage Hotel will be located in Brisbane, Australia.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated, &amp;ldquo;We recognize a significant group of business travelers seeking a consistent and straightforward experience while working in unfamiliar cities.&amp;rdquo; He added, &amp;ldquo;Sage Hotel is designed to meet their needs and complements our existing portfolio of six brands.</description></item></channel></rss>