<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vegan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vegan/</link><description>Recent content in Vegan on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:02:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/vegan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>KVD Vegan Beauty marks a decade of success with the Tattoo Liner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/</guid><description>KVD Vegan Beauty is launching a global campaign, CAT EYES FOR ALL, this March to celebrate the tenth anniversary of their Tattoo Liner. The campaign will feature Instagram-famous feline, @CobytheCat, known for his naturally winged eyes.
The campaign will promote the brand&amp;rsquo;s long-lasting liquid eyeliner, Tattoo Liner, available in Trooper Black and Mad Max Brown, along with the volumizing Go Big or Go Home mascara.
The campaign features other diverse models, including KVD Vegan Beauty International Makeup Artist Fanny Maurer, Chloé Nguyen, and Carmen Lee Solomons, as well as a senior model, to illustrate that Tattoo Liner is suitable for all ages, eye shapes, and ethnicities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/kvd-vegan-beauty-marks-a-decade-of-success-with-the-tattoo-liner/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals, a brand that is committed to being cruelty-free, has launched a new range of eyeshadows</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:42:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</guid><description>Everyday Minerals (EM) prioritizes using the purest natural ingredients to create all-natural, vegan, and cruelty-free makeup. Their products are handmade in Texas and packaged in eco-friendly, recyclable materials.
Source: Everyday Minerals blog.
Vegan makeup is characterized by its exclusion of animal-derived ingredients and its non-reliance on animal testing. Ingredients like lanolin and collagen are examples of animal-derived components. A growing number of cosmetics companies are introducing vegan product lines or, like EM, adopting a fully vegan approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-a-brand-that-is-committed-to-being-cruelty-free-has-launched-a-new-range-of-eyeshadows/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Delcie's provides mooncakes that are halal, vegan, sugar-free, and gluten-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 07:36:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</guid><description>Delcie&amp;rsquo;s Desserts and Cakes is now accepting mooncake orders for 2017.
They offer a variety of halal-certified mooncakes, including vegetarian, vegan, sugar-free, low-sugar, and even gluten-free sugar-free options. Orders are taken on a first-come, first-served basis and require full payment in advance.
Source: Delcie&amp;rsquo;s website. Their popular spiral flaky sugar-free mooncakes are filled with sugar-free pandan paste.
This year, they&amp;rsquo;ve added a new flavor: white lotus with salted mung bean, made without cane sugar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/delcie-s-provides-mooncakes-that-are-halal-vegan-sugar-free-and-gluten-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Everyday Minerals introduces a new line of mineral color correctors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 23:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</guid><description>Source: Everyday Minerals website.
Everyday Minerals claims to have formulated its finest mineral color correctors to date. These all-natural correctors feature jojoba esters, enabling them to conceal imperfections seamlessly without appearing heavy.
The new Jojoba Color Correctors are offered in four shades, each formulated for a specific purpose. The pink-hued Brighten Color Corrector utilizes light-diffusing pigments to instantly illuminate dark circles under the eyes. The Cover Color Corrector, in a natural skin tone, can be used after foundation for concealing blemishes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/everyday-minerals-introduces-a-new-line-of-mineral-color-correctors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore introduces new Vegan OmniMeat Retail Pack</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-introduces-new-vegan-omnimeat-retail-pack/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 22:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-introduces-new-vegan-omnimeat-retail-pack/</guid><description>Source: Green Monday. The OmniMeat Retail Pack.
Green Monday, a Hong Kong social venture promoting sustainable and healthy plant-based living to combat climate change, introduced the OmniMeat Retail Pack to Singapore.
The name &amp;ldquo;OmniMeat&amp;rdquo; reflects its versatility in various dishes. Its texture is appealingly succulent, tender, and juicy, allowing for diverse seasonings.
David Yeung, the founder of OmniMeat and Green Monday, highlights that the product caters exceptionally well to Eastern culinary traditions and palates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-introduces-new-vegan-omnimeat-retail-pack/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-introduces-new-vegan-omnimeat-retail-pack/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>