<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Traveller on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traveller/</link><description>Recent content in Traveller on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:09:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/traveller/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Analyzing the behavior of luxury travelers from China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 19:09:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</guid><description>A recent study on Chinese luxury travelers, conducted by Marriott International and the Hurun Research Institute, reveals evolving travel preferences among young, affluent Chinese travelers aged 18 to 36. These travelers seek personalized experiences, value-added services throughout their journey, and seamless integration of technology.
The study indicates a preference for digital platforms, with WeChat emerging as the primary source for travel information, followed by official accounts, recommendations from friends, and travel professionals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-behavior-of-luxury-travelers-from-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality is introducing an upgraded hotel sleep experience for travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality
SilverNeedle Hospitality, a company focused on hospitality investment, management, and development, is launching the SilverNeedle DreamWeave Sleep System to enhance the sleep quality of its guests. This system will be implemented in all new hotels joining their network across midscale to luxury categories and will be gradually introduced to existing properties in those segments over time.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director and Group CEO of SilverNeedle Hospitality, emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s dedication to improving business travel by acknowledging the importance of sleep for their guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-is-introducing-an-upgraded-hotel-sleep-experience-for-travelers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dubai's tourism numbers have increased thanks to MICE travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 21:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</guid><description>During the first six months of 2014, Dubai&amp;rsquo;s hotels received a record-breaking 5.8 million guests, as reported by Dubai&amp;rsquo;s Department of Tourism and Commerce Marketing (DTCM).
DTCM attributes this surge in tourism to Dubai&amp;rsquo;s prominent position as a regional center for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events (MICE). A prime example was the incentive trip in April that brought in over 14,500 delegates from China alone. Significant business events hosted in the first half of 2014 included Gulfood, the Arabian Travel Market, and Intersec, a major trade show for safety, security, and fire protection in the region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dubai-s-tourism-numbers-have-increased-thanks-to-mice-travelers/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>