<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IP Packets on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-packets/</link><description>Recent content in IP Packets on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ip-packets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IP Exchange - The Final Piece For VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</guid><description>The shift from circuit-switched to packet-switched telephone networks is undeniable. While large companies have adopted enterprise VoIP to enhance efficiency, cut expenses, and prepare for the future, small and medium businesses are considering SIP trunking for bundled high-quality telephone and broadband services. Consumers are switching to cable broadband-telephone packages or third-party VoIP options. However, the PSTN remains.
Currently, VoIP systems and services operate in isolation. On-net calls, meaning calls within the same service regardless of location, are often free...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-exchange-the-final-piece-for-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking and Internet On a T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</guid><description>Many smaller companies utilize T1 lines for dedicated internet access, opting for this solution after experiencing unreliable or unavailable consumer-grade broadband options. T1 lines offer these businesses dependable, robust bandwidth at increasingly affordable prices. However, many are unaware that they can bundle their broadband and telephone services onto a single T1 line.
Traditional T1 lines offer various service options. The original format, designed for the telephone industry, provides 24 channels of digitized telephone service over two pairs of twisted copper phone wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband Ethernet Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</guid><description>While we often associate Ethernet with local area networks (LANs), its reach extends far beyond. Ethernet has transitioned from LANs to metropolitan area networks (MANs) and even wide area networks (WANs), enabling businesses to connect across cities, countries, and even globally.
How does this relate to the Internet? The Internet relies on IP routing, but its growth was fueled by existing telephone company technologies like T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH. These technologies provided the infrastructure to transmit IP packets alongside voice and data traffic...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-ethernet-connections/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>