<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Canada on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/canada/</link><description>Recent content in Canada on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/canada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>The German Constitutional Court's Role in EU Trade Policy: Analyzing the EU/Canada Trade Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:14:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-german-constitutional-court-s-role-in-eu-trade-policy-analyzing-the-eu-canada-trade-agreement/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, Emeritus Professor of International Law, London Metropolitan University; Associate, Oxford Martin School, University of Oxford
A major issue for the EU is whether to sign and provisionally implement CETA, the free trade agreement with Canada. How this power is divided between the EU and its Member States is important, as it determines whether individual countries could veto parts or all of the agreement. This situation is complex, potentially hindering the deal&amp;rsquo;s proponents while empowering its critics.</description></item><item><title>$8.33/mo Small Business &amp; Residential VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-833mo-small-business-residential-voip/</guid><description>Forget expensive phone plans advertised on TV, there&amp;rsquo;s a better option for homes and small businesses. For just $8.33 a month, Phone Power offers unlimited calls within the US and Canada, plus a free hour of international calls.
This Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) service works with your existing internet connection. Phone Power provides a free adapter that connects to your modem and lets you use two phones on a single line.</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>Call Overseas For Pennies From Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>With cell phones now serving as both personal and business lines, affordable landline long distance isn&amp;rsquo;t very useful. The real desire is for better rates on mobile phones. Considering you already have domestic calling and internet, the missing piece is inexpensive international calling.
TEL3 recognized this trend and developed their TEL3Advantage service for mobile users in the US and Canada. Many people need to call contacts internationally, but affordable mobile options have been limited until now.</description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline.</description></item><item><title>Background information for next week's hearing on the scope of EU external trade policy: Opinion 2/15</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/background-information-for-next-week-s-hearing-on-the-scope-of-eu-external-trade-policy-opinion-2-15/</guid><description>Dr Andrés Delgado Casteleiro
Senior Research Fellow, Max Planck Institute Luxembourg for International, European and Regulatory Procedural Law
Introduction
On September 13th and 14th, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) convened a full court hearing to discuss Opinion 2/15. This opinion focuses on the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority to establish a new Free Trade Agreement (FTA) with Singapore. This blog post will provide a concise summary of the key issues likely to arise during these hearings.</description></item><item><title>Commentary on the EU/Canada free trade agreement and its implications on the Irish constitution: Costello v The Government of Ireland and Ors [2022] IESC 44</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 02:23:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/commentary-on-the-eu-canada-free-trade-agreement-and-its-implications-on-the-irish-constitution-costello-v-the-government-of-ireland-and-ors-2022-iesc-44/</guid><description>Dr John Cotter, Lecturer in Law, Keele University, UK
Photo credit: Guiseppe Milo, via wikicommons media
Background
The EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA), signed in 2016 after five years of talks, came at a critical point in EU trade policy. While trade wasn&amp;rsquo;t central to the Brexit vote earlier that year, prominent Brexit supporters used the EU&amp;rsquo;s slow trade deal progress to argue for a more agile UK that could ratify deals faster.</description></item><item><title>Recent advancements in the European Citizens' Initiative have been made as the General Court has issued a ruling on the 'Stop TTIP' initiative.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 19:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-advancements-in-the-european-citizens-initiative-have-been-made-as-the-general-court-has-issued-a-ruling-on-the-stop-ttip-initiative/</guid><description>_Anastasia Karatzia, _Assistant Professor in EU Law, Erasmus University Rotterdam and currently Visiting Research Fellow at the School of Law and Social Justice, University of Liverpool
Introduction
Several months ago, a significant legal development took place regarding the European Citizens&amp;rsquo; Initiative (ECI). The EU’s General Court overturned, for the first time, a European Commission decision. This decision had blocked the registration of a proposed ECI known as ‘Minority SafePack.’ Just recently, the General Court made another impactful judgment concerning the ECI.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU/Canada free trade deal and investor protection disputes a blessing in disguise or a cause for concern?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-canada-free-trade-deal-and-investor-protection-disputes-a-blessing-in-disguise-or-a-cause-for-concern/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent news suggests the EU/Canada free-trade agreement (CETA) faces obstacles due to the German government&amp;rsquo;s opposition to rules concerning investor/state dispute settlement. This situation carries potential implications for various aspects, including the EU/Canada and EU/USA trade deals, the EU&amp;rsquo;s broader trade and investment policies, and even the UK&amp;rsquo;s potential departure from the EU (&amp;ldquo;Brexit&amp;rdquo;).
Background
After commencing negotiations in 2009, the EU and Canada reached a preliminary agreement in 2013, pending finalization of technical points.</description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join.</description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees.</description></item></channel></rss>