<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mexico on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mexico/</link><description>Recent content in Mexico on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mexico/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aeromexico introduces an additional flight connecting Shanghai and Mexico City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 02:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aeromexico-introduces-an-additional-flight-connecting-shanghai-and-mexico-city/</guid><description>Starting July 1st, Aeromexico will expand its service between Shanghai and Mexico City to include a third weekly flight on Sundays. This increase will bring the total number of seats available on the route to over 1,500 each week. The flights, operated by Boeing 777 aircraft, accommodate 277 passengers with 49 business class seats and 228 economy seats.
Each Aeromexico flight features personal entertainment systems, increased passenger space, and lie-flat seats in Clase Premier, its business class section.</description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous.</description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond.</description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees.</description></item></channel></rss>