<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International Agreements on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-agreements/</link><description>Recent content in International Agreements on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-agreements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Connection that's Missing: The Impact of Direct Effect, CETA/TTIP, and Investor-State Dispute Settlement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connection-that-s-missing-the-impact-of-direct-effect-ceta-ttip-and-investor-state-dispute-settlement/</guid><description>By Daniel Thym, Chair of Public, European and International Law, University of Konstanz
International trade agreements, particularly the proposed deals between the EU and the US (TTIP) and Canada (CETA), have garnered significant public interest. However, many legal professionals and students lack familiarity with this area of law and often apply domestic legal concepts to the international arena. For instance, there&amp;rsquo;s an assumption that national courts can enforce international trade rules and that companies can challenge state actions under these agreements in domestic courts.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU once again reinforces the EU's external role with In Vino Veritas ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:48:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-once-again-reinforces-the-eu-s-external-role-with-in-vino-veritas-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While only a handful of EU countries excel in wine production, it&amp;rsquo;s enjoyed throughout the Union. This simple truth underpins the recent Germany v Council ruling, where the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) bolstered the EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign relations authority, aligning with several previous decisions.
Background
This case centers on instances where Member States act as &amp;rsquo;trustees&amp;rsquo; of the EU&amp;rsquo;s external competence. This situation arises when the EU, despite having authority over a subject, cannot join a treaty or international organization dealing with it (a frequent occurrence).</description></item><item><title>The ECJ clarifies EU's authority over copyright law in the Marrakesh Treaty ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 02:37:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-clarifies-eu-s-authority-over-copyright-law-in-the-marrakesh-treaty-ruling/</guid><description>Gesa Kübek, PhD candidate at the law faculty of the University of Passau.
In its February 14, 2017 Opinion 3/15, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) determined that the European Union (EU) possesses exclusive competence to enter into the Marrakesh Treaty to Facilitate Access to Published Works for Persons Who Are Blind, Visually Impaired, or Otherwise Print Disabled (hereafter: Marrakesh Treaty). This decision aligns with Advocate General (AG) Wahl’s prior Opinion, which similarly argued for exclusive EU competence in this domain.</description></item></channel></rss>