<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Packet Switched Architecture on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-switched-architecture/</link><description>Recent content in Packet Switched Architecture on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:11:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/packet-switched-architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Makes the Upgrades Easy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic bandwidth has always been a popular choice for businesses, particularly those requiring high-speed connections. The good news is that fiber optic service is becoming increasingly accessible to businesses. IT managers and executives now face a decision: stick with their existing copper wireline services or upgrade to fiber optics. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the factors that make fiber optics the preferred choice.
Fiber Optics: The Way of the Future..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-makes-the-upgrades-easy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cost Performance Advantage of Ethernet over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</guid><description>Businesses rely on various bandwidth connections for numerous tasks, ranging from credit card processing and email to data transfers and research. While options like DSL, cable, and T1 lines exist, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative due to its cost-effectiveness and performance advantages.
EoC aligns with modern networking, as most networks today utilize Ethernet. Unlike older services designed for voice communication, EoC caters to the digital era&amp;rsquo;s demands, such as email, video streaming, and online activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cost-performance-advantage-of-ethernet-over-copper/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>