<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Process on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-process/</link><description>Recent content in Business Process on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Green Way To Get Documents Signed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 04:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/</guid><description>The excessive paperwork in business today contradicts early predictions of a paperless office. Despite the rise of computers, high-speed printers led to increased printing, resulting in a cycle of paper consumption and shredding.
Cloud services offer a potential solution by enabling work processes that don&amp;rsquo;t rely on physical documents. While some businesses transition to online operations, others remain partially offline, necessitating physical documents for legal and operational purposes.
This reliance on paper persists due to the need for legally valid signatures on agreements, forms, and contracts, as digital communication methods are often insufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-green-way-to-get-documents-signed/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>