<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Machine on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/machine/</link><description>Recent content in Machine on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/machine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bank Simpanan Nasional has launched virtual teller machines in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 05:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-simpanan-nasional-has-launched-virtual-teller-machines-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Bank Simpanan Nasional (BSN) is the first bank in Malaysia to introduce virtual teller machines (VTMs). These machines allow bank tellers to assist customers in different locations throughout Malaysia remotely, through a live virtual banking system.
BSN&amp;rsquo;s adoption of VTMs was inspired by kiosk banking already in place in other countries, including those in Europe, China, Canada, and the US. The project is a collaboration between BSN and Vastcomp to develop a specialized system.</description></item><item><title>De’Longhi introduces the La Specialista Prestigio, a high-end pump espresso coffee machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/de-longhi-introduces-the-la-specialista-prestigio-a-high-end-pump-espresso-coffee-machine/</guid><description>De&amp;rsquo;Longhi recently unveiled its new La Specialista Prestigio espresso machine with a global campaign titled &amp;ldquo;Perfetto.&amp;rdquo; This campaign, directed by Damien Chazelle and starring Brad Pitt, offers a glimpse into Pitt&amp;rsquo;s daily routine, emphasizing how De&amp;rsquo;Longhi&amp;rsquo;s products seamlessly integrate into a refined lifestyle. The advertisement showcases a world where achieving the perfect cup of coffee is as simple as pressing a button, providing a luxurious bean-to-cup experience. The campaign can be viewed on YouTube.</description></item></channel></rss>