<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regulatory Agencies on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulatory-agencies/</link><description>Recent content in Regulatory Agencies on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:54:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulatory-agencies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New EU Regulatory Guidelines for Net Neutrality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
New EU regulations designed to ensure equal treatment of internet traffic were enacted in the fall of 2015 and implemented in April 2016. These net neutrality rules were intended to prevent discrimination by internet service providers and promote innovation, but their effectiveness was debated.
The regulations stipulate that internet providers should treat all traffic the same, regardless of the source, content, or device. However, the vague language and exceptions within the regulations led to uncertainty regarding the level of protection for users and permitted provider activities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ERGA and the Audiovisual and Media Services Directive 2.0: A European Regulators Group without Borders?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 20:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
In 2014, the European Commission created ERGA to help implement the Audiovisual Media Services Directive (AVMSD) and support a unified European market. This built upon the existing High Level Group of Regulatory Authorities, established in 2003, which brought national enforcement bodies together twice a year. The goal was to improve collaboration between these authorities to ensure the AVMSD was applied consistently across Europe. This reflects a broader EU trend of forming networks, sometimes including member states, to promote harmonization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/erga-and-the-audiovisual-and-media-services-directive-2-0-a-european-regulators-group-without-borders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experimenting with EU governance in the Telecoms sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 09:29:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</guid><description>Marta Cantero (Postdoctoral Researcher, University of Helsinki | FiDiPro Project)
Creating a unified digital market for telecommunications within Europe is a primary goal of the current European Commission. [i] However, achieving this single market remains a distant prospect. The current multi-tiered regulatory model for European telecommunications relies heavily on individual nations&amp;rsquo; regulatory bodies to implement the EU&amp;rsquo;s telecom framework. Furthermore, enforcing this framework falls upon the Member States themselves under their own national procedures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experimenting-with-eu-governance-in-the-telecoms-sector/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>