<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Timmermans on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/timmermans/</link><description>Recent content in Timmermans on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/timmermans/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans).</description></item><item><title>Initial reflections on Justice and Home Affairs matters under the new Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 22:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-reflections-on-justice-and-home-affairs-matters-under-the-new-commission/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The proposed structure and roles within the next European Commission, particularly regarding Justice and Home Affairs (JHA) issues, carry significant implications for EU policy. However, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember that the European Parliament (EP) can still influence the final list of Commissioners, as seen in previous years.
Migration and Home Affairs
Contrary to some claims, the new Commission retains a dedicated Commissioner for immigration and home affairs, a position filled by Dimitris Avramopolous.</description></item></channel></rss>