<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jurisdiction of EU Courts on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jurisdiction-of-eu-courts/</link><description>Recent content in Jurisdiction of EU Courts on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/jurisdiction-of-eu-courts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The resolution of disputes and the role of the ECJ in the proposed withdrawal agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 19:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
A key point of contention in post-Brexit EU/UK relations is the degree to which the UK remains bound to the EU Court of Justice (ECJ). This issue arises first in the withdrawal agreement being negotiated, a draft of which was recently proposed by the EU Commission. While it will eventually affect the future relationship between the two, this post focuses on the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-resolution-of-disputes-and-the-role-of-the-ecj-in-the-proposed-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Council v H: Another Court victory in the Common Foreign and Security Policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 01:29:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</guid><description>Graham Butler, PhD Fellow at the Centre for Comparative and European Constitutional Studies, Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen, Denmark
Introduction
This summer, the Court of Justice (the Court) issued two significant decisions influencing the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) legal landscape. Despite the Treaty of Lisbon&amp;rsquo;s integration of this largely intergovernmental area (previously the Second Pillar) into the unified ‘EU’, its legacy persists. Enduring evidence of CFSP as a distinct yet incorporated legal domain allows it to be termed ‘CFSP law’...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/council-v-h-another-court-victory-in-the-common-foreign-and-security-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>An Overview and Initial Observations of the Brexit Withdrawal Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:36:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers from the University of Essex provides a summary and explanation of the Brexit withdrawal agreement, aimed at non-lawyers.
The Scope of the Agreement
The withdrawal agreement outlines the terms of the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the EU but does not define the long-term relationship between the two entities. The future relationship will be negotiated based on a separate political declaration.
Consequences of Non-Ratification
If the withdrawal agreement is not ratified, the UK could leave the EU without an agreement, or potentially remain in the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-overview-and-initial-observations-of-the-brexit-withdrawal-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Court of Justice in Bank Refah Kargaran making a groundbreaking decision by allowing action for damages in relation to CFSP decisions regarding restrictive measures?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</guid><description>Professor Dr. Peter Van Elsuwege and Joyce De Coninck (PhD Researcher), Ghent European Law Institute
The recent Grand Chamber judgment in the case of Bank Refah Kargaran v Council, issued on October 6, 2020, sheds further light on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) jurisdiction concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP). Drawing on previous judgments such as Elitaliana, H v. Council, Rosneft, and SatCen vs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-court-of-justice-in-bank-refah-kargaran-making-a-groundbreaking-decision-by-allowing-action-for-damages-in-relation-to-cfsp-decisions-regarding-restrictive-measures/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resolving conflicts and the agreement for the UK's exit from the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 21:48:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A key point of contention in the Brexit withdrawal agreement is how disputes will be settled. Specifically, there&amp;rsquo;s debate about whether the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) maintains authority over the UK. This post provides an overview of this issue and a detailed analysis of the withdrawal agreement&amp;rsquo;s provisions concerning dispute resolution and the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s role.
This post is the third in a series examining the withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resolving-conflicts-and-the-agreement-for-the-uk-s-exit-from-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enforcing Court of Justice Judgments</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enforcing-court-of-justice-judgments/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 19:44:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enforcing-court-of-justice-judgments/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued a noteworthy decision concerning the &amp;lsquo;infringement procedure,&amp;rsquo; a system for directly upholding EU law within EU courts. This system operates alongside national courts enforcing EU law. Article 258 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU) outlines this system, allowing the Commission to bring cases to the ECJ against Member States allegedly violating EU law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enforcing-court-of-justice-judgments/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enforcing-court-of-justice-judgments/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Transformation of the third pillar: The conclusion of the transition period for EU criminal and policing law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 06:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</guid><description>by Emilio De Capitani
On December 1st, 2014, after five years, the prior &amp;ldquo;third pillar&amp;rdquo; of EU law will transition from intergovernmental control to a supranational system. However, it remains unclear if this shift will result in a consistent policy that is properly executed by Member States and respects human rights.
Specifically, according to Article 10 of Protocol 36, added by the Lisbon Treaty, all EU measures concerning police and judicial cooperation in criminal matters adopted before the Lisbon Treaty will be treated like other EU laws regarding the jurisdiction of the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/transformation-of-the-third-pillar-the-conclusion-of-the-transition-period-for-eu-criminal-and-policing-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What authority should the Court of Justice have in EU Foreign Policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Luigi Lonardo, PhD student, King’s College London
Article 24(1) of the Treaty on the European Union states that the Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) operates under distinct rules and procedures, explicitly stating that the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) holds no jurisdiction over these provisions.
Legal experts are debating whether &amp;ldquo;the CJEU shall not have jurisdiction&amp;rdquo; implies a degree of jurisdiction. AG Wahl articulated this question: Does the exclusion of CJEU jurisdiction encompass all CFSP actions or only specific categories?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-authority-should-the-court-of-justice-have-in-eu-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>