<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MPLS Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-networks/</link><description>Recent content in MPLS Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vote MPLS &amp; Ethernet for Better Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 20:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</guid><description>The 2008 election season is upon us. To determine which candidates best serve your interests, we suggest considering MPLS and Ethernet for reliable bandwidth, improved performance, and reduced costs over 1-3 years. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into their platforms to see if they deserve your vote.
IP Networking is currently the leading technology. Initially confined to local offices, IP has expanded to WANs at state, regional, and national levels. Today, almost all network designs are centered around IP or Internet Protocol...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vote-mpls-ethernet-for-better-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Internet SDN Mimics MPLS At Much Lower Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 04:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, businesses have faced a trade-off between expensive, high-performance WAN bandwidth and affordable, but unreliable, low-performance options. While cable or DSL internet offers cost savings, their inconsistent performance can be problematic. Conversely, dedicated private lines or MPLS networks deliver reliability and performance at a premium cost. If only there were a solution to make the internet perform like an MPLS network at a fraction of the cost. Thanks to SDN, there is...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-sdn-mimics-mpls-at-much-lower-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Lines Connect Dealerships</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 05:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</guid><description>Many businesses, from car dealerships to restaurants, benefit from having multiple locations. However, managing these locations as a unified company requires connecting them effectively. Point-to-point lines and MPLS networks offer solutions for this need.
Consider a car dealership expanding by acquiring another dealership. While this offers strategic advantages, consolidating operations like accounting, marketing, and IT can lead to cost savings. Centralizing these functions requires reliable and efficient connectivity between locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-lines-connect-dealerships/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is 5G Bandwidth Slicing The New Private Network?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:10:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet is great for connecting, but it&amp;rsquo;s not always reliable. While it provides widespread access, low costs, and supports most applications, it can fall short when high performance and reliability are crucial. Issues like latency, packet loss, and congestion can hinder or even prevent interactive applications from working correctly. The solution? Private networks.
What is a Private Network?
The internet is a public network, accessible to almost anyone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-5g-bandwidth-slicing-the-new-private-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth To Support Branch Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</guid><description>Many businesses need multiple locations in a region to stay close to their customers. Connecting these branches seamlessly without breaking the bank is a common challenge. Thankfully, two high-performance networking technologies, Metro Ethernet and MPLS Networks, offer affordable solutions that weren&amp;rsquo;t available even a decade ago.
Carrier Ethernet takes the local networking capabilities of Ethernet and extends them across entire cities. This means easy connection and efficient transmission without needing protocol conversions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Don't Layoff Employees, Evict Them</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:24:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</guid><description>The work-life balance for many employees today feels unbalanced. They often face excessive workloads, whether the company is thriving or facing difficulties, and the constant threat of layoffs creates a stressful environment. However, what if instead of layoffs, companies considered &amp;ldquo;evicting&amp;rdquo; employees from their offices?
This doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean losing their homes, but rather transitioning to a telecommuting model. The concept is that many employees, especially in information-driven fields, can be just as productive, if not more so, working remotely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dont-layoff-employees-evict-them/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Circuit Switched vs Packet Switched Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Over the past few decades, two primary network technologies have been vying for dominance. The first is the traditional telephone system, which served us well throughout the industrial age. The second is the computer-based architecture that has driven the information age. You might recognize these as circuit switching and packet switching.
While both technologies will likely coexist for a while longer, we are at a turning point. From now on, packet switching will be the dominant force in every network, from copper lines to fiber optic cables to wireless connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/circuit-switched-vs-packet-switched-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>We’re Headed Toward Universal Elasticity as a Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 22:01:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the frustration of a slow or unresponsive website, especially when it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for work or entertainment. This sluggishness often stems from resource starvation, where the system lacks sufficient resources like processing power, memory, storage, or bandwidth to handle the current demand.
Resource Starvation Resource starvation occurs when a system&amp;rsquo;s capacity is exceeded. A sudden surge in demand, such as a product going viral, can overload a website designed for typical traffic levels, leading to a frustrating experience for users and potentially lost business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/we-re-headed-toward-universal-elasticity-as-a-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Texas Fiber Optic Network Expansion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</guid><description>Texas is experiencing significant growth in fiber network availability for businesses due to company partnerships and mergers.
Transtelco, a major provider with a fiber network spanning from Houston to Los Angeles and extending into Northern Mexico, has plans to expand its network in both Mexico and Texas. Another significant provider, PAETEC, possesses substantial fiber assets serving major Texas cities like Dallas, Austin, and Houston.
PAETEC and Transtelco have entered a joint venture where PAETEC is expanding Transtelco&amp;rsquo;s fiber connection between El Paso and Temple...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/texas-fiber-optic-network-expansion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cross-Border Private Line Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 08:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</guid><description>When considering private line services for business locations, we often focus on domestic connections. However, international business operations necessitate cross-border line services, which not all carriers provide.
](http://www.megatrunks.com/international/PrivateLines/international_private_lines.php)
International connectivity involves navigating varying regulations, practices, and technical requirements. For example, the US and Europe employ slightly different companding standards for digitized phone calls. While both use the G.711 CODEC for PCM, the US and others utilize Mu-law compression, while Europe and most of the world use A-law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cross-border-private-line-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Encrypted Wavelengths Offer High Bandwidth and High Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 17:12:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data security becomes increasingly critical, every vulnerability in an IT system needs to be found and strengthened. Networks often extend beyond a single location, creating vulnerabilities in MAN and WAN connections that must be addressed. A newer service called Wavelength Encryption or Encrypted Waves offers a solution for users requiring high bandwidth.
How Secure Are Dedicated Lines?
Connection security can vary significantly depending on how data travels between two points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encrypted-wavelengths-offer-high-bandwidth-and-high-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Shared Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 09:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When choosing business internet services, bandwidth is important, but understanding the difference between dedicated and shared connections is crucial.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated bandwidth is exclusively for your use. This might seem obvious, but the recent rise of shared bandwidth makes it worth clarifying. The cost-effectiveness of shared bandwidth often makes businesses reconsider their need for a dedicated line.
Cost Considerations
Shared bandwidth is significantly cheaper than dedicated bandwidth at similar speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-vs-shared-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Long Haul Voice, Video and Data via MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 14:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses need to transmit voice, video, and data across long distances, whether between cities, across the country, or even internationally. While both the internet and dedicated private lines are viable options, there&amp;rsquo;s another solution you might not be familiar with: MPLS networks. This article will explore why MPLS is a strong option for long-distance data transport and how to decide which solution best suits your needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/long-haul-voice-video-and-data-via-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Communications Services To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>A significant shift from traditional phone systems to cloud-based communication is happening right now. XO Communications, a leader in this field, predicts 60% of companies will move almost a third of their voice communications to the cloud in the coming years.
For a free consultation and quotes tailored to your company&amp;rsquo;s communication needs, our partners at Telarus offer fast and reliable service from expert product specialists. Contact them at http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 11:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 3 Ethernet over Copper bandwidth service could be the ideal solution for your business. Here are some more FAQs that might address some of your questions about this fairly new technology.
Q: Is Ethernet over Copper suitable for business telephone systems?
A: While not a direct substitute for traditional analog or ISDN PRI phone lines, EoC can be a budget-friendly upgrade that increases call capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Different Types of VPN Providers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 04:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</guid><description>You prioritize the privacy of your network, but what happens when you need to connect to the outside world? Do you let anyone and everyone in, or do you secure your network across the distance using a private or virtually private network?
Before Virtual Private Networks (VPNs), there were private networks, and they still exist. Some situations demand such high security that the only way to guarantee control and prevent intrusions is through dedicated, point-to-point private lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/different-types-of-vpn-providers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Thirty Carriers, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:53:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</guid><description>Are you overwhelmed and frustrated with your current telecommunications services? Do you feel stuck with your local phone or internet provider and dread seeing your monthly bill?
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to endure this! You deserve a wide range of choices for your voice and data communication needs. Imagine having access to 30 different business-grade carriers, offering everything from basic phone lines to high-speed internet options like wireless and satellite.
Whether you need ISDN PRI lines for your office phone system, MPLS networks to connect multiple locations, or Gigabit Ethernet for high-bandwidth applications like video conferencing, you have options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/thirty-carriers-no-waiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet VPLS Extends Your LAN Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</guid><description>Traditional methods of connecting multiple business locations, such as Frame Relay, VSAT satellite terminals, internet-based VPNs, and dedicated T1 lines, have been around for a while. However, a new technology called Ethernet VPLS offers superior performance and cost advantages, making it a compelling option for businesses with multiple locations, including branch offices, retail franchises, and medical clinics.
Ethernet VPLS, which stands for Virtual Private LAN service, essentially functions as a carrier-managed local area network that can span across cities, states, or even the entire country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-vpls-extends-your-lan-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need a Business Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-business-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 02:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-business-cloud/</guid><description>In the past, telephone calls used dedicated lines that physically connected two parties. This point-to-point system limited network sharing capabilities.
However, packet-switched communications revolutionized this process. Now, constant connections link all locations, while data packets travel across various network pathways. This interconnected network is often visualized as a &amp;ldquo;cloud,&amp;rdquo; where data magically reaches its intended destination. This cloud-based system enables many-to-many communications, contrasting with the previous one-to-one limitation. A prime example is connecting multiple business branches, allowing seamless communication between them without manual intervention...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-business-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-business-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Lines and Virtual Private Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses frequently require private lines for reliable and secure communication between various locations like headquarters, branches, factories, and suppliers. The goal is to create a seamless experience akin to a local area network.
Traditional Point-to-Point Private Lines
Private lines, essentially dedicated wires between two points, have existed for a long time. The digital era introduced T1, DS3, and OC3 lines offering fixed bandwidths at speeds ranging from 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-lines-and-virtual-private-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP over MPLS for Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>Small businesses often utilize SIP Trunking to reduce their monthly telecommunication expenses by combining their telephone and internet broadband services onto a single line. This technology also benefits large corporations and call centers requiring numerous external phone lines and possessing converged voice and data LANs. However, organizations with multiple locations may find SIP over MPLS a more suitable solution.
Deploying SIP over MPLS might be the optimal choice if your organization utilizes an MPLS network for interoffice data sharing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-over-mpls-for-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 3 Types of VoIP Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For years, businesses of all sizes have been transitioning to VoIP phone systems. While some are thrilled with the switch, others find the call quality lacking, with muffled audio and challenging conversations. The technology is the same, so why does VoIP performance vary so greatly? Let&amp;rsquo;s investigate.
What is VoIP?
VoIP, or Voice over Internet Protocol, transforms phones into computer accessories, saving money and enabling features impossible with traditional phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-3-types-of-voip-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Design Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:36:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</guid><description>People often think that Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs) are entirely different, requiring distinct design approaches. But is that always true?
LANs, typically owned by individuals and organizations, rely on packet switching and Ethernet technology, using copper or fiber optic cables. WANs, however, emerged from the telephone industry and initially used circuit switching over telephone lines.
This historical difference led to a technological gap between LANs and WANs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-design-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Lit Buildings Expand Fiber Optic Bandwidth in Houston</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 10:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</guid><description>Houston, Texas, the fourth largest city in the US, is a hub for various industries, including healthcare, energy, manufacturing, and aerospace. The city&amp;rsquo;s demand for high-speed internet, particularly fiber optic bandwidth, is constantly growing. To address this need, Alpheus Communications is expanding its fiber optic network to include key buildings in Houston&amp;rsquo;s business district.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)What does a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; mean? In this context, it refers to a building equipped with active fiber optic service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lit-buildings-expand-fiber-optic-bandwidth-in-houston/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed Security Moves To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud services are expanding beyond the familiar Infrastructure, Platform, and Software as a Service to include Security as a Service. Integra, for example, now offers a suite of Cloud Security Services, including a Cloud Firewall Service.
Many companies find managed security appealing because it removes the need for dedicated IT staff or investments in security hardware. Traditionally, this involved a monthly service fee and an on-premises security device. Cloud-based security takes it further, eliminating the need for physical hardware altogether...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-security-moves-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 13:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</guid><description>MPLS networks are frequently mentioned as a way to connect multiple business locations. But what exactly is MPLS, and why is it superior to other network architectures?
MPLS, or Multi-Protocol Label Switching, is a technology distinct from traditional circuit-switched or packet-switched networks. While it allows IP traffic transmission, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t rely on IP routing.
The advantage of MPLS networks lies in their ability to handle almost any protocol without requiring conversions to fit the network structure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-mpls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>1.5 and 3.0 Gbps Uncompressed HD Video Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</guid><description>Analog television with its standard-definition video signals is a thing of the past. While older 4:3 aspect ratio televisions still exist, they are sustained by cable and satellite receivers. However, high-definition (HD) channels are becoming more prevalent, and standard-definition channels are being phased out as viewers switch to flat-screen HD TVs. The future of television is internet protocol television (IPTV) in high definition, with 3D technology on the horizon.
For broadcasters, distributors, and content providers, traditional video transport methods are no longer adequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/15-and-30-gbps-uncompressed-hd-video-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Managed IT Services Are So Popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</guid><description>The way businesses use information technology services has changed significantly. Instead of managing everything themselves, many companies are turning to managed IT services. This shift is driven partly by the growth of cloud computing and partly by budget limitations in the wake of the recent recession.
Whether due to economic factors or technological advances, businesses are increasingly opting for IT services delivered through colocation, cloud computing, or managed network services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-managed-it-services-are-so-popular/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Mobile Convergence Comes To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s professionals juggle multiple devices like smartphones, tablets, and laptops in addition to their office setups, which often include desktop computers, LAN connections, and speakerphones. This begs the question: how can we unify these devices for a seamless workflow?
This multifaceted connectivity issue has plagued corporate IT departments for years as communication devices multiply faster than solutions for integrating them. Often, the simplest answer is printing business cards with separate numbers for each device...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-mobile-convergence-comes-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Fiber Optic Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 02:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Let&amp;rsquo;s say you need a secure connection with decent bandwidth between two business sites. Should you use the internet, or is there a better option?
The Benefits of Private Lines
The internet has two main advantages: global reach and affordability. However, it also has two significant drawbacks: inconsistent performance and security vulnerabilities.
A superior alternative is private lines, specifically dedicated point-to-point connections. These are genuinely private.
Security is greatly enhanced because accessing a network you&amp;rsquo;re not connected to is incredibly difficult...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-fiber-optic-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Connects Nationwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 19:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) has become known as a quick and dedicated access connection for internet, MPLS networking, and connecting company Local Area Networks (LANs). Its adaptability, user-friendly interface, and affordability have increased demand for this service. However, limited availability has hindered its widespread adoption, but that is about to change.
MegaPath, a prominent competitive carrier, is partnering with Telx, a leading network interconnection provider, to expand the reach of Ethernet over Copper connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-connects-nationwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Wavelength vs Dark Fiber for 10 GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 22:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</guid><description>Businesses needing high bandwidth from a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) often consider dark fiber. A comparable service, dark wavelength (also known as dark lambda), is also worth considering. Let&amp;rsquo;s compare these two options with other common network connections, like point-to-point and MPLS.
What is a Dark Wavelength? While we associate wavelengths with colors of light, a dark wavelength isn&amp;rsquo;t about the absence of color. It&amp;rsquo;s not the same as dark fiber...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-wavelength-vs-dark-fiber-for-10-gige/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Leased Line Prices Lower, More Variety</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</guid><description>For businesses, leased telecom lines have been the long-time standard for direct connections between locations or for dedicated internet access. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available leased line options and the significant price changes in recent years.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s define what a leased line is and how it compares to other bandwidth solutions. The name &amp;ldquo;leased line&amp;rdquo; is fairly self-explanatory. You enter into a contract, usually for 1 to 3 years, with a telecom carrier for exclusive use of a dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/leased-line-prices-lower-more-variety/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Build Your Own World Wide Web</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The internet has its downsides despite the benefits of global and instant information access. Sharing large files between offices, conducting high-quality teleconferences, and experiencing seamless application interactions can be challenging. Network crashes, congestion from high-bandwidth activities, and constant security threats further diminish the internet&amp;rsquo;s appeal. So, is there a better alternative?
The Connectivity Conundrum
Imagine having an exclusive internet solely for your business, customers, and suppliers. Bandwidth wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be an issue, and the network would operate seamlessly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/build-your-own-world-wide-web/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Many Ways To Connect To MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 20:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Connecting multiple business locations is becoming increasingly streamlined with MPLS networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what constitutes an MPLS network and the various ways to establish a connection.
A simple scenario involves connecting two business locations. The straightforward solution is a point-to-point private line, available in various bandwidths to accommodate specific needs. As the name suggests, one end of the line connects to location one, and the other end connects to location two, much like having a physical wire spanning the distance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-ways-to-connect-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cut Telecom Line Expenses, Not Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</guid><description>During economic downturns, businesses often look to cut costs to stay afloat. While eliminating unnecessary expenses is a good start, managers may soon scrutinize even essential budget items.
Instead of panicking and making rash decisions, it&amp;rsquo;s best to proactively identify reasonable cost reductions. This way, you can present well-thought-out proposals and maintain some control over the process.
The key is to maintain productivity while reducing expenses. Instead of completely cutting essential services, focus on achieving the same functionality for less money...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Switch to Switched Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</guid><description>Are you stuck using outdated telecom technology? In the past, you had to use one network protocol internally and a completely different one externally. By switching to switched Ethernet service, your network will have more options and easier interfacing.
What defines outdated telecom? It refers to the traditional transport services that were initially created for telephone technologies and later adapted to connect data networks using the public switched telephone network. Examples include Frame Relay, T1, DS3, and SONET/SDH...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/switch-to-switched-ethernet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Latency Connections Bridge The Atlantic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 05:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</guid><description>The immense volume of data flowing through global fiber optic networks highlights our interconnected world. While intercontinental cables have existed for years, low latency networks are becoming increasingly vital.
High-frequency trading, particularly the use of automated programs, drives the demand for low latency. These programs compete to execute trades milliseconds or even microseconds faster than competitors, a feat impossible for human traders. This speed makes the physical path between traders and exchanges critical, with the delay on this path known as latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-latency-connections-bridge-the-atlantic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EarthLink Offers Healthcare IT Resources</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</guid><description>The potential for healthcare automation to significantly reduce costs in healthcare settings like doctor&amp;rsquo;s offices, clinics, and hospitals is substantial. However, not all healthcare providers have the necessary IT capabilities to modernize and leverage these new technologies. They might also struggle to meet privacy regulations like HIPAA. This is where large network service providers such as EarthLink Business can bridge the gap. An example of this can be seen in how EarthLink supports Monadnock Community Hospital in Peterborough, New Hampshire, as shown in this video...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/earthlink-offers-healthcare-it-resources/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get Your Building Fiber Lit For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</guid><description>Fiber optic bandwidth is currently available at excellent prices. Although many companies are eager to upgrade to faster internet speeds like Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps), GigE (1000 Mbps), or even 10 Gigabit Ethernet, the construction costs to install fiber optic service in their buildings are often prohibitive. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a possibility to have your building fiber lit without any construction costs.
The secret is that certain competitive carriers are willing to cover construction expenses to meet the rising demand for high-bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-building-fiber-lit-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Access An MPLS Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 16:26:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</guid><description>MPLS networks have become a sought-after alternative to costly, proprietary WAN networks and the public internet, which can present performance and security challenges. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what MPLS networks offer and the various ways to access them.
Imagine an MPLS network as a dedicated internet exclusively for businesses. Privately owned and operated, MPLS networks don&amp;rsquo;t provide services or connections for residential users, making them strictly business-to-business (B2B). Numerous service providers operate their own MPLS networks, offering regional, national, or international coverage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5-ways-to-access-an-mpls-network/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Private Line Service With Granular Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve traditionally relied on dedicated point-to-point connections like T1, DS3, and OC3 for private line services. However, a new service called Ethernet Private Line Service (E-Line) offers similar benefits with enhancements and cost savings.
Officially defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF), E-Line provides standardized Carrier Ethernet with robust performance for metropolitan and long-distance networks.
Let&amp;rsquo;s compare E-Line to traditional private lines, which are permanent, exclusive connections often called &amp;ldquo;nailed up&amp;rdquo; circuits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-private-line-service-with-granular-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Networking Services Extend Business Footprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 20:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</guid><description>For businesses with a single office in one city, cloud computing or hosted PBX might suffice, as their communication needs are primarily about connecting to a provider&amp;rsquo;s cloud. However, companies with multiple locations require cloud networking services to link these sites seamlessly.
Cloud networking utilizes public or private networks to connect geographically dispersed locations in various configurations. Examples include the internet, privately managed MPLS networks, and even custom-built networks using leased lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-networking-services-extend-business-footprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Can Improve Telephone Reliability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 22:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</guid><description>Many businesses, even large ones, hold onto their own phone systems believing it&amp;rsquo;s the only way to guarantee reliable communication. But is this true, or is it time to reconsider this assumption?
The phone service industry has experienced a significant shift with the emergence of hosted PBX (HPBX), also called hosted VoIP or cloud communications. Like other cloud-based technologies, this is a game-changer. In the future, we&amp;rsquo;ll wonder why we didn&amp;rsquo;t switch sooner...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-can-improve-telephone-reliability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Ethernet Enable Electronic Health Care?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 01:05:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/</guid><description>The healthcare industry has significant potential for service enhancement and cost reduction. Digitizing, storing, and transferring medical records, along with automating administrative tasks, are readily achievable improvements. Additionally, innovations like remote diagnostics can extend healthcare access to underserved areas and emergency situations. However, the lack of widespread broadband infrastructure, particularly in rural areas, hinders progress.
The limited availability of high-speed internet connections poses a significant obstacle. Many healthcare facilities rely on outdated T1 lines, which are inadequate for transmitting large, high-resolution medical images and electronic medical records, impacting productivity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-ethernet-enable-electronic-health-care/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Years Of The Explainer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 21:04:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</guid><description>T1 Rex’s Business Telecom Explainer turned five this month, with more than 800 posts published since its 2004 launch. Our initial goal was to clarify complex telecommunications services and provide businesses with competitive options. Over time, we&amp;rsquo;ve broadened our scope to encompass a wide range of products, services, and topics relevant to our audience. As we approach our second decade, let&amp;rsquo;s examine the &amp;ldquo;aughts&amp;rdquo; and explore potential future trends.
This explainer blog, as the name suggests, was launched alongside T1Rex...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-years-of-the-explainer/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Ethernet Crush DS3?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</guid><description>Companies needing more bandwidth than a 1.5 Mbps T1 line often upgraded to DS3, but its 45 Mbps speed was often more than they needed. A newer option, Carrier Ethernet (also known as Metro Ethernet), offers a more practical solution with scalable bandwidth at a often lower cost.
Ethernet services are significantly less expensive than DS3 in some markets, costing up to 50% less. However, in areas where Ethernet isn&amp;rsquo;t widely available, prices may be comparable to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-ethernet-crush-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is VPLS Bringing to MPLS Networks?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Businesses with numerous branches have embraced MPLS networks for their affordability and high performance in connecting multiple locations. However, they may be overlooking a superior connectivity solution: Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS).
Essentially, VPLS is an Ethernet transport service operating over existing MPLS networks, enhancing rather than replacing them.
What sets VPLS apart is its ability to unify all your individual LANs into a single, company-wide network. This network transcends geographical limitations, enabling international connections for globally distributed businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-vpls-bringing-to-mpls-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Give Yourself Enough Time to Save on Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:56:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</guid><description>Everyone wants to save money. In business, securing the best deal is a top priority. This is especially true for telecom services, where the goal is maximum service for minimal cost. Achieving this is possible with two key steps: knowing where to find the best deals and allowing sufficient time to implement the optimal solution.
Finding the best deals has become significantly easier. Instead of sifting through phonebooks or tirelessly searching online, businesses can now contact telecom brokers representing numerous providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/give-yourself-enough-time-to-save-on-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>