<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Big Brother Watch on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/big-brother-watch/</link><description>Recent content in Big Brother Watch on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:02:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/big-brother-watch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The ECtHR Grand Chamber makes a ruling on mass surveillance in the case of Big Brother Watch v UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, an expert in internet law from the University of Essex, provides an in-depth analysis of a significant ruling by the Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) concerning the United Kingdom&amp;rsquo;s surveillance regime, specifically its Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA).
This ruling is the culmination of a series of legal challenges against the UK&amp;rsquo;s surveillance practices, brought to light by revelations of extensive government surveillance programs.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US.</description></item></channel></rss>