<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Show on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/show/</link><description>Recent content in Show on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Come to Singapore Gifts Show 2015 for a wide selection of corporate gifts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 20:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-singapore-gifts-show-2015-for-a-wide-selection-of-corporate-gifts/</guid><description>The upcoming Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015 is the ideal event to discover this year&amp;rsquo;s corporate gift trends. Taking place from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, Halls 401 to 403, this international trade event offers free admission. It showcases innovative gifts, premiums, and lifestyle products and services, catering to trade buyers and corporate attendees.
Celebrating its 10th anniversary, SGS 2015 will host 160 booths featuring exhibitors from the Philippines, Malaysia, Sri Lanka, Thailand, and Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival is set to delight visitors in October 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-namyangju-slow-life-international-festival-is-set-to-delight-visitors-in-october-2015/</guid><description>Source: Slow Life Planet website.
This October, the South Korean city of Namyangju will host a global festival celebrating the slow food movement and overall wellness. The Namyangju Slow Life International Festival (남양주슬로푸드국제대회), themed Good Food, Good Life, will run for ten days starting on October 8th. The festival takes place about 30 kilometers east of Seoul. This is the second time Namyangju City is hosting this event. Following the success of the Asio Gusto festival in 2013, the city decided to rename the event and host it every two years.</description></item><item><title>Buyers who prioritize design are encouraging gift and premium manufacturers to elevate their products</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/buyers-who-prioritize-design-are-encouraging-gift-and-premium-manufacturers-to-elevate-their-products/</guid><description>Source: SGS website. SGS 2015 was well attended.
This year&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Gifts Show (SGS), taking place from June 29th to July 1st, sees exhibitors raising their game in response to increasingly design-conscious buyers. As the biggest event of its kind in Singapore, SGS is a trade show for gifts, premiums, lifestyle products, and services, targeting both regional and global markets. Established in 2006, this yearly showcase spans three days and encompasses both an exhibition and industry seminars.</description></item><item><title>Preview of Singapore Gifts Show 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preview-of-singapore-gifts-show-2015/</guid><description>The Singapore Gifts Show (SGS) 2015, held from July 8th to 10th at Suntec Singapore, presented a diverse selection of uniquely Singaporean gifts.
A sample pack from organizer TTG Events included the NYP Postcard Set, SG50 Tattoos, Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig, Miniature Tea Book – Volume II, and a Suction Mug.
Makan Buddies LEGO Minifig (Graceland Gifts, Booth B21)
These personalized LEGO figures demonstrate the potential for designing and 3D printing unique minifigures, as they are known by LEGO enthusiasts.</description></item></channel></rss>