<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scam on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scam/</link><description>Recent content in Scam on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/scam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>There has been an increase in crypto giveaway scams</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/there-has-been-an-increase-in-crypto-giveaway-scams/</guid><description>Source: Group-IB. A screen capture from a fake YouTube video that appears to show Elon Musk.
Group-IB, a cybersecurity firm based in Singapore, has detected a significant surge in websites promoting cryptocurrency giveaway scams using fake YouTube live streams during the first half of 2022. These scams have become increasingly organized, evolving into a distinct market segment with various services supporting fraudulent activities.
The firm&amp;rsquo;s research reveals that while 63% of these new scam domains are registered with Russian registrars, they primarily target English and Spanish-speaking individuals interested in cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>Singapore residents are being targeted by a phone-based phishing campaign, according to DBS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 17:46:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-residents-are-being-targeted-by-a-phone-based-phishing-campaign-according-to-dbs/</guid><description>DBS Bank has issued a warning to residents of Singapore about a phishing scam making use of automated phone calls. Given their customer base of over 4 million in Singapore alone, it is highly likely that scammers will connect with a DBS account holder.
The scam, as reported on the DBS website, begins with an automated voice message in either English or Mandarin. The recipient is told they have an urgent message from DBS Bank and instructed to press either &amp;ldquo;0&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Stay away from Pokemon Go scams and malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stay-away-from-pokemon-go-scams-and-malware/</guid><description>Source: Niantic blog.
The augmented reality game Pokémon Go, highly popular since its July launch, has attracted scammers and cybercriminals. While the game hasn&amp;rsquo;t officially launched in all of Asia, Symantec warns of potential risks for players.
Symantec&amp;rsquo;s blog post details several Pokémon Go scams, from fake PokeCoins to privacy concerns.
Free PokeCoin scams
Pokémon Go offers in-app purchases using real money to buy PokeCoins, a virtual currency. Players use these coins to purchase items like incense to attract Pokémon.</description></item><item><title>Don't fall for the scam of cheap Ray-Ban sunglasses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 08:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/don-t-fall-for-the-scam-of-cheap-ray-ban-sunglasses/</guid><description>Source: ESET.
ESET&amp;rsquo;s spam filters have identified a growing trend of fraudulent emails enticing recipients with deeply discounted luxury items, particularly Ray-Ban sunglasses. These counterfeit websites lack encryption and might be designed to capture victims&amp;rsquo; payment information. While ESET had issued prior warnings about this scam targeting Facebook users, the shift to email attacks broadens the potential victim pool significantly.
“Providing payment card information on these fake websites poses a substantial financial risk,&amp;quot; cautions Lukáš Štefanko, an ESET Malware Researcher.</description></item><item><title>Imperva cautions about potential scams on Singles Day</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imperva-cautions-about-potential-scams-on-singles-day/</guid><description>Imperva, a leading cybersecurity firm dedicated to safeguarding data, has released a new report on e-commerce security and provided recommendations for secure online shopping in light of the upcoming global shopping event on November 11th.
The company highlighted that Chinese e-commerce giants Alibaba and JD.com achieved a record-breaking US$115 billion in sales during Singles Day 2020, emphasizing that the rise in online shoppers is accompanied by a parallel increase in scams.</description></item></channel></rss>