<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Broadband on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband/</link><description>Recent content in Broadband on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/broadband/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>E-Rate Supports Gigabit Internet for Schools &amp; Libraries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:48:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-rate-supports-gigabit-internet-for-schools-libraries/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s evident that broadband internet access is crucial for businesses, education, and individuals. Schools and libraries, in particular, require online access to thrive in today&amp;rsquo;s digital age.
Schools &amp;amp; Libraries are Lagging Surprisingly, many elementary schools and libraries lack adequate internet access. They require modern broadband speeds, surpassing the outdated megabit per second standard. Today&amp;rsquo;s requirements necessitate fiber optic connections.
The FCC acknowledges this need, promoting internet speeds of at least 100 Mbps per 1,000 users for schools and libraries, with plans to increase this to 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>You Are Definitely Going to Need More Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 19:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-are-definitely-going-to-need-more-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, the typical workplace is no more. The usual routines of office life have vanished. Employees are no longer commuting to their desks. Cubicles and parking lots are deserted. Countless desktop computers and phones sit idle.
The New Normal: Where is Everyone?
A small team remains onsite, but the majority of employees are working from home. There&amp;rsquo;s been a massive effort to establish remote connections using personal computers, iPads, and smartphones, relying on cable and cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport Offers Huge Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 11:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-ethernet-transport-offers-huge-advantages/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Data can be moved in many ways. The new top choice is Fiber Optic Ethernet, known as EoF or Ethernet over Fiber, which offers excellent value.
What is Fiber Optic Ethernet Transport?
When fiber optic lines were first installed, Ethernet wasn&amp;rsquo;t a factor. The standard was SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), designed to carry existing DS1 and DS3 phone calls on fiber. Fiber offered significantly more bandwidth than copper twisted pair, microwave, or coaxial cable.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity for Telemedicine and Remote Work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 18:29:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-for-telemedicine-and-remote-work/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The rapid emergence of the Coronavirus pandemic is speeding up existing trends, particularly telemedicine and remote work. Both heavily rely on broadband internet bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the available connection options.
Connecting the User
Most remote workers and telemedicine patients connect from home using devices like desktops, smartphones, laptops, or tablets. Home users often prefer cable broadband with speeds of 30 to 100 Mbps, while remote users rely on public WiFi or 4G/5G cellular broadband.</description></item><item><title>Your Options For Business Internet Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 23:36:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-options-for-business-internet-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses now have more choices than ever when it comes to broadband internet. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the available solutions suitable for companies of all sizes.
Starting Big
Gigabit internet is the ideal scenario for most, but affordability can be a concern. Medium to large companies in most areas, and even smaller businesses in specific locations, might find it within reach.
Location, Location, Location
Your business address significantly impacts both the available services and their costs.</description></item><item><title>Is Broadband the Next Oil?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-broadband-the-next-oil/</guid><description>Customers are enraged by the escalating prices of gasoline and heating oil. The cost of oil seems to be limitless, as traders frantically outbid each other for future contracts. It feels like a never-ending cycle of increasing prices. And now, prepare yourself: the next crisis might involve broadband internet.
You might be wondering how broadband, especially internet broadband, could resemble oil. Oil is a natural resource with over a century of extraction history, while broadband is a relatively recent technological invention.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses.</description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out.</description></item><item><title>The Connectivity You Need For Digital Transformation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-connectivity-you-need-for-digital-transformation/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Almost every business is currently undergoing some form of digital transformation, which involves transitioning from traditional, paper-based methods to digital and online processes. This shift promises faster, more efficient operations that can reduce costs and expand customer reach. However, establishing the necessary infrastructure to support this digital transformation is crucial.
Conducting Business Primarily Online
While most products and services aren&amp;rsquo;t inherently digital, the tools supporting them are. From identifying potential customers to converting them into buyers, serving those customers, and maintaining product flow, every aspect has a digital element.</description></item><item><title>Houston, We’ve Got A 4G Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/houston-we-ve-got-a-4g-solution/</guid><description>Are you satisfied with your current internet service, or does it feel slow, unreliable, and overpriced? Many people struggle with limited broadband access.
Residents of Houston, Texas, and surrounding areas like The Woodlands and Pasadena now have a new option: CLEAR, a 4G wireless broadband service. Powered by Sprint and Clearwire&amp;rsquo;s WiMAX technology, you can check their coverage map to see if you&amp;rsquo;re eligible.
Houston isn&amp;rsquo;t the only location with access to this 4G wireless broadband service.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.1 Makes Cable Act Like Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 07:36:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-31-makes-cable-act-like-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Cable broadband has undergone significant technological advancements, making it a strong competitor to fiber optic bandwidth for many businesses. Companies that previously considered cable as a backup option are now finding its blend of high performance and affordability too attractive to disregard. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the advancements in cable technology and the options it presents for businesses.
Magic #1: The HFC Cable Plant
Cable television started as a basic system, essentially a collection of large antennas feeding signals to distribution amplifiers, providing an improved version of over-the-air television.</description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology.</description></item><item><title>Is Connection Latency Important to Your Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 00:14:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-connection-latency-important-to-your-business/</guid><description>While connection speed often comes to mind first, latency can be just as crucial for private lines and internet access. Latency, in simpler terms, is lag.
What Does Latency Mean?
Latency refers to a delay. While nothing is truly instantaneous, a small enough delay can feel that way. In computing, high latency can make applications seem unresponsive. A slight delay between pressing a key and seeing it on the screen, or a pause after typing a command are both examples of latency.</description></item><item><title>Wireless Business Internet Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 11:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wireless-business-internet-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s interconnected world, businesses depend heavily on infrastructure like electricity, telephone lines, and internet connectivity, often delivered through copper cables. While electricity and landline phones are widely accessible due to national initiatives, internet availability, particularly broadband via copper or fiber optic cables, diminishes as you move away from city centers. Rural areas often lack wired internet infrastructure entirely, leaving businesses with limited choices.
One option for these areas is wireless internet.</description></item><item><title>How to Feed a Hungry WISP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 21:51:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-feed-a-hungry-wisp/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The United States is extensively wired, except in remote areas like farms, rural homes, businesses outside city limits, new developments, and some industrial parks. While universal service often provides phone access, broadband internet is less certain. This is where Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) come in.
Why WISPs?
WISPs function like cell phone providers but focus on high-speed internet. Unlike 4G cellular data, which has low usage limits, WISPs offer generous data allowances similar to cable, telco, or fiber optic services.</description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it.</description></item><item><title>Google has introduced free Wi-Fi at Mumbai Central Station and launched the Indic keyboard app</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-has-introduced-free-wi-fi-at-mumbai-central-station-and-launched-the-indic-keyboard-app/</guid><description>Source: Google Asia Pacific blog.
Beginning January 22nd, individuals passing through Mumbai Central station in India will have access to complimentary, high-speed Wi-Fi provided by Google. This service is part of an initiative revealed in September 2015 to bring high-speed public Wi-Fi to 400 train stations across India.
Collaborating with Indian Railways, which manages one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most extensive railway systems, and RailTel, a provider of internet services as RailWire through its fiber network along many railway lines, Google&amp;rsquo;s Access &amp;amp; Energy team aims to equip 100 of India&amp;rsquo;s busiest stations with Wi-Fi by the end of 2016, with the remaining stations to follow shortly after.</description></item><item><title>Free International Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</guid><description>During tough economic times, everyone appreciates a good deal, especially free offers. Phone Power is offering free international calls through 2008 to promote its competitive business and residential VoIP services. This is a great opportunity for anyone who makes a lot of international calls. Even after the promotion ends, Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s rates remain very affordable.
This holiday season, you can call landlines in the following countries for free: United Kingdom (44), Spain (34), Ireland (353), Israel (972), Germany (49), Singapore (65), France (33), Denmark (45), Greece (30), Italy (39), and China (86).</description></item><item><title>Will SD-WAN Eat MPLS?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:43:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-sd-wan-eat-mpls/</guid><description>SD-WAN, a trending service, is considered a potential alternative to MPLS networks, with cost comparisons hinting at a potential shift similar to how MPLS replaced Frame Relay.
The Need for Network Solutions
Computer networking is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s world, connecting various devices like desktops, laptops, tablets, and even specialized equipment. This interconnectedness is vital for both basic functionality and accessing cloud-based applications.
Traditional Networking Solutions
Private point-to-point circuits offer complete network control and high performance but come with high costs and lengthy setup times.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of Migrating From T1 to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-migrating-from-t1-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines have proven their reliability over decades, sticking with them solely due to past success might not be the best strategy. This article explores compelling reasons to consider alternatives.
Why T1 Lines Were Once Favored
T1&amp;rsquo;s strength lies in its established design and history. Developed for clear long-distance phone connections, T-Carrier technology, encompassing T1, E1, and T3 (DS3), evolved to handle data packets alongside voice calls due to its digital nature.</description></item><item><title>Get double the mobile data for just a small increase with Singtel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-double-the-mobile-data-for-just-a-small-increase-with-singtel/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website.
Coinciding with the start of IT Show 2016, Singtel is introducing DataX2, a new service that doubles customers&amp;rsquo; monthly mobile data for a fixed price of S$5.90. This new option reflects Singtel&amp;rsquo;s focus on data-driven services, building on the success of last year&amp;rsquo;s SIM Only Plan.
DataX2 lets customers double their data when they sign up for or renew a Combo Mobile Plan (Combo 2 or higher).</description></item><item><title>20/20 Mbps Speed on Copper and Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2020-mbps-speed-on-copper-and-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business broadband needs have increased steadily, driven by the shift from text-based information to multimedia and the migration of business operations to cloud services. Simple, low-speed connections are no longer sufficient, with basic internet speeds now reaching tens of Mbps.
A common choice for smaller businesses and remote workers is a 20/20 Mbps connection. This speed adequately supports individual users, small teams, or retail locations while remaining affordable.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Without Usage Metering</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:50:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-without-usage-metering/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Encountering data caps can be a frustrating broadband experience. Like a hidden speed trap, they appear unexpectedly, often causing significant inconvenience. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into data limits, their implications, and strategies to avoid them.
The Origin of Usage Metering
Bandwidth, much like electricity, faces scarcity issues. If readily available at low costs, metering or speed restrictions wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be necessary. However, this is not the reality.
Consider 5G cellular. The demand for broadband has consistently outpaced network capacity expansion.</description></item><item><title>Filling Coverage Gaps With High Quality Business Satellite</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/filling-coverage-gaps-with-high-quality-business-satellite/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses in big cities have it easy when it comes to internet and phone service. There are so many options! But what if your business isn&amp;rsquo;t in a big city? What if you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with slow internet and outdated phone lines? You&amp;rsquo;re not out of luck!
Look Up for Better Options
Stop looking for internet and phone service on the ground. Look up! Satellite service is a great option for businesses that need fast, reliable service.</description></item><item><title>StarHub reintroduces 12GB mobile data bundles and additional features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 15:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-reintroduces-12gb-mobile-data-bundles-and-additional-features/</guid><description>StarHub has introduced a new, budget-friendly package called SurfHub, combining mobile and home internet services.
For a starting price of S$96.56 per month on a 24-month contract, SurfHub customers receive a 4G mobile plan with a minimum of 12GB of data and a 1Gbps fiber broadband connection for their homes. This combined offer costs roughly half the price of a standalone 12GB mobile plan. SurfHub also includes generous benefits like up to 700 minutes of local calls, 1,500 local SMS/MMS messages, and a subsidy for a new mobile phone.</description></item><item><title>2G mobile phones will no longer be operational in Singapore starting from 1 April 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:54:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/2g-mobile-phones-will-no-longer-be-operational-in-singapore-starting-from-1-april-2017/</guid><description>M1, Singtel, and StarHub will discontinue 2G services in Singapore starting April 1, 2017. This includes 2G voice calls, messaging, and data services. Users with 3G and 4G devices will not be impacted.
Since the introduction of 2G service in 1994, mobile networks have progressed significantly. Singapore&amp;rsquo;s widespread 3G and 4G networks have resulted in high rates of smartphone ownership and use. The spectrum currently used for 2G will be reallocated to provide faster, more advanced 3G and 4G services to meet the growing consumer demand for mobile data and faster access speeds.</description></item><item><title>Internet and Ethernet, The Perfect Broadband Match</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-and-ethernet-the-perfect-broadband-match/</guid><description>By John Shepler
There are many types of broadband internet connections, including DSL, cellular, wireless, cable, satellite, and various fiber optic options. Each has pros and cons regarding cost and performance. However, one technology stands out as the best fit for most businesses: the combination of internet and Ethernet.
Why Ethernet?
Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s dominance in wired networks, both big and small, is its biggest strength. It&amp;rsquo;s the standard protocol for Local Area Networks (LANs), making it compatible with almost all network equipment.</description></item><item><title>Smart Grids Picking the Bones of BPL</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smart-grids-picking-the-bones-of-bpl/</guid><description>Were you eagerly anticipating the day when your electrical outlets would provide both electricity and high-speed internet? That dream might not materialize. Broadband over Power Line (BPL), as a consumer internet option, appears to be fading. However, despite complaints from amateur radio operators about interference, BPL is not disappearing entirely. Instead, it&amp;rsquo;s transforming into a utility-focused communication system, potentially offering a solution that benefits everyone.
The turning point for BPL may have been the recent news that Current Communications is ending its BPL service in Dallas, initially intended for 2 million homes.</description></item><item><title>Dude, Where's My Site?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 04:07:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dude-wheres-my-site/</guid><description>Ever feel like the internet is taking a break, but you&amp;rsquo;re not sure if it&amp;rsquo;s just you? Sometimes, websites refuse to load, leaving you wondering if the problem is on your end. A new tool called DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com provides a simple solution. Just enter the website address, and it will tell you if the site is truly down or if it&amp;rsquo;s just your connection.
Created by a Twitter engineer, DownForEveryoneOrJustMe.com addresses the common question of whether a website is offline or if it&amp;rsquo;s a personal issue.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP).</description></item><item><title>The Singtel SIM Only mobile plan provides unparalleled flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singtel-sim-only-mobile-plan-provides-unparalleled-flexibility/</guid><description>Singtel has launched a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;SIM Only&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes data and offers a customizable, contract-free experience.
This unique plan starts with a S$20 Starter Pack that includes 5GB of data (3GB local mobile data and 2GB Singtel Premium WiFi), along with free incoming calls and SMS. Users have the flexibility to add more data, talktime, and SMS/MMS to their plan whenever they need, with reasonable rates that are reflected in their monthly bill.</description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Fixed Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fixed-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 01:04:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fixed-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Businesses are discovering the advantages of Metro Ethernet over traditional copper and fiber optic cables. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a lesser-known alternative: Ethernet over Fixed Wireless, offering a fast and budget-friendly way to get the bandwidth you need.
Ethernet over Fixed Wireless (EoFW) is distinct from familiar portable or mobile wireless services like WiFi, WiMAX, or LTE. While these offer broadband within a defined area for general, unencrypted use, their bandwidth is limited and shared, resulting in unpredictable connection speeds.</description></item><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps.</description></item><item><title>ViewQwest introduces new 2Gbps fiber broadband services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viewqwest-introduces-new-2gbps-fiber-broadband-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/viewqwest-introduces-new-2gbps-fiber-broadband-services/</guid><description>Source: ViewQwest website.
ViewQwest, a high-end internet provider in Singapore, has launched its 2Gbps fiber broadband service.
ViewQwest&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Vignesa Moorthy, stated that the company recognizes the increasing demand for faster internet speeds as people use their home networks for data-intensive activities like streaming and working remotely. He emphasized the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to delivering the fastest residential internet speeds globally and highlighted the easy setup process of their new 2Gbps service.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Near Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:27:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-near-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s clear that businesses today require faster internet speeds than ever before. With most businesses maintaining an online presence and those that don&amp;rsquo;t still relying on the internet for operations or providing WiFi to customers, adequate internet speed is essential. If you find your current connection lagging, a Gigabit Internet broadband upgrade could be the solution, now and in the future.
Do I Really Need Gigabit Internet? The ideal internet connection is one you don&amp;rsquo;t even notice.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases maximum speeds for home office fibre broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-maximum-speeds-for-home-office-fibre-broadband/</guid><description>Singtel will launch a 10Gbps fiber broadband service for residential customers in Singapore this month. This groundbreaking service, leveraging Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation 10GPON (Gigabit Passive Optical Network) technology, follows a successful pilot phase last year.
&amp;ldquo;We promised to provide our customers with the best network innovations and cutting-edge technologies for work and leisure,&amp;rdquo; said Goh Seow Eng, Managing Director of Home Consumer Singapore at Singtel. &amp;ldquo;We recognize that residential customers are consuming more bandwidth and need faster speeds for their online activities.</description></item><item><title>Where Are T1 Lines Available?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-are-t1-lines-available/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re tired of unreliable DSL and cable internet for your business, consider a T1 line. While DSL and cable are suitable for home use, T1 offers a different level of service. As a regulated telecommunications service, T1 ensures consistent bandwidth and reliable uptime, unlike the consumer-grade alternatives.
T1 lines are widely accessible for businesses and function similarly to utilities. If your business has electricity, water, and phone service, you can likely get a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>10 Mbps Fiber Offers Future Growth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-fiber-offers-future-growth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Insufficient bandwidth severely hinders productivity and increases stress levels. Slow loading times for websites, cloud documents, and collaborative platforms, as well as choppy video calls, are just a few of the frustrations. Increased processing power or RAM won&amp;rsquo;t solve this; the only solution is greater network bandwidth.
What Bandwidth Should You Aim For? The required bandwidth varies depending on your usage patterns and the quality of bandwidth you&amp;rsquo;re using.</description></item><item><title>Phone Power’s $14.95 A Month VoIP Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</guid><description>Are you thinking about switching to VoIP phone service, but put off by the high prices? That doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense! VoIP is meant to be a cheaper alternative to traditional landlines. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s still hope. Phone Power offers a fully featured residential and home office VoIP service for only $14.95 per month.
That&amp;rsquo;s more like it! Why pay $25 or $35 per month for local and long-distance calling when you can get the same or better service for $14.</description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Stable Upload and Download Speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 22:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-stable-upload-and-download-speeds/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
A strong internet connection is essential. If you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing fluctuating upload and download speeds, it might be due to the type of bandwidth connection you have.
Why Can’t It Be Like a LAN?
We&amp;rsquo;ve become accustomed to the speed of local area network (LAN) connections. Modern computers typically come equipped with Gigabit or Fast Ethernet (100 Mbps) network interfaces. Gigabit routers and switches are commonplace, as are Cat5E and Cat6 cables.</description></item><item><title>What To Do If You Hate Your Internet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-to-do-if-you-hate-your-internet-service/</guid><description>Many people express frustration about their internet speed or lack of broadband access. While high-bandwidth options might not always be suitable, there are solutions for individuals and small businesses.
Broadband access is a pressing issue, so much so that the government is investing significantly to expand coverage in underserved areas. While this will eventually improve access, universal coverage like electricity or telephone service is not yet feasible. In remote areas, wireless internet is often the best option.</description></item><item><title>Faster Internet Connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:15:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faster-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Faster internet speeds are generally preferred. While a select few enjoy seamless connectivity due to high bandwidth and low latency, most users remain limited by affordability and availability. However, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to settle for restricted internet speed without exploring the available options.
The Internet Landscape Has Evolved
One factor hindering faster internet adoption is complacency with existing providers. We might be content with a service chosen years ago, unaware of recent advancements.</description></item><item><title>The Ultimate Wireless Firewall: Networks That Don’t Connect</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:57:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ultimate-wireless-firewall-networks-that-don-t-connect/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security has become a crucial aspect for any business with an internet connection. Reports of security breaches are alarmingly frequent, and it&amp;rsquo;s possible that we&amp;rsquo;re only seeing the surface of the problem. While publicized breaches often involve compromised customer data, including sensitive information like credit card numbers, many businesses choose to remain silent about intrusions that don&amp;rsquo;t directly impact their customers to avoid negative publicity.
Can Everyone Afford Cyber Security?</description></item><item><title>Upgrade your ISP to GigE and 10GigE</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrade-your-isp-to-gige-and-10gige/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, internet access is crucial, regardless of whether you operate solely online or have a physical store. The need for more bandwidth never seems to end. Now is a good time to think about upgrading your broadband connection to ensure it can handle your needs and help you work efficiently. You might be surprised by the affordability.
What Bandwidth Speed Do You Need? Smaller businesses, like home offices, individual professional offices, or small retail stores, might find 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service sufficient.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Internet Speed Is Easy to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 10:46:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-internet-speed-is-easy-to-find/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Internet bandwidth needs have skyrocketed. While 10 Mbps was once considered high-speed, now even mid-sized offices need around 100 Mbps. For businesses dealing with video production, cloud applications, software delivery, or many users, Gigabit speeds are becoming essential, and thankfully, readily available.
#1 Choice: Ethernet over Fiber
Fiber optic internet is a future-proof solution. Its infrastructure can handle increasing bandwidth demands, from 1 Gbps to potentially 100 Gbps in the future.</description></item><item><title>Lower Cost Last Mile Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lower-cost-last-mile-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet&amp;rsquo;s Most Critical Part: Your Last Mile Connection For internet users like you, especially businesses, the most crucial aspect is the &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connection. This final leg of the network often determines speed and causes the most issues. A better connection is essential, and fiber optic technology is the current gold standard.
Last Mile Limitations: Why Fiber Matters It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that no internet connection is foolproof.</description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands.</description></item><item><title>Try VoIP Phone Service For Under $10 a Month</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 07:45:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/try-voip-phone-service-for-under-10-a-month/</guid><description>Ever considered trying out those new VoIP phone services to see if they&amp;rsquo;re better than your old landline? The ads are tempting, offering combined local and long-distance billing, tons of features without extra charges, and cheap international rates. It all sounds great and much cheaper than your current plan.
Hesitations are understandable. Will you like the service? Will it work well with your internet? Maybe long-term contracts, especially at $40-$50 a month, aren&amp;rsquo;t appealing.</description></item><item><title>100, 1000, 10000 Mbps Internet Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-1000-10000-mbps-internet-speed/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As technology progresses, businesses require significantly faster internet speeds. Our Wide Area Networks (WANs) are now crucial for operations. Today, internet connections of 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps, and even 10,000 Mbps are standard and essential. Fortunately, pricing has decreased as speeds have increased, making these bandwidth levels attainable.
100 Mbps Fast Ethernet
100 Mbps is the current standard bandwidth, replacing the older 45 Mbps DS3 bandwidth. DS3, an upgrade from slower T1 lines, is part of the TDM telecom standard.</description></item><item><title>Your Own Private Information Superhighway</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/your-own-private-information-superhighway/</guid><description>The internet is often compared to a superhighway, and for good reason: it can take you almost anywhere, just like a road system. However, just like real highways, the internet has its drawbacks, such as traffic jams that slow everything down. These slowdowns are especially common in high-traffic areas or on connections with limited capacity.
One significant difference between the internet and physical highways is the lack of traffic prioritization. Unlike ambulances that get preferential treatment on roads, all internet traffic is treated equally.</description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 4.0 Expands 10 Gbps Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-40-expands-10-gbps-cable-broadband/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Fiber optic service is rapidly expanding and is considered the top choice for businesses seeking high-bandwidth internet. However, because installing fiber can be expensive, many businesses choose cable broadband as a practical alternative. The latest cable standard, DOCSIS 4.0, offers comparable speeds to fiber optic service, with download speeds up to 10 Gbps and upload speeds up to 6 Gbps.
What is DOCSIS?
DOCSIS stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification and allows cable TV companies to provide internet service using the same coaxial cables.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless As Fiber Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 06:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-as-fiber-backup/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
To power your business systems, such as phone systems, conferencing tools, and cloud-based software, you need a lot of reliable bandwidth. Usually, fiber optic connectivity is the answer. But what if the fiber line is cut (it happens), can&amp;rsquo;t be installed quickly enough, or is too expensive to install? In these situations, if you&amp;rsquo;re in the right area, fixed wireless might be the best solution.
What is Fixed Wireless?</description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Has the Speed You Need</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 09:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-has-the-speed-you-need/</guid><description>By John Shepler
Gigabit internet speed is like the gold standard for high-speed business connections. But sometimes even 1 Gbps isn&amp;rsquo;t enough, and that&amp;rsquo;s when you need to consider upgrading to 10 Gigabit Internet.
Who Needs 10 Gbps Bandwidth? Most small businesses and almost all residential internet users don&amp;rsquo;t need this much speed. The bragging rights aren&amp;rsquo;t worth the high monthly fees. This level of bandwidth is meant for demanding applications that justify the cost.</description></item><item><title>Upgrading to Fiber FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/upgrading-to-fiber-faq/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your current bandwidth solution is nearing its capacity, it might be time for an upgrade. While your existing setup has served you well, you need something faster, more reliable, and with lower latency. Fiber optic technology offers a compelling solution, especially compared to traditional copper or cable. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore whether fiber is the right choice for your future needs and budget.
What Makes Fiber Superior to Copper?</description></item><item><title>Is MagicJack The Next Ma Bell?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-magicjack-the-next-ma-bell/</guid><description>The telephone industry is facing challenges as young people are increasingly abandoning traditional landlines, which were once considered essential by previous generations. The breakup of the Bell System into smaller regional companies suggests that the era of a single, all-encompassing telephone provider is over. However, the story doesn&amp;rsquo;t end there.
While it&amp;rsquo;s true that cell phones have replaced landlines for a significant portion of the population, particularly among younger demographics who have grown up with wireless technology, the evolution of the industry goes beyond this shift.</description></item><item><title>So Many Locations, So Little Budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 03:41:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-many-locations-so-little-budget/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Connecting multiple business locations has traditionally been expensive and IT-heavy, often leading companies to settle for less than ideal setups. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be the case anymore.
Traditional Business Connections - Why So Pricey?
Dedicated private lines, like T1 or SONET fiber lines, were the standard solution. However, they are costly, with prices increasing for each additional site and rural locations. Managing a network of these lines across multiple sites requires routers and specialized systems, adding to the expense and complexity.</description></item><item><title>How SD-WAN Hands-Off Seamlessly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 05:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-sd-wan-hands-off-seamlessly/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It would be ideal if WAN network connections never failed, but unfortunately, that&amp;rsquo;s not the case. Even the most reliable copper, fiber, or wireless connections eventually experience downtime. This can interrupt phone calls, halt ongoing work, and lead to lost productivity and revenue. However, imagine a solution that ensures your connections remain virtually uninterrupted, experiencing only minor, momentary glitches regardless of the underlying issue.
This solution exists and is called SD-WAN, or Software-Defined Wide Area Networking.</description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business.</description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection.</description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places.</description></item><item><title>Is There Business Fiber Optic Internet Near Me?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:29:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-business-fiber-optic-internet-near-me/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you still dealing with slow internet service plagued by low speeds, network congestion, high latency, packet loss, or all of the above? It&amp;rsquo;s frustrating, right? You&amp;rsquo;re likely spending more on subpar service than you would on a high-performance fiber optic broadband upgrade. The question is: &amp;ldquo;Is business fiber optic internet available in my area?&amp;rdquo;
Times Have Changed
When broadband first became an option, choices were limited. DSL was once the leading technology, with even basic ADSL shared connections offering a significant speed boost over previous options.</description></item><item><title>Connectivity Should Be Invisible</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 23:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connectivity-should-be-invisible/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Slow internet can manifest in many ways, such as buffering videos, unclear VoIP calls, slow website loading, long file downloads, choppy video conferencing, and delayed responses from cloud services. These are all signs of a poor connection.
Ideally, internet connectivity should be invisible, just like other utilities. For instance, you expect lights to turn on when you flip a switch and water to flow when you turn the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Staying Out of the Clouds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 19:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-out-of-the-clouds/</guid><description>While the use of &amp;ldquo;the cloud&amp;rdquo; is widespread in information technology, understanding its complexities is crucial. The cloud often represents large, intricate networks that users may not fully comprehend.
Although many users are content with the cloud&amp;rsquo;s seemingly magical abilities, David G. Rusin, CEO of American Fiber Systems, argues against perceiving internet clouds as uniform entities. He emphasizes the differences in integrity, reliability, and delivery among cloud providers, highlighting the importance of scrutinizing these aspects.</description></item><item><title>Is Municipal WiFi On The Way Out?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-municipal-wifi-on-the-way-out/</guid><description>While WiFi hotspots are incredibly convenient for travelers in airports, hotels, and restaurants, city-wide WiFi hasn&amp;rsquo;t been as successful as initially hoped. The recent closure of Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s Metro WiFi in Philadelphia raises questions about the future of this technology, even though broadband internet is thriving.
Despite a significant increase in broadband adoption, with dial-up becoming nearly obsolete, city-wide WiFi providers are struggling. Earthlink&amp;rsquo;s experience in Philadelphia, where they only gained a fraction of their projected subscribers, highlights this challenge.</description></item><item><title>Various Flavors of Business Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-flavors-of-business-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it may seem like all internet connections are the same, the way you connect significantly impacts your experience. This article will help determine the best option for you: Dedicated or Shared Internet Access.
What is Dedicated Internet Access?
There are two primary methods to connect to the internet: Shared Internet Access, common for consumers and wireless services, and Dedicated Internet Access (DIA).
Dedicated Access mirrors managing an internal network.</description></item><item><title>Business Internet Service For Everyone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 06:34:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-internet-service-for-everyone/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
In contrast to consumer internet access, business internet service has a history of being overly expensive and difficult to obtain, particularly in less populated areas. This perception largely stems from when traditional telephone companies held a monopoly on internet service, resulting in limited choices and exorbitant prices. Thankfully, today&amp;rsquo;s deregulated market offers a different reality. Any business requiring an internet connection can now get one at budget-friendly prices.</description></item><item><title>QT Talk is Both VoIP and Dial-Around</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</guid><description>Many people are interested in VoIP phone service because of its features and affordability, but they also want the freedom of mobile calling. QT Talk offers a solution that combines the advantages of VoIP with the flexibility of cellular service.
QT Talk provides a feature-rich VoIP service, including their popular North America Plus plan. For a low monthly fee, users enjoy unlimited calls to the U.S., Canada, and Puerto Rico, along with a reduced rate to select international destinations.</description></item><item><title>Can SD-WAN Solve Your Low Bandwidth Problem?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 11:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sd-wan-solve-your-low-bandwidth-problem/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Software Defined Networking (SDN) and SD-WAN, specifically, can&amp;rsquo;t magically produce more bandwidth. Upgrading to a dedicated, high-bandwidth service with a service level agreement from a reputable carrier is a more straightforward solution. However, SD-WAN can offer faster and more reliable bandwidth at a lower cost.
The Root of Bandwidth Issues Businesses grappling with bandwidth issues often face budget constraints that limit them to low-cost options or struggle with the unavailability of suitable services in their location.</description></item><item><title>First in Windmills, First in WiMAX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 06:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/first-in-windmills-first-in-wimax/</guid><description>To understand the future of technology in the 21st century, one might look to the Netherlands. The Dutch have consistently been at the forefront of business and technology, and now they&amp;rsquo;re the first in Europe to launch mobile WiMAX as a wireless broadband standard.
Mobile WiMAX, based on the IEEE 802.16e standard, expands on the fixed wireless 802.16d standard. It&amp;rsquo;s being promoted as a large-scale Wi-Fi solution or a remedy for 3G cellular backhaul issues.</description></item><item><title>Is The World Going on a High Fiber Diet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-world-going-on-a-high-fiber-diet/</guid><description>Global reports indicate a surge in individuals choosing fiber optic internet over cable. While the US lags in replacing copper with fiber for home internet, particularly compared to nations like China with a considerably larger fiber optic subscriber base, the shift is undeniable.
Satellite communication, initially envisioned as the solution for global connectivity, has faced limitations. Despite the existence of low earth orbit (LEO) and geosynchronous satellites enabling services like satellite broadband, the technology remains specialized even after five decades.</description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U.</description></item></channel></rss>