<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colocation Hosting on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-hosting/</link><description>Recent content in Colocation Hosting on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/colocation-hosting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Colocation Hosting Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:25:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>To find the most cost-effective bandwidth, look no further than telecommunication carriers. Bandwidth costs increase as you move away from a carrier&amp;rsquo;s Point of Presence (POP). The solution: get closer to the carrier.
While physically moving in with a carrier might not be feasible, businesses can achieve proximity by utilizing colocation centers, also known as carrier hotels. These facilities, often run by third parties, provide a secure and controlled environment where businesses can house their servers close to multiple carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Managed IP Services Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</guid><description>Companies are increasingly interested in cloud services because they can save money and access capabilities that they might not otherwise be able to afford. Cloud services offer a wide range of IP services and can be accessed in-house, privately, or purchased from a provider. While providers offer different services, they all deliver their services over IP networks, leading to the term &amp;ldquo;managed IP services.&amp;rdquo;
Managed services allow carriers or service providers to take responsibility for operations, a task typically handled by on-site IT staff...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/managed-ip-services-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Colocate To An Omaha Data Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 23:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</guid><description>While major corporations might associate colocation data centers with locations like 60 Hudson St in New York City or One Wilshire in Los Angeles, Omaha, Nebraska, presents a compelling alternative.
Beyond being home to Warren Buffett and Berkshire Hathaway, Omaha boasts a robust business environment, earning recognition from Forbes magazine as the nation&amp;rsquo;s top &amp;ldquo;Best-Bang-For-The-Buck City.&amp;rdquo; Crucially, Omaha houses the Scott Data Center complex.
The Scott Data Center offers over 110,000 square feet of data storage, boasting continuous operation since 2006...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-colocate-to-an-omaha-data-center/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>