<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>International Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-law/</link><description>Recent content in International Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/international-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Legal Standing of a Third Country before the CJEU: AG Hogan's Opinion in Case C‑872/19 P Venezuela v Council in Relation to State Immunity and Comity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-standing-of-a-third-country-before-the-cjeu-ag-hogan-s-opinion-in-case-c-872-19-p-venezuela-v-council-in-relation-to-state-immunity-and-comity/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
In a legal opinion issued on February 20, 2021, Advocate General Hogan addressed a crucial procedural issue: Can a non-EU country legally challenge EU actions before the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU)? This question holds significance because the Court has never directly ruled on it within the context of sanctions, and it delves into the principles governing the relationship between EU law and other international law subjects.</description></item><item><title>Is the agreement between the EU and Turkey on refugees and migration considered a treaty?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 00:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-agreement-between-the-eu-and-turkey-on-refugees-and-migration-considered-a-treaty/</guid><description>Maarten den Heijer*, Thomas Spijkerboer**
*Assistant professor of international law at the Universiteit van Amsterdam
**Professor of migration law at the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam.
The European Parliament recently inquired about the legal standing of the EU-Turkey Statement of March 18th, which initiated the return of asylum seekers from Greece to Turkey. Concerns arose because the agreement bypassed the standard EU treaty procedure outlined in Article 218 TFEU. The Parliament seeks clarification on whether the Council views this statement as a binding treaty and, if not, whether Turkey is aware of its non-binding status.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Ruling in Case C-632/20 P Spain v Commission (Kosovo) on Third Parties, Nations, and Other Entities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-case-c-632-20-p-spain-v-commission-kosovo-on-third-parties-nations-and-other-entities/</guid><description>Eva Kassoti, Senior Researcher, CLEER academic co-ordinator, T.M.C. Asser Institute. E-mail: E.Kassoti@asser.nl
Photo credit: Aljabakphoto, via Wikimedia commons - Šar Mountains National Park in Dragaš, Kosovo
On January 17th, 2023, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in Case C-632/20 P, Spain v Commission (Kosovo), deciding that Kosovo can participate in the Body of European Regulators for Electronic Communications (BEREC). This decision, reached despite the EU&amp;rsquo;s non-recognition of Kosovo as a state, clarifies that &amp;ldquo;third country&amp;rdquo; status, as defined by the EU, can include territories not recognized as sovereign states and that these entities are eligible for participation in EU agencies.</description></item><item><title>Is the draft UK/EU renegotiation deal considered to be 'legally binding and irreversible'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 13:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal-considered-to-be-legally-binding-and-irreversible/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The draft agreement regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s EU membership has sparked significant debate. While some, mostly within the UK, believe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t go far enough, others, primarily from the remaining EU member states, argue it grants excessive revisions to EU law for a single member state. These are primarily substantive concerns. While I have previously addressed some immigration-related issues within the draft, I will delve into other substantive matters later.</description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to remain in the single market even after exiting the EU? The proposed lawsuit regarding Article 127 of the EEA.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 12:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-remain-in-the-single-market-even-after-exiting-the-eu-the-proposed-lawsuit-regarding-article-127-of-the-eea/</guid><description>Could the UK Remain in the Single Market While Exiting the EU? Steve Peers
A potential legal battle questions whether the UK can remain part of the European Economic Area (EEA) even if it leaves the EU. This situation involves both international and national legal complexities. Let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the EEA itself.
Understanding the EEA
Established in 1994, the EEA treaty aimed to expand the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market to European Free Trade Area (EFTA) nations.</description></item><item><title>The relationship between the EU and Morocco and the issue of the Western Sahara: the European Court of Justice and the principles of international law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 04:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-relationship-between-the-eu-and-morocco-and-the-issue-of-the-western-sahara-the-european-court-of-justice-and-the-principles-of-international-law/</guid><description>Markus W. Gehring: University Lecturer, University of Cambridge; J.S.D. (Yale), LL.M. (Yale), Dr jur. (Hamburg), MA (Cantab); Deputy Director, Economic Law at CIGI
On December 21, 2016, the Court of Justice issued its appeals decision in the case of Council v. Front Polisario. This Grand Chamber judgment, reached under an expedited procedure, overturned the prior decision made by the EU General Court in Front Polisario v Council roughly a year before.</description></item><item><title>EU Animal Welfare Rules' Extraterritorial Reach</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-animal-welfare-rules-extraterritorial-reach/</guid><description>By Jessica Lawrence, PhD student, VU University Amsterdam
In the Zuchtvieh-Transport case, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) determined that Regulation 1/2005, concerning the protection of animals during transport, applies beyond EU borders. This means that even when transport starts within the EU and ends outside its borders, the regulation still governs the journey. This decision is significant as it promotes animal welfare but also reflects the CJEU’s expanding interpretation of EU jurisdiction, stretching conventional international law principles on &amp;rsquo;territorial jurisdiction'.</description></item><item><title>The legal status and impact of the UK/EU renegotiation deal.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 14:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-status-and-impact-of-the-uk-eu-renegotiation-deal/</guid><description>Is the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal legally binding? Steve Peers explores whether the UK&amp;rsquo;s renegotiated EU membership deal is legally binding and what implications this has. He examines various aspects of the deal, including its legal status, enforceability, and potential for reversibility.
Legal Complexity and Forms The renegotiation deal is comprised of seven legal documents: a Decision by EU Heads of State and Government, a Statement by the same group (including a draft Council Decision), a European Council Declaration, and four Commission declarations.</description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice provides additional clarification on how the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement applies to Western Sahara.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 15:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-provides-additional-clarification-on-how-the-eu-morocco-fisheries-partnership-agreement-applies-to-western-sahara/</guid><description>By Markus W. Gehring, Lecturer in Law, University of Cambridge
On February 27, 2018, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its judgment in a case referred by the High Court of England and Wales. The case, Western Sahara Campaign UK v. HM Revenue and Customs, Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, C-266/16, concerned the legality of EU fishing activities in waters adjacent to Western Sahara.</description></item><item><title>The politicization of treaty obligations in private schools.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-politicization-of-treaty-obligations-in-private-schools/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-politicization-of-treaty-obligations-in-private-schools/</guid><description>Dr Kasey McCall-Smith, Senior Lecturer in Public International Law, University of Edinburgh
The Labour Party&amp;rsquo;s 2019 Annual Conference has drawn significant attention, particularly for its resolution to eliminate private schools in the UK. This highlights the need to examine politicians&amp;rsquo; passionate pronouncements in light of legal realities, especially international and human rights law. Similar situations arose earlier this year when Theresa May presented a unilateral statement on the UK&amp;rsquo;s interpretation of the Withdrawal Agreement Protocol on Ireland/Northern Ireland and when Geoffrey Cox MP incorrectly suggested that the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties (VCLT) offered a simple solution to the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the backstop.</description></item></channel></rss>