<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Covid on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/covid/</link><description>Recent content in Covid on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Changi Airport Group announces the closure of Terminal 2 for a period of 18 months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:34:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/changi-airport-group-announces-the-closure-of-terminal-2-for-a-period-of-18-months/</guid><description>Source: CAG. Changi Airport.
Due to a significant decrease in air travel and the low likelihood of a return to pre-pandemic levels soon, Changi Airport Group (CAG) has decided to consolidate operations at Changi Airport. This move aims to reduce operating costs like utilities and cleaning for CAG and its partners while optimizing resource allocation across the airport&amp;rsquo;s terminals.
Starting May 1, 2020, Terminal 2 (T2) will halt operations for 18 months, relocating airlines to other terminals*.</description></item><item><title>The financial consequences of the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 06:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-financial-consequences-of-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>Blockchain&amp;rsquo;s potential in fostering trust within networks is significant.
The World Bank Group has been actively supporting clients throughout the COVID-19 pandemic. William Zhang, a Lead Information Security Architect and Blockchain Specialist at the World Bank Group, highlighted the severe economic impact of COVID-19, including a US$4 trillion global GDP decline, significant job losses, and numerous business closures.
Zhang, speaking at a webinar titled &amp;ldquo;Leveraging Blockchain Innovations to Cope with the COVID-19 New Normal,&amp;rdquo; organized by the 10x1000 Tech for Inclusion Programme, noted that projections indicate a 9% increase in both poverty and extreme poverty.</description></item><item><title>Singtel increases its offering of free content as the circuit-breaker in Singapore is extended</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-increases-its-offering-of-free-content-as-the-circuit-breaker-in-singapore-is-extended/</guid><description>Singtel TV is expanding its free preview by adding 10 more channels while the circuit breaker period is extended. This is in addition to the 95,000 hours of programming already offered for free on Singtel TV and Singtel CAST, which was launched last month to help entertain people stuck at home.
From May 1st to 31st, Singtel TV and Singtel TV GO will offer a free preview with more entertainment, factual, news, and other programming from popular channels including National Geographic and FOX Family Movies.</description></item><item><title>Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas is continuing its guest outreach program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-senses-hotels-resorts-spas-is-continuing-its-guest-outreach-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas.
Since late March 2020, Six Senses Hotels Resorts Spas has been offering its guests and followers daily live chats, cooking demonstrations, and meditation and yoga sessions.
Recognizing that many people are hesitant to resume travel despite the easing of COVID-19 restrictions, the company introduced six new themes for its #AtHomeWithSixSenses campaign.
These themes - Wellness, Eat, Grow, Sustainability, Sleep and From the Heart of Six Senses - will continue to be explored through content on the Six Senses website (sixsenses.</description></item><item><title>According to Henley &amp; Partners, APAC passports provide greater international travel opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 21:41:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-henley-partners-apac-passports-provide-greater-international-travel-opportunities/</guid><description>The 2021 Henley Passport Index, which ranks global passports based on the number of destinations accessible without a prior visa, places Japan in first place when disregarding temporary restrictions. This is the third year in a row that Japan has achieved the top spot, independently or tied with Singapore. The index, which uses exclusive data from the International Air Transport Association (IATA), demonstrates the Asia Pacific (APAC) region&amp;rsquo;s dominance, a trend experts predict will continue.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean businesses are adapting to unprecedented circumstances</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-adapting-to-unprecedented-circumstances/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 11:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-businesses-are-adapting-to-unprecedented-circumstances/</guid><description>The COVID-19 pandemic forced businesses to adapt in order to survive lockdowns. In Singapore, several companies found innovative ways to reinvent themselves:
Audio House
Audio House, a retailer known for selling electronics and appliances, typically relies on its physical showroom and in-person customer interactions. When Singapore&amp;rsquo;s lockdown restrictions forced the closure of their showroom, Audio House had to find new ways to operate.
To retain their sales team and equip them with new skills, Audio House implemented an &amp;ldquo;Online Concierge&amp;rdquo; service.</description></item><item><title>Singapore intensifies its response to COVID-19</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-intensifies-its-response-to-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 05:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-intensifies-its-response-to-covid-19/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for National Development and Second Minister for Finance, Lawrence Wong, who also co-leads the task force for COVID-19, recently announced new measures to combat the country&amp;rsquo;s recent surge in cases, which jumped from 212 on March 14 to 385 by March 20.
Wong stated that the government&amp;rsquo;s goal is to reduce social interactions and limit activities that could potentially spread the virus. He hopes these measures will result in fewer people in public spaces.</description></item><item><title>Dermatologists have created a one-of-a-kind hand sanitizer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 03:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</guid><description>● Developed by dermatologists with a deep understanding of skin care and patient requirements.
● Eliminates 99.99% of common household germs and viruses, including SARS-COV-2, upon application.
● Remains effective for 24 hours, even after handwashing, minimizing the need for frequent reapplication.
DS Skin Clinic and its global network of clinics have introduced the DS Skin Clinic All-Day Hand Sanitizer. This innovative product is engineered to outperform existing hand sanitizers available in the market.</description></item><item><title>Singtel unveils National Day film for 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 10:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-unveils-national-day-film-for-2020/</guid><description>Singtel&amp;rsquo;s latest National Day film celebrates the resilience of Singaporeans as they face the challenges of COVID-19. Titled This is the year, the film is available on Singtel TV and social media platforms.
This is the year highlights the difficulties brought on by the pandemic and pays homage to the spirit of progress that drives Singaporeans forward.
Source: Singtel video. This is the year we will not have the F1 race.</description></item><item><title>Customers of AIA Singapore receive complimentary coverage for Covid-19</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-aia-singapore-receive-complimentary-coverage-for-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 05:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-of-aia-singapore-receive-complimentary-coverage-for-covid-19/</guid><description>AIA Singapore is offering complimentary COVID-19 coverage to eligible customers. This additional coverage is automatic and requires no action from the customer.
The company stated that this initiative underscores their commitment to supporting the health and well-being of their customers, particularly during challenging times.
Customers eligible for this benefit will receive it automatically. The coverage will remain active until December 31, 2020, or 30 days after the DORSCON level returns to green, whichever comes first.</description></item><item><title>Cainiao will collaborate with Ethiopian Airlines to provide cold chain air freight services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 09:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cainiao-will-collaborate-with-ethiopian-airlines-to-provide-cold-chain-air-freight-services/</guid><description>Source: Alibaba Group. Cainiao will distribute temperature-sensitive medications, including COVID-19 vaccines, globally, excluding Africa, via Dubai in partnership with Ethiopian Airlines.
Cainiao Smart Logistics Network, the logistics branch of Alibaba Group Holdings, has partnered with Ethiopian Airlines. Their collaboration will establish a specialized cold chain air freight system to transport temperature-controlled medical supplies. These shipments will originate from Shenzhen Airport, recognized as China&amp;rsquo;s first medical cross-border cold chain facility.</description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized businesses in the Asia-Pacific region are feeling positive about their recovery following the COVID-19 pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 15:17:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-businesses-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-feeling-positive-about-their-recovery-following-the-covid-19-pandemic/</guid><description>A recent HP study titled &amp;ldquo;Survival to Revival&amp;rdquo; surveyed small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in the Asia-Pacific region and found that over half believe they will not only survive the pandemic but thrive in its aftermath. Digital transformation is considered a key factor in this recovery.
The study revealed that 60% of respondents view digital transformation as crucial, particularly in areas like innovative work processes, flexible work arrangements, and tailored products and services.</description></item><item><title>British Airways assures that flying is safe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:14:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-airways-assures-that-flying-is-safe/</guid><description>Source: British Airways. Doyle.
In his initial address after becoming British Airways&amp;rsquo; CEO, Sean Doyle stated that the airline believes flying poses a minimal health risk. He cited data from IATA suggesting only 44 COVID-19 cases have been linked to flights since early 2020, while 1.2 billion passengers traveled during that time.
During his speech at Airlines 2050: Beyond the Crisis, Doyle emphasized, &amp;ldquo;Ensuring the safety of our customers and crew remains our top priority, and we&amp;rsquo;re implementing all necessary safety protocols to protect them.</description></item><item><title>A company based in Singapore is providing a portable COVID-19 testing solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-company-based-in-singapore-is-providing-a-portable-covid-19-testing-solution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-company-based-in-singapore-is-providing-a-portable-covid-19-testing-solution/</guid><description>Cell ID, a medical technology company based in Singapore, has developed a portable genetic testing device that can determine if a person has COVID-19. The device, called the Quiz PCR Biochip, is small enough to fit in the palm of your hand and utilizes laptop software to analyze the results. By using biotechnology, it can perform two tests simultaneously outside of a traditional laboratory setting.
Results are delivered quickly, with positive cases identified in as little as five minutes and negative results available within an hour.</description></item><item><title>SAP reported that small and medium-sized enterprises in the Asia-Pacific region have adopted remote work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 05:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sap-reported-that-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-the-asia-pacific-region-have-adopted-remote-work/</guid><description>A recent study titled &amp;ldquo;Digital, Resilient, and Experience-driven: How Small and Midsize Organisations Can Prepare for the New Economy,&amp;rdquo; conducted by SAP in conjunction with Oxford Economics, reveals that small and mid-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the Asia-Pacific region are well-situated to flourish in the evolving business landscape following the COVID-19 pandemic.
The study, which surveyed 2,000 senior executives globally, including 832 from APAC countries like Singapore, Australia, and Japan, examined the priorities and digital readiness of SMEs.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Sports Hub has successfully adapted during the pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-sports-hub-has-successfully-adapted-during-the-pandemic/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Sports Hub. Plans for 2021.
The Singapore Sports Hub has adjusted its focus in 2021 to deliver impactful experiences, building on the lessons learned from 2020. This includes their earlier efforts, from providing safe housing for migrant workers during the peak of COVID-19 to creating new event formats for local audiences.
Despite the global pandemic impacting the Hub&amp;rsquo;s ability to host its typical lineup of large-scale sporting and entertainment events, it shifted gears to become a source of support for the community.</description></item><item><title>Residents of Hong Kong can enjoy an additional complimentary night at New World Millennium Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residents-of-hong-kong-can-enjoy-an-additional-complimentary-night-at-new-world-millennium-hong-kong/</guid><description>The New World Millennium Hong Kong Hotel, a prominent five-star establishment situated on the Victoria Harbour waterfront in Tsim Sha Tsui East, is offering a special &amp;ldquo;1+1 Bonus Night&amp;rdquo; room package to Hong Kong residents. Until September 30th, residents booking a one-night stay can enjoy an additional night free of charge.
This promotion is exclusively available to Hong Kong residents and requires HKID verification upon check-in. By reserving a City View room or a higher category for a single night, guests will automatically receive a second night&amp;rsquo;s stay complimentary.</description></item><item><title>Seeking innovative solutions to address the challenges posed by COVID-19</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seeking-innovative-solutions-to-address-the-challenges-posed-by-covid-19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 18:22:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seeking-innovative-solutions-to-address-the-challenges-posed-by-covid-19/</guid><description>The Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) in Singapore has launched an initiative through its Open Innovation Platform (OIP) to address challenges arising from COVID-19 and beyond. Established in 2018, the OIP helps companies source creative ideas, expertise, and resources to meet their innovation and business needs, fostering the development of novel digital solutions.
This Innovation Call, themed &amp;ldquo;COVID-19 &amp;amp; Beyond – Innovation for Social Good&amp;rdquo;, aims to find solutions for issues faced by vulnerable individuals and businesses in Singapore.</description></item><item><title>The effectiveness of SingaMask can last for up to 365 washes, and we are currently developing even longer-lasting face masks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-effectiveness-of-singamask-can-last-for-up-to-365-washes-and-we-are-currently-developing-even-longer-lasting-face-masks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 04:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-effectiveness-of-singamask-can-last-for-up-to-365-washes-and-we-are-currently-developing-even-longer-lasting-face-masks/</guid><description>Source: SmartComm World. People wearing the
SingaMask 365.
The SingaMask, designed and manufactured in Singapore by SmartComm World, is a reusable face mask boasting N95-level efficacy and the ability to be washed up to 365 times.
SmartComm World highlights three key features of this innovative mask:
Versatility
The SingaMask can be worn dry, like traditional masks, or wet.
Durability
Repeated washing enhances the mask&amp;rsquo;s comfort and fit while improving airflow.</description></item><item><title>Xero thoroughly examines the effects of COVID-19 on small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 17:55:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xero-thoroughly-examines-the-effects-of-covid-19-on-small-businesses/</guid><description>Xero, a global platform for small businesses, has published two reports examining the economic and emotional effects of the COVID-19 pandemic on small businesses worldwide.
Source: Xero&amp;rsquo;s Emotional metrics: small business mindsets during the pandemic report. From January to August 2020, small business owners experienced a range of emotions, from feeling &amp;ldquo;worn down&amp;rdquo; to a sense of loss.
The Xero Small Business Insights (SBI) Special Report, Pandemic Insights: Small Business Experience, was created in collaboration with AlphaBeta (part of Accenture) and utilizes anonymized and aggregated data from over 300,000 Xero subscribers.</description></item><item><title>Dash has increased its services in response to the COVID-19 outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 05:16:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dash-has-increased-its-services-in-response-to-the-covid-19-outbreak/</guid><description>Dash, a mobile wallet by Singtel, is introducing new features to assist customers and partners during the COVID-19 pandemic. These features offer more convenient options for sending money, shopping online, and connecting businesses with customers while social distancing measures are in place.
Dash is providing free mobile remittance services to help employers and foreign workers in Singapore affected by stay-at-home guidelines and travel restrictions. This service allows for secure digital money transfers to seven countries: Bangladesh, China, India, Indonesia, Malaysia, Myanmar, and the Philippines.</description></item></channel></rss>