<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LTE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lte/</link><description>Recent content in LTE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/lte/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi increases LTE coverage in the Klang Valley, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. In this image, Digi&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Albern Murty (left), demonstrates the high quality and reliability of their 4G LTE network through a video call. The call connects with Hitz.FM radio personalities Ean and Adam C, visible on the smaller screen to the left. Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer, stands on the right.
Digi Telecommunications has significantly broadened its LTE network coverage in the Klang Valley, more than doubling its reach in this region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-increases-lte-coverage-in-the-klang-valley-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC has unveiled the Desire 620 and 620G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:44:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</guid><description>HTC has introduced the HTC Desire 620 dual sim, the successor to the HTC Desire 610.
Source: HTC. The 620G in Milkyway gray.
Jack Yang, President of HTC South Asia, stated that the new HTC Desire model provides a balance of modern design, strong processing, and fast connectivity, making it a suitable option for budget-conscious entertainment enthusiasts.
The Desire 620 dual sim is equipped with a Snapdragon 410 Qualcomm processor, Android 4...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-has-unveiled-the-desire-620-and-620g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Fiber Gold Rush Is On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 12:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</guid><description>The transition from copper wires to fiber optic strands has been recognized as a necessity for some time. This shift is driven by the growing need for bandwidth as technology progresses. Over the past few decades, various sectors, including internet service providers, cable companies, healthcare facilities, and large enterprises, have progressively adopted fiber optic connections. Services like Metro Ethernet have made this transition feasible even for mid-sized businesses. Now, small businesses and individual consumers are poised to benefit from this technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fiber-gold-rush-is-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is 4G and Why Do You Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re constantly bombarded with ads for 3G phones and wireless aircards, and now 4G is emerging. But what does this new technology mean and why should you care?
2G, 3G, 4G—these &amp;ldquo;Gs&amp;rdquo; represent different generations of wireless broadband. This technology evolves so rapidly that various generations often coexist in the same region. This is intentional. If you&amp;rsquo;re in an area with weak 3G coverage, your device automatically connects to slower 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-4g-and-why-do-you-want-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Wars This Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:17:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</guid><description>The race for 4G dominance is about to start, even though 3G deployment is still underway. Major carriers like AT&amp;amp;T, Verizon, and Sprint have upgraded most of their towers in populated areas, and 3G devices are readily available. However, the focus is shifting to 4G due to the increasing demand for bandwidth from sophisticated mobile applications and the ongoing competition among carriers.
The value of 4G lies in its potential to enable future advancements rather than just meeting current needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-wars-this-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Next Decade of Bandwidth - Part IV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 15:35:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</guid><description>The most desirable wireless frequencies will soon be completely allocated. These prime frequencies, ranging from a few hundred to a few thousand MHz, offer high bandwidth, strong building penetration, and accommodate small antennas. The problem is that the number of these channels is finite. Similar to real estate, once the best spots are taken, expansion continues into less ideal areas.
Finding more bandwidth means moving up or down the electromagnetic spectrum, which presents challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-decade-of-bandwidth-part-iv/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Speedier Network For The iPhone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 23:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</guid><description>While the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s popularity is a boon for AT&amp;amp;T, which holds the exclusive contract, the device&amp;rsquo;s data demands present a significant hurdle.
Historically, cellular towers primarily handled voice calls, with data as a secondary function. Early data speeds were adequate for text-based services, but the advent of camera phones, web browsers, and video streaming dramatically increased bandwidth requirements. Today&amp;rsquo;s users demand home and work-level speeds, typically between 3 to 10 Mbps, far exceeding the capabilities of older networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/speedier-network-for-the-iphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will WiMAX Become WiMedium?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 19:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</guid><description>WiMAX, a wireless broadband standard, was envisioned as the key to 4G mobile networks and roaming. However, other technologies are catching up and might become the dominant force in 4G.
WiMAX aimed to broaden WiFi&amp;rsquo;s reach from a few hundred feet to many miles, allowing mobile devices to seamlessly switch between towers for continuous connectivity, similar to cell phone networks. It promised significantly faster speeds compared to existing cellular broadband, suitable for indoor and outdoor use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-wimax-become-wimedium/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is WiMAX Worth the Wait?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 02:02:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</guid><description>For years, the arrival of WiMAX, a new wireless broadband standard, has been highly anticipated. From its conceptual phase to the development of standards, equipment certification, and the launch of pilot projects, the journey of WiMAX has been closely followed. However, with its impending arrival, the question arises: will WiMAX still live up to its initial hype?
WiMAX, short for Worldwide Interoperability for Microwave Access, is a globally recognized standard with potential applications in various fields such as cellular backhaul, mobile internet, business broadband, and even as a potential replacement for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-wimax-worth-the-wait/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Quietly Encroaching on 3G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 23:47:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</guid><description>Cellular companies are promoting 3G wireless technology as the most advanced available. However, a faster technology called 4G is being gradually introduced across the country. This situation reflects the typical progression of technology, where an invention like wireless data service undergoes continuous advancements. Like early personal computers compared to today&amp;rsquo;s models, mobile data is following a similar path of growth.
Cellular carriers dominate wide-area mobile service due to their extensive network infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-quietly-encroaching-on-3g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tripping the LTE Fantastic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:59:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</guid><description>Although fiber optic and mobile WiMAX are getting a lot of attention, LTE could become the next major broadband technology. Could gigabit wireless communication be on the horizon?
People struggling with slow 1G connections or the first iPhone might find the idea of 1,000 Mbps speeds on their mobile devices unrealistic. It seems like there wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough bandwidth from cell towers. However, emerging technologies may increase wireless bandwidth significantly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripping-the-lte-fantastic/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel provides eSIMs for the Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 12:19:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</guid><description>Source: Samsung website. This Samsung Gear S3 frontier LTE smartwatch functions on Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE network.
Singtel has launched the Samsung Gear S3 frontier (LTE) on its 4G LTE network. Equipped with an eSIM, this smartwatch offers independent 4G LTE connectivity. This allows users to make and receive calls, send text messages, and browse the internet without needing their smartphones.
Singtel customers will also experience 4G ClearVoice, also known as VoLTE...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-provides-esims-for-the-samsung-gear-s3-frontier-lte-smartwatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Digi introduces 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru, Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:51:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: Digi. Pictured at the launch of Digi&amp;rsquo;s 4G LTE service in Johor Bahru are (from left): Tuan Haji Rizal B. Abd Malek, Regional Head of the Malaysian Communications and Multimedia Commission (SKMM) Southern Region; Loh Keh Jiat, Digi&amp;rsquo;s Chief Sales Officer; YB Datuk Ir Haji Hasni B Haji Mohammad, Chairman of the Johor Executive Council for Public Works, Rural and Regional Development; Digi’s Chief Network Officer Kesavan Sivabalan; and Ng Chak Khin, Digi’s Head of Southern Region...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digi-introduces-4g-lte-service-in-johor-bahru-malaysia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is LTE too LATE?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</guid><description>The variety of mobile wireless standards, with names like 1xRTT and EVDO, can be confusing, similar to the evolution of computer processors. This is because wireless broadband technology is still developing, unlike the more mature design of PCs. LTE, short for Long Term Evolution, is the latest advancement causing excitement. But is it truly significant, or is it too insignificant or too delayed?
LTE aims to be a global standard for mobile communication, developed by the 3rd Generation Partnership Project (3GPP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-lte-too-late/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indosat Ooredoo introduces nationwide 4G-LTE service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 19:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</guid><description>Source: Ooredoo.
Indosat Ooredoo has introduced its high-speed 4G-LTE service across Indonesia. The company stated that the improved connectivity and call clarity offered by its new 4Gplus data network come at the same cost as its existing 3G services.
In the last two years, Indosat Ooredoo has doubled its network speeds, achieving the fastest 3G internet speeds available. Independent tests show its 4Gplus service can reach download speeds of up to 185Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indosat-ooredoo-introduces-nationwide-4g-lte-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Grade 4G LTE Broadband for Work at Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 07:27:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Suddenly, everyone is working remotely, and reliable internet access is crucial. Remote areas often lack fast, low-latency bandwidth, making work challenging. Thankfully, 4G LTE cellular broadband and high-performance modem/routers provide a quick, affordable solution without long-term contracts.
Wireless: The Solution
Forget about slow, expensive wired or fiber optic installations, especially for temporary setups. Wireless broadband offers a practical alternative, readily available wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a decent cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-grade-4g-lte-broadband-for-work-at-home/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The HTC Desire 510 provides budget-friendly LTE capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 22:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</guid><description>HTC&amp;rsquo;s most budget-friendly LTE smartphone is hitting the shelves just days after the company launched the Desire 210 in Singapore. Starting September 6, 2014, you can find the HTC Desire 510 at mobile carriers and major retailers across Singapore. This device boasts a quad-core LTE processor, a 4.7” display, and runs on Android 4.4.
Source: HTC.
&amp;ldquo;While the industry has been buzzing about the impact of 4G, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to overlook that only a handful of high-end devices truly utilize this technology,&amp;rdquo; says HTC CEO, Peter Chou...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-htc-desire-510-provides-budget-friendly-lte-capabilities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3G 4G Mobile Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 18:55:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</guid><description>Mobile internet usage has increased, but bandwidth limitations are comparable to the early days of dial-up compared to today&amp;rsquo;s broadband. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine current mobile internet speeds.
The current standard, 3G wireless, provides speeds between 500 Kbps and 1.5 Mbps through cellular carriers. These carriers are the same ones providing cell phone service, using the same towers, so coverage is identical.
The demand for 3G increased dramatically after the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s release. The first iPhone utilized AT&amp;amp;T&amp;rsquo;s EDGE network, a 2...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3g-4g-mobile-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Broadband for the Bandwidth Starved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While it&amp;rsquo;s evident that we exist in a connected world, not everyone enjoys the optimal level of connectivity. Some areas remain underserved, lacking sufficient bandwidth. So, what can be done if you find yourself in such a situation?
Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry, Broadband Exists!
In the past, broadband access was limited to specific areas, leaving many with only dial-up connections. Fortunately, the situation has significantly improved, with broadband internet access now available in most places...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-bandwidth-starved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cell Phone Wireless Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 14:15:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</guid><description>Cell phones today are capable of much more than just voice calls. The mobile networks have evolved to carry both voice and data, offering wireless broadband internet access that rivals DSL and cable connections.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t explored mobile internet recently, you might be surprised by its speed and availability. Currently, two competing systems are widely available, with two even faster networks in their early stages.
AT&amp;amp;T promotes its HSDPA and EDGE networks, notably featuring the Apple iPhone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cell-phone-wireless-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Is Making Obsolescence Obsolete</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</guid><description>Keeping up with technology is a constant struggle, similar to swimming against a strong current. Any pause or delay can cause you to fall behind competitors who are advancing rapidly.
Technology is constantly evolving, becoming outdated quickly. The longer you rely on existing technology, the more outdated it gets, eventually lacking support or functionality. While the physical hardware may remain functional, it struggles to utilize the latest resources and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-is-making-obsolescence-obsolete/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>