<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>291KSBG4000 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/291ksbg4000/</link><description>Recent content in 291KSBG4000 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/291ksbg4000/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4000: Final Adjustments, Some Odds and Ends and a Test Drive with Cal Tjader</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 15:10:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-final-adjustments-some-odds-and-ends-and-a-test-drive-with-cal-tjader/</guid><description>After switching the original black plinth with a teak one from a Beogram 4002, it was time for the final adjustments and a test run of the Beogram 4000 turntable. I started by setting the platter height, tilt, and alignment with the surrounding aluminum panels. Next, I adjusted the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowest point to make sure the needle wouldn&amp;rsquo;t touch the black ribs on the platter if the platter detection system malfunctioned.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New Arrival From Germany - A First Peek</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:25:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-arrival-from-germany-a-first-peek/</guid><description>A Beogram 4000 turntable arrived from Germany for restoration, packaged securely with double boxes and separate protection for the platter.
The inner box housed the Beogram within a styrofoam liner, while the two accompanying cartridges, an MMC20 E and an MMC20 EN, were packaged together. Unfortunately, the cartridges shifted during transit, causing the cantilever of the EN to press against the E cartridge&amp;rsquo;s plastic shroud. Thankfully, upon careful inspection, it appears that both cantilevers remain undamaged.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s arm carriage, attention shifted to the keypad—the turntable&amp;rsquo;s control center housing the early digital control system. A single screw secures the keypad, allowing access to its internal components.
Uniquely, this keypad lacked visible wiring underneath, unlike other 4000 models with wiring behind the latch. Instead, the wiring harness was cleverly routed into the pad from the front, simplifying reassembly.
The restoration process began by addressing the fragile light bulbs illuminating the arm position scale and RPM trimmers.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Arm Lowering and Tracking Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-arm-lowering-and-tracking-systems/</guid><description>My work began on the Beogram 4000 turntable that arrived from Germany. As is my practice, the tracking and arm lowering mechanisms were the first to be refurbished. The arm lowering mechanism, controlled by a solenoid and damper arrangement, is pictured here:
After removing components requiring cleaning and lubrication, the area looked like this:
Here are the disassembled parts:
With cleaning and lubrication complete, reassembly followed. Next, I addressed the seized damper-to-arm linkage, accessible only after detaching the sensor arm.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the PCBs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-pcbs/</guid><description>Following the control cluster restoration of a Beogram 4000, attention turned to the PCBs. The main PCB was initially in average condition.
The standard procedure involves replacing all electrolytic capacitors with high-quality Japanese equivalents, installing a new RPM relay, and substituting the original single-turn RPM adjustment trimmers with 25-turn encapsulated ones for increased precision. Capacitor replacement is critical as aging and potential leakage can lead to operational issues. The RPM section, shown below, exemplifies this.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of a Cracked Cartridge Mount with a 3D Printed Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:56:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-a-cracked-cartridge-mount-with-a-3d-printed-assembly/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently repairing has a common issue: a cracked MMC cartridge mount. This piece, made from a more delicate plastic in the 4000 compared to the later 4002 models, tends to deteriorate over time. Here&amp;rsquo;s a visual representation of the problem:
To begin the repair, the tonearm needs to be removed to access the damaged part. After removing the back screw, the tonearm can be gently pulled out:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the AC Motor and Replacement of the Reservoir and Motor Capacitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 01:28:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-ac-motor-and-replacement-of-the-reservoir-and-motor-capacitors/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s printed circuit boards, attention shifted to the capacitors associated with the reservoir and motor, as well as the AC motor itself. The capacitor and motor section appeared as shown before any servicing.
Visual inspection revealed leakage from the larger capacitors, indicating a critical need for replacement. The extent of the capacitor bay&amp;rsquo;s condition was evident upon their removal.
The AC motor was extracted for servicing, taking advantage of its disconnected state from the capacitors.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Exchange of Black Painted Plinth with a Teak Plinth from a Beogram 4002</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-exchange-of-black-painted-plinth-with-a-teak-plinth-from-a-beogram-4002/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on restoring a Beogram 4000 turntable, and it came with a perplexing modification: a black-painted plinth. While I appreciate the iconic design of the original, I found myself needing to replace the plinth entirely. The photos below illustrate the process:
Here’s the turntable with the black plinth, showing the cracked guidance washers, a common issue I’ve encountered:
I took the plinth off, which requires removing the keypad to access a hidden bolt:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Replacement of the Sensor Arm Bulb with a LED Assembly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:15:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-replacement-of-the-sensor-arm-bulb-with-a-led-assembly/</guid><description>Following the replacement of the damaged MMC cartridge mount in the Beogram 4000 restoration, the next step was to switch out the last incandescent bulb with an LED replacement. The image displays the bulb housing removed from the sensor arm.
The underside of the small PCB and its wiring are shown here:
Constructed on a flexible printed circuit board, the LED module is designed to mimic the energy consumption of the original light bulb, preventing any issues with the Beogram&amp;rsquo;s control system (which verifies if the bulb is working).</description></item></channel></rss>