<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Messaging on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/messaging/</link><description>Recent content in Messaging on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:12:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/messaging/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Are You A Sentio Being?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 03:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re someone who likes to stay ahead of the curve in technology without breaking the bank, now is the time to make a move. The LG Sentio, a free high-quality smartphone, is a prime example of getting significant value without spending a lot.
You might be wondering how a high-value phone can be free. It&amp;rsquo;s a combination of taking advantage of technological advancements at the right moment and knowing where to find the best deals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-you-a-sentio-being/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Send Fax From Email On Your Computer or Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 06:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</guid><description>Do you recall fax machines with thermal paper rolls? Those messages had a distinct look and tended to fade. To preserve them, you&amp;rsquo;d copy them onto regular paper using a laser printer, then diligently wash the strange residue off your hands.
Fax technology has significantly evolved. Thermal paper is out, and even traditional fax machines are becoming rare. Cloud-based electronic transmission and storage are the modern alternatives.
Sending and receiving faxes via email is the contemporary approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/send-fax-from-email-on-your-computer-or-smartphone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The new NYNJA app allows you to communicate, make purchases, and utilize cryptocurrency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 05:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</guid><description>Source: NYNJA Group. Screen captures of the NYNJA app, currently in beta.
NYNJA Group, a Hong Kong-based communications and mobile technology firm, has introduced NYNJA, a new communications app with a built-in digital marketplace and cryptocurrency wallet.
The NYNJA app works across multiple platforms and integrates voice, text, and visual messaging with business management and e-commerce tools. Its features are powered by its own financial ecosystem and cryptocurrency, NYNJACoin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-new-nynja-app-allows-you-to-communicate-make-purchases-and-utilize-cryptocurrency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry 8830 is World Class</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 14:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</guid><description>Verizon Wireless has engineered a BlackBerry that functions domestically and internationally. This is notable because Verizon uses the CDMA network in the US, while the rest of the world primarily uses GSM.
Previously, this difference prevented Verizon phones from roaming internationally. To solve this, Verizon created a device with both CDMA and GSM capabilities. In the US, the CDMA component accesses the 800 and 1900 MHz bands, including EV-DO broadband. Outside the US, the GSM component accesses the 900 and 1800 MHz bands, including GPRS broadband...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-8830-is-world-class/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LG enV Envy Touch Phone Messaging Machine</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 21:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</guid><description>Do you find yourself desiring a modern touchscreen phone but also require a physical QWERTY keyboard? The new LG enV Touch eliminates this dilemma by offering both!
When closed, the &amp;ldquo;enV Touch&amp;rdquo; resembles a typical touchscreen smartphone. The exterior features a 3-inch, 800x480 pixel color TFT touchscreen with tactile feedback and customizable shortcuts. However, a hidden surprise awaits inside: a second 3-inch, 800x400 pixel color display. This internal screen, paired with a spacious QWERTY keyboard, prioritizes efficient typing over touch input...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-env-envy-touch-phone-messaging-machine/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals are using the popularity of Netflix and WhatsApp to distribute malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:41:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</guid><description>Source: Check Point Research. The Google Play page for the FlixOnline app.
Hackers are spreading Android malware disguised as an app to unlock Netflix content. Check Point Research (CPR) discovered that this malware automatically responds to incoming WhatsApp messages with malicious links.
The malware was initially concealed within an app called FlixOnline on Google Play. While promising users access to global Netflix content on their phones, it actually tracked victims’ WhatsApp notifications and automatically replied to messages using externally provided content...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-are-using-the-popularity-of-netflix-and-whatsapp-to-distribute-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The LG Lotus is Square to Be Hip</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 20:19:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</guid><description>The LG Lotus LX600, a new and innovative phone in the mobile market, boasts a unique square design. Don&amp;rsquo;t let its shape fool you; this phone is powerful and designed for messaging.
The LG Lotus LX600 is slim, lightweight, and square. It flips open to reveal a full, backlit QWERTY keyboard. Despite this feature, it remains compact, even compared to typical messaging smartphones.
The LG Lotus has a lot to offer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lg-lotus-is-square-to-be-hip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cricket Offers Advantages For Urban Dwellers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 19:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</guid><description>Are you constantly on your cell phone, talking or texting? Do you live in or around a city and use the internet frequently outside your home or work? If so, Cricket Wireless has cellular service deals that might be perfect for you.
Cricket Wireless operates differently than traditional cell phone providers. First, there are no contracts. Second, most services are unlimited with one exception. Plans range from $30 to $60 per month, all offering unlimited service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cricket-offers-advantages-for-urban-dwellers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Going Incognito With SANYO and Sprint</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 00:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</guid><description>When you need a phone for discreet texting, the SANYO Incognito from Sprint is the perfect choice. Its sleek, minimalist design resembles a small, black monolith. Don&amp;rsquo;t be fooled by its understated appearance, though, as this phone is packed with features. The mirrored shell conceals a monochrome display and essential buttons for making calls.
Open the SANYO Incognito to reveal a full QWERTY keyboard with generously sized keys, perfect for rapid texting...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/going-incognito-with-sanyo-and-sprint/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE now offers conference call support for groups of up to 200 people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</guid><description>Source: LINE. Screenshots of the new voice call feature.
LINE has introduced a new feature for group calls in its latest update (iPhone and Android v.5.11, Windows Desktop v.4.5). This update allows up to 200 users to participate in a single voice call. The group voice call function will soon be available for LINE&amp;rsquo;s Mac desktop client, too.
When someone starts a group call, members in the group chat are notified and can choose to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-now-offers-conference-call-support-for-groups-of-up-to-200-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Smoothstone Offers Awareness In the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>The traditional office phone, once a large and stationary fixture on every desk, is becoming a relic of the past. Modern business communication has evolved into a dynamic and multifaceted process, incorporating instant messaging, online collaboration tools, file sharing, and web-based applications alongside traditional voice calls and conferencing. This evolution begs the question: are conventional PBX systems still equipped to handle the demands of today&amp;rsquo;s business environment?
As outdated phone systems increasingly hinder productivity, many companies are turning to cloud-based solutions for a more modern approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/smoothstone-offers-awareness-in-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Twitter Really 75 Years Old?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:58:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</guid><description>You might be amazed to discover that the core concept of Twitter predates you, your parents, and possibly even your grandparents.
While Twitter itself wasn&amp;rsquo;t around back then, a similar idea existed. In 1935, London had the &amp;ldquo;Notificator,&amp;rdquo; a robot messenger described by BoingBoing. This public vending machine allowed people to leave notes for friends. Users could write messages on a continuous paper strip, insert a coin, and their message would move up, making room for the next one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-twitter-really-75-years-old/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Email Hosting Without A Website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/email-hosting-without-a-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 23:13:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/email-hosting-without-a-website/</guid><description>A personalized email address, often essential for businesses and organizations, can be obtained without having a full website. While creating a website solely for a custom email is an option, email hosting without a website offers a more budget-friendly alternative.
Using a free webmail service like Hotmail or Gmail might appear unprofessional for businesses. While Gmail is perceived as more professional, it lacks the branding element a personalized email address offers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/email-hosting-without-a-website/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/email-hosting-without-a-website/</a></p></description></item><item><title>LINE has implemented encryption for its chat rooms</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</guid><description>Source: LINE. The new encryption
indicator is in the shape of a lock icon.
LINE users in Singapore can now experience increased privacy and security for a safer user experience.
The latest version of the LINE messaging app introduces a new lock icon indicator. This icon helps users identify chat rooms protected with end-to-end encryption. The icon, gradually being released globally, signifies that messages are only readable by the sender and recipient, remaining secure even as they pass through LINE&amp;rsquo;s servers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/line-has-implemented-encryption-for-its-chat-rooms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX Enables New Telephone Apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</guid><description>Just like apps revolutionized smartphones, they are now transforming desktop and laptop experiences, moving away from traditional software. And yes, this wave of innovation has reached phone systems too. AireSpring is leading the way with a suite of apps designed for their AirePBX cloud-hosted system.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the possibilities. CommPortal acts as your messaging hub, allowing you to manage voicemail, activate a one-number service for seamless device switching, prioritize callers, and utilize click-to-dial functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Put Some Sanity Back In Your Email</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/</guid><description>Are you happy with your email? Do you have a good relationship? All the time you spend together, you&amp;rsquo;d think you&amp;rsquo;d be perfect for each other. Or maybe not.
Email can feel like a burden we can&amp;rsquo;t escape. At first, it was amazing, maybe even love at first sight. But over time, it became overwhelming. Everything seemed important at the beginning, but now it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find what matters in the constant flood of messages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/put-some-sanity-back-in-your-email/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>