<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Family Reunion on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-reunion/</link><description>Recent content in Family Reunion on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/family-reunion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the free movement of people in the European Economic Area (EEA) distinct from that in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-free-movement-of-people-in-the-european-economic-area-eea-distinct-from-that-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Karin Fløistad: PhD Candidate, European University Institute; practicing lawyer at Norwegian law firm Simonsen Vogt Wiig
The UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit relationship with the EU often involves discussions about the free movement of people, with the EEA Agreement frequently cited as a potential model. This piece will analyze two key distinctions between the EEA Agreement&amp;rsquo;s approach to the free movement of people and that of full EU membership.
The EEA Agreement integrates the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market with three members of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA): Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein.</description></item><item><title>Can the Dublin III Regulation strengthen family reunification? The CJEU's ruling on the ability to appeal denials of take charge requests.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Leiden University
Photo credit: DFID
Unaccompanied minors can appeal a receiving EU member state&amp;rsquo;s denial of a request to assume responsibility for their asylum case. This conclusion from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) comes from its judgment in the I. &amp;amp; S. case. Interestingly, the District Court of Haarlem in the Netherlands initially posed the question because the Dublin III Regulation, which governs such transfers, doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly provide for this appeal right.</description></item><item><title>An important Irish ruling on compensation for violation of EU free movement law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:56:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-important-irish-ruling-on-compensation-for-violation-of-eu-free-movement-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Although the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) affirmed the right of individuals to sue Member States for damages resulting from breaches of EU law over two decades ago in the Francovich case, most subsequent lawsuits have been initiated by businesses seeking compensation for financial losses. The CJEU has yet to address a case involving damages claims related to the free movement of EU citizens.</description></item><item><title>Integration requirements for family reunification: the CJEU restricts the autonomy of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In recent times, many EU member states have started requiring non-EU citizens to pass an integration test before they can be reunited with their families in the EU. The EU&amp;rsquo;s family reunification rules allow for this, stating that family members joining non-EU citizens &amp;ldquo;may be required to comply with integration measures.&amp;rdquo; However, for family members of refugees and highly skilled migrants with EU Blue Cards, these tests can only be applied after they arrive.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families.</description></item><item><title>Review of EU Free Movement, Immigration, and Asylum Law in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 14:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/review-of-eu-free-movement-immigration-and-asylum-law-in-2014/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
The free movement of EU citizens and immigration and asylum from non-EU countries are central issues within EU law that have sparked considerable debate in recent years. This blog post examines the numerous legal developments in these areas over the past year. It first analyzes the disagreements surrounding the free movement rights of EU citizens and then explores the conflicting priorities in EU immigration and asylum law.</description></item><item><title>Feedback on the Commission's latest guidance for Family Reunions for Third-Country Nationals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:53:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/feedback-on-the-commission-s-latest-guidance-for-family-reunions-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Family life is essential for everyone living in the EU, regardless of their citizenship. For non-EU citizens (third-country nationals), family reunification is governed by the EU Directive on family reunion, adopted in 2003. Recently, the European Commission released new guidance on this Directive, offering potential for its better implementation and understanding. Although the guidance addresses several issues effectively, there are points that require further improvement or clarification.</description></item><item><title>Is Childhood Coming to an End? The Court of Justice Affirms the Right of Unaccompanied Child Refugees to Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-childhood-coming-to-an-end-the-court-of-justice-affirms-the-right-of-unaccompanied-child-refugees-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Reaching the age of 18 is a major milestone, signifying a transition to adulthood. While it may not bring immediate changes to family dynamics, it holds significant legal implications.
However, in immigration and asylum law, turning 18 can mean reduced legal rights, especially for vulnerable unaccompanied minors. Given lengthy legal processes, a key question arises: When an applicant starts as a minor but turns 18 before the process concludes, do they keep the protections afforded to children?</description></item><item><title>Gathering of EU citizens residing in their home country: Understanding the Surinder Singh and Carpenter rulings for family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:45:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gathering-of-eu-citizens-residing-in-their-home-country-understanding-the-surinder-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
This article examines when an EU citizen residing in their home country can assert rights under EU law for family members to join them. This analysis stems from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) addressing judgments in the Surinder Singh and Carpenter cases. These cases involve family reunification for EU citizens who return to their home country after residing in another Member State and for EU citizens who provide services in another Member State.</description></item><item><title>Latest CJEU judgment on family reunion, children's rights, and effective remedies.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/latest-cjeu-judgment-on-family-reunion-children-s-rights-and-effective-remedies/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
For parents, raising teenagers presents a constant awareness of time&amp;rsquo;s passage. But consider parents separated from their children by the unfeeling nature of immigration policies: missing milestones, first words, and school events. Even when these parents strive to fulfill family reunion requirements, their children may age out of eligibility during the lengthy application process, leaving a profound void.
Family reunification within the EU for non-EU families is primarily governed by the EU Family Reunion Directive, allowing for the admission of children who haven&amp;rsquo;t reached adulthood.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's stance on the minimum age requirement for spouses in a family reunification application</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:56:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-stance-on-the-minimum-age-requirement-for-spouses-in-a-family-reunification-application/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently ruled in the Noorzia case concerning the age requirement for family reunification. The case revolved around whether a national law, requiring both the sponsor and their spouse to be 21 years old when applying for family reunification, aligns with European Union (EU) law. The CJEU determined that the national law was indeed consistent with EU Directive 2003/86/EC.</description></item><item><title>New ruling from the ECtHR changes the landscape of ECHR and EU law regarding the expulsion of seriously ill migrants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-ruling-from-the-ecthr-changes-the-landscape-of-echr-and-eu-law-regarding-the-expulsion-of-seriously-ill-migrants/</guid><description>Dr Lourdes Peroni*, Postdoctoral Research Fellow, Ghent University Human Rights Centre (ECHR aspects) and Professor Steve Peers (EU law aspects)
The Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) significantly altered its stance on the expulsion of seriously ill migrants in the landmark 2016 Paposhvili v. Belgium judgment. This ruling clarifies when Article 3 of the ECHR, prohibiting torture or inhuman or degrading treatment, applies. The Court unanimously decided to move away from the strict interpretation of Article 3 established in N.</description></item><item><title>British lawyers have made a significant impact on EU (migration) law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 22:15:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/british-lawyers-have-made-a-significant-impact-on-eu-migration-law/</guid><description>Kees Groenendijk, Professor Emeritus, Radboud University Nijmegen, Netherlands.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) acknowledged the significant contributions of its British members to European integration and legal precedent. This recognition prompts reflection on the impact of British legal professionals on EU law, particularly in the areas of migration and free movement.
British judges and advocates-general, with their common law background, played a key role in shaping the CJEU into a more transparent and adaptable institution.</description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the CJEU's K. &amp; B. ruling on the effectiveness of refugees' right to family reunion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-cjeu-s-k-b-ruling-on-the-effectiveness-of-refugees-right-to-family-reunion/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Assistant professor at the Institute of Immigration Law at Leiden University
Introduction
In most EU Member States, family reunification for non-EU citizens residing within their borders and their non-EU family members living abroad is regulated by Directive 2003/86. The UK, Ireland, and Denmark opted out of this directive. This directive has a more lenient system for refugees seeking family reunification, which Member States can restrict to family connections formed before entering the Member State.</description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Responding to Giles Fraser on family values and Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:27:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responding-to-giles-fraser-on-family-values-and-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Giles Fraser&amp;rsquo;s article, which criticizes &amp;ldquo;Remainers&amp;rdquo; for not considering family issues, is flawed. In reality, many &amp;ldquo;Remainers,&amp;rdquo; including Professor Peers himself, have openly discussed the impact of Brexit on families.
Fraser&amp;rsquo;s central argument is that children should be responsible for the care of their aging parents. He criticizes social mobility, particularly the free movement within the EU, which he believes leads individuals away from their communities and families.</description></item><item><title>A Personal Perspective on Citizens' Rights Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-personal-perspective-on-citizens-rights-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
I seldom share personal experiences on this blog or elsewhere. However, I believe it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to approach immigration from a personal angle, not just as an abstract concept. While economic data is valuable for understanding the economic impact, and legal analysis is vital for activists and negotiators, it&amp;rsquo;s equally important to remember that migrants are individuals and families whose lives are impacted by immigration policy changes.</description></item><item><title>Are the new proposals for simplifying Schengen visa applications for third-country national family members of EU citizens comprehensive enough?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-the-new-proposals-for-simplifying-schengen-visa-applications-for-third-country-national-family-members-of-eu-citizens-comprehensive-enough/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU citizens with family members who are non-EU citizens often face obstacles to free movement, especially when those family members are from Asia, Africa, or the Caribbean. Traveling outside of the Schengen area with these family members often requires obtaining visas, adding complexity to their trips.
The European Commission&amp;rsquo;s recent proposals on visas, if adopted, could bring some relief. One proposal focuses on revising the existing &amp;ldquo;Schengen visa&amp;rdquo; rules, which permit travel across Schengen countries for three months.</description></item><item><title>The Handbook on Marriages of Convenience by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbook-on-marriages-of-convenience-by-the-commission/</guid><description>Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, School of Law, University of Reading
In September 2014, the Commission introduced a Handbook designed to guide Member States in addressing marriages of convenience between EU citizens and non-EU nationals. The goal is to combat these marriages without unduly restricting the free movement rights of EU citizens. The Commission emphasizes that the guidelines, developed in collaboration with Member States, are not legally binding and don&amp;rsquo;t supersede existing EU law or its future interpretations.</description></item><item><title>Just like the sun, hope shines bright: Court of Justice decision expands refugee minors' right to family reunification.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-like-the-sun-hope-shines-bright-court-of-justice-decision-expands-refugee-minors-right-to-family-reunification/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani (PhD) is a linguist agent working for the European Commission and a member of Amnesty International Belgique francophone’s Sexual Orientation and Gender Identity (OSIG) coordination group. The opinions and perspectives presented in this article are solely those of the author and do not necessarily represent the views, policies, or opinions of the European Commission or Amnesty International.
Photo credit: Enno Lenze, via Wikimedia Commons
As of this writing, the European Parliament recently voted to approve the EU’s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, despite concerns raised by over 50 civil society organizations.</description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives.</description></item><item><title>Gazing into the Void: The Future of Citizens' Rights in the Event of a No Deal Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gazing-into-the-void-the-future-of-citizens-rights-in-the-event-of-a-no-deal-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
After resisting guarantees for EU27 citizens&amp;rsquo; rights in the UK for over two years, the UK government has finally issued a plan outlining the treatment of EU27 citizens in the UK and UK citizens in the EU27 in a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit scenario. This comes as the UK Parliament prepares to vote on the withdrawal agreement and after the European Commission published its own position on this matter.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU changes the rules for family reunification for Turkish citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-changes-the-rules-for-family-reunification-for-turkish-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice&amp;rsquo;s recent decision in Dogan essentially creates a new framework for family reunification applicable to most Turkish citizens residing in the EU. These rules, however, will vary from one Member State to another.
The case revolved around Mrs. Dogan&amp;rsquo;s application to join her husband in Germany after a separation of thirteen (now sixteen) years. Her application was rejected due to inadequate German language proficiency. Despite passing the language test, her written German was deemed insufficient because of illiteracy.</description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends.</description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection).</description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union provides clarification on the Singh and Carpenter rulings for EU citizens' family reunions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 07:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-provides-clarification-on-the-singh-and-carpenter-rulings-for-eu-citizens-family-reunions/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Typically, EU law doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant residency rights to non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in their own home country. However, recent court rulings have clarified two key exceptions to this rule, albeit with unexpected outcomes. These rulings stem from Advocate-General Sharpston&amp;rsquo;s December 2013 opinion, as discussed in a prior blog entry.
The O and B case: Revisiting Singh
In 2007, O, a non-EU citizen, and their Dutch partner, sponsor O, moved to Spain.</description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach.</description></item><item><title>The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has upheld the temporary free movement rights of third-country family members of EU citizens.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-cjeu-has-upheld-the-temporary-free-movement-rights-of-third-country-family-members-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent ruling from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the McCarthy case addresses a crucial question about EU free movement law in the UK: can the UK restrict the ability of family members (who are third-country nationals) of UK (and other EU) citizens to visit the UK?
The case involved a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual British and Irish citizen).</description></item></channel></rss>