<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Global Crossing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/global-crossing/</link><description>Recent content in Global Crossing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:39:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/global-crossing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Vyvx and Genesis Offer Worldwide Video Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 00:39:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</guid><description>The Power of Fiber for Video Transport Those working in video production, distribution, news, or sports broadcasting need reliable video transport. While satellites have been the traditional choice, fiber optic networks offer compelling advantages, including vast bandwidth, minimal latency, and accessibility in popular locations. The Level 3 and Global Crossing merger brought together their video transport expertise, resulting in a comprehensive range of services.
Level 3&amp;rsquo;s Emmy Award-winning Vyvx service provides broadcast fiber services, managed video networks, teleport and satellite services, and venue-specific services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vyvx-and-genesis-offer-worldwide-video-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Coming Level 3 Global Crossing Juggernaut</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 19:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</guid><description>The future of business hinges on strong global connections, and the merger of Level 3 Communications and Global Crossing aims to deliver just that. By combining their infrastructure, they&amp;rsquo;re creating a network with a truly global reach.
This $2 billion acquisition will see their combined fiber optic network reach 70 countries across three continents. Level 3 brings a robust US network with long-haul and metropolitan fiber, plus transatlantic cables connecting major US and European cities with low latency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-coming-level-3-global-crossing-juggernaut/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EtherSphere Spans The World With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Global Crossing, through its EtherSphere solutions, provides standardized Carrier Ethernet services globally, offering a centralized network solution for multinational companies with dispersed operations.
EtherSphere offers various standardized Ethernet services defined by the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF). These services include Point-to-Point Ethernet Private Line (EPL) or E-Line, multipoint connections like Ethernet Virtual Private Line (EVPL), Point-to-Multipoint or E-Tree, and Multipoint-to-Multipoint Ethernet Private LAN or VPLS (Virtual Private LAN Service) E-LAN.
This range of Ethernet services caters to diverse connectivity needs for interconnecting multiple locations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethersphere-spans-the-world-with-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>