<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ca/</link><description>Recent content in CA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 08:25:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CA Technologies has implemented a new global parental leave policy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-has-implemented-a-new-global-parental-leave-policy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 08:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-has-implemented-a-new-global-parental-leave-policy/</guid><description>CA Technologies is implementing a new parental leave policy to support changing family dynamics and promote work-life balance and gender diversity. The company will now offer a minimum of 12 weeks paid leave during the first year after the birth or adoption of a child to all employees globally. This benefit provides financial support and flexibility for parents to care for their child during the first year.
Melinda Walsh, VP of People Business Partner for Asia Pacific and Japan at CA Technologies, stated this new policy demonstrates the company&amp;rsquo;s commitment to employee well-being and enhances their existing family-friendly benefits.</description></item><item><title>Generating passwords can be likened to navigating a minefield</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/generating-passwords-can-be-likened-to-navigating-a-minefield/</guid><description>A popular joke on Twitter highlights the struggle of creating secure passwords, mocking the complex requirements that often feel excessive. However, the humor underscores a serious issue: the necessity of strong passwords in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Simple passwords are widely considered inadequate in preventing unauthorized access, leading organizations to ban easily guessable combinations.
Despite this understanding, the recent Adobe security breach revealed that many users still rely on weak passwords. The most common passwords found in the leaked data were alarmingly basic, with &amp;ldquo;123456&amp;rdquo; topping the list.</description></item></channel></rss>