<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Employer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employer/</link><description>Recent content in Employer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/employer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aon Hewitt announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers award in Thailand for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-hewitt-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-award-in-thailand-for-2016/</guid><description>Leading employers in Thailand boast engagement scores that are 24 points higher than the average company. This trend is particularly noticeable among Gen Y employees (born between 1979 and 1990), who report engagement levels 22 points higher when working for a top employer. A striking 89% of employees at these leading companies would recommend their workplace to job seekers, significantly surpassing the 68% market average. Among the top performers, Advanced Info Services earned the distinguished title of &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Employers.</description></item><item><title>Aon announces the recipients of the Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017 award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aon-announces-the-recipients-of-the-aon-best-employers-singapore-2017-award/</guid><description>Employee engagement at companies recognized as Aon Best Employers rose by two percentage points this year, reaching 82%.
Aon Best Employers are setting the standard for positive employer branding, achieving scores from 83% to 92% in employee perception across all levels of tenure.
Five special recognitions were given this year, including the introduction of a new award category: Best Employer for Startups.
Source: Aon. Aon Best Employers Singapore 2017.</description></item><item><title>The UAE has a strong presence in LinkedIn's list of the top 100 most sought-after employers in EMEA for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 06:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uae-has-a-strong-presence-in-linkedin-s-list-of-the-top-100-most-sought-after-employers-in-emea-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: LinkedIn blog.
LinkedIn has released its list of the 100 Most In-Demand Employers in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa for 2015. These rankings, showcasing the most sought-after companies in the region, are based on a comprehensive analysis of billions of professional interactions with companies on the LinkedIn platform.
Nine companies from the UAE, the only Middle Eastern nation represented, secured a spot on the list. Emirates claimed sixth place, followed by Saudi Aramco (15th), Etihad (20th), Emaar (27th), and Etisalat (30th).</description></item><item><title>Avanade has been recognized as one of the top employers in Malaysia and Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 15:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avanade-has-been-recognized-as-one-of-the-top-employers-in-malaysia-and-singapore/</guid><description>Avanade, a company specializing in Microsoft solutions, has received the 2023 Top Employer award in Malaysia and Singapore from the Top Employers Institute.
Source: Avanade. Kapoor.
The Top Employers Institute Programme grants certifications to companies based on their answers and performance on a survey evaluating their Human Resources (HR) practices. Avanade earned recognition for its exceptional practices in all areas reviewed, including People Strategy, Work Environment, Talent Acquisition, Learning, Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion, Wellbeing, and others.</description></item><item><title>Just the Tech Jobs, Please</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:47:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-the-tech-jobs-please/</guid><description>Feeling anxious about your job security in this uncertain economy? Or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re an employer searching for the perfect candidate for a specific tech role. In either scenario, you need a platform that cuts through the noise of generic job boards. JustTechJobs is your solution - a specialized job portal dedicated exclusively to tech positions.
Upon visiting JustTechJobs, you&amp;rsquo;ll instantly notice a list of freshly posted tech jobs. The site showcases a diverse range of positions from across the United States, updated daily.</description></item><item><title>The Singapore Computer Society reveals the top 10 tech companies to work for in 2017</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-singapore-computer-society-reveals-the-top-10-tech-companies-to-work-for-in-2017/</guid><description>The Singapore Computer Society (SCS), the largest professional organization for infocomm and digital media professionals in the country, has revealed the winners of its &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Company to Work For Award&amp;rdquo;. The announcement took place at the SCS&amp;rsquo;s annual Tech3 Forum conference.
This award recognizes four organizations out of the ten &amp;ldquo;Best Tech Companies to Work For&amp;rdquo; as overall winners. These companies have developed innovative practices and demonstrated workplace excellence within the infocomm and digital media (ICM) industry.</description></item><item><title>Many of the top employers on Glassdoor's list for 2014 have offices in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 05:06:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/many-of-the-top-employers-on-glassdoor-s-list-for-2014-have-offices-in-asia/</guid><description>Glassdoor, an online platform where individuals share salary data and company insights, has unveiled its sixth annual Employees’ Choice Awards. This year, the awards highlight both the 50 Best Places to Work and, for the first time, the 50 Best Medium-Sized Companies to Work For.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that Glassdoor&amp;rsquo;s user base is predominantly located in the United States. Consequently, the feedback might not accurately reflect workplace sentiments in all regions, particularly as some recognized companies may not have a presence in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Asian companies place a high value on feedback received during exit interviews</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</guid><description>A recent report from Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, reveals that most companies believe in the value of honest feedback during exit interviews, whether formal or informal. In fact, seven out of ten Asian companies conduct these interviews.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Acquiring Insights From The Exit Process To Build A Better Workplace,&amp;rdquo; the report highlights how improvements made based on exit interview feedback can help organizations attract and retain top-tier talent.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item><item><title>Accenture says that CEOs must lead the effort to reskill their employees</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accenture-says-that-ceos-must-lead-the-effort-to-reskill-their-employees/</guid><description>Source: Accenture website. The image illustrates the essential skills needed for the workforce of the future, highlighting technical proficiency, adaptability, and problem-solving abilities.
A recent report by Accenture Strategy emphasizes that in the rapidly evolving digital world, CEOs need to prioritize reskilling their employees to ensure they remain competitive and adaptable.
The report, titled &amp;ldquo;Harnessing Revolution: Creating the Future Workforce,&amp;rdquo; argues that CEOs should prioritize their employees and place them at the center of transformation to build a successful workforce for the future.</description></item></channel></rss>