<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pin/</link><description>Recent content in Pin on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bank Muscat is launching chip and PIN debit cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</guid><description>Bank Muscat, Oman&amp;rsquo;s leading financial services provider, has issued 500,000 chip and PIN debit cards equipped with enhanced security features for daily transactions and cash withdrawals. These new cards simplify daily purchases and grant access to Bank Muscat&amp;rsquo;s extensive network of 153 branches, ATMs, and CDMs throughout Oman.
The chip-based cards offer increased transaction security by mandating PIN authentication at point-of-sale terminals. New customers will automatically receive the Chip &amp;amp; PIN card, while existing Bank Muscat debit cardholders will transition to the new card upon renewal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bank-muscat-is-launching-chip-and-pin-debit-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Polishing the Hood and a Strange Hinge Pin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 12:08:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m completing the restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable by addressing the final detail: polishing the dust cover. This one, like many I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered, had scratches from improper storage.
This particular unit had a non-original hinge pin, longer than the original, causing it to protrude. I shortened it, restoring a flush fit. The aluminum trim on the other side had also detached, which I reattached using double-sided tape for easy future removal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-polishing-the-hood-and-a-strange-hinge-pin/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>