<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Phones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phones/</link><description>Recent content in Business Phones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-phones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted PBX Adds Video Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:34:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems, also known as Hosted VoIP or Hosted PBX, are gaining popularity with businesses of all sizes. This technology offers advanced features without requiring a large upfront investment. Now, these systems are evolving to incorporate video services as well.
MegaPath, a leading network and cloud service provider, is enhancing its hosted PBX offerings by including cloud-based unified communications video services.
A new generation of business phones makes voice and video integration possible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-pbx-adds-video-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Attention: Telephone System Dealers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 17:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</guid><description>For businesses selling, installing, or servicing business telephone systems, a new business model called the VAR Network is gaining popularity nationwide. This model helps generate more business without requiring upfront expenses.
The VAR Network is an online database system showcasing business profiles of numerous telephone and computer networking dealers. This fully automated platform connects potential customers seeking telecom assistance with qualified dealers in their area. Dealers are notified of potential matches and can choose to pursue these opportunities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/attention-telephone-system-dealers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise Communications Services To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 08:48:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>A significant shift from traditional phone systems to cloud-based communication is happening right now. XO Communications, a leader in this field, predicts 60% of companies will move almost a third of their voice communications to the cloud in the coming years.
For a free consultation and quotes tailored to your company&amp;rsquo;s communication needs, our partners at Telarus offer fast and reliable service from expert product specialists. Contact them at http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-communications-services-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E911 For Enterprise VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 00:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</guid><description>The transition from traditional phone lines to internet-based calling has brought about some unexpected issues, particularly with emergency services. We often take 911 for granted, assuming help will always be on the way. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case with internet-based phone systems.
Imagine a scenario where a fire breaks out in your office. You dial 911, report the emergency, and evacuate. However, the fire department ends up at your company&amp;rsquo;s headquarters instead of your current location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e911-for-enterprise-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VXSuite Takes the Scary Out of VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You understand that Unified Communications, powered by VoIP telephony, is the future of business communication. You also recognize its potential to boost productivity. However, the fear of completely overhauling your existing system is holding you back. While your current phones, connected through old wiring, might seem adequate for making and receiving calls, they limit your communication capabilities. To unlock more advanced features, transitioning to an all-IP network is essential...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vxsuite-takes-the-scary-out-of-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unified Communications for the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Large companies have embraced unified communications (UC) to enhance their business phone systems and employee productivity. While initially adopted by enterprises, UC is gaining traction among small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) due to its similar advantages.
Unified communications centralizes electronic business communications, which have expanded beyond traditional desk phones. While desk phones remain important, we now utilize cell phones, smartphones, tablets, laptops, and desktop PCs. UC integrates these devices into a cohesive system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unified-communications-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Telecommunications from Packet8</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</guid><description>If your company is outgrowing its current phone system but a full-blown PBX system seems like overkill, there&amp;rsquo;s a middle ground: hosted telecommunications.
Instead of housing your own PBX equipment, hosted solutions put that functionality in the cloud, similar to website hosting. You get all the features of an in-house system without the bulky hardware. Your office phones connect to the provider&amp;rsquo;s equipment through your broadband connection.
Packet8 is a leading provider of hosted telecom for small to medium businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-telecommunications-from-packet8/</a></p></description></item><item><title>PRI vs POTS Telephone Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 11:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</guid><description>Business telephone systems come in various sizes, from single-line setups to large enterprise systems with thousands of phones. This article aims to help you determine the right system size for your business needs.
The most basic phone service is known as POTS, or Plain Old Telephone Service, although it&amp;rsquo;s often marketed as a business line or dial-tone service. This service provides an analog connection to the nearest telephone company&amp;rsquo;s Central Office (CO)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-vs-pots-telephone-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX Enables New Telephone Apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</guid><description>Just like apps revolutionized smartphones, they are now transforming desktop and laptop experiences, moving away from traditional software. And yes, this wave of innovation has reached phone systems too. AireSpring is leading the way with a suite of apps designed for their AirePBX cloud-hosted system.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the possibilities. CommPortal acts as your messaging hub, allowing you to manage voicemail, activate a one-number service for seamless device switching, prioritize callers, and utilize click-to-dial functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where to Get a 1-800 Number Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 20:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</guid><description>Want a 1-800 number without the high price tag? You can get one for just $5! Maintaining the number costs a mere $5 monthly, with incoming calls at 6.9 cents per minute—a small price for most businesses, and one with significant potential benefits.
Why? Because anyone dialing your 1-800 number found it through an advertisement, business card, flyer, newspaper, television, billboard, or radio. They have a reason for calling, usually translating to a motivated customer...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-to-get-a-1-800-number-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Many POTS Lines in a Trunk?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 22:59:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</guid><description>When a business is just starting, it might rely on a single phone line – a traditional desk phone or perhaps a cordless model with a speakerphone. This basic setup, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), uses the PSTN (Public Switched Telephone Network). POTS relies on physical copper wires connecting your phone directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office. These lines, often called &amp;ldquo;landlines,&amp;rdquo; use analog signals based on long-established standards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-pots-lines-in-a-trunk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Call Centers Move To the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud-based phone systems are gaining popularity as a replacement for traditional phone systems. Businesses are recognizing the benefits of moving their phone systems to the cloud. So why aren&amp;rsquo;t call centers embracing this technology?
Actually, some call centers are already using cloud-based systems. Smaller and geographically dispersed call centers are more likely to transition from physical to cloud-based phone systems. Larger call centers face more challenges in adopting this technology because their needs extend beyond basic phone functionality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-centers-move-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fonality Call Center in a Box</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</guid><description>Thinking about starting a call center but worried about the initial expenses and complex setup? While a large-scale call center requires significant investment, there are solutions for businesses looking to add call center capabilities or start small and gradually expand. Fonality offers a &amp;ldquo;call center in a box&amp;rdquo; solution, providing a simplified yet robust system.
This solution utilizes an off-the-shelf PC tower functioning as a Linux server, with the option to upgrade to a rack-mount server for increased capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fractional ISDN PRI For Telephone Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 19:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</guid><description>ISDN PRI is a great option for businesses that need a robust phone system. It provides 23 digital lines with features like fast call switching and Caller ID on a single, cost-effective line. However, not all businesses need that many lines.
Smaller businesses or those with lower call volumes can opt for Fractional ISDN PRI, which offers the same features but with fewer lines. This option allows businesses to customize the number of lines they need, typically around 12, leading to significant cost savings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-isdn-pri-for-telephone-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is HPBX Your Next PBX?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 12:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</guid><description>Businesses across the country are ditching their in-house phone systems and returning to outside phone service providers, mirroring a past era. However, modern telephony has evolved significantly. While maintaining in-house phone systems seemed cost-effective initially, companies are realizing that it comes with unexpected expenses and complexities.
Larger businesses often require numerous phone lines, leading to challenges in internal communication. Having individual lines for each phone necessitates long-distance charges for calls outside the company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-hpbx-your-next-pbx/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>