<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Child Benefit on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/child-benefit/</link><description>Recent content in Child Benefit on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/child-benefit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The immigration issues in the UK renegotiation deal have been finalized.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 20:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-immigration-issues-in-the-uk-renegotiation-deal-have-been-finalized/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
David Cameron has successfully negotiated a deal regarding the UK&amp;rsquo;s membership in the EU. This post, the first in a series about the deal, focuses on &amp;ldquo;EU immigration&amp;rdquo; or, in terms of EU law, the free movement of EU citizens. I will delve into other important matters (competitiveness, Eurozone relations, sovereignty) and the legal structure of the deal later.
The deal comprises seven legal documents: a Decision by the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government (the &amp;ldquo;Decision&amp;rdquo;); a Statement from the Heads of State and Government (an agreed Council Decision); a Declaration by the European Council (representing the EU Member States&amp;rsquo; Heads of State and Government); and four declarations by the Commission.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item><item><title>Disregard the children! CJEU supports automatic exclusions from family benefits in Case C-308/14 Commission v UK</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disregard-the-children-cjeu-supports-automatic-exclusions-from-family-benefits-in-case-c-308-14-commission-v-uk/</guid><description>Charlotte O&amp;rsquo;Brien, Senior Lecturer, York Law School The Court of Justice is increasingly distancing itself from the social welfare systems of Member States. Although the Court once suggested that citizenship is paramount and forms the basis for financial solidarity, guaranteeing some support from a host state for EU citizens facing temporary hardship, this stance is changing.
With the Court moving away from the concept of citizenship, the idea of a reasonable burden may be disappearing.</description></item></channel></rss>