<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Perfume on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/perfume/</link><description>Recent content in Perfume on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:35:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/perfume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The next big trend could be fragrances that help with weight loss</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-big-trend-could-be-fragrances-that-help-with-weight-loss/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-next-big-trend-could-be-fragrances-that-help-with-weight-loss/</guid><description>When the perfume Prends-Moi was introduced in the UK in 2012, there was a waiting list of 6,000 people. Its marketing as a &amp;ldquo;slimming fragrance&amp;rdquo; is unusual, attributing this property to &amp;ldquo;betaphroline,&amp;rdquo; a plant-derived ingredient. Veld&amp;rsquo;s, the maker of Prends-Moi, suggests that a simple sniff can help curb snacking.
Research firm TechNavio, in a report on the French fragrance market, highlighted the potential of slimming fragrances to boost demand.
Faisal Ghaus, Vice President of TechNavio, stated that a fragrance company had introduced a slimming fragrance in France designed for weight loss.</description></item><item><title>Experience the delightful combination of fragrance and culinary delights at Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:02:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-delightful-combination-of-fragrance-and-culinary-delights-at-caf-wolseley-bangkok-and-jo-malone-london/</guid><description>Café Wolseley Bangkok and Jo Malone London have partnered to create a luxurious British experience, blending Café Wolseley’s culinary talents with Jo Malone London’s signature scents.
Source: Café Wolseley Bangkok. Café Wolseley Bangkok&amp;rsquo;s Through the Grapevine menu is inspired by the aromatic notes of Jo Malone&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense.
This collaboration celebrates the launch of Jo Malone London&amp;rsquo;s Cypress &amp;amp; Grapevine Cologne Intense. Available from July 1st to August 31st, guests can experience the Through the Grapevine lunch menu at Café Wolseley Bangkok.</description></item><item><title>Immerse yourself in the holiday spirit with the Holiday fragrance by House of Sillage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 14:39:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/immerse-yourself-in-the-holiday-spirit-with-the-holiday-fragrance-by-house-of-sillage/</guid><description>Source: House of Sillage.
House of Sillage, a high-end perfume maker, introduces its Holiday fragrance for the Christmas season. The perfume features a blend of mandarin, peach, and vetiver, creating a festive aroma.
The design of the fragrance bottle draws inspiration from the illuminated Rockefeller Center Christmas tree in New York City. Its snow globe cap, crafted from 18-karat gold and white gold, depicts a scene of falling snow. The floral and citrus perfume is housed in a hand-polished glass bottle with an ombre lacquer finish.</description></item><item><title>Fragrance Du Bois opens a temporary store at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 16:16:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fragrance-du-bois-opens-a-temporary-store-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Fragrance Du Bois.
Fragrance Du Bois has opened a temporary boutique at TANGS, a major department store in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Orchard Road shopping area, until September 4, 2015. This marks their second appearance at TANGS this year. The pop-up offers customers a direct encounter with niche perfumery and showcases Fragrance Du Bois&amp;rsquo; fragrances, all made with 100% pure, natural oud.
Nicola Parker, Brand Director of Fragrance Du Bois, noted a rising interest in niche perfumery.</description></item><item><title>GUESS honors the GUESS woman with GUESS Double Dare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guess-honors-the-guess-woman-with-guess-double-dare/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guess-honors-the-guess-woman-with-guess-double-dare/</guid><description>Source: GUESS.
GUESS presents GUESS Double Dare, a new fragrance with floral, woody, and amber notes that embody the lively spirit of the GUESS woman.
Givaudan perfumer Marypierre Julien drew inspiration from Marilyn Monroe when creating this perfume. Julien remarked that Monroe&amp;rsquo;s captivating beauty, style, playful spirit, and boldness, particularly her meticulous attention to detail in crafting her image, inspired her to capture these qualities in the fragrance.
Source: GUESS.</description></item><item><title>Adidas Originals celebrates originality with the Born Original fragrance pair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 20:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adidas-originals-celebrates-originality-with-the-born-original-fragrance-pair/</guid><description>Source: adidas Originals.
Adidas Originals, the renowned streetwear brand, introduces a new fragrance pair: Born Original. These dynamic scents, one for men and one for women, embody the spirit of embracing individuality and authenticity.
Born Original reflects the energetic and empowering essence of the adidas Originals brand, grounded in individuality, authenticity, and imagination. The Born Original fragrances, For Him and For Her, present a vibrant blend of contrasting notes.</description></item></channel></rss>