<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Telephones on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephones/</link><description>Recent content in Business Telephones on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-telephones/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted VoIP Solutions Include New Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</guid><description>Cloud services are changing how we think about technology. Just like server racks are moving to the cloud, so are office phone systems. Traditional PBX systems are being replaced by cloud-hosted solutions. But this transition begs the question: what happens to the physical phone lines?
Similar to connecting data servers off-site, a connection called a SIP Trunk links your on-premise network to the hosted PBX. While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to use existing analog phones with adapters, this approach misses out on the advanced features of Voice over IP (VoIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TelePacific’s SmartVoice Trunking Offers Telephone Smarts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</guid><description>TelePacific Communications offers a unique and intelligent solution called SmartVoice for small and medium-sized businesses seeking telephone and internet services. This SIP trunking solution provides both voice and data over a single line. Unlike traditional Integrated T1 lines, SmartVoice stands out by supporting various business telephone systems and offering significantly greater traffic capacity.
SIP trunking uses an IP-based transmission line specifically designed for enterprise VoIP telephone systems. SIP, or Session Initiation Protocol, is the signaling technology employed by numerous IP phone systems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telepacific-s-smartvoice-trunking-offers-telephone-smarts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Toll Free Number Availability Now</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toll-free-number-availability-now/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 04:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toll-free-number-availability-now/</guid><description>Considering a toll-free number for your business but worried about the hassle of finding an available one, dealing with paperwork, and waiting for service? There&amp;rsquo;s a much easier way.
You can get a toll-free number set up immediately. Simply choose the number you want from a list and activate your service online in minutes at Kall8’s Instant Online Activation site. This fully automated self-service process is available 24/7, so you can start using your new toll-free number right away...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toll-free-number-availability-now/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/toll-free-number-availability-now/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-1 Digital Phone Lines For PBX Systems</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 16:34:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</guid><description>Many modern business phone systems utilize T-1 lines to link their buildings to the local telephone company. This is because merging multiple individual lines into one or two T-1 lines is more cost-efficient. This holds true whether your internal phone system is analog or digital, as even most VoIP systems rely on T-1 lines for external calls.
Smaller setups like basic one or two-line phones or key systems with 4-6 lines typically use analog lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-digital-phone-lines-for-pbx-systems/</a></p></description></item><item><title>End of the Premises Contact Center</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 20:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business telephone systems have evolved significantly. We&amp;rsquo;ve transitioned from single-line phones to switchboards, automated systems, and sophisticated call center PBXs. However, one thing remained constant: these systems were all located on-site.
What’s Wrong With Premises Equipment?
Keeping everything in-house seems appealing because it gives you control over functionality, access, and services. You might even believe that in-house systems are more reliable than off-site solutions.
On-premises systems offer visibility and control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/end-of-the-premises-contact-center/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does a VoIP Call Work?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</guid><description>VoIP is often called a network service, not a phone service, which matters for technical folks and business owners, but less so for everyday users. After all, a phone is a phone; you expect it to work the same way.
The aim with VoIP has been to closely replicate the experience of traditional landlines. Now that this is largely accomplished, the focus is shifting towards making VoIP calls sound even better than traditional calls, aiming for what&amp;rsquo;s called HD or high-definition voice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business VoIP Solution Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about switching your business phone system from the traditional analog or PBX setup to VoIP (Voice over Internet Protocol), it&amp;rsquo;s wise to explore the various business VoIP options available before making a complete overhaul. The best choice for you depends on your specific needs and, by selecting wisely, you can maximize your telephony investment.
The main reasons to consider VoIP are cost savings, enhanced calling features, or a combination of both...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-voip-solution-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A Visual Guide To Enterprise VoIP Justification</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</guid><description>Thank you to MegaPath Broadband Service Providers for this interesting infographic.
Is your company missing out on the advantages of enterprise VoIP technology, which can potentially reduce costs and increase productivity? A variety of on-site and hosted options are available to accommodate businesses of all sizes. Explore business VoIP solutions and pricing from MegaPath and other providers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-visual-guide-to-enterprise-voip-justification/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>