<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Center Consolidation on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-center-consolidation/</link><description>Recent content in Data Center Consolidation on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-center-consolidation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bandwidth For Data Center Consolidation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</guid><description>Businesses are constantly looking for ways to cut costs without sacrificing quality, and increasing efficiency is a great way to do that. While you might believe you&amp;rsquo;ve maximized your data center efficiency, there might be untapped potential.
Many organizations evolve organically, starting small and expanding over time through growth, acquisitions, and mergers. This often leads to a patchwork system of data centers, each designed for specific needs. However, as circumstances change, inefficiencies creep in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-for-data-center-consolidation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Multiple Data Center Dilemma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</guid><description>The increasing number of mergers and acquisitions has left many companies with a surplus of data centers. Instead of choosing one data center to become the central hub, companies should consider the unique characteristics of each facility, such as equipment, applications, and staffing. Furthermore, consolidating data centers necessitates a reassessment of connectivity.
While internal network traffic often surpasses external traffic, the rising reliance on cloud services demands greater Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>