<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tapetransport on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tapetransport/</link><description>Recent content in Tapetransport on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:26:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tapetransport/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beocord 9000: Finishing Up The Tape Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/</guid><description>The Beocord 9000 tape transport is now fixed and reassembled. Cleaning and lubrication were done on all moving parts, including the thrust roller assembly, even though it wasn&amp;rsquo;t being replaced.
The reassembly process involved reinstalling several components, starting with the take-up and supply reel assembly.
Next, the clutch, interconnecting mechanics, flywheel, belts, cassette holder, and opening damper assembly were put back in place.
To test the restored transport before installing it in the Beocord 9000, it was temporarily swapped into a different Beocord 9000...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-finishing-up-the-tape-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Opening It Up</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/</guid><description>Bang &amp;amp; Olufsen audio devices from the early 1980s are great to repair because their components are easily accessible for service and inspection.
One of the first things to examine on Beocord 8000 through 9000 series cassette decks is the tape transport mechanism. While replacing the belts is part of regular maintenance, there are other mechanical aspects to address.
Upon opening this Beocord 9000, I immediately noticed a small broken part...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-opening-it-up/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: The Tape Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/</guid><description>After cleaning the belt residue, the tape transport needs to be removed for disassembly. Three screws and four connectors need to be detached to free the tape transport. The image shows the Beocord tape transport ready for restoration.
The next stage involves taking the tape transport apart to clean, lubricate, and repair it, including replacing any worn rubber wheels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-the-tape-transport/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beocord 9000: Identifying Repairs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:05:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/</guid><description>Taking apart the tape transport allows for thorough cleaning and reveals hidden areas that require attention. While this approach makes sense for restoration, disassembling most of the transport is necessary anyway for replacing the rubber wheels.
NOTE: It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to avoid disturbing the tape head assembly. It&amp;rsquo;s likely still properly aligned, or very close to it. Unless you&amp;rsquo;re certain they&amp;rsquo;re faulty, there&amp;rsquo;s no need to remove the tape heads at this stage...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beocord-9000-identifying-repairs/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>