<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Asia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia/</link><description>Recent content in Asia on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Apple has revealed that the Apple Watch will be available in additional countries starting on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 19:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Source: Apple.
Apple has announced the availability of the Apple Watch in more countries, including Singapore, South Korea, and Taiwan, starting June 26th. The smartwatch will be sold through Apple&amp;rsquo;s website, physical stores, and authorized retailers.
Select retailers such as BOONTHESHOP Cheongdam in Seoul and Malmaison by The Hour Glass in Singapore will offer a curated collection of Apple Watch models at launch. In the Asia Pacific region, the Apple Watch is already for sale in Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, and Japan...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/apple-has-revealed-that-the-apple-watch-will-be-available-in-additional-countries-starting-on-june-26th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing the most rapid growth for SWIFT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</guid><description>SWIFT, a financial messaging service, has announced a significant increase in new corporate clients from the Asia Pacific region between May and December 2015, with 29 new companies joining the network.
SWIFT provides a unified platform for corporations to communicate financial information with their banks globally, leading to enhanced visibility and more efficient treasury operations. This connection allows for greater automation and standardization of financial processes. Currently, over 1,500 corporate groups, representing roughly 30,000 entities, utilize SWIFT to manage their banking relationships worldwide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The US has published the 2016 Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 18:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</guid><description>The Office of the United States Trade Representative (USTR) has released its annual Special 301 Out-of-Cycle Review of Notorious Markets report. The 2016 review calls attention to online and physical marketplaces around the world that reportedly engage in or facilitate significant copyright infringement and trademark counterfeiting.
USTR Michael Froman emphasized the problem of piracy and counterfeiting in online markets, saying that governments need to address these issues throughout the supply chain to protect consumers from unsafe products...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-has-published-the-2016-special-301-out-of-cycle-review-of-notorious-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Be cautious of insiders when it comes to protecting data privacy: Infowatch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</guid><description>The most significant danger to data privacy in Southeast Asia comes from internal actors. Cybersecurity firm InfoWatch Group&amp;rsquo;s recent study reveals that careless top executives and employees with access to sensitive data are the primary cause of data leaks in ASEAN nations.
The company states that executives, employees, IT administrators, and other authorized personnel caused slightly more than 56% of compromised data incidents in Southeast Asia. External attacks and former employees were responsible for the remaining 44%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/be-cautious-of-insiders-when-it-comes-to-protecting-data-privacy-infowatch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BenQ introduces new digital signage, projectors, and interactive flat panels, creating a buzz</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 12:14:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</guid><description>BenQ, a leading provider of visual display technology, has introduced a range of new projectors, digital signage, and interactive flat panels, all emphasizing high quality and innovative design. The company highlighted its commitment to delivering excellent visual experiences across various sectors, including business, retail, and food &amp;amp; beverage.
Business The MX666+ projector.
The MX666+ is the first wireless business projector to feature Near Field Communication (NFC) technology and USB connectivity, making it ideal for bring-your-own-device environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-introduces-new-digital-signage-projectors-and-interactive-flat-panels-creating-a-buzz/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel has declared the champions of Season 1 for the PVP Esports Corporate Championship</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 01:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</guid><description>Teams from Singapore and Indonesia emerged victorious in the corporate category of Singtel&amp;rsquo;s 2020 PVP Esports Community Championships (Season 1).
Deloitte&amp;rsquo;s team, DeloitteOne, and DBS&amp;rsquo;s team, TurretHeist, secured the top spots in the Dota 2 and Mobile Legends: Bang Bang Corporate Championships, respectively. The Indonesian team, HZL Legion (RM Djamiah Putra), claimed victory in PlayerUnknown&amp;rsquo;s Battlegrounds (PUBG): Mobile.
Each winning team received over S$5,000 in cash and prizes. The grand finals, held online from September 5th to 6th due to the COVID-19 pandemic, saw teams competing remotely...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-has-declared-the-champions-of-season-1-for-the-pvp-esports-corporate-championship/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to create a successful email campaign</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</guid><description>To ensure your marketing emails are read, prioritize the customer&amp;rsquo;s experience, advises GetResponse, a company specializing in online marketing tools.
GetResponse CEO Simon Grabowski highlights three key elements for a successful email marketing strategy:
Understanding Subscriber Behavior
Analyze past email opens and clicks to gain insights into your subscribers&amp;rsquo; interests, email habits, and peak engagement times.
Optimizing for Device Preferences
With over 40% of emails being deleted due to poor mobile optimization, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to tailor content for different devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-create-a-successful-email-campaign/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Globetrekker Challenge creates a wellness portal for Garmin in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Globetrekker Challenge, a Singapore-based corporate wellness software company, will provide their corporate wellness platform to Garmin for distribution across Asia and the Pacific. This collaboration leverages each company&amp;rsquo;s strengths, allowing them to focus on their core offerings.
Globetrekker&amp;rsquo;s platform offers customizable wellness programs, real-time analytics reporting, and health risk profiling for employers. Through this partnership, Garmin&amp;rsquo;s clients can access these features and integrate them with Garmin&amp;rsquo;s wearable devices, creating a comprehensive employee health improvement solution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/globetrekker-challenge-creates-a-wellness-portal-for-garmin-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Working in Southeast Asia can lead to compromising ethics and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/working-in-southeast-asia-can-lead-to-compromising-ethics-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 20:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/working-in-southeast-asia-can-lead-to-compromising-ethics-and-values/</guid><description>A recent study by Milieu Insight explored the connection between employee resignations and the alignment of personal and corporate values. The study aimed to understand how employees perceive workplace values, their feelings towards them, and if they&amp;rsquo;ve experienced any conflicts.
The study revealed that 88% of Singaporean respondents have positive relationships with most or all colleagues. A similar sentiment was echoed across Southeast Asia, with over 90% of respondents observing a supportive culture among colleagues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/working-in-southeast-asia-can-lead-to-compromising-ethics-and-values/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/working-in-southeast-asia-can-lead-to-compromising-ethics-and-values/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Unique guest experiences offered by the Peninsula Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</guid><description>The Peninsula Hotels recently announced their Peninsula Academy Summer programs for this year. The luxury hotel group offers exclusive experiences focused on food, fashion, and art, perfect for corporate events or special clients.
Source: Peninsula Hotels.
Each program includes unique touches like bespoke Peninsula transportation, ranging from private helicopters and chauffeured Rolls-Royces to MINI Cooper S Clubman vehicles.
Here are some highlights from their Asian properties:
The Peninsula Hong Kong presents &amp;ldquo;Caviar Connoisseurship,&amp;rdquo; providing an in-depth look into the world of sustainably-farmed caviars, exploring their distinct qualities and ideal enjoyment methods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Limited edition spring drinks are being introduced at Starbucks stores in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 22:36:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/</guid><description>Starbucks is celebrating spring in Asia with a variety of limited-edition drinks, ranging from refreshing iced options to comforting hot beverages.
Source: Starbucks. Coconut Water Espresso Shakerato.
The Coconut Water Espresso Shakerato blends Starbucks&amp;rsquo; espresso with ice, poured over chilled coconut water sweetened with coconut syrup. It&amp;rsquo;s finished with espresso foam and a lime slice. This beverage is available iced only.
Source: Starbucks. New Valencia Orange Cocoa Cappuccino.
The New Valencia Orange Cocoa Cappuccino starts with a Valencia orange mocha sauce, layered with steamed milk and espresso shots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-spring-drinks-are-being-introduced-at-starbucks-stores-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore's food and beverage industry delves into creating value at a profound level</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</guid><description>Lee&amp;rsquo;s presentation shared industry forecasts on the Asian food industry opportunity.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) sector is transitioning its focus from productivity to value creation. Led by the Singapore Manufacturing Federation (SMF) and International Enterprise Singapore (IE Singapore), the industry is undergoing a transformation as manufacturers prioritize innovation, expansion, and globalization.
Lee says Singapore F&amp;amp;B manufacturers have much to offer
the world.
From April 12th to 15th, FoodAsia2016 will feature a variety of local companies with novel creations as part of the Singapore Pavilion spearheaded by SMF...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-s-food-and-beverage-industry-delves-into-creating-value-at-a-profound-level/</a></p></description></item><item><title>COPC releases contact center training schedule for the second half of 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</guid><description>COPC, a consulting firm specializing in customer experience enhancement, has announced its training schedule for the latter half of 2015. The firm offers in-person classes focusing on operational areas within customer contact.
Kathleen Jezierski, COO of COPC, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s approach: &amp;ldquo;Customers interact with companies through many touch points such as phone, email, social media, mobile and the web. We take our call center expertise and apply our proven best practices to manage these newer channels to deliver a unified experience...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copc-releases-contact-center-training-schedule-for-the-second-half-of-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Singapore and Korea have emerged as the top universities in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 07:44:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</guid><description>The National University of Singapore (NUS) has achieved the top ranking in Asia for the first time, according to the QS University Rankings: Asia 2014 published on www.topuniversities.com. These rankings indicate a shift in influence within the region as Singapore and Korea surpass Japan and Hong Kong.
Source: QS website.
NUS&amp;rsquo; accomplishment is paralleled by Nanyang Technological University (NTU), securing 7th place, its highest position yet. Korea&amp;rsquo;s KAIST advances from 6th to 2nd, while Seoul National University (4th) and Postech (9th) also feature in the top 10...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-singapore-and-korea-have-emerged-as-the-top-universities-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bankers in the APAC region predict a decrease in M&amp;A activity under President Trump's administration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</guid><description>A recent survey of 300 Asia Pacific mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) professionals conducted by Intralinks, a secure platform used by dealmakers for content sharing, found that 75% of respondents believe a potential presidency under Donald Trump would negatively impact M&amp;amp;A activity in the region. This mirrors the global sentiment revealed by Intralinks&amp;rsquo; survey of 1,500 M&amp;amp;A professionals worldwide.
Intralinks&amp;rsquo; Global M&amp;amp;A Sentiment Survey shows 75% of Asian dealmakers consider Trump the most detrimental presidential candidate for M&amp;amp;A activity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bankers-in-the-apac-region-predict-a-decrease-in-m-a-activity-under-president-trump-s-administration/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bosch is advocating for an increase in the number of vehicles in Southeast Asia to be equipped with safety features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 06:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</guid><description> Road traffic deaths in ASEAN countries are estimated at 117,000 annually, with over half involving motorcycles.
 An increasing number of countries and territories, including Japan, Taiwan, and India, are making motorcycle antilock braking systems (ABS) mandatory for new motorcycles.
 Malaysia is the first and only ASEAN nation to require all new cars to have electronic stability control (ESC) as of 2018.
Bosch believes Southeast Asia can do more to enhance road safety...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bosch-is-advocating-for-an-increase-in-the-number-of-vehicles-in-southeast-asia-to-be-equipped-with-safety-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Euromonitor has discovered that India and China have lower-than-average per capita calorie purchases</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</guid><description>A new study by Euromonitor International reveals how many nutrients people consume daily from packaged foods and beverages. This data, found in their Passport: Nutrition database, tracks the consumption of calories, fats, saturated fats, carbohydrates, sugars, salt, protein, and fiber across 54 countries.
Globally, we buy enough packaged food and soft drinks to consume 1.5 trillion calories per day, averaging 765 calories per person. While a healthy daily intake is around 2,000 calories, North America and Western Europe exceed 1,500 calories, contrasting with India&amp;rsquo;s 150 and China&amp;rsquo;s 510...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-has-discovered-that-india-and-china-have-lower-than-average-per-capita-calorie-purchases/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Spotify reveals top music of 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</guid><description>Source: Spotify.
Spotify has unveiled its Year in Music, analyzing data from 50 million users and over 7 billion hours of music to determine 2014&amp;rsquo;s top songs and artists.
UK artist Ed Sheeran leads as the most streamed artist globally, with over 860 million streams on Spotify. His album, released in June to critical acclaim, also achieved the highest number of streams, exceeding 430 million.
In Singapore, Jay Chou maintains his position as the most streamed Asian artist for the second consecutive year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/spotify-reveals-top-music-of-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Casual dining is becoming more popular globally</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:12:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</guid><description>A global market research firm, Euromonitor International, determined that consumer food service sales increased by 5.7% worldwide in 2015, a rise from the previous year&amp;rsquo;s growth rate of 5.3%. Fast casual dining experienced the most significant growth within the industry at 10.4%, generating an extra US$3.4 billion in revenue between 2014 and 2015.
Elizabeth Friend, a Consumer Foodservice Strategy Analyst at Euromonitor International, observed, &amp;ldquo;Consumers are changing their dining habits, especially in developed countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/casual-dining-is-becoming-more-popular-globally/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In Asia, cards account for 52% of payments, but there are new emerging payment tools</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</guid><description>A study by ACI Worldwide and Ovum, &amp;ldquo;2017 Global Payments Insight Survey: Merchants and Retailers,&amp;rdquo; found that 79% of merchants and retailers believe a comprehensive approach to payments across different channels is crucial for a positive customer experience.
The study showed that while the EMV chip card standard has reduced in-person fraud, online fraud is on the rise. Merchants and retailers are planning to significantly increase their investments in payments to improve customer experience (a 50% increase compared to 2015)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-asia-cards-account-for-52-of-payments-but-there-are-new-emerging-payment-tools/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Genesys says that Asian businesses require a greater understanding of e-commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 22:34:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</guid><description>Source: Genesys.
Thomassain.
This year marks the first time Asia Pacific has surpassed Europe as the biggest online shopping market, according to Genesys, and this upward trend is expected to continue.
The increasing accessibility of the internet, the expanding use of smartphones and tablets, and the potential of the Chinese market are all contributing to a surge in e-commerce throughout Asia. Erwann Thomassain, Head of Marketing, Asia Pacific, at Genesys, notes that by the end of 2014, business-to-consumer e-commerce sales in Asia will reach US$525 billion, representing half of all global online sales...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/genesys-says-that-asian-businesses-require-a-greater-understanding-of-e-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance reveals the top influential brands in Asia for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</guid><description>Source: Brand Alliance. The brand gallery at Marina Bay Sands is open until August 21st.
Brand Alliance, using its brand leadership platform Influential Brands, has announced the 2015 Asia’s Top Influential Brands. This announcement leverages consumer insights gathered from 2013 to 2015.
This year, the Asia’s Top Influential Brands awards expanded to include over 100 categories. These categories span various sectors, ranging from food and beverage (F&amp;amp;B) and fast-moving consumer goods (FMCG) to financial services and property development...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-reveals-the-top-influential-brands-in-asia-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BHM Asia introduces a new booking platform for its X2 and Away villa brands in Chiang Mai</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</guid><description>Source: www.VillasChiangMai.com
BHMAsia, a hospitality management and development firm operating in the Asia-Pacific region, has recently launched VillasChiangMai.com. This new website showcases all of their villa rentals available in Chiang Mai, under both their X2 and Away brands.
BHMAsia highlights that their Chiang Mai villas offer more space compared to a typical hotel room, featuring distinct bedrooms and common areas. Some villas can even accommodate groups of up to 14 people...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bhm-asia-introduces-a-new-booking-platform-for-its-x2-and-away-villa-brands-in-chiang-mai/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EIU has identified six areas of growth in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:47:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</guid><description>A new study by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) highlights six industry sectors poised for significant growth in Asia: engineering services, environmental technology, food processing, healthcare, oil &amp;amp; gas, and wholesale &amp;amp; retail. Commissioned by InvestKL, Kuala Lumpur&amp;rsquo;s investment agency, the &amp;ldquo;industry dynamism&amp;rdquo; barometer suggests sustained corporate investment in Asia will drive long-term economic expansion.
Engineering Services
Asia&amp;rsquo;s need for new infrastructure is fueling rapid growth in engineering services. An estimated US$8 to US$9 trillion will be invested in infrastructure between 2010 and 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eiu-has-identified-six-areas-of-growth-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU-Asean Business Council has introduced a new agenda aimed at increasing trade between ASEAN and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:26:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</guid><description>The EU-ASEAN Business Council (ABC), the leading advocate for European businesses operating in the ASEAN region, has proposed several actions to strengthen trade and investment ties between ASEAN and the EU. These recommendations were released to coincide with the 26th ASEAN Summit held in Malaysia.
The Agenda for the promotion of trade and investment between ASEAN and Europe was presented to ASEAN Economic Ministers and EU Trade Commissioner Cecilia Malmström on April 26 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-asean-business-council-has-introduced-a-new-agenda-aimed-at-increasing-trade-between-asean-and-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore remains a popular regional hub and is ranked as the fourth-most expensive city in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:25:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</guid><description>Hong Kong is the world&amp;rsquo;s most expensive city, joined by four other Asian cities in the top 10. Chinese cities, including Shanghai (7th) and Beijing (10th), dropped in the rankings due to a weaker yuan. Singapore holds the fourth spot, while Tokyo climbed to fifth from 11th.
Mercer Cost of Living Survey – Worldwide Rankings 2016 (The Mercer international basket, including rental accommodation costs)
Rank as of March City Country 2015 2016 2 1 HONG KONG Hong Kong 1 2 LUANDA Angola 3 3 ZURICH Switzerland 4 4 SINGAPORE Singapore 11 5 TOKYO Japan 13 6 KINSHASA Dem...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-remains-a-popular-regional-hub-and-is-ranked-as-the-fourth-most-expensive-city-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top food in Asia can be found in China, Japan, Singapore, and Thailand, according to Asia's 50 Best Restaurants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</guid><description>For the best dining experience, consider the top 10 restaurants in Asia, according to Asia&amp;rsquo;s Best 50 Restaurants for 2014.
Most of these top-rated establishments are located in Thailand, Japan, China, or Singapore. The top 10 list features two restaurants from Bangkok, two from Tokyo, three from Hong Kong, and two from Singapore: Nahm, in Bangkok, Thailand, is known for its guinea fowl curry with shampoo ginger and holy basil...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-food-in-asia-can-be-found-in-china-japan-singapore-and-thailand-according-to-asia-s-50-best-restaurants/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technology usage in 2015 could be vastly different</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 03:49:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</guid><description>Source: Intel infographic. Learn more here.
Our current world relies on multiple connected devices, and this trend will only intensify. Intel believes that while we currently utilize various devices like wearables, smartphones, tablets, and PCs, the future holds even more significant changes.
Hermann Eul, VP and GM, Mobile and Communications Group at Intel, points out that users constantly demand better device performance. He highlights that in 2015, devices will need to meet the need for improved imaging, extended battery life without sacrificing performance, integrated experiences, and enhanced responsiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technology-usage-in-2015-could-be-vastly-different/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asians struggle with their comfort levels when it comes to using air conditioning</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 22:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</guid><description>A Hong Kong-based startup, Ambi Labs, has initiated a crowdsourcing campaign for their latest product, Ambi Climate. This innovative device is designed to optimize air conditioning systems based on two years of user feedback gathered from ten Asian markets.
Source: Ambi Labs.
Ambi Labs conducted extensive online surveys across ten major Asian markets, engaging with over 4,000 participants. The findings revealed that the most significant challenge with air conditioners lies in maintaining a comfortable room temperature...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asians-struggle-with-their-comfort-levels-when-it-comes-to-using-air-conditioning/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Southeast Asia is a region where digital marketing is effective</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 03:03:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</guid><description>Source: Adobe website.
Recent research from Adobe highlights the growing importance of mobile devices for marketers in Southeast Asia, emphasizing its effectiveness in customer interaction and engagement. This shift toward mobile-first business strategies is particularly prominent in the Asia Pacific region.
Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Digital Index &amp;ldquo;Best of the Best Benchmark&amp;rdquo; for 2015 analyzed website performance across eight regions, including Southeast Asia. By comparing the top 20% of websites (&amp;ldquo;best of the best&amp;rdquo;) with the overall average across six key performance indicators, the research provides valuable insights into the strategies of high-performing digital marketing organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/southeast-asia-is-a-region-where-digital-marketing-is-effective/</a></p></description></item><item><title>By the second quarter of 2015, there will be four new JW Marriott hotels opening in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 22:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Marriott. The JW Marriott Hotel Chongqing.
Marriott International&amp;rsquo;s luxury brand, JW Marriott Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, is expanding its presence in Asia with four new properties scheduled to open by the second quarter of 2015. These additions include three hotels in Greater China (Chongqing, Shenzhen Bao&amp;rsquo;an, and Macau) and one in India (Mumbai Sahar). This expansion will bring the brand&amp;rsquo;s footprint to 28 hotels and resorts in the Asia-Pacific region, including 11 in China and seven in India...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/by-the-second-quarter-of-2015-there-will-be-four-new-jw-marriott-hotels-opening-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL Global Forwarding introduces a new road freight network across Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 14:23:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</guid><description>DHL Global Forwarding, a leading provider of air, sea, and road freight services in Europe and Asia, has established a comprehensive road freight network connecting five major Asian cities: Singapore, Penang, Bangkok, Hanoi, and Shenzhen. This strategic move capitalizes on the rapid expansion of road freight in the Asia Pacific region, projected to grow at a rate of 8.3% annually between 2014 and 2019, reaching an estimated value of US$822 billion by 2019...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-global-forwarding-introduces-a-new-road-freight-network-across-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top hotels in Asia can be found in the Maldives and the UAE in the Middle East</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 18:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</guid><description>Based on TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s rankings, this year&amp;rsquo;s best Asian hotels are predominantly located in the Maldives. Of the top ten, four resorts are in the Maldives and two are in Bali. Including three more Maldivian resorts in the top 25 results in the Maldives representing 28% of the list, alongside an additional Balinese hotel. India also has a strong presence, boasting four hotels within the top 25.
Source: TripAdvisor website. The Gili Lankanfushi Maldives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-hotels-in-asia-can-be-found-in-the-maldives-and-the-uae-in-the-middle-east/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CA Technologies believes that Asia has the potential to become a central hub of global innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</guid><description>Lionel Lim, President for Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan at CA Technologies, believes the significant data exchange happening within Asia indicates the region&amp;rsquo;s potential to become a leading force in innovation.
During a Chinese New Year event in Singapore, Lim stated that Asia is capable of matching Europe and the US in driving innovation. He emphasized that the focus is shifting from cost reduction to accelerating innovation.
Lim highlighted four key areas for innovation and differentiation: improving user experience, ensuring convenient, fast, and secure data access, utilizing technologies that boost business growth, and strengthening IT skills...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ca-technologies-believes-that-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-a-central-hub-of-global-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A book comparing Asian data privacy laws to international standards is available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-book-comparing-asian-data-privacy-laws-to-international-standards-is-available/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 12:22:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-book-comparing-asian-data-privacy-laws-to-international-standards-is-available/</guid><description>Graham Greenleaf&amp;rsquo;s Asian Data Privacy Laws: Trade &amp;amp; Human Rights Perspectives (ISBN 978-0-19-967966-9) is a groundbreaking examination of data privacy legislation across Asia.
Source: OUP.
Professor Greenleaf, a Law Professor at the University of New South Wales, Australia, and Co-founder and Co-Director of the open-access Australasian Legal Information Institute, explores 26 countries and individual jurisdictions. The book provides a thorough analysis of the 14 jurisdictions with specific data privacy laws, comparing them to global benchmarks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-book-comparing-asian-data-privacy-laws-to-international-standards-is-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-book-comparing-asian-data-privacy-laws-to-international-standards-is-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Compass Index indicates a positive business outlook in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 21:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Despite a global economic downturn, the Compass Index shows optimism in the Asia Pacific (APAC) business sector, with Australian businesses reporting the highest confidence levels. However, the Index emphasizes that maintaining growth requires agility and innovation in business practices.
Source: Compass Index infographic. Australia is particular optimistic on business growth. Compass Offices, a provider of Asian serviced offices, virtual offices, and meeting rooms, surveyed their global clientele for the Compass Index...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-compass-index-indicates-a-positive-business-outlook-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Labuan IBFC experienced a 12.3% increase in new company registrations in 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 04:21:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</guid><description>Labuan International Business and Financial Centre (Labuan IBFC), a prominent international business and financial hub in the Asia Pacific region, demonstrated strong performance across all financial sectors in 2014. These sectors include banking, insurance, leasing, wealth management, and Islamic finance, with a 12.3% rise in new company registrations compared to the previous year.
The organization highlights that 70% of companies registered in Labuan IBFC come from Asia, with 57% from Southeast Asia, particularly Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/labuan-ibfc-experienced-a-12-3-increase-in-new-company-registrations-in-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The membership promotion at EatPlayLive is available until the end of the year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 05:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</guid><description>Source: EatPlayLive Facebook page. Live life on the edge.
The Asian lifestyle app EatPlayLive, recently introduced in Singapore, has a limited-time offer for a one-year membership. For a limited time, you can get a year of membership for S$100, discounted from the regular price of S$180.
EatPlayLive offers enticing deals and experiences that could potentially save members thousands of dollars annually. These range from dining discounts at renowned restaurants like Senso, Chef’s Table, and Angelina to unique experiences at establishments such as Culinaryon, Arteastiq, The Fullerton Spa, and Amara Sanctuary Resort Sentosa...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-membership-promotion-at-eatplaylive-is-available-until-the-end-of-the-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The beauty industry acknowledges the growing demand in Asia for products that promote relaxation and stress relief</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:38:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</guid><description>A recent report by market intelligence agency Mintel reveals that the Asia-Pacific region produced one-third of all new beauty and personal care products aimed at relaxation and stress relief in the first nine months of 2018. This represents a significant increase from 2015 when the region accounted for only 26% of similar global product launches.
Sharon Kwek, Senior Innovation and Insights Analyst, Beauty and Personal Care at Mintel, addressed the in-cosmetics Asia event stating that today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced, demanding world has normalized stress...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-beauty-industry-acknowledges-the-growing-demand-in-asia-for-products-that-promote-relaxation-and-stress-relief/</a></p></description></item><item><title>FHA2016 ends on a positive note</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</guid><description>Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016), the leading trade show for Asia&amp;rsquo;s food and hospitality sector, concluded successfully.
Source: Singapore Exhibition Services. The showfloor at FHA2016.
Lindy Wee, Chief Executive of Singapore Exhibition Services, noted that as consumer preferences change, so do buyer demands. She expressed satisfaction that FHA remains a crucial platform for exhibitors to introduce innovative products and for global buyers to source them, effectively serving the food and hospitality sectors.
FHA featured a comprehensive range of products and services, from ingredients and equipment to hotel amenities and software...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fha2016-ends-on-a-positive-note/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ericsson predicts that the Internet of Things will surpass mobile phones by 2018</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</guid><description>According to the most recent Ericsson Mobility Report*, the Internet of Things (IoT) is poised to become the biggest category of connected devices, surpassing mobile phones by 2018.
The number of IoT connected devices is projected to rise by 23% annually from 2015 to 2021, with cellular IoT predicted to experience the fastest growth. By 2021, nearly 16 billion of the anticipated 28 billion connected devices will be IoT devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ericsson-predicts-that-the-internet-of-things-will-surpass-mobile-phones-by-2018/</a></p></description></item><item><title>China has a strong presence in the new City Momentum Index by Jones Lang LaSalle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 05:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</guid><description>Five cities in Asia Pacific and the Middle East — Dubai, Wuhan, Shanghai, Hong Kong and Singapore — are among the top 10 in Jones Lang LaSalle&amp;rsquo;s new City Momentum Index (CMI). This index identifies cities worldwide with significant short-term socio-economic and commercial real estate momentum, as well as strong long-term growth potential.
Jeremy Kelly, Director of Global Research at Jones Lang LaSalle, explains that city momentum is not solely determined by GDP growth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/china-has-a-strong-presence-in-the-new-city-momentum-index-by-jones-lang-lasalle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You can now access Fashion Television as a standalone satellite channel in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-access-fashion-television-as-a-standalone-satellite-channel-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-access-fashion-television-as-a-standalone-satellite-channel-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Fashion Television website.
Asian fashion enthusiasts can now enjoy Fashion Television as a dedicated satellite channel. While Fashion Television has been offering fashion programming to Asian viewers as part of other content blocks since 1999, this dedicated channel allows over a billion people access to its content 24/7.
Fashion Television International, based in London, opted to utilize the Asiasat 7 satellite, operated by Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s Asiasat Satellite Telecommunications Co...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-access-fashion-television-as-a-standalone-satellite-channel-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-can-now-access-fashion-television-as-a-standalone-satellite-channel-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>JLL reports that tech startups are a significant driver of real estate demand in the APAC region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:25:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</guid><description>New types of office users are emerging in the form of startups, with more tech companies exploring unconventional spaces such as coworking facilities and industrial properties, according to JLL, a real estate and investment management firm.
The technology sector in the Asia Pacific region has experienced significant growth, driven by mobile technology, e-commerce, and the rise of fintech. This growth has fueled demand for both traditional office spaces and business parks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jll-reports-that-tech-startups-are-a-significant-driver-of-real-estate-demand-in-the-apac-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Canon PhotoMarathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore in November</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 14:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM. Now in its 12th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon 2014 is the biggest photography competition in the region. Taking place in Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, Vietnam, India, Thailand, and Cambodia, the competition offers a fantastic chance for companies to form teams and compete in the Corporate Challenge category.
Companies can participate by assembling a team of at least three individuals who register as a group. In contrast to the open and student divisions, corporate teams are evaluated collectively...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wealthy individuals from Southeast Asia are choosing to travel within the region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:16:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</guid><description>A 2016 survey of wealthy Southeast Asian consumers by UOB found that travel is a major part of their lifestyle, with over 90% of respondents from Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, and Thailand taking at least one international holiday per year.
However, economic concerns are leading these travelers to choose destinations closer to home. Over 60% of those surveyed have opted for vacations within Asia. In fact, Asian countries, excluding Australia, were the top five travel destinations over the past year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wealthy-individuals-from-southeast-asia-are-choosing-to-travel-within-the-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BERI considers Taiwan to be a top candidate for establishing its Asia Pacific headquarters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</guid><description>Is your business searching for a new Asia-Pacific regional headquarters? Taiwan might be the ideal location.
Business Environment Risk Intelligence (BERI) released its third &amp;ldquo;Report on the Evaluation of Environmental Risks of Investment&amp;rdquo; for 2013 in December 2013. The report ranks 50 countries and territories based on their &amp;ldquo;Profit Opportunity Recommendation&amp;rdquo; metric. Switzerland secured the top position, followed by Singapore and then Taiwan.
Taiwan holds the second position globally, just behind Singapore, for operational risk...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beri-considers-taiwan-to-be-a-top-candidate-for-establishing-its-asia-pacific-headquarters/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The 5-Min Video Challenge has been introduced by the Singtel Group</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</guid><description>Source: The 5-Min Video Challenge website. Invitation to enter the local rounds.
Singtel Group launched The 5-Min Video Challenge to promote creative content across its global markets. The competition is a collaborative effort among Singtel&amp;rsquo;s associates, including Optus, AIS, Airtel, Globe, and Telkomsel. Winning videos will be shared with over 600 million customers within the Singtel Group.
Content creation is a key element of the Group&amp;rsquo;s strategy for customer engagement in a world where mobile devices are everywhere and demand for online video entertainment is high...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-5-min-video-challenge-has-been-introduced-by-the-singtel-group/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia Pacific accounts for half of all card spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</guid><description>New data from Euromonitor International reveals that global consumer reliance on card payments increased from 2014 to 2015, with the Asia Pacific region leading this trend.
By 2015, the Asia Pacific region accounted for half of all card spending. This growth is projected to continue, with the region comprising 54% of the estimated US$29.2 trillion global card payment value by 2020. China&amp;rsquo;s favorable regulations for card and electronic payments have greatly contributed to this surge...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-pacific-accounts-for-half-of-all-card-spending/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jack Wills has opened its flagship store in Singapore, marking its 78th store worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:10:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</guid><description>The popular British fashion brand, Jack Wills, known for its classic British style, launched its first store in Singapore at Raffles City Shopping Centre on November 4th. The brand is favored by well-known British figures like Princes William and Harry, Emma Watson, and Cheryl Cole. Their trademark, &amp;ldquo;Fabulously British,&amp;rdquo; reflects the brand&amp;rsquo;s focus on high-quality clothing inspired by British heritage.
The store&amp;rsquo;s black and white exterior leads into an interior featuring herringbone wood floors, a hand-painted Union Jack, and a colonial-style room divider with velvet Union Jack curtains...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jack-wills-has-opened-its-flagship-store-in-singapore-marking-its-78th-store-worldwide/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Starbucks Teavana is now offered in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 06:39:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Starbucks has launched Starbucks Teavana, its line of handcrafted tea drinks and whole leaf tea sachets, in over 6,200 stores across 16 markets in the China and Asia Pacific region. This marks the global availability of Starbucks Teavana. Starbucks Teavana offers unique, layered flavor experiences in both iced and hot formats.
John Culver, Group President of Starbucks Global Retail, highlighted the growing consumer demand for new and unique taste experiences and positioned the Teavana launch as a way to leverage Starbucks&amp;rsquo; expertise in crafting beverages and sourcing premium ingredients to become a leader in the tea category...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starbucks-teavana-is-now-offered-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three of the top 25 hotels in the world, as listed by TripAdvisor, are located in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 13:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</guid><description>TripAdvisor&amp;rsquo;s 2014 Traveler&amp;rsquo;s Choice awards highlights 25 diverse hotels worldwide. Notably, three hotels from Asia secured spots within the top 10. Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s The Upper House claimed the second position, while India&amp;rsquo;s Oberoi Udaivilas and Oberoi Mumbai ranked fifth and ninth, respectively.
The Upper House, nestled in Pacific Place, holds the top spot among hotels in Hong Kong. One reviewer praised it as their &amp;ldquo;best hotel experience,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing its flawlessness. A remarkable 97% of the reviews for this hotel are positive...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-of-the-top-25-hotels-in-the-world-as-listed-by-tripadvisor-are-located-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Abbott introduces the Freestyle Libre Pro System for glucose monitoring in India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</guid><description>Research from the Asia Diabetes Foundation (ADF) indicates a growing trend of type II diabetes among young adults in Asia. A collaborative study by the ADF and Merck, called the Joint Asia Diabetes Evaluation (JADE), revealed that 18% of participants from nine Asian countries and territories were diagnosed with diabetes before the age of 40. This condition is known as young-onset diabetes.
While pharmaceutical company Merck offers the drug Janumet XR for type II diabetes treatment, healthcare company Abbott takes a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abbott-introduces-the-freestyle-libre-pro-system-for-glucose-monitoring-in-india/</a></p></description></item><item><title>India is making strides towards achieving global recognition for its universities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 23:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</guid><description>Indian educational institutions are increasingly recognizing the value of global university rankings, according to Quacquarelli Symonds (QS), the organization behind the recently released Asian Universities Ranking for 2014. This year&amp;rsquo;s list features 17 Indian universities, a significant increase from the 11 included in the previous year.
Source: QS website.
While the latest rankings show a slight dip in rankings for most of India&amp;rsquo;s top universities, the substantial increase in the number of represented institutions suggests a positive trajectory for the future...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-is-making-strides-towards-achieving-global-recognition-for-its-universities/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hotdesk and Compass provide short-term workspace solutions in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 01:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Hotdesk, a platform for finding temporary office space, has teamed up with Compass Offices to provide on-demand workspaces and meeting rooms for professionals on the move. These spaces can be reserved for various durations, including daily, weekly, or monthly.
Studies from IDC indicate that by 2015, there will be a significant increase in the number of mobile workers globally, with over 1.3 billion individuals adopting this work style. Notably, the Asia Pacific region is projected to have the highest concentration, with over 838 million mobile workers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hotdesk-and-compass-provide-short-term-workspace-solutions-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asia's talent and innovation are highlighted in global indices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</guid><description>The Global Innovation Index (GII) 2017, a collaborative effort by Cornell University, INSEAD, and the World Intellectual Property Organization (WIPO), highlights India and Vietnam for surpassing their developmental peers. The GII, which assesses the innovative capacity of approximately 130 economies, underscores India&amp;rsquo;s emergence as a hub for innovation in Asia.
This year&amp;rsquo;s GII points to a persistent disparity in innovation between developed and developing economies, alongside sluggish growth in research and development (R&amp;amp;D) investment from both governments and corporations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-s-talent-and-innovation-are-highlighted-in-global-indices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy is dedicated to creating impressive and impactful business identities for small businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</guid><description>GoDaddy: Expanding Beyond Domains to Empower Small Businesses While GoDaddy is known for domain names, it has evolved into much more. CEO Blake Irving emphasizes the company&amp;rsquo;s focus on supporting small businesses, a demographic often overlooked despite representing a significant portion of most economies.
Irving highlights that small businesses, even those with a single employee, present a vast untapped market. Traditional solutions often cater to either large enterprises or individual consumers, leaving small businesses underserved...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-is-dedicated-to-creating-impressive-and-impactful-business-identities-for-small-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Food&amp;HotelAsia will be larger and improved in 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</guid><description>Ting speaking at a media preview for FHA.
Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia (FHA), a major food and hospitality trade show in Asia, is approaching its 40th anniversary of serving the industry&amp;rsquo;s needs.
Since its 1978 inception, FHA has attracted a predominantly international exhibitor base (over 80%), underscoring its global reach. FHA provides a platform for showcasing innovative products, technologies, and solutions from around the world, facilitating connections and business opportunities for trade buyers and sellers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/food-hotelasia-will-be-larger-and-improved-in-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cartrack tracks vehicles in multiple countries</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</guid><description>Source: Cartrack website.
Cartrack, a company specializing in fleet management, insurance telematics, vehicle tracking, and recovery services, is expanding its presence.
The company is capitalizing on the rising number of vehicles and the expanding telematics sector. Leveraging its Singapore office as a central hub, Cartrack has established new branches in Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand, the Philippines, and Hong Kong this year.
Cartrack Singapore CEO, Evert Ong, highlighted the significant growth originating from both small and medium-sized enterprises and larger corporations aiming to enhance their fleet and workforce operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cartrack-tracks-vehicles-in-multiple-countries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong, Tokyo, and Dubai ranked among the top 10 cities for hotel Wi-Fi speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</guid><description>Hotelwifitest.com, a website that evaluates hotel Wi-Fi quality, has published a list of cities ranked by the percentage of hotels with subpar Wi-Fi. Stockholm earned the top spot for hotel Wi-Fi satisfaction, followed by Hong Kong and Amsterdam.
Source: Hotelwifitest.com
The company suggests travelers verify Wi-Fi quality before making a hotel reservation. Hotelwifitest.com not only provides a platform for users to test their upload, download, and latency speeds but also showcases hotels that have undergone testing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-tokyo-and-dubai-ranked-among-the-top-10-cities-for-hotel-wi-fi-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian companies place a high value on feedback received during exit interviews</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</guid><description>A recent report from Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, reveals that most companies believe in the value of honest feedback during exit interviews, whether formal or informal. In fact, seven out of ten Asian companies conduct these interviews.
Titled &amp;ldquo;Acquiring Insights From The Exit Process To Build A Better Workplace,&amp;rdquo; the report highlights how improvements made based on exit interview feedback can help organizations attract and retain top-tier talent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-companies-place-a-high-value-on-feedback-received-during-exit-interviews/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asian cities have been rearranged in Mercer's Cost of Living Survey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:35:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</guid><description>Five Asian cities—Hong Kong (ranked 2nd), Tokyo (3rd), Singapore (5th), Seoul (6th), and Shanghai (8th)—were named among the top 10 most expensive cities for expatriates in this year&amp;rsquo;s ranking.
Currency fluctuations played a significant role in shaping the rankings of most Asian cities.
While all mainland Chinese cities surveyed experienced a drop in ranking, Tianjin (12th) stood out as an exception, climbing 18 positions.
Mumbai, India made a remarkable jump of 25 places this year, attributed to robust economic growth, inflation, and a stable currency...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asian-cities-have-been-rearranged-in-mercer-s-cost-of-living-survey/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Hilton bans shark fin to align with the changing attitudes towards the Chinese delicacy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 10:45:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</guid><description>In February 2014, the Hilton group made an impactful announcement: it would eliminate shark fin from all of its 96 owned and managed properties in Asia Pacific by April 1, 2014. This decision was a significant blow to the waning popularity of the dish, once a staple at Chinese banquets.
[Image of shark fin served with scallops and crabmeat]
This decision was the culmination of a gradual phase-out. In December 2012, Hilton stopped readily offering shark fin at its managed properties in China and Southeast Asia, making it available only upon request...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hilton-bans-shark-fin-to-align-with-the-changing-attitudes-towards-the-chinese-delicacy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Younger shoppers favor purchasing clothing online</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</guid><description>A recent YouGov study found that consumers in the Asia Pacific region (APAC) still prefer physical stores for buying clothes. Over three-quarters (79%) of those surveyed visited a physical store for clothing purchases in the past year.
This trend is particularly strong in Hong Kong, Australia, and Malaysia, with 88%, 85%, and 84% of respondents favoring in-store shopping, respectively. Online shopping through websites is the second most popular option, with nearly half (45%) of APAC respondents using this method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/younger-shoppers-favor-purchasing-clothing-online/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GoDaddy has expanded its presence to 11 Asian markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:56:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</guid><description>GoDaddy, a global technology provider for small businesses, has expanded its reach into 11 Asian markets. This expansion brings GoDaddy&amp;rsquo;s cloud-based products and customer support services to millions of small and medium enterprises (SMEs) within the region.
With these 11 new markets, GoDaddy now operates in 14 markets across Asia, encompassing 10 languages. These markets include Hong Kong (English and Traditional Chinese), Indonesia, Japan, Malaysia (English and Malay), Philippines (English and Filipino), Singapore (English and Simplified Chinese), South Korea, Taiwan, Thailand, and Vietnam...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/godaddy-has-expanded-its-presence-to-11-asian-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Trademarks from Asia in a world that is interconnected</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:05:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</guid><description>Asian brands aiming to go global don&amp;rsquo;t have the luxury of slowly building a reputation over decades, according to experts who spoke at the 136th annual meeting of the International Trademark Association (INTA). This information was shared in a newsletter by IP Mirror, a company specializing in domain name registration, cloud hosting, and brand protection.
Source: INTA website.
The event, held in Hong Kong in early May, highlighted several strategies for Asian brands expanding globally, as reported by IP Mirror:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/trademarks-from-asia-in-a-world-that-is-interconnected/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Foul Odor of Decaying Prepaid Calling Cards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</guid><description>Prepaid calling cards are a popular choice for international calls due to their incredibly low advertised rates. The cards often boast incredibly low per-minute rates, but these rates don&amp;rsquo;t tell the whole story. Like perishable food, prepaid calling cards have a limited lifespan once you start using them.
Hidden in the fine print on the back of these cards are details about connection fees, minimum call durations, and weekly service fees...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foul-odor-of-decaying-prepaid-calling-cards/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Asia Pacific is dedicated to being the preferred bank for entrepreneurs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 01:21:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</guid><description>Source: Credit Suisse. Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer, Asia Pacific, Credit Suisse.
Credit Suisse has taken a proactive approach to the looming threat of technological disruption. Instead of being passively disrupted, the company has embraced digitalization in its traditional wealth management services, according to Helman Sitohang, Chief Executive Officer for Asia Pacific at Credit Suisse. He made these remarks during his opening address at the fourth annual Credit Suisse Global Megatrends Conference in Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/credit-suisse-asia-pacific-is-dedicated-to-being-the-preferred-bank-for-entrepreneurs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>InnoVen provides funding for e-commerce startups in Malaysia and Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 20:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</guid><description>United Overseas Bank (UOB) and Temasek&amp;rsquo;s joint venture, InnoVen Capital (InnoVen), has entered into two venture debt financing agreements with Southeast Asian e-commerce startups. These startups are part of a group of 20 companies from Southeast Asia, India, and China that InnoVen has selected for venture debt funding in the coming six months. The targeted sectors include e-commerce, financial technology, logistics, and big data.
During the first quarter of this year, InnoVen secured financing deals with Malaysia-based KFit Holdings, an e-commerce health and fitness company that has received funding from Sequoia Capital, and Thailand-based Pomelo Fashion, an e-commerce fashion company backed by Jungle Ventures...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innoven-provides-funding-for-e-commerce-startups-in-malaysia-and-thailand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various approaches to talent management in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: ECN.
Attracting and retaining skilled managers in Asia has become increasingly crucial for business leaders.
A recent survey by the Economist Corporate Network (ECN) of 550 member companies in Asia revealed that 95% of CEOs actively engage in talent management practices. However, their level and type of involvement differ significantly.
The report, Aligned for Success? Strategy, talent management and the role of the CEO in Asia, indicates that CEOs primarily focus on the strategic aspects of human capital, such as forecasting future workforce needs and organizational design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2016, Japan and Australia are expected to attract significant real estate investment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 08:23:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</guid><description>Asian real estate trends in 2016 are predicted to mirror those of 2015, with substantial capital flowing into prime properties and investors seeking refuge in the region&amp;rsquo;s most established and stable markets, according to the Emerging Trends in Real Estate Asia Pacific 2016 report, a joint publication by the Urban Land Institute (ULI) and PwC.
Japan and Australia remain top choices for real estate investment and development. Tokyo, Sydney, Melbourne, and Osaka secured four of the top five positions for promising markets in the Asia Pacific region, with Ho Chi Minh City rounding out the list in fifth place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2016-japan-and-australia-are-expected-to-attract-significant-real-estate-investment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>South Asia has the potential to become the leading export region in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 21:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</guid><description>By implementing policies that enhance productivity, South Asia could substantially increase its global market share in electronics, motor vehicles, and apparel by 2030, according to a new World Bank report titled &amp;ldquo;South Asia’s Turn: Policies to Boost Competitiveness and Create the Next Export Powerhouse.&amp;rdquo; The report emphasizes that improving firm productivity is crucial for boosting competitiveness in Pakistan and the rest of South Asia. While acknowledging the region&amp;rsquo;s investment climate challenges, the report focuses on less-explored factors like the impact of cities and clusters, global value chains, and firms&amp;rsquo; capacity for innovation and efficient resource utilization...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/south-asia-has-the-potential-to-become-the-leading-export-region-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopee is making a big effort to bring in more community members to its e-commerce platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</guid><description>Since launching late last year, Shopee has experienced significant growth in Southeast Asia and Taiwan, as illustrated by Feng&amp;rsquo;s chart.
Source: Shopee. Feng shows off the Shopee e-commerce platform on a screen replicating what is on his phone.
Shopee, the e-commerce branch of Garena, unveiled two new initiatives at its inaugural Biannual Press Conference: Shopee Free Shipping (currently in beta) and Shopee University. These programs represent the start of a comprehensive growth strategy for the mobile-first social marketplace, focused on improving user experience for both buyers and sellers and fostering a strong Shopee community...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopee-is-making-a-big-effort-to-bring-in-more-community-members-to-its-e-commerce-platform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Five Asian hotels are ranked in the top 25 of Expedia Insiders' Select 2014</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 05:34:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</guid><description>Expedia unveiled its 2014 Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select list in early July. This list highlights the best hotels globally, as determined by almost two million verified customer reviews and Expedia&amp;rsquo;s own travel experts.
Source: Blue Karma Resort website.
Out of over 290,000 bookable properties on Expedia&amp;rsquo;s global websites, 650 hotels received the Insiders&amp;rsquo; Select designation in 2014.
Here are a few of the top 25 hotels from this year&amp;rsquo;s list:
2. Blue Karma Resort - Seminyak, Bali..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-asian-hotels-are-ranked-in-the-top-25-of-expedia-insiders-select-2014/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Indonesia emerges victorious in the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</guid><description>For the third consecutive year, an Indonesian artist has earned the UOB Southeast Asian Painting of the Year Award. This year, the United Overseas Bank (UOB) recognized 36-year-old Gatot Indrajati for his relief acrylic painting, Right or Wrong My Home. This artwork also garnered him the 2016 UOB Painting of the Year, Indonesia award.
Judges praised Indrajati&amp;rsquo;s innovative combination of wood, a traditional Indonesian art material, with paint. This creates a visually captivating and modern piece of art...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/indonesia-emerges-victorious-in-the-uob-southeast-asian-painting-of-the-year-award/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The US CDC has compiled a list of airports worldwide that are smoke-free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 13:11:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</guid><description>Of the 50 busiest airports globally, 23 have implemented completely smoke-free indoor environments. This means that 46% of the busiest airports offer protection from secondhand smoke for travelers and employees, as per a recent report from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). The remaining 27 airports permit smoking in designated areas or spaces equipped with ventilation systems.
An airport was classified as having a smoke-free policy only if smoking was completely prohibited in all indoor areas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-us-cdc-has-compiled-a-list-of-airports-worldwide-that-are-smoke-free/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Improve your sleep with the Sleep with Six Senses program</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 01:47:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</guid><description>Source: Six Senses. Better sleep with the new Sleep with Six Senses programme.
Six Senses partnered with Sleep Doctor Dr. Michael Breus to launch its improved sleep standard called Sleep With Six Senses. Currently, five resorts offer this standard, with complete implementation across all locations expected by mid-2017. All future resorts will feature this program from their opening day.
The experience begins with a pre-arrival online questionnaire. This allows a designated Sleep Ambassador to understand the guest&amp;rsquo;s relationship with sleep and tailor the room accordingly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/improve-your-sleep-with-the-sleep-with-six-senses-program/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Supplying office pantries with items from FoodAsia2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:24:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</guid><description>The recent Food&amp;amp;HotelAsia2016 (FHA2016) trade event showcased a diverse selection of office pantry-friendly foods at the FoodAsia halls and Halal Supermarket zone.
One notable display was by Camel, a company known for snacks like nuts and dried fruit. A camel statue stood atop a mound of their products, greeting attendees. Competitor Tong Garden was also present at the event.
Another highlight was Nuhoney, a sparkling honey drink made in Singapore using Australian honey...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/supplying-office-pantries-with-items-from-foodasia2016/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>