<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Long-Term Residence on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-term-residence/</link><description>Recent content in Long-Term Residence on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-term-residence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The lives of UK nationals living in other EU Member States have been significantly altered by Brexit.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:48:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</guid><description>Sarah McCloskey and Tamara Hervey, Sheffield Law School
Following a string of significant political shifts, many can relate to the feelings of unease and worry stemming from the resulting instability. Currently, those hit hardest are individuals who have exercised their right to free movement without fear of it being revoked. This is the essence of Brexit: a source of discontent for some, a daily news item for others, but for EU citizens in the UK and UK citizens residing in other Member States, it holds the power to drastically alter their lives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-lives-of-uk-nationals-living-in-other-eu-member-states-have-been-significantly-altered-by-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 2: EU Commission's Proposal for Long-Term Resident Non-EU Citizens and Poundshop Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 18:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</guid><description>The free movement of people within the EU, a fundamental principle, generally applies to EU citizens and citizens of countries with specific agreements. However, EU immigration law allows for limited mobility of non-EU citizens within member states under stricter conditions. This article explores whether these limitations create a &amp;ldquo;discount&amp;rdquo; version of free movement for non-EU citizens.
One such measure is the EU long-term resident (LTR) status for non-EU citizens, established in 2003 and amended in 2010...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Commission's new proposal for long-term resident non-EU citizens (part 1)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Marcomob, via Wikimedia commons
The EU has a longstanding interest in regulating the legal status of non-EU citizens residing long-term within its Member States as part of its broader legal migration policy. The current law, a 2003 Directive amended in 2010, focuses on extending rights to those with refugee or subsidiary protection status. A recent Commission proposal aims to further expand the rights of this large group of non-EU citizens...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>