<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pseudowires on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pseudowires/</link><description>Recent content in Pseudowires on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pseudowires/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>VPLS Is The Ethernet Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 23:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-is-the-ethernet-cloud/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re all familiar with cloud networks, but wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be great to have a private cloud connecting all your business locations?
Virtual Private LAN Service (VPLS) offers a solution. While not a fully private cloud, it comes close.
VPLS allows you to share a private multipoint network built on technology like Multi-Protocol Label Switching (MPLS). MPLS networks can handle various traffic types, including Ethernet, making it ideal for diverse needs.</description></item><item><title>VPLS over MPLS Connects Locations Worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:10:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vpls-over-mpls-connects-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Older technologies like frame relay and TDM point-to-point connections are being replaced by MPLS networks. This shift from switched circuit to packet-switched networks reflects the declining significance of traditional telephone traffic in global voice, data, and video communication.
MPLS&amp;rsquo;s adaptability makes it the preferred WAN technology. The acronym&amp;rsquo;s MP stands for Multi-Protocol, signifying its ability to handle various traffic types. By attaching a label to each packet, MPLS ensures seamless transmission from origin to destination via Label Switching (LS).</description></item></channel></rss>