<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Netbooks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/netbooks/</link><description>Recent content in Netbooks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/netbooks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cellular Netbooks Are Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Do you spend most of your computing time on the go? If so, a computer designed for mobility might be perfect for you, like one of the new netbooks with built-in 3G cellular internet access.
You might be thinking laptops aren&amp;rsquo;t that bulky and work fine at a coffee shop.
That&amp;rsquo;s true. A laptop with a wireless modem aircard would be comparable to a netbook in functionality. However, laptops are heavier and often carry unnecessary extras...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cellular-netbooks-are-downright-cheap/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can Wireless Broadband Displace DSL and Cable?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 20:36:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</guid><description>Wired technologies, like DSL and Cable for consumers and T1 lines for businesses, have allowed broadband to replace dial-up internet access. However, a new competitor, wireless technology, could potentially disrupt wireline broadband just as it did to dial-up.
While Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) have existed for years, their limited coverage and small service areas haven&amp;rsquo;t posed a significant threat to telephone or cable companies. Business wireless internet remains mostly in major city centers, while consumer wireless targets rural areas beyond the reach of DSL and cable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-wireless-broadband-displace-dsl-and-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will Cell Phones Replace Laptop Computers?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 12:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</guid><description>Laptops have taken over as the primary mobile work tool, but their days may be numbered. They are bulky, heavy, and require constant charging. A simple legal pad is starting to look more appealing in comparison. The search is on for a mobile device that offers the right balance of power and portability. Could the answer be cell phones?
The idea of an all-in-one cell phone is appealing because most people carry one anyway...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-cell-phones-replace-laptop-computers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google's Plan To Chew Up Microsoft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 09:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</guid><description>A recent Wall Street Journal article hints at Google&amp;rsquo;s next target: Microsoft.
Google&amp;rsquo;s goals might extend beyond replacing Microsoft as the dominant force in PC operating systems. Their ambition could be complete control over all devices with embedded computers, essentially every electronic device.
This theory stems from reports that PC manufacturers like Hewlett-Packard are experimenting with Google&amp;rsquo;s Android operating system in netbooks. Android, primarily a mobile phone operating system, might seem harmless to established PC operating systems, but that might be a miscalculation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/googles-plan-to-chew-up-microsoft/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>