<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GSM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gsm/</link><description>Recent content in GSM on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gsm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Xperience the Sony Ericsson Xperia X10</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:37:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</guid><description>The Xperia X10 might be the perfect smartphone you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for. It boasts an 8.1 Megapixel camera and a 4-inch touchscreen, which begs the question: do you really need to carry a separate camera?
The Xperia&amp;rsquo;s camera eliminates that need with features like flash, 16x zoom, touch focus, geo-tagging, smile detection, and a &amp;lsquo;send to web&amp;rsquo; option. It&amp;rsquo;s adaptable for landscape, portrait, night, beach, and various other settings. You can even edit photos directly on the phone using apps from the Android Market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/xperience-the-sony-ericsson-xperia-x10/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry Torch Fires Up Mobile Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 20:18:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</guid><description>The BlackBerry Torch symbolizes a new era in mobile business communication, much like the Olympic torch marks the start of the Games.
This smartphone combines a touch screen with a slide-out QWERTY keyboard and introduces the BlackBerry 6 operating system. BlackBerry highlights the new OS&amp;rsquo;s ability to aggregate social media and RSS feeds, enable faster web browsing with multiple open tabs, provide universal search functionality, offer enhanced multimedia with a YouTube app, and ensure easy setup and personalization with a user-friendly design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberry-torch-fires-up-mobile-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>4G Wireless Broadband Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</guid><description>Wireless broadband is becoming increasingly popular and poised to replace many traditional wireline technologies thanks to its portability and mobility. However, the limited availability and speed of wireless connections have hindered its wider adoption and application. The emergence of 4G wireless technology offers a promising solution.
](http://www.cellphoneplansfinder.com/)
While 4G wireless lacks a precise definition, it generally refers to bandwidth comparable to cable broadband or Ethernet over copper business connections. With its high speed and broad coverage, 4G has the potential to serve both desktop and mobile devices...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/4g-wireless-broadband-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HSUPA Joins HSDPA for Cellular Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 15:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</guid><description>AT&amp;amp;T is nearing completion of its enhanced cellular broadband network, known as HSPA (High Speed Packet Access). This advancement is timely, as the latest BlackBerry Bold and the anticipated upgraded iPhone will utilize the increased data speeds now available. Although most attention has been on download enhancements, AT&amp;amp;T has also been quietly improving upload capabilities, hinting at the potential of upcoming mobile applications.
HSPA is an upgrade within the complex world of mobile technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hsupa-joins-hsdpa-for-cellular-broadband/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DROID 2 Global is a World Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 03:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</guid><description>The DROID 2 Global is a smartphone with a 1.2 GHz processor capable of making and receiving calls in over 200 countries. This Verizon phone works internationally through its unique ability to utilize both GSM and CDMA networks.
While Verizon primarily uses CDMA, incompatible with most global networks, the DROID 2 Global incorporates multiple network support. This includes WCDMA, GSM, HSDPA, CDMA EV-DO, EDGE, GPRS, and HSUPA, encompassing various forms of communication...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/droid-2-global-is-a-world-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-Mobile G2 With Google is 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 01:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</guid><description>T-Mobile is raising the bar for smartphones with its new G2, a Google phone that seamlessly integrates with Google Voice. This allows for voicemails to be converted to text and read like emails or texts.
Powered by Android 2.2, the G2 boasts a 3.7-inch full touch screen with seven customizable home panels. Users can personalize their experience with thousands of apps and widgets from the Android Market.
One of the G2&amp;rsquo;s standout features is its Adobe Flash Player, unlike a well-known competitor...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-mobile-g2-with-google-is-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Daddy Wants a BlackBerry</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:06:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</guid><description>With Father&amp;rsquo;s Day around the corner, forget the usual tie or car-related gifts. This year, give Dad what he truly desires: a cutting-edge BlackBerry Bold for both work and personal use. And here&amp;rsquo;s a secret: you can find it online at a great price.
The BlackBerry Bold combines style and functionality. Its sleek black design exudes professionalism and practicality. This BlackBerry boasts an impressive email client with the renowned &amp;ldquo;push&amp;rdquo; email feature, seamlessly integrating up to 10 accounts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/daddy-wants-a-blackberry/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Have SIM, Will Travel</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:11:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</guid><description>SIM Simminy, SIM Simminy, SIM SIM Siree
Having the right phone is essential for international travel.
Traveling to a foreign country can be exciting, but discovering your cell phone is unusable can put a damper on your trip. Without a working phone, you&amp;rsquo;ll be stuck using expensive hotel phones to stay in touch.
Fortunately, with a little planning, you can avoid this problem. The key is to ensure your cell phone is compatible with the network used in your destination country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/have-sim-will-travel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BlackBerry's Bold Move to HSDPA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 06:42:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</guid><description>BlackBerry, the company known for its wireless devices, is launching a new model called &amp;ldquo;Bold&amp;rdquo; with enhanced features like a sharper display, increased storage, a faster processor, and a 2-megapixel camera. However, the most significant advancement lies in its connectivity. The Bold surpasses standard EDGE data services by incorporating tri-band HSDPA and Wi-Fi, catering to the growing demand for desktop-like web browsing and video streaming among professionals.
Adding to the excitement, rumors are circulating about Apple&amp;rsquo;s iPhone selling out in anticipation of a new model featuring HSDPA technology...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/blackberrys-bold-move-to-hsdpa/</a></p></description></item><item><title>I'm Not Paying For That Aircard</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 07:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</guid><description>Fast and dependable office internet connections are great when you&amp;rsquo;re stationary, but mobile work demands solutions like WiFi hotspots or cellular broadband. While these options are suitable, not all laptops are equipped for cellular broadband.
Aircards, sometimes called wireless modems, bridge this gap. Similar to WiFi access cards, these devices allow laptops to connect to cellular broadband networks. In the past, laptops primarily used built-in modems, requiring separate cards for WiFi...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/im-not-paying-for-that-aircard/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HTC Aria Social Networking Smartphone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 08:36:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a way to stay connected, forget dogs – get FriendStream! This service lets you interact with friends through Facebook, Twitter, and Flickr, all from the HTC Aria, a cutting-edge Android smartphone.
The Aria boasts a sleek, seamless design crafted from a single piece of black aluminum. It&amp;rsquo;s compact enough for your pocket yet powerful enough for work and play. Its sizable 3.2-inch touchscreen features pinch-to-zoom functionality, automatically adjusting text size for comfortable website browsing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/htc-aria-social-networking-smartphone/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>