<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Retroactive Criminal Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retroactive-criminal-law/</link><description>Recent content in Retroactive Criminal Law on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/retroactive-criminal-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU bolsters criminal law protection of the EU's finances in The Italian Job.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-bolsters-criminal-law-protection-of-the-eu-s-finances-in-the-italian-job/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Contrary to popular belief, fraud against the EU budget is not typically committed by corrupt EU officials. As per EU reports, the usual culprits are individuals or companies exploiting EU funds managed by Member States. These violations also extend beyond spending to include EU income reduction, such as evading customs duties on imports.
Establishing and upholding EU-wide regulations for such misconduct has been challenging. However, the Court of Justice (CJEU) significantly strengthened the law in this area with its recent Taricco judgment.</description></item><item><title>Two perspectives on Taricco II: Criminal law, human rights, and constitutional pluralism.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 03:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-perspectives-on-taricco-ii-criminal-law-human-rights-and-constitutional-pluralism/</guid><description>The never-ending legal case, Jarndyce and Jarndyce, drags on. Over time, this meaningless case has become so convoluted that nobody understands it. The parties involved are the least informed, yet it&amp;rsquo;s been noted that two Chancery lawyers can&amp;rsquo;t discuss it for five minutes without disagreeing on every point. Countless children have been born into this case, young people have married into it, and the elderly have died during it. Many have unknowingly become parties in Jarndyce and Jarndyce with no explanation, and entire families have inherited bitter resentment alongside the suit.</description></item></channel></rss>