<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business VoIP on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-voip/</link><description>Recent content in Business VoIP on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 19:29:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-voip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Enterprise SIP Trunking Consolidates Phone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 19:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/</guid><description>When was the last time you examined your telephone network? And I don&amp;rsquo;t mean just looking at your bills for excessive long-distance usage or disconnected lines. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about a thorough review of your phone system&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure and its connections.
If you have multiple locations, you might unknowingly be tangled in a web of connections that drain your budget every month. This is especially common for companies that have expanded through acquisitions, where each site might have a completely different setup, leading to unnecessary expenses.</description></item><item><title>What XO’s 1,000,000 VoIP Customers Predicts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 12:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-xo-s-1-000-000-voip-customers-predicts/</guid><description>XO Communications, a leading competitor in the telecom industry, recently celebrated a significant achievement: reaching one million business VoIP users.
Reaching this milestone in just five years surprised even XO. This rapid adoption might be unexpected for those hesitant about embracing VoIP technology. We&amp;rsquo;ve all experienced the downsides of poorly implemented VoIP – distortion, dropped calls, and poor sound quality. However, successful implementations demonstrate that these issues are avoidable. After all, a million businesses can&amp;rsquo;t be wrong.</description></item></channel></rss>