<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Discrimination Law on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discrimination-law/</link><description>Recent content in Discrimination Law on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/discrimination-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CJEU's decision on the importance of parenthood in EU law slips away from us.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Most EU laws and court decisions on sex discrimination focus on improving women&amp;rsquo;s job opportunities and ensuring equal treatment in the workplace. A recent ruling by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the Maistrellis case tackles these issues from a different perspective: a father&amp;rsquo;s access to parental leave when the mother isn&amp;rsquo;t employed or looking for work. This judgment brings up important questions about how EU employment and discrimination laws affect family life...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-the-importance-of-parenthood-in-eu-law-slips-away-from-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU has confirmed that self-employed workers are protected from discrimination, including on the basis of sexual orientation, under anti-discrimination and labor rights laws.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 21:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</guid><description>A Closer Look at Worker Protections: Analyzing the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in Case C-356/21 By Chiara De Capitani, linguist agent at the European Commission and PhD candidate and honorary fellow in European law at the University of Naples “L&amp;rsquo;Orientale”. The information and views set out in this article are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the official opinion of the European Commission.
Photo credit: Silar, via Wikimedia Commons..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-confirmed-that-self-employed-workers-are-protected-from-discrimination-including-on-the-basis-of-sexual-orientation-under-anti-discrimination-and-labor-rights-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Faith in action: the CJEU's decisions on headscarves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 05:13:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer, UCL Faculty of Laws and author of Religion and the Public Order of the Euorpean Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’ordre juridique de l’Union européenne (Bruylant 2013).
Nearly two decades after the Framework Directive on discrimination in employment was implemented, the Court of Justice issued its first significant decisions regarding workplace discrimination based on religion. These rulings placed the Court in a politically sensitive area, presenting considerable risk for an international judicial body like the CJEU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faith-in-action-the-cjeu-s-decisions-on-headscarves/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dr. David L. Parris v. Trinity College Dublin and Others represents yet another missed chance to effectively protect LGB rights under EU law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 20:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</guid><description>By Dr. Alina Tryfonidou, Associate Professor in EU Law, University of Reading
Introduction
The recent ruling in the Parris case represents a missed chance for the European Court of Justice (ECJ) to provide meaningful protection to LGB individuals and same-sex couples under EU law. While recent cases like Asociaţia Accept and Hay suggested a shift towards stronger protection of LGB rights, the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s judgment in Parris, similar to the Léger case preceding it, reveals a hesitancy to address matters considered sensitive by Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dr-david-l-parris-v-trinity-college-dublin-and-others-represents-yet-another-missed-chance-to-effectively-protect-lgb-rights-under-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Revisiting Coleman: The Impact of Racial Discrimination on Collateral Damage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/</guid><description>Simon Cox
The Court of Justice of the European Union in Luxembourg recently heard arguments in a case regarding racial discrimination against Roma people. The case involves a non-Roma woman arguing that anyone negatively impacted by racially discriminatory actions deserves legal recourse under EU law. This case challenges the court&amp;rsquo;s prior decision in Coleman and seeks to clarify who can invoke EU discrimination law.
This case, originating from the Sofia Administrative Court, involves ten preliminary questions under the European Union Directive 2000/43 regarding racial discrimination...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/revisiting-coleman-the-impact-of-racial-discrimination-on-collateral-damage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Further information regarding the horizontal direct impact of the principle of age nondiscrimination can be found in the case of Dansk Industries (DI).</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 08:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</guid><description>Giovanni Zaccaroni, Ph.D (University of Bologna), Junior lawyer FratiniVergano The Court of Justice, in the recent DI case, further defined the differences in applying rights derived from Directive 2000/78/EC, which prohibits employment discrimination based on religion, disability, sexual orientation, and age, and the general principle of non-discrimination based on age in employment matters.
This builds upon previous landmark cases like Mangold and Kucukdeveci. In these cases, the Court addressed the obligation to prevent age discrimination in employment when challenged by national laws...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/further-information-regarding-the-horizontal-direct-impact-of-the-principle-of-age-nondiscrimination-can-be-found-in-the-case-of-dansk-industries-di/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Referendum Briefing 6: The Impact on EU Employment and Equality Law Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers suggests that while some claim there would be a &amp;ldquo;bonfire of rights&amp;rdquo; if the UK left the EU, particularly in employment and equality, others argue that the EU has no bearing on these laws in the UK. This post will demonstrate that EU law has significantly improved employment and equality rights in the UK, especially for women in the workplace.
A study of all UK cases reaching the EU court concerning these issues reveals that 60% of cases involving equal treatment for women resulted in findings that UK law was inadequate, leading to improved workplace protections for women...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-referendum-briefing-6-the-impact-on-eu-employment-and-equality-law-post-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU judgment in NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford has erased the blurry line between employment discrimination and the right to freedom of expression.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</guid><description>Chiara De Capitani, Ph.D. Researcher in International Studies at the University of Naples &amp;ldquo;L&amp;rsquo;Orientale&amp;rdquo;
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case C‑507/18, NH v Associazione Avvocatura per i diritti LGBTI — Rete Lenford, centers around the balance between freedom of expression and the harmful impact of discriminatory language. Advocate General Eleanor Sharpston aptly used bird metaphors in her opinion, likening discriminatory statements to volatile birds that can quickly spread their harmful effects...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-judgment-in-nh-v-associazione-avvocatura-per-i-diritti-lgbti-rete-lenford-has-erased-the-blurry-line-between-employment-discrimination-and-the-right-to-freedom-of-expression/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What approach should the CJEU take in addressing religious discrimination in the workplace?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:46:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</guid><description>Ronan McCrea*
* Senior Lecturer at the Faculty of Laws at UCL and the author of Religion and the Public Order of the European Union (OUP 2010) and Religion et l’Ordre juridique de l’Union Europeenne (Bruylant 2013).
Recent weeks have seen two opinions from Advocates General of the Court of Justice of the European Union concerning religious expression in the workplace. This follows a period where religious issues were largely absent from Luxembourg case law...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-approach-should-the-cjeu-take-in-addressing-religious-discrimination-in-the-workplace/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>