<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PBX System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-system/</link><description>Recent content in PBX System on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pbx-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ShoreTel Connect CLOUD Goes Way Beyond VoIP</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 06:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shoretel-connect-cloud-goes-way-beyond-voip/</guid><description>VoIP phone systems are often viewed as a direct substitute for conventional analog business phone systems, encompassing Key Telephone and PBX systems. The transition to this modern technology eliminates the need for separate phone and computer networks and allows businesses to move their internal switching system to the cloud. Moreover, switching to IP phones unlocks a wider array of features, often referred to as Unified Communications (UC).
ShorTel, a recognized leader in business communications, is widely used by companies of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste</description></item><item><title>DS1 Telephone Service Lowers Business Phone Bills</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 02:56:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-telephone-service-lowers-business-phone-bills/</guid><description>DS1, more commonly known as T1, is a digital telecommunications standard that can potentially save businesses substantial amounts of money on their phone bills. Despite its benefits, many people are unfamiliar with it.
Although the terms are often used interchangeably, there&amp;rsquo;s a slight distinction between DS1 and T1. DS1 (Digital Signal 1) refers to the format of the digital signal transmitted over the line, while T1 describes the physical four-wire copper connection itself.</description></item><item><title>What Does “Five Nines” Mean to You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 11:25:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-does-five-nines-mean-to-you/</guid><description>Authored by John Shepler
Decoding Five Nines: A Look at Reliability The gold standard for traditional phone service and high-end network gear is &amp;ldquo;five nines reliability.&amp;rdquo; But what&amp;rsquo;s the meaning behind this commonly used phrase? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out.
Availability vs. Reliability &amp;ldquo;Five nines&amp;rdquo; translates to 99.999%, a figure often mistaken for reliability. In reality, it represents &amp;ldquo;availability.&amp;rdquo; True availability goes beyond just hardware failures; it encompasses the actual usable time of a system.</description></item><item><title>T1 vs SIP For Business Telephone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-vs-sip-for-business-telephone/</guid><description>Large businesses with high call volumes require different telecommunications solutions compared to small offices. While T1 lines have been the traditional choice, SIP Trunking is emerging as a strong alternative. This article explores the pros and cons of each technology to help businesses make informed decisions.
T1 lines were initially developed by telephone companies to connect central offices and handle numerous calls simultaneously. This technology, using T-carrier standards (T1 and T3), enabled high-capacity call transportation.</description></item><item><title>PRI Phone Line Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 18:42:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pri-phone-line-connections/</guid><description>Analog business phone lines are suitable for small offices and retail spaces that don&amp;rsquo;t need many outside lines. If you require more than six lines, an option like ISDN PRI might be a better fit.
ISDN PRI, which stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface, is a standard for transmitting calls digitally over regular phone lines. It&amp;rsquo;s the larger of two primary options, with the smaller being BRI (Basic Rate Interface).</description></item></channel></rss>