<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Banking on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/banking/</link><description>Recent content in Banking on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/banking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing the most rapid growth for SWIFT</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-the-most-rapid-growth-for-swift/</guid><description>SWIFT, a financial messaging service, has announced a significant increase in new corporate clients from the Asia Pacific region between May and December 2015, with 29 new companies joining the network.
SWIFT provides a unified platform for corporations to communicate financial information with their banks globally, leading to enhanced visibility and more efficient treasury operations. This connection allows for greater automation and standardization of financial processes. Currently, over 1,500 corporate groups, representing roughly 30,000 entities, utilize SWIFT to manage their banking relationships worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Connects Businesses Throughout Latin America</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 06:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-connects-businesses-throughout-latin-america/</guid><description>In recent years, numerous businesses have opted for Carrier Ethernet services for various connectivity needs, including Dedicated Internet Access (DIA), point-to-point private lines, last-mile access to MPLS networks, and meshed connections linking multiple business locations within the United States. This capability is now expanding globally. For instance, Level 3, a prominent international carrier, received recognition from the Metro Ethernet Forum (MEF) for its services in the Caribbean and Latin America.</description></item><item><title>Gaining Entry to the EU's Financial Services Market in the Absence of a Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-entry-to-the-eu-s-financial-services-market-in-the-absence-of-a-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Bartlomiej Kulpa, LLM (Twitter: @KulpaBart)
Introduction
When Boris Johnson became British Prime Minister, a no-deal Brexit appeared increasingly possible. UK-based financial services firms were left wondering if and how they would be able to continue serving clients in the remaining 27 EU countries. These firms currently depend on &amp;ldquo;passporting rights,&amp;rdquo; which allow them to operate across borders. According to The Economist, in 2016, 5,476 British financial services firms used 336,421 European passports to offer their products across the EU.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU going too far by capping bankers' bonuses?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 10:19:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-going-too-far-by-capping-bankers-bonuses/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Public opinion of bankers is currently quite low. Many people attribute the 2008 global financial crisis and the resulting European austerity measures to inadequate banking regulations and irresponsible actions by bankers. This sentiment has fueled a significant reformation of EU banking regulations, including transferring banking supervision to the European Central Bank, establishing new rules for bank bailouts, and creating provisions for criminal penalties against bankers engaged in market abuse.</description></item><item><title>What implications does the climate case against ING have for monetary policy?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 03:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-implications-does-the-climate-case-against-ing-have-for-monetary-policy/</guid><description>Annelieke Mooij, Assistant Professor, Tilburg University
Photo credit: Sandro Halank, via Wikimedia Commons
The Dutch environmental organization “milieudefensie” threatened legal action against ING bank in the Netherlands. On February 14, 2024, ING declared it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t yield to the organization&amp;rsquo;s demands, making a lawsuit highly probable. While seemingly a domestic issue, this case could have significant European implications, particularly for the Monetary Union and the European Central Bank&amp;rsquo;s (ECB) independence.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's ruling in Safe Interenvios addresses issues of money laundering, customer due diligence, and data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:02:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-ruling-in-safe-interenvios-addresses-issues-of-money-laundering-customer-due-diligence-and-data-protection/</guid><description>Marcin Kotula, Legal Officer at the European Commission
The views expressed are purely those of the author and may not in any circumstances be regarded as stating an official position of the European Commission
Background
This analysis examines a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) judgment concerning a case, Safe Interenvios, which originated from a preliminary reference submitted by a Provincial Court in Barcelona. The Barcelona court requested the CJEU to clarify the interpretation of the third Anti-Money Laundering Directive (AML Directive) in relation to a dispute involving a financial institution, Safe Interenvios, and several banks.</description></item><item><title>Global Payout expands MoneyTrac assistance to the Philippines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 12:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-payout-expands-moneytrac-assistance-to-the-philippines/</guid><description>Global Payout, a company that offers business-to-business electronic payment solutions, has expanded its proprietary MoneyTrac consolidated payment gateway (CPG) platform to the Philippines.
MoneyTrac allows users to make secure payments to employees and business partners. Users can configure virtual accounts to meet specific payment needs, sending funds to bank accounts in supported countries, debit cards, credit cards, or even other users on the system.
Bill Rochfort, President and VP of Sales, highlighted the significant opportunity in providing financial services to the Philippines&amp;rsquo; large population, including millions of Filipinos working abroad (OFWs).</description></item><item><title>Challenging the legality of ECB restrictions on Greek bank accounts – and ways you can support the cause</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 07:08:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-the-legality-of-ecb-restrictions-on-greek-bank-accounts-and-ways-you-can-support-the-cause/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Many citizens across the EU have observed the plight of Greeks limited to €60 withdrawals per day with sympathy and apprehension. This situation stems from the European Central Bank (ECB) restricting emergency funds for Greek banks.
Beyond the human cost, the ECB&amp;rsquo;s actions raise serious legal, political, and economic concerns. A core function of any central bank is acting as a last-resort lender for banks, a role the ECB is demonstrably failing to fulfill in this case.</description></item></channel></rss>