<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SIP Trunk on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunk/</link><description>Recent content in SIP Trunk on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sip-trunk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Phone Line Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Every business, regardless of size, requires at least one telephone line. While phone lines may seem straightforward, you might have more choices than you realize. Are you confident that your business has the most suitable phone line?
Plain Old Telephone Service
The traditional analog phone line, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), is a basic and familiar option.
POTS lines are simple, consisting of a single twisted copper pair connecting a standard RJ-11 phone jack on your wall directly to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-line-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted VoIP Solutions Include New Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 09:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</guid><description>Cloud services are changing how we think about technology. Just like server racks are moving to the cloud, so are office phone systems. Traditional PBX systems are being replaced by cloud-hosted solutions. But this transition begs the question: what happens to the physical phone lines?
Similar to connecting data servers off-site, a connection called a SIP Trunk links your on-premise network to the hosted PBX. While it&amp;rsquo;s possible to use existing analog phones with adapters, this approach misses out on the advanced features of Voice over IP (VoIP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-voip-solutions-include-new-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated Bandwidth vs Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</guid><description>Businesses choose dedicated internet services, like T1 lines and Ethernet over Copper, when they prioritize consistent performance and service guarantees, or when shared options aren&amp;rsquo;t available. Cable broadband, on the other hand, attracts businesses with its high bandwidth for a lower cost. Although cable lacks service guarantees, its proven track record and widespread availability, especially during business hours, make it appealing.
The term &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; in this context signifies that a specific bandwidth amount is exclusively allocated to the user...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Services For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 01:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</guid><description>Traditionally, business-grade telecom services rely on physical wires like copper or fiber optics. This often makes IT managers apprehensive when asked for immediate high-bandwidth internet access, point-to-point transmission, or VoIP telephone service, knowing that WAN networking rarely offers instant solutions. However, a solution called fixed wireless service is emerging as a viable option.
Imagine having the same bandwidth services without the need for physical wires. This technology differs significantly from mobile phone services or short-range wireless access points...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-services-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When More Bandwidth Doesn’t Help</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 06:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of this situation: your reliable internet connection, a T1 line or DS3 circuit, has suddenly become sluggish. Your VoIP calls sound distant, employees struggle to work, and frustrated customers can&amp;rsquo;t even communicate properly. The obvious solution seems to be getting more bandwidth, right?
While that seems logical, doubling your internet speed might not solve the problem, leaving you with the same issues and double the cost. Why is that?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-more-bandwidth-doesn-t-help/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Telephone Wiring is a Thing of the Past</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 17:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</guid><description>The traditional telephone network, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), utilizes a vast network of thin copper wires connecting buildings to local telephone exchanges. This system, designed solely for analog communication, efficiently serves businesses using traditional phones and low-speed devices like fax machines.
Imagine two parallel road systems: high-speed freeways representing computer networks and slower county roads symbolizing the telephone network. Coexisting within the same regions, each serves distinct traffic needs...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-telephone-wiring-is-a-thing-of-the-past/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Where Hosted PBX Solutions Save</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</guid><description>Business phone systems vary from basic setups with a handful of phones to sophisticated systems connecting multiple locations. A newer approach, hosted PBX, simplifies things. But do these solutions truly cut costs and maintain call quality?
A single landline represents the simplest scenario, with a fixed monthly fee for unlimited local calls. Long-distance and international calls may involve separate providers or services for cost savings. This basic service, known as POTS (Plain Old Telephone Service), appears straightforward because its complexity resides with the provider, handling the intricate connections for billions of calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/where-hosted-pbx-solutions-save/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is VoIP For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about the benefits of switching from traditional phone services to VoIP, and for good reason. Businesses can gain a lot from enterprise VoIP solutions. However, there are potential downsides to watch out for to ensure a smooth transition. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what VoIP is and how it compares to your current phone service.
One thing that often causes confusion about VoIP is the name itself...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technologies That Should Stay in 2012</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 05:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</guid><description>While technological advancements are incremental, they often force us to upgrade to the latest devices while clinging to older ones for compatibility. Eventually, the old tech fades away, replaced by the new, only for the cycle to repeat itself. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some technologies that are nearing obsolescence.
Analog phone systems are on the verge of disappearing. Their outdated features, lack of mobile compatibility, and proprietary wiring make them impractical. While analog lines offer clear voice quality and affordability for small businesses, their lack of mobility is a dealbreaker...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technologies-that-should-stay-in-2012/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>