<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tangential Arm Assembly on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tangential-arm-assembly/</link><description>Recent content in Tangential Arm Assembly on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tangential-arm-assembly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Reinstalling the Floating Chassis Components</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:07:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-reinstalling-the-floating-chassis-components/</guid><description>All the necessary restoration parts for the Beogram 4002 (Type 5513) turntable are now available, marking the start of the reassembly process.
The reinstallation begins with securing the floating chassis, equipped with the tangential arm assembly, back into the Beogram 4002 cabinet. The process starts by fitting the Beolover replacement suspension lock bushings onto the floating chassis. Subsequently, the suspension locks are positioned within the cabinet base. The floating chassis is then carefully lowered onto these locking bolts, and the remaining locking mechanisms are put in place.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 Type 5513: Going over the chassis and mechanical parts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:28:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-type-5513-going-over-the-chassis-and-mechanical-parts/</guid><description>The two circuit boards that needed component updates are finished. Now, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the Beogram 4002&amp;rsquo;s cabinet and its mechanical parts.
I prefer working on the floating chassis with it removed, which is easier since I&amp;rsquo;ll disassemble most of the tangential arm.
This revealed some hidden issues.
Initially, I believed the three chassis lock bushings were okay because they looked fine. However, examining the locking mechanism showed otherwise.
This was the first indication of the bushings&amp;rsquo; poor condition.</description></item></channel></rss>