<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Twisted Pair on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/twisted-pair/</link><description>Recent content in Twisted Pair on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/twisted-pair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Aktino Sends 90 Mbps Down Copper Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</guid><description>Advancements in technology are challenging the belief that fiber optic cable is necessary for transmitting DS3 or Carrier Ethernet beyond local networks. Aktino, a company based in California, has developed carrier equipment that enhances the performance of traditional unshielded twisted pair copper loops. This technology enables the delivery of DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) or over 90 Mbps of Carrier Ethernet bandwidth over a CSA (Carrier Serving Area) spanning 12,000 feet. Consequently, numerous businesses and cell tower locations, previously limited in terms of connectivity, can now access high bandwidth connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/aktino-sends-90-mbps-down-copper-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Point to Point Dedicated T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 20:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</guid><description>Although a traditional service, point-to-point dedicated T1 lines remain popular. This article examines their functionality and applications.
](http://www.t1t3today.com/) Initially designed for internal use, telephone companies used T1 lines to combine 24 individual analog phone lines into a single digital connection. Their key characteristics included serial digital transmission via a maximum of two twisted pair wires, regeneration to extend transmission distance, fixed private connections between two points, a multiplexing method to separate concurrent calls, and a 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/point-to-point-dedicated-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Is The New Telephone Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</guid><description>For over a century, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard for telephone service, and remarkably, it remains a leading technology today. However, this isn&amp;rsquo;t a simple case of &amp;ldquo;what&amp;rsquo;s old is new again.&amp;rdquo; While the copper wires themselves are familiar, the technology now utilizes digital signals instead of the analog signals of the past.
You might wonder why copper is still relevant in the age of fiber optics. The answer is cost-effectiveness...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-is-the-new-telephone-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Believe 200 Mbps EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 02:53:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is a widely used technology that delivers mid-band Ethernet connections without the delays and costs of fiber optic installation. Although initially considered a temporary solution, EoC has become a strong competitor to fiber services.
](http://www.ethernetovercopper.co/)Businesses currently using T1 lines or considering them are a key market for EoC. T1 is a well-established, dependable, and cost-effective telecom service that offers 1.5 Mbps using one or two pairs of twisted copper telephone wiring...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-believe-200-mbps-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth For Rural Areas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</guid><description>Contrary to popular belief, Ethernet WAN service isn&amp;rsquo;t confined to cities. There are ways to get Ethernet connectivity even in rural areas.
Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity among small and medium businesses. It uses existing telephone wiring to deliver Ethernet speeds from 3 to 50 Mbps, and even over 100 Mbps in some places. This makes it a cost-effective option for businesses that need high bandwidth. However, EoC has distance limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-for-rural-areas/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>