<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Phone System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phone-system/</link><description>Recent content in Phone System on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/phone-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best Way to Manage Your Phone System: Get Rid of It</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 19:42:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
What do all businesses have in common? Telephones. And what&amp;rsquo;s a common need for all business phone systems? Management. But imagine if you could eliminate that burden – wouldn&amp;rsquo;t that be fantastic and give your business a competitive edge? It certainly could. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why, and more importantly, how.
The Problem with Traditional Phone Systems
The traditional business phone is a bulky piece of equipment, filled with analog technology and tethered to the phone company with its own dedicated line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/best-way-to-manage-your-phone-system-get-rid-of-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rise Of The Cloud Hosted PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 21:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</guid><description>Traditional, in-house PBX systems might be nearing obsolescence with the emergence of cloud-hosted solutions like AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s AirePBX. This innovation signifies a return to an older model where the service provider manages the switching system, but with modern technological advancements.
This shift back to provider-managed systems, reminiscent of early telephone networks, offers significant cost advantages due to increased competition and the use of existing network infrastructure for VoIP services. Businesses no longer need to invest in separate wiring or proprietary equipment, leading to more competitive offerings and feature-rich options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rise-of-the-cloud-hosted-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fonality Call Center in a Box</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</guid><description>Thinking about starting a call center but worried about the initial expenses and complex setup? While a large-scale call center requires significant investment, there are solutions for businesses looking to add call center capabilities or start small and gradually expand. Fonality offers a &amp;ldquo;call center in a box&amp;rdquo; solution, providing a simplified yet robust system.
This solution utilizes an off-the-shelf PC tower functioning as a Linux server, with the option to upgrade to a rack-mount server for increased capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>