<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CNY on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cny/</link><description>Recent content in CNY on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:44:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick reference guide for Chinese New Year in the Year of the Water Tiger</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 18:44:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</guid><description>In 2022, the ox replaces the rat as the third animal in the 12-year Chinese zodiac cycle, bringing hope for positive change. Chinese New Year commences on February 1st, ushering in a period of customary greetings and well wishes.
A wish for plentiful business opportunities.
生意兴隆.
Common greetings include &amp;ldquo;Happy New Year&amp;rdquo; (新年快乐, xin nian kuai le) and &amp;ldquo;Congratulations on receiving riches and prosperity&amp;rdquo; (恭喜发财, gong xi fa cai). Prosperity holds significant value in Chinese culture, particularly during Chinese New Year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-reference-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-water-tiger/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Azerai reveals special promotions for Chinese New Year in 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 07:43:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</guid><description>Source: Azerai. Exterior, Hue. Constructed in 1930 as the residence of the French Resident Superieure, this colonial mansion forms the hotel&amp;rsquo;s heart. The mansion&amp;rsquo;s noticeable facade, characterized by its elongated horizontal lines and nautical motifs, is a testament to Art Deco architectural style. Its two harmonious wings, home to a vast tropical garden and a saltwater pool, were constructed in 2005, reflecting a modern take on Art Deco.
Azerai has unveiled special offers and activities for Chinese New Year at its Vietnamese properties...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/azerai-reveals-special-promotions-for-chinese-new-year-in-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel's 2022 Chinese New Year film features the Angs and the Huangs facing off on Sentosa with the addition of 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 23:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Poster for The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger, Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Chinese New Year festive film for 2022.
To celebrate the Year of the Tiger and the values of family and community central to the holiday, Singtel has released its annual Chinese New Year short film. The Hunt for the Lucky Tiger is the third installment in a series of films by Singtel featuring the amusing rivalry between two families...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-s-2022-chinese-new-year-film-features-the-angs-and-the-huangs-facing-off-on-sentosa-with-the-addition-of-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick guide for Chinese New Year in the year of the rat</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</guid><description>The rat is associated with a new 12-year cycle in the Chinese zodiac. Legend has it that a race among all the animals determined which twelve would be featured in the zodiac. The animals finished in the following order: rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon, snake, horse, goat, monkey, rooster, dog, and pig. This sequence dictates the order of the animals in the zodiac.
The rat is generally agreed to be very clever...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-the-year-of-the-rat/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo unveils a retail sales guide for Chinese New Year in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 02:48:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</guid><description>Criteo, a commerce media company, has unveiled insights from the 2022 Chinese New Year (CNY) to help retailers anticipate consumer demand and leverage similar trends in 2023.
Starting in January 2022, retail sales surpassed typical levels (based on the average between December 18th and 31st, 2021) until a week prior to CNY 2022 (February 1st), indicating a strong consumer appetite for purchasing. In Southeast Asia (SEA), retail sales hit a peak of 27% on January 25th, a week before CNY...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-unveils-a-retail-sales-guide-for-chinese-new-year-in-2023/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Experience the joyous abundance at PARKROYAL COLLECTION Marina Bay, Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/</guid><description>PARKROYAL COLLECTION Marina Bay, Singapore, celebrates the Year of the Dragon with &amp;ldquo;Jubilant Abundance,&amp;rdquo; featuring traditional feasts and an array of Chinese New Year delicacies.
Peach Blossoms
Peach Blossoms presents modern Chinese cuisine rooted in classic Cantonese flavors. For Lunar New Year, enjoy six special set menus, including the seven-course &amp;ldquo;Blessings&amp;rdquo; menu at S$2,388 per table of 10, and the six-course &amp;ldquo;Year of the Dragon Imperial&amp;rdquo; menu at S$398++ per person...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-joyous-abundance-at-parkroyal-collection-marina-bay-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DBS/POSB introduces Chinese New Year service offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 12:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</guid><description>To celebrate the Year of the Rabbit, DBS/POSB is expanding its blended digital and physical (&amp;ldquo;phygital&amp;rdquo;) Chinese New Year (CNY) gifting and rewards programs.
This CNY, customers can take advantage of the following:
Conveniently order DBS QR Gift cards (QR AngBaos) through the bank&amp;rsquo;s chatbot, digibot, and have them delivered before CNY.
A chance to win a Tesla Model 3 and other rewards, including cash rebates, by switching to QR Gift and other DBS/POSB digital transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dbs-posb-introduces-chinese-new-year-service-offerings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sanya EDITION is preparing for Chinese New Year 2020</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</guid><description>Source: The Sanya EDITION.
In anticipation of the Chinese New Year, The Sanya EDITION presents two unique offerings that provide a genuine experience of Chinese culture.
Guests can immerse themselves in culture and history through The Sanya EDITION&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with the Forbidden City. This partnership features a temporary shop and exhibit highlighting fine arts and teas. Those with a passion for cuisine will enjoy the luxurious interpretations of Chinese dishes prepared by world-renowned Michelin-starred chefs, specially invited by The Sanya EDITION for the celebratory period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sanya-edition-is-preparing-for-chinese-new-year-2020/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Quick guide to Chinese New Year for the Year of the Pig</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 22:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</guid><description>The Lunar New Year period is a time when Chinese communities are filled with a palpable sense of celebration. Vibrant red decorations, believed to bring good luck, are prominently displayed, and the atmosphere is alive with the melodies of traditional festive music. The Chinese New Year, which falls on February 5th in 2019, is a time when well-wishes are exchanged, particularly during the first fifteen days of the lunar year...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/quick-guide-to-chinese-new-year-for-the-year-of-the-pig/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Soar to new heights with Lunar New Year festivities at the Pan Pacific Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:06:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/</guid><description>Source: Pan Pacific Singapore. The image displays two of the yusheng choices offered for the Lunar New Year in 2024.
From January 1st to February 25th, 2024, Pan Pacific Singapore presents Lunar New Year specialties designed to bring prosperity.
Hai Tien Lo (海天楼)
This acclaimed restaurant serves refined Cantonese cuisine with modern influences. Throughout the Lunar New Year season, Hai Tien Lo will emphasize its celebratory menus: Set menus - January 22nd to February 25th..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/soar-to-new-heights-with-lunar-new-year-festivities-at-the-pan-pacific-singapore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the trend for 2020 sustainable red packets?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 19:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. Orange/bottle carrier (left) with sustainable
hongbaos middle and right.
For the year 2020, Singtel chose to prioritize sustainability with their red envelope (hongbao) design. Instead of traditional paper, they opted for a material derived from sugarcane stalks after juice extraction.
Two designs were created. The first displays the character 欣, signifying &amp;ldquo;happiness and prosperity&amp;rdquo;. The second features a Chinese couplet, 竞发无极添新彩, 欣荣丰盛增辉煌, translating to &amp;ldquo;delight, happiness, progress with superior competitive advantage, bursting with exciting changes and new opportunities&amp;rdquo;...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-trend-for-2020-sustainable-red-packets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Carlton Hotel Singapore reveals its promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 22:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Source: Carlton Hotel Singapore. The Carlton Hotel is offering special dining options for the 2024 Lunar New Year celebration.
The Carlton Hotel Singapore welcomes the Lunar New Year with exclusive dining experiences available at Wah Lok Cantonese Restaurant, take-away options, and more.
Wah Lok Cantonese Restaurant presents six Lunar New Year set menus from January 29th to February 24th, 2024. Prices begin at S$468++ for four people. A new menu, &amp;ldquo;Happiness 年年有余,&amp;rdquo; is available for S$1,348++ for eight guests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-carlton-hotel-singapore-reveals-its-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Observe the fireworks display on February 11 at the Regent Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</guid><description>For the Lunar New Year, The Regent Hong Kong offers various culinary experiences:
Hong Kong Cuisine 1983
Celebrate with symbolic à la carte dishes (HK$468 to HK$980) like Lohei (HK$580) for prosperity, prawns in salted egg yolk (HK$580) for wealth, and braised Wagyu beef cheek (HK$980) for strength. Their HK$438 Good Fortune Turnip Cake Gift Box contains two 800g turnip cakes, one traditional and one smoked with tea leaves, sugarcane, imperatae, and brown sugar...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>