<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Payables on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payables/</link><description>Recent content in Payables on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:52:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/payables/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zero Dollar Checks and Mekorma MICR are both essential tools for managing your finances effectively.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 11:52:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</guid><description>I recently encountered a situation with zero-dollar checks and Mekorma MICR software. To clarify, Dynamics GP software generates zero-dollar checks when an invoice is fully paid through methods like credit memos or manual payments. This often happens before a check run or when opting for automatic application of unapplied documents during check runs.
These zero-dollar checks, appearing on the edit list after a check batch is created, act as placeholders, allowing for a remittance advice to be printed within the check run, confirming the invoice was settled using existing credits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zero-dollar-checks-and-mekorma-micr-are-both-essential-tools-for-managing-your-finances-effectively/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Please don't end my year...</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</guid><description>Let&amp;rsquo;s debunk some common misconceptions about year-end closing in Dynamics GP:
Myth #1: All adjusting entries must be finalized before closing the General Ledger.
This is false. Dynamics GP allows posting to the most recent historical year. After closing 2009, for instance, adjustments can still be made to it, just not to 2008. This requires enabling &amp;ldquo;allow posting to history&amp;rdquo; in GL setup and ensuring the fiscal period is open in Fiscal Period Setup...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/please-don-t-end-my-year/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover this hidden gem by reviewing the distribution report.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 22:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/</guid><description>Need a way to see which invoices were paid by a specific check, or view the payment details for those invoices? Users often ask for this information, but it can be tricky to find in Microsoft Dynamics GP. The SmartList feature isn&amp;rsquo;t ideal (unless you have SmartList Builder and even then, it takes some setup) because one check can pay multiple invoices.
A simple solution, especially if you don&amp;rsquo;t have SmartList Builder, is the Check Distribution Report...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-this-hidden-gem-by-reviewing-the-distribution-report/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>