<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Facebook on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/facebook/</link><description>Recent content in Facebook on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/facebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Facebook enhances the Messenger chat platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:28:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-enhances-the-messenger-chat-platform/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
During Facebook&amp;rsquo;s F8 conference, the company launched Messenger Platform. With over 40 apps available for download, users can enhance their conversations through GIFs, photos, videos, audio clips, and more.
Source: Facebook. Users will be prompted to install new apps.
Source: Facebook. Messenger will allow businesses and customers to communicate directly, replacing traditional methods like email or phone calls.
Facebook also provided a sneak peek of Businesses on Messenger.</description></item><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation.</description></item><item><title>Could Data Protection be Returning Home? The CJEU's Ruling on Data Protection Law in Relation to Jehovah's Witnesses and Political Canvassing.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:24:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-data-protection-be-returning-home-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-data-protection-law-in-relation-to-jehovah-s-witnesses-and-political-canvassing/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re showering when the doorbell unexpectedly interrupts. Hoping it&amp;rsquo;s the anticipated Amazon delivery with a birthday gift for your daughter, you rush downstairs, only to find a pair of Jehovah&amp;rsquo;s Witnesses.
After dismissing their pleas, you close the door, putting the encounter out of your mind. However, they haven&amp;rsquo;t forgotten you. To maintain their focus on potential converts, they keep records of visited homes, categorizing residents as &amp;ldquo;Believer,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Unbeliever,&amp;rdquo; or perhaps even &amp;ldquo;Satanist,&amp;rdquo; depending on your towel situation.</description></item><item><title>Facebook claims that only native and video advertisements provide substantial value</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:07:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-claims-that-only-native-and-video-advertisements-provide-substantial-value/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Head of Ad Tech, Dave Jakubowski, recently stated that exchanges and banners lack significant value in a blog post. He highlights that Facebook conducted a test using &amp;ldquo;a buying platform&amp;rdquo; within Atlas, their ad solution. The test revealed that despite reaching real people accurately, many ads were low-quality or fraudulent.
Although effective in removing these poor ads, Facebook was surprised by the sheer volume of ineffective inventory. The test also demonstrated that only native and video ad formats yielded substantial value.</description></item><item><title>Is EU data protection law violated by Facebook and the USA? The CJEU hearing in Schrems.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-eu-data-protection-law-violated-by-facebook-and-the-usa-the-cjeu-hearing-in-schrems/</guid><description>Simon McGarr, a solicitor at McGarr Solicitors, provides an overview of the Schrems v Data Protection Commissioner case heard by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The case revolves around Austrian law student Max Schrems&amp;rsquo; legal challenge concerning the transfer of his personal data from Facebook to the United States. Schrems argues that such transfers violate his data privacy rights due to the risk of mass surveillance under US law.</description></item><item><title>Letv reaches one million Facebook likes within two months</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:12:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/letv-reaches-one-million-facebook-likes-within-two-months/</guid><description>Source: Socialbakers.
Letv, a company that has yet to formally debut in India, has already amassed a following of one million on Facebook in just 60 days. According to Socialbakers, Letv is currently the top and fastest-growing phone brand page in India. In contrast, it took Xiaomi India more than 400 days to achieve the same milestone*.
Over the past month, Letv has consistently ranked high in Facebook popularity, rivaling established brands like HTC, Motorola, Lava, Vivo, and Xiaomi in India.</description></item><item><title>In 2014, Facebook dominated the social network advertising market in terms of spending</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 20:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2014-facebook-dominated-the-social-network-advertising-market-in-terms-of-spending/</guid><description>In 2014, global spending on social network advertising saw a 41% increase, reaching over US$15.3 billion and representing 11% of all digital ad spending, according to a Global Social Network Forecast from Strategy Analytics. Facebook dominated this sector, securing three-quarters of global social network ad spend, while Twitter captured 8%. Projections for 2015 anticipate continued growth in social network ad spending, estimated to reach US$24.2 billion, a 29% rise.
Leika Kawasaki, the report&amp;rsquo;s author, highlights the robust expansion of the social network market across all regions.</description></item><item><title>The impact of Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein v. Wirtschaftsakademie Schleswig-Holstein GmbH on Facebook fan pages and EU data protection regulations.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 03:43:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-unabh-ngiges-landeszentrum-f-r-datenschutz-schleswig-holstein-v-wirtschaftsakademie-schleswig-holstein-gmbh-on-facebook-fan-pages-and-eu-data-protection-regulations/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
Case Summary
The Wirtschaftsakademie, a business using a Facebook fanpage, was ordered by the Unabhängiges Landeszentrum für Datenschutz Schleswig-Holstein (ULD), a German data protection authority, to deactivate their page. The ULD argued that the page failed to warn visitors about potential data collection by Facebook through cookies.
This case highlights the benefits and data implications associated with Facebook fanpages. Page administrators benefit from free, anonymous user statistics through &amp;ldquo;Facebook Insights,&amp;rdquo; while Facebook gathers data for targeted advertising.</description></item><item><title>The 'Save' feature is a new addition to Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:35:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-save-feature-is-a-new-addition-to-facebook/</guid><description>Facebook has launched a new feature allowing users to save items they find on the platform for later viewing. According to a July 21st blog post, savable content includes links, locations, movies, TV shows, and music.
This &amp;ldquo;Save&amp;rdquo; feature will be rolled out globally across iOS, Android, and web platforms in the coming days.
Source: Facebook blog.
Facebook Software Engineer Daniel Giambalvo, the author of the blog post, emphasizes that saved items remain private unless a user chooses to share them with friends.</description></item><item><title>The Zakat Fund in the UAE uses social media to inform and engage with the public</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 15:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-zakat-fund-in-the-uae-uses-social-media-to-inform-and-engage-with-the-public/</guid><description>To enhance public understanding of zakat and promote transparency, the UAE&amp;rsquo;s Zakat Fund is leveraging social media to engage with the public.
According to H.H Abdullah ibn Aqeedah Al Muhairy, Secretary-General of the Zakat Fund, the organization is utilizing platforms like Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Instagram, and Google+. This allows the public to stay informed about current activities and initiatives, and provides an avenue for inquiries, announcements, and feedback. The Zakat Fund is responsible for collecting and distributing zakat and charitable donations according to the eight Islamic categories.</description></item><item><title>Understand your social media presence with Socialbakers' Social Health Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:39:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understand-your-social-media-presence-with-socialbakers-social-health-index/</guid><description>Socialbakers, a company specializing in social media analytics and optimization, has launched its Social Health Index, a tool created in collaboration with Lenovo. This industry benchmark offers brands a single metric to assess their social marketing performance across multiple platforms. It allows them to effortlessly measure their overall social media presence and compare it to their competitors over a period of time.
Jan Rezab, CEO and Co-Founder of Socialbakers, stated that the Social Health Index is the first benchmark of its kind, providing context to brands&amp;rsquo; social marketing efforts.</description></item><item><title>Identifying gender through Facebook posts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 20:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/identifying-gender-through-facebook-posts/</guid><description>A 2013 study featured in the research journal Plos One reveals that language use in social media can indicate a user&amp;rsquo;s gender and age. The study, &amp;ldquo;Personality, Gender, and Age in the Language of Social Media: The Open-Vocabulary Approach,&amp;rdquo; found that men and women choose distinct words and phrases online. Location and age also factor into language choices.
Singapore bank DBS&amp;rsquo; lucky red packets
The study&amp;rsquo;s authors, from the University of Pennsylvania and University of Cambridge, noted that women tend to express emotions using words like &amp;ldquo;love,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;wonderful,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;excited.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item><item><title>In 2015, Facebook highlighted the things that caught the world's interest</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 06:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2015-facebook-highlighted-the-things-that-caught-the-world-s-interest/</guid><description>Source: Facebook.
Facebook recently unveiled its &amp;ldquo;Year in Review&amp;rdquo; for 2015, featuring a dedicated website and video.
The company highlighted major global conversations, with the US presidential election taking the lead. This was followed by discussions surrounding the November 13 Paris attacks, the Syrian civil war and resulting refugee crisis, the Nepal earthquakes, and the Greek debt crisis.
On the entertainment front, &amp;ldquo;Game of Thrones&amp;rdquo; reigned supreme as the most popular TV show, while &amp;ldquo;Star Wars: The Force Awakens&amp;rdquo; dominated movie discussions globally.</description></item><item><title>A democratic option to the Digital Services Act's collaboration between governments and online platforms in addressing disinformation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 09:22:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-democratic-option-to-the-digital-services-act-s-collaboration-between-governments-and-online-platforms-in-addressing-disinformation/</guid><description>By Paul De Hert* and Andrés Chomczyk Penedo**
* Professor at Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium) and associate professor at Tilburg University (The Netherlands)
** PhD Researcher at the Law, Science, Technology and Society Research Group, Vrije Universiteit Brussel (Belgium). Marie Skłodowska-Curie fellow at the PROTECT ITN. The author has received funding from the European Union’s Horizon 2020 research and innovation programme under the Marie Skłodowska-Curie grant agreement No 813497</description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data.</description></item><item><title>Backing Down In The Face of Twitter</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:20:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-down-in-the-face-of-twitter/</guid><description>At the end of 2011, major companies like GoDaddy and Verizon Wireless faced significant public backlash that caused them to reverse recently announced decisions. GoDaddy quickly backpedaled on their support for SOPA after online outrage, while Verizon abandoned their plan to charge a $2 payment fee due to public outcry and potential FCC involvement. These incidents, while seemingly isolated, point to a larger pattern found in other events from the past year.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor releases list of highest-rated companies for their culture and values</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 22:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-releases-list-of-highest-rated-companies-for-their-culture-and-values/</guid><description>Glassdoor, a website that collects workplace insights from employees, has released its list of the top 25 companies for culture and values. Several well-known companies in the Asia Pacific region are featured.
Twitter secured the top spot with a 4.5-star rating, with one employee calling it &amp;ldquo;the best place I have ever worked.&amp;rdquo; PR agency Edelman followed closely behind with a 4.4-star rating, described by an employee as &amp;ldquo;the only agency I will ever work for.</description></item><item><title>Free E-Books to Get More Sales Leads</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-e-books-to-get-more-sales-leads/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive market, businesses face constant pressure to attract and retain customers. Finding new customers is crucial for growth, as a lack of fresh leads can cause a business to stagnate and eventually fail. Companies that can&amp;rsquo;t adapt to changing market conditions risk being overtaken by more agile competitors or innovative startups.
To help your business thrive, we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled a list of free ebooks offering valuable insights on enhancing sales and marketing strategies in the age of social media:</description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory.</description></item><item><title>Facebook introduces a user-friendly, streamlined video advertising format</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 10:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-introduces-a-user-friendly-streamlined-video-advertising-format/</guid><description>Over one-third of mobile internet users in Saudi Arabia are receptive to video advertisements, exceeding the global average of 22%.
Facebook is introducing &amp;ldquo;Slideshow,&amp;rdquo; a new, user-friendly video ad format designed to increase reach across various devices and connection speeds.
In a blog post announcing Slideshow, Facebook highlights a recent report indicating that people in regions like the Philippines, where connectivity can be slow, costly, or both, and where feature phones are common, are even more receptive to video ads.</description></item><item><title>Asia Miles has launched a new Facebook travel game specifically designed for travelers in Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 12:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asia-miles-has-launched-a-new-facebook-travel-game-specifically-designed-for-travelers-in-hong-kong/</guid><description>Asia Miles members in Hong Kong have the opportunity to win 100,000 miles this month. To participate, visit the Asia Miles Facebook page and find the post featuring travel tips for Taipei from social media influencer Ming Jai (Ming 仔).
Participants are asked to identify two Asia Miles categories that apply to Ming Jai&amp;rsquo;s itinerary. Then, they need to design an additional day of travel in Taipei with a budget of HK$5,000 or less, incorporating at least three categories for earning miles.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU interprets the e-commerce Directive regarding Facebook's responsibility for defamatory posts.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, several legal decisions have addressed how individuals can control their information online. Two cases, GC et al and Google v CNIL, focused on how search engines should interpret their obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This post will focus on a third case, Glawischnig-Piesczek v Facebook, which examined how the e-Commerce Directive&amp;rsquo;s prohibition on general monitoring applies to &amp;ldquo;stay down&amp;rdquo; notices. The case raises a broader question about the consistency of different internet regulations, including those related to intellectual property, child exploitation, and terrorism.</description></item><item><title>'The Right to Erase Personal Data': Upcoming EU legislation begins to form</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 01:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-right-to-erase-personal-data-upcoming-eu-legislation-begins-to-form/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The strong reaction to the ‘right to be forgotten’ in EU data protection law is focused on the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in the Google Spain case. This judgment indirectly established the right by interpreting the existing EU data protection directive. However, this ruling&amp;rsquo;s impact could be limited since the EU is in the process of replacing that directive.
The European Commission presented the first draft of the new General Data Protection Regulation in early 2012, and the European Parliament (EP) voted on it this past spring.</description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002.</description></item><item><title>Consumer law and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): Case C-319/20 involving Facebook Ireland - Advocate General's opinion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 05:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Facts
The Federation of German Consumer Organisations initiated legal proceedings in German courts against Facebook. They claimed that Facebook violated data protection rules by failing to provide sufficient information about data collection practices related to free, third-party games offered on its platform. The Federation argued that this also infringed upon unfair competition and consumer protection regulations. The case reached the Bundesgerischtshof, which raised concerns about the Federation&amp;rsquo;s legal standing to bring the action following the implementation of the GDPR.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v.</description></item><item><title>Integrating Social Media And Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 06:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrating-social-media-and-reality/</guid><description>We navigate two distinct realms: the digital sphere of communication, online activities, and social media, and the physical world of tangible experiences, relationships, and work. Although these realms overlap, their connection has been tenuous until recently.
Poken has emerged as a solution to bridge this gap between the digital and physical. As expected, it comprises both physical and virtual elements.
The tangible aspect is a device called Poken, resembling a digital avatar or a flash drive.</description></item><item><title>Facebook Singapore has established an office that is truly local and fosters creativity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 12:14:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/facebook-singapore-has-established-an-office-that-is-truly-local-and-fosters-creativity/</guid><description>Facebook&amp;rsquo;s new South Beach office embodies its transparent and interconnected work environment. Local culture and unique design elements are woven into the fabric of the Singapore office.
Numerous pantries, meeting spaces, and snack areas provide ample opportunities for casual conversation and networking. One such area features a snack stand designed as a traditional pushcart, with treats presented in bamboo steamers.
A Facebook-themed mahjong table offers another avenue for fostering connections and spontaneous interactions.</description></item><item><title>Instagram outperformed Facebook during the Rio 2016 Olympics</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 01:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instagram-outperformed-facebook-during-the-rio-2016-olympics/</guid><description>Source: ComScore. Social network interactions between Facebook and Instagram for July 2016 around the Olympic games, which ran from 5 to 21 August.
ComScore, a media measurement company, found that Instagram was the top platform for engagement during the 2016 Rio Olympics, even though Facebook, its parent company, was primarily used for pre-event official content sharing.
In June, the UK ranked third globally in unique visitors to the official Rio Olympics website (RIO2016.</description></item><item><title>A case involving Facebook, defamation, and free speech is currently pending in the CJEU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 20:47:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-case-involving-facebook-defamation-and-free-speech-is-currently-pending-in-the-cjeu/</guid><description>Preliminary Notes on the Pending Case Glawischnig-Piesczek v. Facebook Ireland Limited
Dr Paolo Cavaliere, University of Edinburgh Law School, paolo.cavaliere@ed.ac.uk
Introduction
The Court of Justice of the European Union will soon release a potentially groundbreaking decision regarding political speech and internet platform liability. The court will address two related but distinct issues: the extent of platforms&amp;rsquo; responsibility to remove illegal content, specifically if it applies to content similar to posts previously deemed unlawful, and whether such obligations apply beyond the court&amp;rsquo;s jurisdiction.</description></item></channel></rss>