<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legal Migration on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/legal-migration/</link><description>Recent content in Legal Migration on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/legal-migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Integration requirements for family reunification: the CJEU restricts the autonomy of Member States.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integration-requirements-for-family-reunification-the-cjeu-restricts-the-autonomy-of-member-states/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In recent times, many EU member states have started requiring non-EU citizens to pass an integration test before they can be reunited with their families in the EU. The EU&amp;rsquo;s family reunification rules allow for this, stating that family members joining non-EU citizens &amp;ldquo;may be required to comply with integration measures.&amp;rdquo; However, for family members of refugees and highly skilled migrants with EU Blue Cards, these tests can only be applied after they arrive.</description></item><item><title>Strategy on immigration policy in the EU by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</guid><description>This is an unofficial preview of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s communication on the EU migration agenda, scheduled for release on May 13th. Please be aware that the content may change before publication and may be incomplete.
I. Introduction
Migration has been a constant throughout human history, driven by a range of factors such as political oppression, war, poverty, opportunity, and family reunification. Each migrant&amp;rsquo;s story is unique, and their movement has diverse impacts on society, necessitating a variety of responses.</description></item><item><title>The initial ruling by the CJEU on integration requirements for third-country nationals.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-initial-ruling-by-the-cjeu-on-integration-requirements-for-third-country-nationals/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice recently addressed whether Member States can mandate integration courses for immigrants in the case of P and S, which involved the EU Directive on long-term residence for non-EU citizens. This decision has broader implications because similar integration requirements exist in other EU directives, such as the one concerning family reunification for non-EU citizens. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that EU free movement law does not allow Member States to impose such conditions on EU citizens or their families.</description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal.</description></item><item><title>Putting an end to the exploitation of seasonal workers: EU legislation targets the easiest issues.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-the-exploitation-of-seasonal-workers-eu-legislation-targets-the-easiest-issues/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 15:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/putting-an-end-to-the-exploitation-of-seasonal-workers-eu-legislation-targets-the-easiest-issues/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU struggled to create legislation regarding migrant workers from outside the EU. Member States finally agreed on laws focused on higher-income migrants: the Blue Card Directive and the Directive on intra-corporate transferees. The EU also established general rules for admitting labor migrants with the single permit Directive.
In a new development, the EU introduced rules for lower-paid seasonal workers last year. This group is particularly susceptible to exploitation.</description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals.</description></item><item><title>What are the reasons behind the ineffectiveness of the Blue Card Directive for highly-skilled workers, and what solutions can be implemented to improve its functionality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 18:38:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-are-the-reasons-behind-the-ineffectiveness-of-the-blue-card-directive-for-highly-skilled-workers-and-what-solutions-can-be-implemented-to-improve-its-functionality/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 2009, the EU introduced the ‘Blue Card’ Directive to attract highly qualified individuals from non-EU countries. As part of a broader strategy for legal immigration, this Directive is crucial. However, a recent Commission assessment suggests that the Directive has not effectively reached its goals. This raises the question of necessary revisions for improvement.
Implementing the Directive
While all EU Member States obligated to implement the Directive have done so, the actual impact has been underwhelming.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU has made a ruling on the loss of immigration status for residents who are absent from the territory.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-has-made-a-ruling-on-the-loss-of-immigration-status-for-residents-who-are-absent-from-the-territory/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Individuals can lose their immigration status if they are absent from the country that granted it for a specific duration. However, a recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruling explored the impact of short interruptions during this absence. The case focused on long-term EU resident status for non-EU citizens, which could have implications for those under EU free movement law and the Brexit withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ rules on discrimination against Italian families in accessing benefits</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 13:34:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-rules-on-discrimination-against-italian-families-in-accessing-benefits/</guid><description>Virginia Passalacqua, post-doctoral researcher in EU law, Utrecht University
Italy presents a paradoxical situation: while offering substantial financial aid to wealthy families upon the birth of a child, the nation provides no support to non-EU domestic workers employed by those same families when they have children. This disparity highlights the systemic discrimination embedded in Italian legislation over the past two decades, disproportionately impacting foreign families who experience significantly higher poverty rates compared to their Italian counterparts.</description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths.</description></item><item><title>The Council's stance on the Directive for long-term residents is a serious consideration of rights being taken away.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 20:13:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-s-stance-on-the-directive-for-long-term-residents-is-a-serious-consideration-of-rights-being-taken-away/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: JLogan, via Wikimedia commons
While the European Commission and Parliament aim to enhance the legal standing of long-term non-EU residents within the EU, the Council&amp;rsquo;s approach generally weakens their position, especially regarding acquiring long-term residency. This stance follows the Council&amp;rsquo;s recent agreement on a May 2022 Commission proposal for a revised directive on this matter (contrasting with the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s position from spring 2023), meant to replace the existing 2003 Directive (previously amended in 2010 to encompass those with refugee or subsidiary protection).</description></item><item><title>Mr. Avramopolous travels to Brussels: reflections on the European Parliament hearing for the new Migration Commissioner</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/mr-avramopolous-travels-to-brussels-reflections-on-the-european-parliament-hearing-for-the-new-migration-commissioner/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Throughout his extensive three-hour hearing at the European Parliament, Dimitris Avramopolous, the nominee for Commissioner for migration and home affairs, consistently emphasized his commitment to liberal values. He expressed strong support for upholding the Schengen system, adopting a liberal stance on asylum and legal migration, and protecting the freedom of movement for EU citizens. However, he fell short of providing specifics on the implementation of these principles and how the various facets of EU policy in this domain would harmonize.</description></item><item><title>Additional research is required to further explore the EU's efforts to attract a greater number of non-EU researchers and students.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU member states, similar to other economically advanced nations, require a growing number of highly skilled workers. Current EU regulations have not significantly increased the influx of students and researchers from other countries, prompting the Commission to propose revisions in 2013. Both the European Parliament (EP) and the Council have agreed on their respective stances for the proposed law and are preparing to negotiate a final version.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member.</description></item><item><title>Will the new Directive on intra-corporate transferees improve the safeguarding of third-country nationals and bolster EU competitiveness?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</guid><description>Lucia Brieskova, PhD candidate at Oxford Brookes University
This post examines the new EU Intra-Corporate Transfers Directive (ICTD) concerning legal economic migration. This analysis is divided into three parts. First, it explains the background and motivation behind introducing this Directive and its connection to other EU directives on economic migration. Second, it outlines the key changes this Directive brings. Finally, it highlights potential issues that will be analyzed in future posts.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: EU Commission's Proposal for Long-Term Resident Non-EU Citizens and Poundshop Free Movement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 18:15:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-2-eu-commission-s-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-and-poundshop-free-movement/</guid><description>The free movement of people within the EU, a fundamental principle, generally applies to EU citizens and citizens of countries with specific agreements. However, EU immigration law allows for limited mobility of non-EU citizens within member states under stricter conditions. This article explores whether these limitations create a &amp;ldquo;discount&amp;rdquo; version of free movement for non-EU citizens.
One such measure is the EU long-term resident (LTR) status for non-EU citizens, established in 2003 and amended in 2010.</description></item><item><title>The EU Commission's new proposal for long-term resident non-EU citizens (part 1)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 17:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-commission-s-new-proposal-for-long-term-resident-non-eu-citizens-part-1/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Photo credit: Marcomob, via Wikimedia commons
The EU has a longstanding interest in regulating the legal status of non-EU citizens residing long-term within its Member States as part of its broader legal migration policy. The current law, a 2003 Directive amended in 2010, focuses on extending rights to those with refugee or subsidiary protection status. A recent Commission proposal aims to further expand the rights of this large group of non-EU citizens.</description></item></channel></rss>