<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WAN Links on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-links/</link><description>Recent content in WAN Links on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wan-links/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>