<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sdwan on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sdwan/</link><description>Recent content in Sdwan on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sdwan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Managed SD-WAN Can Help Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Going digital can be great for business until you hit roadblocks trying to make it work. One of these unexpected hurdles is the need for way more internet bandwidth than you anticipated. You can struggle to make it work without going bankrupt, or you can use managed SD-WAN to make your connectivity invisible.
Why Is Connectivity Such a Big Deal Now?
When your business was primarily physical, a standard broadband connection for internet access was probably enough...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-managed-sd-wan-can-help-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>