<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GigE Port on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige-port/</link><description>Recent content in GigE Port on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/gige-port/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fiber Internet Availability and Lower Prices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time for businesses to switch from traditional wireline internet to fiber optic service. You might be surprised how accessible and affordable fiber internet has become.
Fiber Optic Internet: What&amp;rsquo;s New?
A decade ago, fiber optic internet was only for large corporations due to its high cost. The service, primarily offered by major telephone companies, was limited in availability and very expensive.
This has changed drastically. Today, Ethernet has become the most popular fiber optic service, with prices comparable to older T1 or T3 lines while offering significantly more bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-internet-availability-and-lower-prices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why You Want A GigE Port</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 12:44:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</guid><description>Is it difficult to predict your future bandwidth requirements? You might be aware of your current traffic levels, but what about tomorrow, next week, or during peak seasons like holidays? How can you plan for the unknown?
Inaccurate bandwidth estimations can lead to overspending on unused capacity or, even worse, business losses due to insufficient bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to optimize your bandwidth allocation.
Traditional telecom services often come with lengthy installation and upgrade processes, making them inflexible...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-you-want-a-gige-port/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>