<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TCA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tca/</link><description>Recent content in TCA on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/tca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Opinion of the Legal Service of the Council on the Brexit agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:59:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</guid><description>This document presents the EU Council legal service&amp;rsquo;s analysis of whether the Brexit deal requires approval from both the EU and its Member States (a &amp;lsquo;mixed agreement&amp;rsquo;), or solely from the EU. It concludes that the EU can act alone due to the deal encompassing a blend of exclusive EU competences and competences shared between the EU and its member states. This aligns with Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) case law, which allows the EU to enact a treaty encompassing shared competences either independently or jointly with its Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-the-legal-service-of-the-council-on-the-brexit-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extradition from Ireland to the UK post-Brexit: examining the extent of EU authority</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 23:14:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Brexit&amp;rsquo;s legal ramifications are vast and multifaceted. For the first time since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) will address these implications, at least from the EU&amp;rsquo;s perspective.
A recent opinion from a CJEU Advocate General provides insight into expedited questions referred by the Irish Supreme Court (following an appeal from the Irish High Court). This case concerns extradition from Ireland to the UK under both the Brexit withdrawal agreement and the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-examining-the-extent-of-eu-authority/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 2: An Overview of the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement on Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</guid><description>A Summary and Overview of the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
Starting January 1, 2021, the UK-EU relationship transitioned from the Brexit withdrawal agreement to a new framework. This new framework relies partly on the existing withdrawal agreement and partly on the newly established Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). It’s important to note that two additional agreements, concerning security information and Euratom, were also established.
This piece provides a summary of the TCA, drawing from initial observations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-2-an-overview-of-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-on-brexit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 4 of the Brexit agreement: Examination of dispute resolution and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement between the EU and UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction and Overview
A crucial element of the &amp;lsquo;Brexit deal&amp;rsquo;, formally called the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA), is dispute resolution. This post provides a thorough analysis of the treaty&amp;rsquo;s dispute resolution mechanisms and offers a concise summary upfront. (An update on April 29, 2021, incorporates the final TCA article numbers).
This is the fourth post in a series examining the TCA. It follows an overview of the TCA, an analysis of its social security provisions by Professor Tamara Hervey, and an exploration of the connections between the TCA and human rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-4-of-the-brexit-agreement-examination-of-dispute-resolution-and-the-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-between-the-eu-and-uk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad, TCA Abu Dhabi, and Miral collaborate to showcase Abu Dhabi as a preferred destination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has partnered with the Abu Dhabi Tourism &amp;amp; Culture Authority (TCA Abu Dhabi) and Miral Asset Management (Miral) to enhance Abu Dhabi&amp;rsquo;s standing as a top global destination for tourism, business, and culture.
This collaboration will see the three entities working together to attract more visitors and stopover travelers to Abu Dhabi. Joint efforts will include marketing and communication initiatives, sharing market insights and data, developing loyalty programs, and organizing business and leisure events both within the Emirate and internationally...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-tca-abu-dhabi-and-miral-collaborate-to-showcase-abu-dhabi-as-a-preferred-destination/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis 1: Examination of Healthcare Entitlements in the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 17:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</guid><description>Professor Tamara Hervey from the University of Sheffield examines the healthcare entitlements, if any, provided by the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) that was provisionally agreed upon on December 24, 2020.
Introduction
The TCA includes provisions for social security coordination, similar to EU law but considerably weaker. These provisions are found in Heading Four and are not typical of standard trade agreements like CETA.
Many are interested in the future of the European Health Insurance Card (EHIC) scheme, as private travel insurance is often expensive or inaccessible, particularly for the elderly...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-1-examination-of-healthcare-entitlements-in-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Analysis of the Environment and Climate Provisions in the Brexit Deal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</guid><description>Introduction
The start of the new year marked a significant shift in the UK-EU relationship, ending the Brexit transition and ushering in the provisional Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA). This post delves into the TCA&amp;rsquo;s environmental and climate change provisions, drawing on prior analyses of the TCA&amp;rsquo;s overview, social security provisions, human rights aspects, and dispute settlement mechanisms. (Updated as of April 28, 2021, to reflect the final TCA article numbering)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-of-the-environment-and-climate-provisions-in-the-brexit-deal/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU's Decision on Extradition from Ireland to the UK Post-Brexit: Getting Brexit Done</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 07:07:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
This week, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its first ruling concerning the impact of Brexit on the EU since the UK&amp;rsquo;s departure. This follows closely on the heels of last week&amp;rsquo;s opinion from the Advocate General. The case was referred to the CJEU by the Irish Supreme Court, which was considering an appeal against a previous Irish High Court decision...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-decision-on-extradition-from-ireland-to-the-uk-post-brexit-getting-brexit-done/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>