<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Entrepreneurship on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entrepreneurship/</link><description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement was initiated in Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-was-initiated-in-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: GEM Facebook page.
The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) launched officially in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia today. This non-governmental organization (NGO) aims to create a platform for entrepreneurs from various sectors like social entrepreneurship, technology, and halal to connect.
“This NGO brings together community leaders from different networks who will cultivate strong partnerships for Malaysia and our entrepreneurs,&amp;quot; shared YBhg. Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Abdullah, GEM patron and Secretary General Treasury, Ministry of Finance.</description></item><item><title>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement provides a platform for new entrepreneurs to thrive on a global scale</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-entrepreneurship-movement-provides-a-platform-for-new-entrepreneurs-to-thrive-on-a-global-scale/</guid><description>The Global Entrepreneurship Movement (GEM) has been chosen to develop, curate content for, and design the strategy of the Global Entrepreneurship Community (GECommunity) for 2016. The soft launch of this initiative took place at the World Islamic Economic Forum (WIEF) in Jakarta, Indonesia. The Finance Ministry, through the National Entrepreneurs Development Office (NEDO) and the Malaysian Global Innovation and Creativity Centre (MaGIC), is hosting GECommunity 2016.
GECommunity aims to establish Malaysia as a global hub for connectivity and innovation.</description></item><item><title>The ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 has been met with an enthusiastic and positive reception</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 02:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asean-entrepreneurship-summit-2015-has-been-met-with-an-enthusiastic-and-positive-reception/</guid><description>Source: 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. The 1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit 2015 in Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, was officially opened by Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah.
Source: _1ASEAN Entrepreneurship Summit. _Pictured from left to right (back row): Dato’ Seri Ahmad Husni Mohamad Hanadzlah, Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Minister of Finance II, alongside Tan Sri Dr Mohd Irwan Serigar Bin Abdullah, Secretary General of Treasury, Malaysia. They are joined by 10 children, each representing a different ASEAN nation.</description></item></channel></rss>