<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Plated on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plated/</link><description>Recent content in Plated on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/plated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated DIN Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</guid><description>During the ongoing refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a corroded DIN5 plug was replaced after a new output relay had been installed. The original plug showed significant signs of wear.
A high-quality Rean DIN5 plug with gold-plated terminals was chosen as a replacement. Photos document the preparation of the cable and the installation process. The author notes the limited space inside the DIN5 plug, making it difficult to separate the signal and ground connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Installation of a New Gold Coated DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>My restoration of the Beogram 4000 is progressing well. I&amp;rsquo;ve added a grounding switch and a new gold-plated Neutrik DIN5 plug. The switch allows users to choose between the grounding setup of the older 4000/4002 models (separate signal and system grounds) and the later 4004 models (combined grounds). This option helps prevent ground loops and the resulting humming, depending on the amplifier being used. I wrote a detailed post on this topic a while back...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-installation-of-a-new-gold-coated-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 07:19:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The last step in restoring my Beogram 4002 (5523) was replacing the old and slightly corroded RCA plugs. The picture highlights the original plugs:
This image showcases the new gold-plated Amphenol RCA plugs during installation:
The straightforward design of these plugs, which simplifies installation and ensures solid solder connections, is something I appreciate. And here is the finished product:
I need to wait for the PCBs for my new RIAA phono preamp design, so there will be a slight delay...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Corroded RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) currently under restoration was equipped with RCA plugs and a grounding wire instead of the typical DIN 5 connector. The plugs and grounding terminal were noticeably dirty and corroded.
The RCA plugs were switched out for all-metal gold-plated ones, and a new grounding terminal was installed.
These compact RCA plugs lack color coding, so 3D-printed inserts were created. These inserts enclose the back of the plugs and provide a visual distinction between the left and right channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New DIN 5 Plug and Installation of a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:48:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a severely corroded and improperly installed DIN 5 plug, clearly not the original. The attached photos illustrate its poor condition.
One of the pictures highlights a loose black wire, potentially a makeshift attempt to address humming issues (unsurprising given the plug&amp;rsquo;s installation). Adding to the problem, a poorly executed soldering job had left one of the signal leads disconnected.
I removed the old plug and prepared the wires for a new one, as shown in the photo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Pins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</guid><description>A gold-plated plug is the finishing touch for a fully restored signal path. Here&amp;rsquo;s the process on a Beogram 4002(5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on:
Above is the original plug in rough shape due to oxidation.
The new Rean plug offers a neat and tidy internal layout.
Placing the metal enclosure back results in an even more visually appealing look. That&amp;rsquo;s the Beolove!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>