<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EU Army on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-army/</link><description>Recent content in EU Army on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eu-army/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Briefing 1 on the EU Referendum: Will the UK have influence over the EU's future as a member?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-1-on-the-eu-referendum-will-the-uk-have-influence-over-the-eu-s-future-as-a-member/</guid><description>The potential risks associated with remaining in the EU due to its future trajectory have been a subject of debate during the Brexit referendum. Some argue that the UK might be forced into accepting an EU army, further integration of the single currency, or other undesirable developments. However, the crucial point is whether the UK possesses the power to govern such advancements, either through veto or opting out.
This analysis will address the key concerns related to continued EU membership, demonstrating how the UK maintains control through opt-outs or veto power in each scenario.</description></item><item><title>Could the EU be considering the formation of a military force, and would the UK have the power to block it?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/could-the-eu-be-considering-the-formation-of-a-military-force-and-would-the-uk-have-the-power-to-block-it/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent discussions have centered around whether the EU is forming an army and if the UK has the power to veto such a move before Brexit. This debate, while heated, often lacks clarity. This piece aims to provide a clear understanding of the situation, concluding that the recent proposals don&amp;rsquo;t constitute an EU army, making a UK veto irrelevant.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy initially avoided defense matters, respecting Irish neutrality and the UK&amp;rsquo;s commitment to NATO.</description></item></channel></rss>