<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MSO on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mso/</link><description>Recent content in MSO on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mso/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Comcast’s 100 Gbps Core Network Supports Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</guid><description>Over the past year, major telecom companies have been upgrading their core networks from 40 Gbps to 100 Gbps. Comcast recently joined this trend by incorporating Ciena&amp;rsquo;s Wave Logic 3 interfaces into their existing Ciena 6500 packet optical platforms. This begs the question: why would a cable company make this change, and how can it benefit your business?
Comcast is widely recognized as a Cable TV provider, or MSO (Multi-System Operator)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comcast-s-100-gbps-core-network-supports-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Disruptive Metro Ethernet over Fiber Pricing Arrives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</guid><description>The increasing use of Ethernet over Fiber (EoF) by large companies, as a cheaper option compared to SONET fiber optic services, has made many believe that fiber optic technology is only for big players. However, that notion is no longer true, as affordable fiber optic bandwidth is now accessible to all.
The surprising reason behind the unexpectedly low cost of Mbps or Gbps bandwidth, often half the anticipated price or even less, is Cable TV...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/disruptive-metro-ethernet-over-fiber-pricing-arrives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Get Fiber Services From A Cable Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</guid><description>When considering new or replacement fiber optic services, telecom companies, including telephone companies and competitive service providers (CLECs), are the usual suspects. While most bandwidth providers operate their own core networks, they often lease &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connections from these telcos, particularly for SONET services, which originated in the telephone industry.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
However, cable companies, or MSOs (Multi-System Operators), present an alternative. These providers bypass telco infrastructure entirely, having built their networks from scratch to deliver television signals to homes and businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-get-fiber-services-from-a-cable-company/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DOCSIS 3.0 Fiberizes Cable Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 20:33:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</guid><description>Cable companies have been envious of Verizon&amp;rsquo;s FiOS fiber optic service because it surpasses the broadband capabilities of coaxial cable. However, a new upgrade to the DOCSIS cable broadband standard might change that. This upgrade boosts digital download speeds to rival those of fiber optic connections, all without needing a fiber optic line to the home.
DOCSIS, which stands for Data Over Cable Service Interface Specification, is the standard for cable modems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/docsis-30-fiberizes-cable-broadband/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>