<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Youth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/youth/</link><description>Recent content in Youth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/youth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Singtel introduces new LVL UP plan tailored for young people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-introduces-new-lvl-up-plan-tailored-for-young-people/</guid><description>Source: Singtel website. The LVL UP plan is targeted at youths.
Singtel introduced a new mobile plan called &amp;ldquo;LVL UP&amp;rdquo; for young adults, coinciding with the start of The PC Show 2017. The name, inspired by the gaming term &amp;ldquo;level up,&amp;rdquo; signifies advancement to higher levels of difficulty in games. This plan provides free upgrades for Singtel&amp;rsquo;s Youth Combo plans and additional data.
This plan, available to students and full-time National Servicemen aged 26 and under, offers close to S$600 in savings over two years.</description></item><item><title>Within the next five years, one-third of young Arabs intend to launch their own businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/within-the-next-five-years-one-third-of-young-arabs-intend-to-launch-their-own-businesses/</guid><description>According to the 2016 ASDA’A Burson-Marsteller Arab Youth Survey, over one-third of young Arabs plan to launch their own businesses within the next five years. The survey indicates that young Arabs believe governments could do more to support them, such as promoting affordable lending, enhancing training and education opportunities, and reducing bureaucratic hurdles.
When asked if their generation is more likely to start businesses than previous ones, 54% agreed. GCC youth were the most optimistic at 62%, compared to 54% in North Africa and 44% in the Levant.</description></item></channel></rss>