<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Australia on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/australia/</link><description>Recent content in Australia on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Vines Resort &amp; Country Club introduces a new garden venue for meetings, incentives, conferences, and events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</guid><description>Source: The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club. The Pavilion.
The Vines Resort &amp;amp; Country Club, located near Perth, Australia, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Pavilion.&amp;rdquo; This new event space is a specially designed garden structure situated at the front of the resort, offering scenic views of the golf course and surrounding gardens. It&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for events such as conference gatherings or product launches.
The open-air venue, capable of hosting 100 guests, has three sides open to the elements...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vines-resort-country-club-introduces-a-new-garden-venue-for-meetings-incentives-conferences-and-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises in Australia have the opportunity to utilize Microsoft Lync through iiNet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 07:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</guid><description>Parallels, a company that provides platforms for delivering cloud services, has announced the successful deployment of Microsoft Lync through Parallels Automation at iiNet. iiNet is the second-largest DSL internet provider in Australia and a major competitor in the country’s telecommunications market. This new Microsoft Lync service from iiNet will provide small and medium enterprises (SMEs) across Australia with access to affordable, enterprise-grade voice, telephony, and video calling services.
Source: iiNet website...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-in-australia-have-the-opportunity-to-utilize-microsoft-lync-through-iinet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad Airways now includes Melbourne as a destination for its A380 aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has launched a new era of luxury air travel between Melbourne and Abu Dhabi with the introduction of the A380 superjumbo. This flagship aircraft, which features luxurious amenities like The Residence and next-generation cabins, will operate on one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily flights between the cities, replacing a three-class Boeing 777-300ER. Passengers can enjoy innovative hospitality services during their flight, including a dedicated Butler, Inflight Chef, Flying Nanny, and Food and Beverage Managers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-airways-now-includes-melbourne-as-a-destination-for-its-a380-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Book appointments through Vaniday</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 04:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</guid><description>Source: Vaniday. Vaniday has been launched in Singapore.
Vaniday, a platform for beauty and wellness services, has expanded to Singapore, its first market in Southeast Asia. The company recently secured €15 million in initial funding to support its growth.
Vaniday wants to change how people find, book, and experience beauty and wellness services. The app and website allow users to browse a wide selection of salons and book appointments directly from the salon&amp;rsquo;s schedule...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/book-appointments-through-vaniday/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Australian government, in collaboration with Microsoft and MassChallenge, aims to enhance the local startup ecosystem</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</guid><description>The Australian government is investing A$280,000 to bring MassChallenge, a leading global startup accelerator, to Australia. The goal is to support the growth of local startups.
MassChallenge, in partnership with Microsoft Australia and the Australian government, will offer resources such as idea-pitching competitions, boot camps, and mentoring to strengthen the Australian startup ecosystem. As a non-profit, equity-free accelerator, MassChallenge provides promising startups with the opportunity to compete for millions of dollars in cash awards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-australian-government-in-collaboration-with-microsoft-and-masschallenge-aims-to-enhance-the-local-startup-ecosystem/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Some businesses are finding success with crowdfunding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 17:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</guid><description>Crowdfunding, particularly through platforms like Kickstarter, has proven very successful for certain entrepreneurs. The typical project presents a concept and images of the product in development and seeks funding from backers. Both entrepreneurs and their backers can be located anywhere globally.
Funding is usually sought through tiered pledges, where higher pledges receive products with additional features. This process is often gamified with &amp;ldquo;stretch goals,&amp;rdquo; where exceeding funding targets unlocks new rewards for all backers at specific milestones...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/some-businesses-are-finding-success-with-crowdfunding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Successful demonstration of augmented reality video calls over long distances using 5G technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 01:54:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</guid><description>Source: Singtel. An Optus engineer at Optus’ live 5G site in Sydney, Australia conducts a 5G augmented reality video call using an OPPO 5G test device with Singtel engineers in Singapore.
Singtel, Optus, and Ericsson have given a glimpse into the future of communication by making a successful 5G video call with augmented reality (AR) between Singapore and Australia.
This call, using OPPO 5G test devices equipped with Qualcomm 5G modems on both countries&amp;rsquo; 5G networks, demonstrates the potential of real-time AR on 5G networks built by Ericsson...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/successful-demonstration-of-augmented-reality-video-calls-over-long-distances-using-5g-technology/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Text Messaging To The Stars</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 20:31:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</guid><description>Instead of texting Hollywood stars, how about sending a message to another planet? You can join a project called &amp;ldquo;Hello From Earth,&amp;rdquo; which sent text messages to Gliese 581d, a planet outside our solar system. Located 20 light years away in the constellation Libra, it will take about 20 years for your message to reach these potential extraterrestrials.
While we don&amp;rsquo;t know who or what might receive our messages, many people chose to send greetings of peace...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/text-messaging-to-the-stars/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Google is ranked first in the Brandindex Australia rankings for 2016</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</guid><description>Source: YouGov BrandIndex. Overall brand rankings for 2016 in Australia.
YouGov BrandIndex has released its 2016 rankings for Australia. Having monitored brands in Australia since mid-2015, BrandIndex currently tracks over 260 brands. Alphabet&amp;rsquo;s Google secured the top position, followed by YouTube, another Alphabet subsidiary, and then ALDI, the discount retailer.
Here are some other notable findings:
In the automotive sector, Toyota, Mazda, and Mercedes-Benz secured the top three spots...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-ranked-first-in-the-brandindex-australia-rankings-for-2016/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Gold Coast, Australia will be home to the first Hyde location outside of the US</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 15:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</guid><description>Accor is expanding its partnership with sbe beyond the US, selecting Australia as the first Asia Pacific location. Hyde, their luxury lifestyle brand known for its Los Angeles Sunset Strip inspiration, will debut Hyde Paradiso on the Gold Coast in March 2019. This venue promises an all-day experience, transforming into a sophisticated lounge and dining destination in the evening.
Simon McGrath, COO of Accor Pacific, highlights the partnership&amp;rsquo;s goal to deliver unique lifestyle experiences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-gold-coast-australia-will-be-home-to-the-first-hyde-location-outside-of-the-us/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vivid Sydney will once again enchant audiences starting on May 27th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 21:22:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</guid><description>The longest-running Vivid Sydney will illuminate Sydney Harbour and other beloved locations for 23 nights, from May 27 to June 18, 2016. This year marks the eighth anniversary of the world&amp;rsquo;s largest festival of light, music, and ideas. The festival is owned, managed, and produced by Destination NSW, the NSW Government&amp;rsquo;s tourism and major events agency.
Sandra Chipchase, Destination NSW Chief Executive Officer and Executive Producer of Vivid Sydney, stated that this year&amp;rsquo;s Vivid Sydney promises an incredible program where art, creativity, and innovation converge, captivating both local and international visitors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vivid-sydney-will-once-again-enchant-audiences-starting-on-may-27th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore and Australia provide the fastest mobile data speeds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 10:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</guid><description>Source: Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report.
According to Ericsson, Singapore is the only Southeast Asian nation with mobile networks strong enough to consistently support high-bandwidth applications, like streaming video, on consumer devices.
The November 2015 Ericsson South East Asia and Oceania regional Ericsson Mobility Report states that Singapore is also the region’s first and only country with a smartphone subscription rate exceeding 100%.
Both Singapore and Australia can provide high-definition video streaming anywhere their mobile networks reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-and-australia-provide-the-fastest-mobile-data-speeds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has reopened</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</guid><description>The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders has finished renovating all guest rooms, bathrooms, and suites, offering visitors a revitalized stay in the heart of the city.
Source: Holiday Inn website. The Holiday Inn Melbourne on Flinders.
Every room was completely emptied to give the architect a fresh start in designing a space with the modern traveler&amp;rsquo;s needs in mind. Striking new interiors are highlighted by floor-to-ceiling windows, equipped with electronically controlled blackout blinds that can be adjusted from the bedside...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-holiday-inn-melbourne-on-flinders-has-reopened/</a></p></description></item><item><title>New website offers discounted gym classes in Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 05:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</guid><description>Source:
FILLMYCLASS.
Similar to discounts for last-minute travel bookings, you can find more affordable gym classes at the last minute too.
A new website called FILLMYCLASS has launched in Melbourne, Australia. This website connects fitness enthusiasts with open spots in fitness classes at gyms and studios nearby.
FILLMYCLASS founder Daniel Waide states, &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s all about flexibility. The aim is to encourage more people to be active. Offering the ability to select classes that fit their schedule at any gym or studio increases the likelihood of people becoming and staying active...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-website-offers-discounted-gym-classes-in-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Counterfeit software discovered in Singapore sold as authentic in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 15:37:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>This image depicts a counterfeit Certificate of Authenticity (COA). It only displays the product name and lacks any anti-counterfeiting measures.
Microsoft recently uncovered a case of software piracy originating from a supplier in Singapore. The case involved an Australian reseller found to be in possession of fake COAs and other counterfeit software and hardware.
COAs are labels or stickers affixed to the packaging of products like Windows, Office, and Windows Server...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/counterfeit-software-discovered-in-singapore-sold-as-authentic-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines' Capital Express Service links Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 07:22:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</guid><description>Singapore Airlines is launching a new &amp;ldquo;Capital Express&amp;rdquo; route, connecting Singapore, Canberra, and Wellington. Starting on September 20, 2016, the airline will offer four weekly flights between these cities, subject to regulatory approval. The route will operate on a Singapore-Canberra-Wellington schedule for outbound flights and a Wellington-Canberra-Singapore schedule for return flights.
The flights will utilize retrofitted Boeing 777-200 aircraft, configured with 38 Business Class seats and 228 Economy Class seats. This service marks a significant milestone as it will be Canberra&amp;rsquo;s first regularly scheduled international service and the first non-stop connection between the capitals of Australia and New Zealand...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-capital-express-service-links-singapore-canberra-and-wellington/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Capella Sydney celebrates its first anniversary with joy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</guid><description>Source: Capella Sydney. To celebrate its one-year anniversary, Capella Sydney is providing a special deal with a A$365 credit applicable throughout the hotel and breakfast for two. The offer encompasses:
- Daily breakfast at Brasserie 1930
- Exclusive access to The Living Room, a shared area present in every Capella establishment. This space allows guests to participate in daily Capella customs and experience Sydney&amp;rsquo;s heritage through a curated display of local historical items and art...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-sydney-celebrates-its-first-anniversary-with-joy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces the Dreamliner to Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 23:16:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has started using Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners for flights to Perth, Australia. These planes provide passengers with larger windows, improved air quality, spacious storage, and advanced technology for a more comfortable journey.
Flight EY486, the first Dreamliner flight, arrived in Perth on June 2nd and was greeted with a water cannon salute. This daily service replaces the Airbus A330-200, increasing capacity by 14%, with Business Class seating up by 27%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-the-dreamliner-to-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In 2017, Etihad will assume control of Virgin's Sydney-Abu Dhabi slots</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 09:19:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</guid><description>Etihad Airways will increase flights between Abu Dhabi and Sydney to twice daily starting February 6, 2017. Flights EY450 departing Abu Dhabi in the morning and EY451 departing Sydney in the afternoon will now operate seven days a week.
This schedule change coincides with strategic partner Virgin Australia&amp;rsquo;s move to shift its Abu Dhabi operations from Sydney to Perth, effective June 9, 2017. Etihad Airways will expand its current codeshare agreement with Virgin Australia to include their new tri-weekly Perth-Abu Dhabi flights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2017-etihad-will-assume-control-of-virgin-s-sydney-abu-dhabi-slots/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Limited edition experiences are a popular trend in the food service industry in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 04:11:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</guid><description>In 2015, Australian diners increasingly embraced their inner foodies, craving novel culinary experiences. Food service operators responded with innovation, experimenting with formats, menus, and dining concepts, according to a Euromonitor blog post.
One example highlighted by the research firm is Hotel Marriott in Melbourne&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table for 12&amp;rdquo; concept, launched in October 2015. This exclusive dining experience offered a four-course degustation menu for a limited group of twelve guests, available only one night a week...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/limited-edition-experiences-are-a-popular-trend-in-the-food-service-industry-in-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Six Accor hotels in Australia have been inducted into the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 07:28:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</guid><description>Many Accor hotels in Australia have received recognition from TripAdvisor for their exceptional service in the tourism and hospitality sector. Several of these hotels were even honored for their fifth consecutive year of outstanding performance, earning them a place in the TripAdvisor Hall of Fame.
Six Accor hotels achieved this Hall of Fame distinction this year:
The Sebel Melbourne Flinders Lane Quay West Suites Melbourne The Sebel Maroochydore Pullman Palm Cove Sea Temple Resort and Spa Pullman Cairns International The Sebel Mandurah Accor Hotels Australia&amp;rsquo;s Chief Operating Officer, Simon McGrath, remarked that the variety of Accor brands, locations, and hotels featured in the 2015 TripAdvisor Hall of Fame demonstrates the high quality of the group&amp;rsquo;s properties across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/six-accor-hotels-in-australia-have-been-inducted-into-the-tripadvisor-hall-of-fame/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Achieving institutional equilibrium and the process of negotiating global treaties</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</guid><description>Andrés Delgado Casteleiro, Lecturer at Durham Law School
Introduction
In a ruling on Case C-425/13, Commission v Council, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with clarifying the Council&amp;rsquo;s authority in providing directions to the Commission during international negotiations. This case, decided on Thursday, specifically concerned the linking of Australia&amp;rsquo;s emissions trading system with the EU&amp;rsquo;s and involved examining the balance of power between the Council and the Commission during such negotiations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/achieving-institutional-equilibrium-and-the-process-of-negotiating-global-treaties/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sage Hotel in West Perth has been opened by Silverneedle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 11:39:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</guid><description>Source: Silverneedle. Sage Hotel, West Perth.
SilverNeedle, a hotel group based in Singapore, has partnered with Australian Development Capital (ADC), a Perth-based real estate developer, to open a new Sage Hotel in West Perth.
This A$35 million project marks the debut of the Sage Hotel brand in Perth, a city gaining popularity among Singaporean business and leisure travelers, and positions the brand within the upscale hotel market.
Sage aims to provide a unique experience that reflects the local community and goes beyond standardized global hospitality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sage-hotel-in-west-perth-has-been-opened-by-silverneedle/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australians are worried about the amount of sugar in fizzy drinks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 04:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</guid><description>Australia&amp;rsquo;s carbonated soft drink (CSD) market is experiencing ongoing challenges due to consumer worries about sugar content, as reported by Mintel, a global market intelligence firm.
Mintel predicts that the total sales volume of CSDs in Australia will likely decrease by 2.3% in 2017, following a 4.7% drop from 2014 to 2016.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research suggests that growing awareness of sugar&amp;rsquo;s negative effects has prompted many Australians to reevaluate their sugar consumption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australians-are-worried-about-the-amount-of-sugar-in-fizzy-drinks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Accor expands its footprint in regional Queensland with the addition of Mercure Rockhampton</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</guid><description>The Travelodge Hotel in Rockhampton has transitioned to the Mercure brand as part of a new franchise agreement with Accor. This addition expands Mercure&amp;rsquo;s presence to over 50 properties in Australia and New Zealand, and more than 810 globally.
Conveniently located in the city center and a short distance from the airport, the Mercure Rockhampton underwent renovations in 2008. The eight-story hotel boasts 74 rooms, views of the Fitzroy River, six conference rooms, an outdoor pool, a fitness center, a 24-hour reception, and convenient access to attractions like Great Keppel Island...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-expands-its-footprint-in-regional-queensland-with-the-addition-of-mercure-rockhampton/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Preparations for Vivid Sydney start two weeks before Lights On</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</guid><description>Sydney is getting ready for Vivid Sydney, a major festival celebrating light, music, and ideas in the Southern Hemisphere. Over 50 light installations and projections will illuminate the city starting May 24th.
Source: Vivid Sydney. An artist&amp;rsquo;s impression by Andrew Thomas Huang &amp;amp; Bemo on the Austral Floral Ballet, part of Vivid Light 2019. For 23 days, Vivid Sydney will transform the city into a captivating display of color with stunning light sculptures and large-scale projections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/preparations-for-vivid-sydney-start-two-weeks-before-lights-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Companies that experience data breaches in the Asia Pacific region are unlikely to be forgiven</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 02:53:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</guid><description>New research from SafeNet reveals that data breaches significantly influence customer trust. The global study, including participants from Japan and Australia, found that 65% wouldn&amp;rsquo;t patronize a business that experienced a financial data breach, compromising credit card details, bank accounts, or login credentials.
SafeNet&amp;rsquo;s Q2 Breach Level Index reported 237 data breaches from April to June 2014, exposing over 175 million records globally. These findings highlight the impact of data breaches on customer loyalty and revenue...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-that-experience-data-breaches-in-the-asia-pacific-region-are-unlikely-to-be-forgiven/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australia, Singapore, and the UAE are among the top 10 destinations on people's relocation wishlist</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 01:16:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</guid><description>A recent report by Hydrogen Group, a global recruitment firm, reveals a growing trend of professionals seeking international work opportunities. The study found that the number of individuals open to working abroad doubled over a five-year period, rising from 16% in 2010 to 35% in 2014. Furthermore, 40% of respondents believe there are no obstacles to relocating for work.
While the US and UK were the most popular destinations, followed by Australia, Singapore ranked as the most preferred Asian country at seventh place...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australia-singapore-and-the-uae-are-among-the-top-10-destinations-on-people-s-relocation-wishlist/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Frost &amp; Sullivan anticipates a need for independent analyses to support IPOs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 09:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/</guid><description>A research and consulting firm, Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan, predicts significant growth for the Australian Stock Exchange (ASX) in 2017, with nearly 45 companies already lined up for initial public offerings (IPOs). This positive outlook comes after the ASX saw a stable number of IPOs in 2016, similar to the previous year. Notably, technology and fintech companies made up about 25% of these listings.
Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan played a key role in several 2016 ASX IPOs by providing independent market reports (IMRs)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/frost-sullivan-anticipates-a-need-for-independent-analyses-to-support-ipos/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Innovators under 35 in Singapore are looking for applicants from Southeast Asia and Australia/New Zealand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 13:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</guid><description>EmTech Singapore is searching for ten innovative individuals under 35 from Southeast Asia, Australia, and New Zealand. These individuals should embody innovation in business and technology and will be featured in the Innovators Under 35 Singapore competition. The competition seeks those responsible for significant advancements, innovations, and impactful contributions to their target audiences.
Organized by MIT Technology Review since 1999, Innovators Under 35 has acknowledged some of the world&amp;rsquo;s brightest minds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/innovators-under-35-in-singapore-are-looking-for-applicants-from-southeast-asia-and-australia-new-zealand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TripAdvisor has announced the winners of the Travelers' Choice awards for world landmarks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 10:45:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</guid><description>TripAdvisor, the popular travel website, has revealed the winners of its Travelers’ Choice awards for top global attractions. Now in their second year, the awards recognized 929 attractions, with a special highlight on the top 25. Asian and Middle Eastern landmarks secured four spots in the global top ten, while an Australian park earned a coveted place among the top ten parks worldwide.
Top 10 World Landmarks
Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque, Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tripadvisor-has-announced-the-winners-of-the-travelers-choice-awards-for-world-landmarks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CoAssets expands its crowdfunding portfolio by including small and medium-sized enterprise projects and sets its sights on Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</guid><description>CoAssets, a crowdfunding company based in Singapore, is expanding its platform to assist Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs). This expansion allows SMEs to connect with potential investors, addressing the funding challenges many businesses face. CoAssets&amp;rsquo; platform already facilitates real estate crowdfunding and will now provide a space for SMEs to seek funding.
Getty Goh, CEO of CoAssets, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s successful history in real estate crowdfunding and the increasing demand for business loans in Singapore as key drivers for this expansion...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/coassets-expands-its-crowdfunding-portfolio-by-including-small-and-medium-sized-enterprise-projects-and-sets-its-sights-on-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad introduces new First &amp; Business Class Lounge in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways has opened its first Australian First and Business Class Lounge at Sydney Airport. The new lounge is the latest addition to the airline’s global network of premium lounges.
Situated near Gate 51 in Pier C of the international terminal, the lounge provides a comfortable atmosphere for guests. It features high-quality furnishings and a modern design inspired by Etihad Airways’ flagship lounges in Abu Dhabi.
Etihad Airways’ President and CEO, James Hogan, who inaugurated the lounge, highlighted the importance of a seamless and consistent experience for travelers, from the lounge to the flight...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-introduces-new-first-business-class-lounge-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Sydney ICC Hotel will now be referred to as the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</guid><description>Source: Accor. Artist&amp;rsquo;s rendition of the Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
Accor, the leading hotel group in Australia, will manage the new International Convention Centre (ICC) Hotel in Sydney under its luxury Sofitel brand. The hotel will be called Sofitel Sydney Darling Harbour.
This Sofitel hotel is part of the New South Wales government&amp;rsquo;s A$2.5 billion project to transform Darling Harbour, creating a new hub for conventions, exhibitions, and entertainment in Sydney...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-sydney-icc-hotel-will-now-be-referred-to-as-the-sofitel-sydney-darling-harbour/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Sydney's Christmas programme has been officially launched by the City</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 18:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</guid><description>Source: City of Sydney. Lord Mayor Clover Moore launched the Sydney Christmas program at Martin Place.
Sydney has officially begun its Christmas celebrations, featuring an array of decorations, carols, light displays, concerts, Christmas trees, and special retail events.
Lord Mayor Clover Moore expressed her enthusiasm for the festivities, stating, &amp;ldquo;Each year, we warmly welcome thousands of people from all over Sydney to the city center for our Christmas celebrations. With live concerts, vibrant light projections, excellent shopping opportunities, and the chance for kids to meet Santa, there&amp;rsquo;s something for everyone - visitors, shoppers, and locals alike...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sydney-s-christmas-programme-has-been-officially-launched-by-the-city/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad announces first destinations for Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:06:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, has announced the initial destinations for its new Airbus A380 and Boeing 787 Dreamliner aircraft.
Source: Etihad. The Boeing 787-9.
The Abu Dhabi-based airline will start flying its first A380 to London&amp;rsquo;s Heathrow Airport in December 2014, with a second A380 added to the same route in the first quarter of 2015. By the end of 2015, Etihad Airways will have five A380s in service, with plans to also introduce them on routes to Sydney and New York&amp;rsquo;s JFK Airport...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-announces-first-destinations-for-airbus-a380-and-boeing-787-dreamliner-aircraft/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singtel now offers budget-friendly roaming options for Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
Singtel is introducing a new &amp;ldquo;Roam Like Home&amp;rdquo; DataRoam Saver plan for customers traveling to Australia. The DataRoam Saver Australia (Monthly) 1 GB plan is currently offered at a promotional price of S$10 for the first gigabyte of data. After exceeding this limit, users will be charged S$0.10 per megabyte.
Singtel claims this plan is the most budget-friendly option available and builds upon the success of the DataRoam Saver Malaysia (Monthly) 1 GB plan launched last October...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-now-offers-budget-friendly-roaming-options-for-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality has introduced its second Sage Hotel in Perth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</guid><description>Source: SilverNeedle Hospitality.
SilverNeedle Hospitality, based in Singapore, is expanding its upscale Sage Hotel brand in Perth, Western Australia, with a second location. This announcement comes just weeks after the brand launched with a hotel in Brisbane.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated that Sage Hotels are designed for a specific type of business traveler: one who wants a consistent and straightforward experience while working in new cities...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-has-introduced-its-second-sage-hotel-in-perth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Australian consumers are pleased to use contactless cards for payment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 07:42:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</guid><description>A recent Mastercard survey highlights the increasing popularity of digital payment methods among Australians. Over 80% of Australians use contactless payments, also known as &amp;ldquo;tap and go,&amp;rdquo; weekly. This preference is so strong that a significant number of consumers get frustrated when stores don&amp;rsquo;t offer this option, with some even choosing to shop elsewhere.
Supermarkets, retail stores, and petrol stations are the most common places where Australians use contactless cards. Mastercard Australia and New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Head of Market Development and Payment Innovation, Garry Duursma, emphasizes that Australians view tap and go as a faster and more convenient payment method...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/australian-consumers-are-pleased-to-use-contactless-cards-for-payment/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates introduces Airbus A380 to Perth route</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 13:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</guid><description>Starting May 1, 2015, Emirates will introduce its Airbus A380 aircraft to the Perth, Australia route. This upgrade from a Boeing 777-300ER on one of the three daily Dubai-Perth flights signifies Perth&amp;rsquo;s growth as a global destination.
This change will increase capacity by 136 seats per flight and 1,904 seats weekly, highlighting Emirates&amp;rsquo; dedication to travelers visiting Western Australia&amp;rsquo;s capital city. Barry Brown, Emirates’ Divisional Senior Vice President, Commercial Operations - East, emphasized the importance of Australia as a destination by highlighting this fifth Emirates A380 service in partnership with Qantas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-introduces-airbus-a380-to-perth-route/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AirAsia X will provide a connection between Kuala Lumpur and Auckland</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 15:35:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</guid><description>Source: AirAsia. AirAsia X launches flights from Kuala Lumpur to Auckland.
AirAsia X, the long-haul, budget-friendly part of the AirAsia Group, is starting flights to Auckland, New Zealand, from Kuala Lumpur. The route will have a stopover on the Gold Coast of Australia and begins on March 22, 2016.
Benyamin Ismail, CEO of AirAsia X, stated that New Zealand is a top-tier destination that the company has always valued. He expressed excitement about returning to the country and offering this new service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-x-will-provide-a-connection-between-kuala-lumpur-and-auckland/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the choice between the EU and the Commonwealth a true dilemma for the UK, or is it a misleading decision?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The UK is part of many international organizations: the EU, NATO, the UN Security Council, and the Commonwealth are just a few examples. Out of these, the Commonwealth, which recently held its latest summit, has the strongest ties to British history and culture because it primarily consists of former British colonies. (There are some Commonwealth members that were never colonies, and certain former colonies like the US opted not to join...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-choice-between-the-eu-and-the-commonwealth-a-true-dilemma-for-the-uk-or-is-it-a-misleading-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Check Point warns that free USB devices may be carriers of malware</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</guid><description>Source: Victoria Police. The unmarked USB drives used are similar to these.
On September 21st, law enforcement in Victoria, Australia, issued a warning to residents of Pakenham, a Melbourne suburb, about unlabeled USB drives found in mailboxes.
According to the Victoria police statement, people have been discovering unmarked USB drives in their mailboxes. When connected to computers, these drives have exposed victims to fraudulent streaming service offers and other serious problems...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/check-point-warns-that-free-usb-devices-may-be-carriers-of-malware/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Autograph Collection is ready to make its first appearance in Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</guid><description>Australian companies have a new, upscale event location. Pier One Sydney Harbour is joining the Autograph Collection, a curated group of almost 60 unique hotels globally. This harborside hotel provides a picturesque setting for meetings and events, featuring eight meeting rooms with expansive water views.
Source: Marriott International. From Sydney to San Diego - Autograph Collection set to debut in three new world class destinations, including Pier One Sydney Harbour in Sydney, Australia...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-autograph-collection-is-ready-to-make-its-first-appearance-in-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The top goal for urban Australians is to spend more time with their family</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 22:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/</guid><description>The increasing presence of technology in everyday life has led many Australians to desire a better work-life balance. Market intelligence agency Mintel reports that 38% of Australians are hoping to achieve this balance in the coming year.
Mintel&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that more than half of Australians living in metropolitan areas (51%) want to prioritize spending time with family in the next year. This desire is even more pronounced in families with three or more members, reaching 60%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-top-goal-for-urban-australians-is-to-spend-more-time-with-their-family/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Etihad plans to increase the number of flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 23:51:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</guid><description>Etihad Airways, the national airline of the United Arab Emirates, will begin offering daily A380 flights between Abu Dhabi and Melbourne starting June 1, 2016. This will affect flight numbers EY460/461, one of the airline&amp;rsquo;s two daily trips between the cities. This change replaces one of the three-class Boeing 777-300ER aircraft currently used. Passengers can now enjoy The Residence by Etihad, a luxurious private three-room suite, and other cutting-edge products and services across all cabins...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-plans-to-increase-the-number-of-flights-between-abu-dhabi-and-melbourne/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Emirates is set to introduce a third daily service to Brisbane</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 14:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</guid><description>Source: Emirates. Plane in Emirates livery.
Emirates will begin offering a third daily flight to Brisbane, Australia starting December 1, 2017, adding to their current two daily flights.
This direct flight will utilize a Boeing 777-200LR, which boasts eight First Class seats, 42 Business Class seats, and 216 Economy Class seats. This will increase the route&amp;rsquo;s capacity by 3,724 seats weekly, both to and from Brisbane and Emirates&amp;rsquo; Dubai hub...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/emirates-is-set-to-introduce-a-third-daily-service-to-brisbane/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hyatt Regency is back in Sydney and is now focusing on positioning the hotel for MICE events</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 16:51:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</guid><description>Hyatt Hotels announced that a hotel situated at 161 Sussex Street, previously operating under the Four Points by Sheraton brand, will transition to Hyatt Regency Sydney starting November 30, 2016. This change signifies the return of the Hyatt Regency brand to Sydney. The company is strategically positioning the Hyatt Regency Sydney as a prime location for conferences.
The introduction of Hyatt Regency Sydney aligns with the growing demand for business, meetings, incentives, conferences and exhibitions (MICE), as well as leisure travel within the Australian market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hyatt-regency-is-back-in-sydney-and-is-now-focusing-on-positioning-the-hotel-for-mice-events/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CSIRO is expediting promising research through ON Accelerate3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/csiro-is-expediting-promising-research-through-on-accelerate3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 22:32:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/csiro-is-expediting-promising-research-through-on-accelerate3/</guid><description>The Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organisation (CSIRO) has chosen 10 teams for ON Accelerate3, a nationwide program supporting research projects in Australia. This program began in 2015 to enhance innovation by connecting different fields, industries, science, and business.
These teams, representing various institutions like Flinders University and CSIRO, are tackling challenges in areas such as food security and healthcare. CSIRO Chief Executive Dr. Larry Marshall emphasized the diversity of this group, their potential to create new jobs, and their ability to address significant societal issues...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/csiro-is-expediting-promising-research-through-on-accelerate3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/csiro-is-expediting-promising-research-through-on-accelerate3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Monitoring social media shows the sentiments towards Formula One in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>In July, Microsoft launched Microsoft Social Listening in eight Asia Pacific markets. This service is designed to help professionals in sales, marketing, and customer care understand and engage with customers on social media more effectively. Microsoft Social Listening provides tools for analyzing market intelligence from social conversations, including sentiment analysis across multiple platforms. It also allows users to monitor products, brands, competitors, and campaigns globally in real time to gain a comprehensive understanding of their customers and their business in the social media landscape...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/monitoring-social-media-shows-the-sentiments-towards-formula-one-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ibis Hotels partners with Deezer to create a musical experience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels.
Ibis Hotels, a budget-friendly option within the Accor group, has launched a new campaign in Australia. Through a partnership with Deezer, a global music streaming platform, guests can now immerse themselves in the world of music.
This collaboration gives guests staying at ibis, ibis Styles, and ibis Budget hotels access to ibis PLAY, a dedicated microsite. This platform offers a variety of music-centric content, including regularly updated local concert listings, curated playlists, music news, artist interviews, photo galleries, exclusive ibis content, and a spotlight on Australian live acts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ibis-hotels-partners-with-deezer-to-create-a-musical-experience/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Big companies are scaling back, while small businesses remain optimistic for 2016 in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</guid><description>At the start of 2016, business sentiment in China presents a mixed picture. While confidence among large companies has slightly declined, smaller businesses are expressing optimism, according to separate reports from MNI Indicators and CPA Australia.
The MNI China Business Sentiment Indicator dipped to 52.3 in January, down from 52.7 in December. Although this still indicates expansion for the second consecutive month, it marks the first month-over-month decrease since November. Businesses have also tempered their future expectations, as reflected in the Future Expectations Indicator&amp;rsquo;s 0...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/big-companies-are-scaling-back-while-small-businesses-remain-optimistic-for-2016-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Come to Vivid Sydney and immerse yourself in the biggest festival of light, music, and ideas in the world</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 10:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</guid><description>Source: Vivid Sydney/Destination NSW.
Vivid Sydney, a global festival celebrating light, music, and ideas, will illuminate Sydney until June 8th. Last year, the festival drew in 1.43 million attendees.
Stuart Ayres, the NSW Minister for Trade, Tourism and Major Events, highlighted the festival&amp;rsquo;s ability to transform Sydney for 18 days and nights with creativity and vibrant light displays. He emphasized it as a must-see event for showcasing the city&amp;rsquo;s pride...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/come-to-vivid-sydney-and-immerse-yourself-in-the-biggest-festival-of-light-music-and-ideas-in-the-world/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DHL eCommerce has launched a new Fulfillment Center in Sydney</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</guid><description>DHL eCommerce, a branch of the logistics giant Deutsche Post DHL Group, has opened a Fulfillment Center in Sydney, Australia. The new center will help the company meet the demands of Australia&amp;rsquo;s rapidly growing number of online shoppers buying goods from overseas.
Damien Sheehan, Managing Director for DHL eCommerce in Australia, highlighted the significance of Australian online shoppers, stating, “Australian shoppers are some of the most frequent buyers from international sellers online, and their influence will only grow as cross-border e-commerce continues to expand at an average rate of 29% annually through 2020...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dhl-ecommerce-has-launched-a-new-fulfillment-center-in-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SilverNeedle Hospitality introduces the new Sage Hotel brand, catering specifically to upscale business travelers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</guid><description>SilverNeedle Hospitality, headquartered in Singapore, has introduced a new upscale hotel brand, Sage Hotel, tailored for business travelers. The first Sage Hotel will be located in Brisbane, Australia.
Iqbal Jumabhoy, Managing Director &amp;amp; Group Chief Executive Officer at SilverNeedle Hospitality, stated, &amp;ldquo;We recognize a significant group of business travelers seeking a consistent and straightforward experience while working in unfamiliar cities.&amp;rdquo; He added, &amp;ldquo;Sage Hotel is designed to meet their needs and complements our existing portfolio of six brands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/silverneedle-hospitality-introduces-the-new-sage-hotel-brand-catering-specifically-to-upscale-business-travelers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Every night in Sydney, it's Lights On for Vivid Sydney!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 02:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</guid><description>Source: Destination NSW. Vivid Sydney in action.
The tenth anniversary of Vivid Sydney, the world’s largest festival of light, music and ideas, has begun. As Australia’s largest event, Vivid Sydney transforms the city into a captivating display of illumination, sound, and creativity.
The festival commenced with the symbolic &amp;lsquo;Lights On&amp;rsquo; moment, with all eyes on the Sydney Opera House for the &amp;lsquo;Lighting of the Sails&amp;rsquo;. This year&amp;rsquo;s display, created by Australian artist Jonathan Zawada, featured dynamic digital sculptures of commonplace objects and elements from nature, morphing and changing before the viewers&amp;rsquo; eyes...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/every-night-in-sydney-it-s-lights-on-for-vivid-sydney/</a></p></description></item><item><title>In May 2015, SilkAir will begin operating flights to Cairns, Australia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</guid><description>SilkAir, the regional subsidiary of Singapore Airlines, will begin offering direct flights between Singapore and Cairns, Queensland, Australia, starting May 30, 2015, pending regulatory approval. Cairns will be the airline&amp;rsquo;s second Australian destination after Darwin, which launched in March 2012.
SilkAir intends to operate the Cairns route three times a week on Mondays, Thursdays, and Saturdays, through circular routings with Darwin. The inaugural flight and subsequent Saturday flights will depart Singapore for Cairns non-stop, returning to Singapore via Darwin...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-may-2015-silkair-will-begin-operating-flights-to-cairns-australia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>TeamAhoy introduces a new project management software that focuses on people</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/</guid><description>Source: TeamAhoy.
Bramanis.
TeamAhoy (previously known as Birds Eye View), an Australian company, has introduced the first public version of its project management software. The startup highlights that its software differentiates itself by prioritizing the human element, unlike competitors.
Founder Damian Bramanis explains that while teams consist of people, most project management tools don&amp;rsquo;t reflect this in their design. He believes TeamAhoy stands out by offering managers a user-friendly platform that centers around individuals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/teamahoy-introduces-a-new-project-management-software-that-focuses-on-people/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Fuel &amp; Trip Calculator from Bayswater Car Rentals eliminates the need for guessing petrol budgets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 08:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</guid><description>To help people budget for fuel costs and travel time, Bayswater Car Rentals (BCR) has introduced the Fuel &amp;amp; Trip Calculator. This online tool is available to everyone, not just BCR customers.
Arnold Kluck, CEO of BCR, explained that the company was founded to provide budget-friendly car rentals. He noted that customers frequently underestimate petrol costs at the end of their rental period, as it’s easy to overlook this expense during travel planning...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-fuel-trip-calculator-from-bayswater-car-rentals-eliminates-the-need-for-guessing-petrol-budgets/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>