<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-telephony/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Telephony on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:19:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/digital-telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Need A Special Phone For VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:19:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-special-phone-for-voip/</guid><description>Many people ask if a special phone is required for VoIP service. The answer depends on the situation.
Regular phones can&amp;rsquo;t plug directly into internet equipment because they use incompatible connectors. To bridge this gap, you need a special phone or an adapter.
Many residential and small business VoIP services, like PhonePower, offer adapters. These adapters allow you to connect your existing phone to your internet modem or router. Inside the adapter, circuitry converts the analog signals of your phone into digital packets for the internet, and vice versa.</description></item><item><title>So, What Does ISDN Stand For?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 18:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/so-what-does-isdn-stand-for/</guid><description>If your business uses telephone systems, you&amp;rsquo;ve likely encountered the term ISDN. This piece explains what ISDN is and how it can benefit your company.
ISDN, or Integrated Services Digital Network, is a digital telephone standard initially intended to replace analog lines for both residential and business users. While DSL, cable broadband, and VoIP surpassed ISDN in the residential market with their higher bandwidths and lower costs, ISDN found its niche as a popular trunking service for business PBX telephone systems and a few specialized applications.</description></item></channel></rss>