<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sure Step on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sure-step/</link><description>Recent content in Sure Step on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:59:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sure-step/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I'm not sure if my implementation methodology is working properly.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:59:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</guid><description>Christina and Steve rarely collaborate on blog posts due to the coordination involved, but they decided to team up to address common project failures. They believe that most project issues stem from flawed methodologies rather than individual mistakes. A structured implementation methodology like Sure Step can help avoid these problems.
Steve recounts instances where partners sought his help on troubled projects, needing him to fix integrations or customizations urgently and at discounted rates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-m-not-sure-if-my-implementation-methodology-is-working-properly/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Practicing and Opinions on Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:47:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</guid><description>I recently co-trained a new course in Atlanta called &amp;ldquo;Project Managing Microsoft Dynamics Implementations with Microsoft Dynamics Sure Step&amp;rdquo; (Course 80053A). This course was paired with a one-day class, &amp;ldquo;Project Management Skills Essentials for Microsoft Dynamics,&amp;rdquo; developed by Kristi Honey and Scott Mertes.
The first day concentrated on the essential soft skills needed for each stage of an implementation. We had many engaging discussions throughout the day. It was a fantastic opportunity to gain insights from different perspectives on Dynamics implementation project management...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/practicing-and-opinions-on-microsoft-dynamics-sure-step/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>