<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Book on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/book/</link><description>Recent content in Book on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:33:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Startup Capitals conference will begin on May 20th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</guid><description>Source: Startup Capitals&amp;rsquo; website.
Startup Capitals, a leading-edge conference inspired by the recent book of the same name by Singapore-based author and journalist Zafar Anjum, will be held on May 20th in Singapore at The POD, NLB, 100 Victoria Street.
This one-day event, coinciding with the book&amp;rsquo;s official launch, will highlight the innovation and startup ecosystems of globally impactful cities. It will unite all facets of these ecosystems – entrepreneurs, business leaders, innovators, researchers, educators, government officials, and venture capitalists – under one roof...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-startup-capitals-conference-will-begin-on-may-20th/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The book Soirees, Sojourns &amp; Stories details the most memorable moments of the Raffles narrative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:36:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</guid><description>Raffles Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, a leader in luxury hospitality known for its iconic properties, has released Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories.
Created in partnership with Rizzoli New York, the 200-page slipcased book, Soirees, Sojourns &amp;amp; Stories by Natasha Fraser-Cavassoni, explores the development of Raffles&amp;rsquo; heritage of elegance and exceptional service around the world. It covers the period from the opening of its flagship hotel in Singapore in 1887 to the recent debut of Raffles Warsaw in Poland...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-book-soirees-sojourns-stories-details-the-most-memorable-moments-of-the-raffles-narrative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Skills and challenges for global citizens</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:13:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</guid><description>A new book by an INSEAD professor explores the unique skills and challenges faced by &amp;ldquo;citizens of the world&amp;rdquo; – individuals who hold multiple passports or live outside their home country. These individuals often come from diverse backgrounds, navigating multiple cultures and languages, which has driven their success. Author Linda Brimm, an Emeritus Professor of Organisational Behaviour at INSEAD, emphasizes the importance of a global mindset in international business and problem-solving, stating that these individuals offer valuable insights for addressing today&amp;rsquo;s complex challenges...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/skills-and-challenges-for-global-citizens/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance is set to release a new book highlighting the achievements of influential brands in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</guid><description>Brand Alliance, a brand consulting firm, is releasing its inaugural book, &amp;ldquo;Influential Brands: A documentary of their heroic rise.&amp;rdquo; This book launch coincides with the firm&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;2014 Influential Brands&amp;rdquo; conference, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes&amp;rdquo;, taking place on November 7, 2014, at the Suntec City Convention Centre.
Source: Brand Alliance. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s brand story is in the book.
The book offers never-before-seen insights into the development of well-known brands, particularly those from Singapore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Heroes from Asian brands share their brand journey stories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 20:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</guid><description>Influential Brands, a program organized by Brand Alliance, held its 2014 conference in Singapore on November 7th. The event, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes,&amp;rdquo; recognized the success of leading brands in the region. Several individuals representing these successful brands participated in a panel discussion, sharing their insights and experiences.
The panel included (from left) moderator Amy Lim, Founder of Brand Alliance; Esther Tang-Loo, Executive Director of Focus Network Agencies; Han Keen Juan, Executive Chairman of Old Chang Kee Group; Debra Soon, Managing Director of Channel NewsAsia; Woon Tai Ho, Director for Media and Marketing at Singapore’s National Art Gallery; Allen Law, Group Chief Executive of Park Hotel Group; and Dr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/heroes-from-asian-brands-share-their-brand-journey-stories/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Discover more about Malaysia's demographics by reading a book on the population of Malaysia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</guid><description>Source: ISEAS website.
The second edition of The Population of Malaysia, authored by Saw Swee-Hock, former Professor of Statistics at the National University of Singapore and Chairman of the National Statistical Commission of Singapore from 1971 to 1975, has been released.
This updated analysis of Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s diverse population offers valuable insights for businesses interested in the Malaysian market. Dr. Saw leverages his extensive knowledge of the country, gained through his upbringing, teaching experience at the University of Malaya, and involvement in population census planning, to provide unique perspectives...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/discover-more-about-malaysia-s-demographics-by-reading-a-book-on-the-population-of-malaysia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>