<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NVIDIA on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nvidia/</link><description>Recent content in NVIDIA on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:30:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/nvidia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Customers who purchase the GeForce RTX 3080 and 3090 are eligible to receive a Call of Duty game bundle</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/customers-who-purchase-the-geforce-rtx-3080-and-3090-are-eligible-to-receive-a-call-of-duty-game-bundle/</guid><description>Image: Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War promotional image highlighting the Woods Operator Pack and Confrontation Weapons Pack.
NVIDIA is running a limited-time promotion offering a free copy of Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War with the purchase of qualifying GeForce RTX 3080 or 3090 graphics cards and pre-built PCs.
Releasing on November 13, 2020, Call of Duty: Black Ops Cold War is the newest installment in the popular Call of Duty series.</description></item><item><title>The speech recognition app can transcribe discussions involving several individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 11:46:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-speech-recognition-app-can-transcribe-discussions-involving-several-individuals/</guid><description>Source: NVIDIA blog post. The Otter team at AISense.
AISense, a company based in the US, has introduced Otter, an application that uses GPU technology to record and transcribe speech from multiple speakers. Unlike most currently available software that needs to be trained on a single voice, Otter can accurately recognize and differentiate between various speakers.
Sam Liang, AISense co-founder and CEO, highlights in a blog post that capturing human-to-human interactions is significantly more challenging than interactions like those with virtual assistants like Alexa, Siri, or Google Assistant.</description></item></channel></rss>