<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IT Services on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-services/</link><description>Recent content in IT Services on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/it-services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosting vs VPS</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</guid><description>Virtual Private Servers (VPS) offer a hosting solution for websites that have outgrown shared hosting but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for the cost and responsibility of a fully dedicated server. However, a new option allows for flexible scaling and a pay-as-you-go model: cloud server hosting.
Discussions about cloud computing versus managing your own data center are becoming increasingly common. However, many companies haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the stage where investing in a complete in-house data center is necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-vs-vps/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When It Comes to Computer Networks, Trust No One and No Thing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Network security is a major concern for businesses today. One might even miss the days of isolated computers, unconnected to any network.
However, even those isolated computers weren&amp;rsquo;t entirely secure. Malware could still spread and confidential files could be copied through physical transfer of files using floppy disks. The challenge today is that modern networks, encompassing local networks, data centers, multiple cloud platforms, and the internet, make it incredibly difficult to track who is accessing the network and their intentions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-it-comes-to-computer-networks-trust-no-one-and-no-thing/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dual Core, Quad Core, Up to 64 Core Managed Dedicated Servers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</guid><description>The race for faster processors has shifted its focus. Instead of increasing clock speeds, the industry is now prioritizing multi-core and multi-processor designs to improve performance.
The good news is that there are affordable options for powerful processing, including managed dedicated servers with excellent support.
Entry-level systems typically feature dual-core processors. For increased power, users can opt for quad-core or hexa-core (6 cores) configurations. For even greater performance, dual or quad-processor dedicated servers are available...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dual-core-quad-core-up-to-64-core-managed-dedicated-servers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosting Providers For Converged Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 19:40:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</guid><description>The use of cloud computing services is rapidly increasing. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted them yet, you might be hesitant due to concerns about cost-effectiveness, security, or the cloud&amp;rsquo;s ability to meet all your IT requirements. However, this is changing quickly. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the current options for small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs).
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
When we envision cloud computing, we often picture a massive, centralized system handling operations for countless companies. While this perception is prevalent, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t represent the entire market...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosting-providers-for-converged-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Managed WiFi Right for You?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 21:31:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Broadband internet access is widely available and has become a standard expectation. Consumers rely on it to stay connected while on the move, and businesses use it to provide connectivity to customers and allow employees to work flexibly.
Considering 3G and 4G cellular?
Cellular broadband on smartphones is excellent for wide area coverage, but it has limitations. Data usage limits can lead to unexpectedly high costs. Additionally, many computers, tablets, and other devices lack built-in cellular connectivity, even if users are willing to pay extra for it...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-managed-wifi-right-for-you/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 Gbps Wavelength Service Open for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:05:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</guid><description>While many businesses are enjoying the advantages of 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet, bandwidth capabilities are increasing exponentially. 100 Gbps wavelength service is now available on the West Coast, a thousandfold increase over standard 100 Mbps Ethernet. What necessitates such high bandwidth, and where can it be obtained?
The factors driving the demand for 100 Gbps bandwidth are the same ones that make 100 Mbps nearly entry-level. Many smaller businesses struggle with their outdated T1 lines, which operate at a slow 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-gbps-wavelength-service-open-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting vs Cloud Data Centers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve been managing your own data center for a long time, but your company is expanding, and your server room can no longer keep up. Now you have a decision to make: either rent more space for the extra servers, storage, and other equipment, or think about migrating everything to the cloud. It&amp;rsquo;s a major choice that demands serious thought before any money is spent.
Isn’t Everyone in the Cloud?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-vs-cloud-data-centers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Types of Clouds You Should Know About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of cloud-based IT services might leave you wondering if you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. To help you decide, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the three primary cloud types and which applications are well-suited for cloud environments.
These days, it seems everyone is offering cloud services, primarily based on three architectures: public, private, and hybrid clouds.
The most common is the public cloud, a specialized data center owned and operated by a provider serving numerous paying customers concurrently...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-types-of-clouds-you-should-know-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hosted Network Monitoring Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</guid><description>The increasing reliance on electronic transactions, online services, and cloud technologies has made networks essential for businesses. This dependence requires IT departments to prioritize network monitoring, either through in-house solutions or external providers.
While companies have traditionally monitored their internal networks, extending this practice to telecom connections is crucial. This includes dedicated lines, public internet connections, and VPNs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to enhance network monitoring processes.
Smaller businesses often face challenges with network monitoring outside of business hours...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s Wrong With Bring Your Own Bandwidth?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 02:54:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</guid><description>When procuring new IT services, you often face a choice: start fresh with services and connectivity from a new provider or layer new IT services onto your existing network. If your current MAN and WAN connections are satisfactory, you might be inclined to stick with them. However, other factors warrant consideration.
Not all service providers offer bandwidth. Many VoIP, cloud computing, and other specialized providers focus solely on their specific offerings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-wrong-with-bring-your-own-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Cloud In a Kit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</guid><description>Cloud computing offers significant advantages, but you might be hesitant to move your sensitive applications to a public cloud environment. Fortunately, there are alternatives to public clouds. Besides public clouds, there are also private clouds and hybrid clouds. Hybrid clouds combine public and private cloud environments, allowing you to run less sensitive applications on the public cloud while maintaining more sensitive data on a private cloud.
While public cloud cost savings are well-known, you might wonder if private clouds offer similar benefits...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-cloud-in-a-kit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Cloud Data Centers Are Multiplying</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 11:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</guid><description>The number of cloud-based service offerings has significantly increased, with almost every telecom and IT company seemingly having a cloud offering. But what&amp;rsquo;s causing this rapid growth?
There are two primary factors driving the implementation of cloud computing services. First, a robust data center is needed to house all the necessary equipment, along with adequate cooling, backup power, and security. Second, reliable connectivity is crucial. A groundbreaking cloud service is useless if it can&amp;rsquo;t be delivered reliably...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-cloud-data-centers-are-multiplying/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Does Cloud Computing Work In Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 04:04:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</guid><description>The term &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; is frequently used today. But what exactly is it, and how can it benefit your business by improving efficiency, speed, and affordability? Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into it.
In business, the term &amp;ldquo;cloudy&amp;rdquo; often carries a negative connotation, implying uncertainty and unpredictability. Naturally, clarity and predictability are preferred, especially from a financial standpoint. Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s understandable why people might be skeptical when advised to transition their business to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-cloud-computing-work-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How The Cloud Provides Virtualization For The SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:56:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</guid><description>Virtualization has been a popular topic for large businesses for a while. It allows them to maximize their existing resources, turning one server into multiple virtual ones and distributing heavy workloads across platforms. But can smaller businesses also benefit from virtualization?
The answer is a resounding yes, thanks to the cloud. The cloud&amp;rsquo;s power lies in virtualization, enabling it to function as a massive data center accessible to numerous users. By efficiently utilizing virtualization, cloud providers can create an illusion of infinite resources, making each user feel like the sole user...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-the-cloud-provides-virtualization-for-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit and 10 Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 07:44:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you ever wanted to expand your Local Area Network (LAN) to reach locations across a city or even further? A Metro Fiber Ethernet connection can help. This type of connection acts as an extension of your existing LAN, linking multiple locations seamlessly.
The Challenge of Connecting Multiple LANs
Private networks, typically Ethernet LANs, give you complete control within your own space. You manage the cabling, switches, routers, user devices, and overall network operations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-and-10-gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>It's 10:00. Do You Know Where Your Website is?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-1000-do-you-know-where-your-website-is/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-1000-do-you-know-where-your-website-is/</guid><description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t it frustrating when a website goes down? It&amp;rsquo;s like friends playing a prank call with a song about being &amp;ldquo;down.&amp;rdquo; But instead of a song, a downed website means lost business.
Rather than relying on prankster pals, a professional site monitoring service offers a better solution. These services constantly watch for server issues, providing a reliable alternative to friends with questionable humor.
These services don&amp;rsquo;t just point and laugh. They offer detailed data like uptime/downtime graphs, average response times, and error notifications, giving you a comprehensive view of your website&amp;rsquo;s performance over time...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-1000-do-you-know-where-your-website-is/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/its-1000-do-you-know-where-your-website-is/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Vocal IP Networx Offers Free SNMP Monitoring</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely familiar with the challenges of managing T1 lines and bandwidth, especially keeping track of service availability across different vendors and equipment. While large companies have dedicated IT teams, smaller businesses often handle this responsibility as issues arise.
Wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be beneficial to have affordable network monitoring support? Vocal IP Networx, a leading IP telephony provider, offers a solution: free, continuous SNMP monitoring for all circuits and customer premises equipment (CPE) they provide...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/vocal-ip-networx-offers-free-snmp-monitoring/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>