<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/summer/</link><description>Recent content in Summer on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/summer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience Ritu Kumar's summer 2015 collection up close and personal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-ritu-kumar-s-summer-2015-collection-up-close-and-personal/</guid><description>Source: Ritu Kumar website.
High-end Indian fashion house Ritu Kumar has released its Summer 2015 Collection, available now at their flagship Dubai location in the BurJuman Shopping Centre. This collection features pieces from both the Ritu Kumar and Label Ritu Kumar lines.
Designed for the modern woman, the Ritu Kumar Summer 2015 collection provides a variety of styles for day or evening wear, from kurtis to skirts and suits. The line incorporates fabrics like jersey, crepe, cotton georgette, and cotton voile.</description></item><item><title>Abu Dhabi International Airport has increased its summer flights by 18% compared to 2013</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abu-dhabi-international-airport-has-increased-its-summer-flights-by-18-compared-to-2013/</guid><description>Abu Dhabi International Airport&amp;rsquo;s summer 2014 flight schedule is its busiest ever, featuring six new destinations and 71 additional weekly flights to India.
Airport authorities reported an 18% increase in weekly flights compared to the previous summer, rising from 1,052 to 1,242, catering to both business and leisure travelers.
New nonstop routes debuting this summer include flights from Abu Dhabi to Los Angeles, Zurich, Belgrade (Serbia), Perth, Jaipur, and Yerevan (Armenia).</description></item><item><title>Unique guest experiences offered by the Peninsula Academy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unique-guest-experiences-offered-by-the-peninsula-academy/</guid><description>The Peninsula Hotels recently announced their Peninsula Academy Summer programs for this year. The luxury hotel group offers exclusive experiences focused on food, fashion, and art, perfect for corporate events or special clients.
Source: Peninsula Hotels.
Each program includes unique touches like bespoke Peninsula transportation, ranging from private helicopters and chauffeured Rolls-Royces to MINI Cooper S Clubman vehicles.
Here are some highlights from their Asian properties:
The Peninsula Hong Kong presents &amp;ldquo;Caviar Connoisseurship,&amp;rdquo; providing an in-depth look into the world of sustainably-farmed caviars, exploring their distinct qualities and ideal enjoyment methods.</description></item><item><title>Gulf Air reveals its summer 2018 schedule</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 04:13:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-reveals-its-summer-2018-schedule/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air. Plane in Gulf Air livery.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has launched its Summer 2018 schedule, increasing both flight frequency and passenger capacity to popular destinations for the peak travel season between mid-June and mid-September 2018.
Flights to Amman, Jordan, will increase to three times daily, while flights to Beirut, Lebanon, will increase to twice daily. Istanbul, Turkey, a popular summer destination, will have 12 weekly flights during peak season, and flights to Baghdad, Iraq, will permanently increase to five times per week.</description></item><item><title>Get 10% off and receive gifts with the HMH summer offer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-10-off-and-receive-gifts-with-the-hmh-summer-offer/</guid><description>Hospitality Management Holdings (HMH) is offering a summer deal: guests can enjoy a 10% discount on bed and breakfast rates and receive a daily voucher redeemable at any of the hotel&amp;rsquo;s restaurants or spas. This promotion is valid until September 21, 2015.
Laurent Voivenel, CEO of HMH, highlighted the company&amp;rsquo;s presence in 15 cities across the Middle East and North Africa (MENA) region. He stated, &amp;ldquo;Due to significant demand from Saudi Arabia and other GCC countries, over 70% of our rooms have been booked in advance.</description></item><item><title>Experience the ultimate luxury getaway at Mulia Bali and be transported to paradise. #GetRaptured with Mulia Bali</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 13:38:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-ultimate-luxury-getaway-at-mulia-bali-and-be-transported-to-paradise-getraptured-with-mulia-bali/</guid><description>Source: Mulia Bali via TravMedia Asia. RAPTURE logo.
Mulia Bali, a beachfront hotel, invites partygoers to their annual summer event, RAPTURE – Mulia Summer Party, taking place by the hotel&amp;rsquo;s iconic Courtyard Pool and beach. Scheduled for September 1st, this recurring event aims to become a signature experience and set a new standard for daytime parties in Bali.
This end-of-summer celebration will showcase renowned singers, international DJs, dancers, and impressive decor by Mulia.</description></item><item><title>The Global Day of Discovery at Renaissance Hotels worldwide is celebrated on June 26th</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 04:54:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-global-day-of-discovery-at-renaissance-hotels-worldwide-is-celebrated-on-june-26th/</guid><description>Renaissance Hotels is hosting its third annual Global Day of Discovery on June 26th at over 150 locations. On this day, almost every hotel will offer guests and community members the opportunity to explore something new. These events, designed by hotel Navigators, include musical performances, culinary experiences, art displays, cultural activities, and unique local excursions.
This day marks the start of the Renaissance Hotels&amp;rsquo; Summer of Discovery calendar, a summer-long series of exclusive events at all 157 hotels worldwide.</description></item><item><title>Get away to The Meydan Hotel or Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp; Spa this summer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 13:16:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-away-to-the-meydan-hotel-or-bab-al-shams-desert-resort-spa-this-summer/</guid><description>Source: Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality website.
Meydan Hotels &amp;amp; Hospitality is offering a summer promotion called &amp;ldquo;The Great Escape&amp;rdquo; for AED 490 per night at both Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa and The Meydan Hotel until September 30, 2015. This offer is well-suited for short business trips.
Located a 45-minute drive from the city, Bab Al Shams Desert Resort &amp;amp; Spa provides an authentic desert experience amidst the sand dunes.</description></item></channel></rss>