<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Myanmar on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/myanmar/</link><description>Recent content in Myanmar on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/myanmar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor makes a comeback in Myanmar with The Lake Garden in Nay Pyi Taw</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 06:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-makes-a-comeback-in-myanmar-with-the-lake-garden-in-nay-pyi-taw/</guid><description>Source: Accor Hotels. The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw.
Accor, a leading international hotel operator in the Asia-Pacific region, has established its first hotel in Myanmar: The Lake Garden, Nay Pyi Taw. This recently constructed, upscale establishment is part of the MGallery Collection and is conveniently located a short distance from both the Myanmar International Convention Centre (MICC) and Nay Pyi Taw International Airport.
Patrick Basset, Chief Operating Officer for Accor in multiple Southeast Asian nations, highlighted the significance of this opening as it marks Accor&amp;rsquo;s return to Myanmar.</description></item><item><title>Grand Mercure makes its first appearance in Myanmar</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 13:37:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/grand-mercure-makes-its-first-appearance-in-myanmar/</guid><description>AccorHotels has launched its first Grand Mercure hotel in Myanmar. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire, with its 175 guest rooms and suites, provides a view of the Schwedagon Pagoda. Local artist Pyar Dade designed the accommodations.
Source: AccorHotels. The Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire. Patrick Basset, COO of AccorHotels, Upper Southeast and Northeast Asia and the Maldives, stated, “This is our first Grand Mercure in Myanmar and the opening of Grand Mercure Yangon Golden Empire reflects the cultural touchstone of the destination and heritage in bringing local stories to life.</description></item><item><title>Air China's new routes will make traveling between China and Myanmar more convenient</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-china-s-new-routes-will-make-traveling-between-china-and-myanmar-more-convenient/</guid><description>Air China will launch new flight routes connecting Beijing to Yangon and Chengdu to Yangon via Kunming on March 30th. These additions will expand travel options from both the main hub in Beijing and the regional hub in Chengdu.
Source: Air China
At the close of 2013, Air China initiated non-stop flights from Beijing to Chiang Mai and Siem Reap. The airline plans to continue expanding its &amp;ldquo;Pilgrimage Tour&amp;rdquo; offerings in 2014.</description></item><item><title>AirAsia introduces new flights between Penang and Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 18:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airasia-introduces-new-flights-between-penang-and-yangon/</guid><description>AirAsia has launched direct flights connecting Penang to Yangon, Myanmar, making it the airline&amp;rsquo;s seventh international destination accessible from its northern hub. Penang also offers direct flights to other international destinations, such as Ho Chi Minh City, Singapore, Medan, Jakarta, Surabaya, and Bangkok.
This new route will operate three times a week, starting on March 22, 2016. The flight schedule for Penang, Malaysia (PEN) – Yangon, Myanmar (RGN) is as follows:</description></item><item><title>The Traders Hotel in Yangon has been rebranded as the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-traders-hotel-in-yangon-has-been-rebranded-as-the-sule-shangri-la-yangon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 07:26:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-traders-hotel-in-yangon-has-been-rebranded-as-the-sule-shangri-la-yangon/</guid><description>After a comprehensive two-and-a-half-year renovation, Shangri-La Hotels and Resorts has rebranded the Traders Hotel, Yangon in Myanmar to the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon.
Situated on Sule Pagoda Road near its 2,000-year-old namesake, the 484-room hotel has been a prominent landmark in the city&amp;rsquo;s central business district since 1996, remaining a popular hub for business gatherings.
Source: Shangri-la. Service staff in the Peacock Lounge.
While the building&amp;rsquo;s exterior is modern, the lobby of the Sule Shangri-La, Yangon evokes a sense of a bygone colonial era with its white columns and grand staircase leading to an open balcony.</description></item></channel></rss>