<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>EoMPLS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eompls/</link><description>Recent content in EoMPLS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/eompls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is a Virtual Leased Line Right For Your Applications?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-a-virtual-leased-line-right-for-your-applications/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines have been a popular choice for businesses since they were introduced by telephone companies decades ago. This article explores the concept of virtual leased lines and their potential benefits for businesses.
Before delving into virtual leased lines, let&amp;rsquo;s review traditional leased lines and their functionality.
Leased Lines vs Shared Bandwidth
A leased line is a dedicated telecommunications line rented for a specific duration, usually 1 to 3 years.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item></channel></rss>