<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Business Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Strategies For The Hunkered Down Economy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:58:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategies-for-the-hunkered-down-economy/</guid><description>While the new year has arrived, the economic situation remains challenging. Unemployment is still high, companies are focusing on cost-cutting over revenue growth, and uncertainty about the future persists. Consumers are tightening their belts and spending less, leaving businesses with little choice but to do the same. It&amp;rsquo;s understandable to hesitate before making significant moves when the path ahead is unclear.
Does this mean your business is stuck or in irreversible decline?</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry.</description></item><item><title>Cheaper DS3 Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 07:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cheaper-ds3-connections/</guid><description>Your business needs more bandwidth, but the price of a DS3 connection might seem daunting. While upgrading from a T1 line to a DS3 might have seemed expensive in the past, prices have gone down. Even with the current economic climate, a DS3 connection could now be within your budget.
DS3, or Data Service level 3, is a digital telecommunications standard initially designed for telephone systems. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the T-Carrier system and works seamlessly with SONET fiber optic networks.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth To Support Branch Offices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:46:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-to-support-branch-offices/</guid><description>Many businesses need multiple locations in a region to stay close to their customers. Connecting these branches seamlessly without breaking the bank is a common challenge. Thankfully, two high-performance networking technologies, Metro Ethernet and MPLS Networks, offer affordable solutions that weren&amp;rsquo;t available even a decade ago.
Carrier Ethernet takes the local networking capabilities of Ethernet and extends them across entire cities. This means easy connection and efficient transmission without needing protocol conversions.</description></item><item><title>Broadband For The Home Office</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:26:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/broadband-for-the-home-office/</guid><description>Home office users have a lot of choices when it comes to internet bandwidth, from basic residential DSL and cable to professional options like FIOS, Business DSL, T1, or even Carrier Ethernet. Which one is the right fit? Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of what&amp;rsquo;s available and what makes sense for home-based work.
Residential broadband services are often the best choice for home offices, primarily because they&amp;rsquo;re the most affordable. These services are usually confined to residential areas.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper vs Bonded T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 02:32:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-bonded-t1/</guid><description>T1 lines have long been considered a reliable connection option for small to medium businesses, gaining traction as prices dropped in recent years. However, a new technology called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) offers even greater bandwidth at a lower cost and with simpler connectivity.
EoC, like T1, uses existing twisted-pair telephone wiring commonly found in business locations. Traditional T1 lines use two twisted pairs within this wiring, allowing for simultaneous two-way data transfer at 1.</description></item><item><title>Increasing Bandwidth By Pair Bonding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</guid><description>When your T1 line starts reaching its bandwidth limit, upgrading to a DS3 line might seem like the next step, but it comes with challenges. DS3 often requires fiber optic cable instead of the copper used for T1, and the cost difference is significant.
A simpler solution for a moderate bandwidth boost is adding another T1 line and using &amp;ldquo;pair bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines two lines into one, effectively doubling your bandwidth to 3 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet.</description></item><item><title>T1 Broadband For Rural Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-broadband-for-rural-business/</guid><description>Government funding is being used to expand rural broadband access, as it&amp;rsquo;s generally understood that service providers have overlooked these areas due to their sparse populations. But what about businesses in these locations? Do they face similar internet limitations?
In most cases, businesses in rural areas shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be deprived of reliable internet any more than they are deprived of multi-line phone service. The existing copper telephone lines can also deliver broadband.</description></item><item><title>FastE and GigE WAN Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 03:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-and-gige-wan-connections/</guid><description>While businesses require increasing bandwidth, their budgets remain stagnant. This begs the question: will companies face limitations in throughput, potentially losing customers due to slow e-commerce websites?
Not necessarily. There&amp;rsquo;s a solution called Ethernet that can provide the necessary network performance for productivity and customer satisfaction.
Standard 10 Mbps Ethernet connections are widely accessible via copper or fiber optic cable. Faster options are also offered: Fast Ethernet (FastE) at 100 Mbps and Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) at 1000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit to 10 Gigabit to 100 Gigabit WAN</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:28:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-to-10-gigabit-to-100-gigabit-wan/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As more business operations transition to the cloud and remote work becomes increasingly common, the demand for robust Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth has surged. Fortunately, providers offer excellent solutions for establishing high-bandwidth connections between locations and to the internet.
Fiber Optic Ethernet WAN
Fiber optic connectivity has become the leading choice for business bandwidth. Businesses still relying on older technologies like T1 lines, ISDN PRI, or DS3 bandwidth may be facing limitations and nearing obsolescence.</description></item><item><title>DS1 Bandwidth vs Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds1-bandwidth-vs-ethernet/</guid><description>DS1, commonly called T1, is a popular choice for business internet. This article will explain DS1 and compare it to another popular option: Ethernet over Copper.
While the terms are often used synonymously, DS1 and T1 are slightly different. They both come from a set of technical standards created by Bell Labs called the T-carrier system, which was originally a digital replacement for analog phone lines. Though designed for telephones, DS1 and T1 are now widely used for dedicated internet connections and private lines.</description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Cost Reduction Ideas</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-cost-reduction-ideas/</guid><description>Getting the best price on everything your business buys is crucial for success, and bandwidth is no exception. Telecom expenses can be significant, but there are ways to save without sacrificing productivity.
One surprisingly simple step is to get updated competitive quotes. Bandwidth prices change rapidly, so your current understanding might be outdated.
While gathering quotes used to be time-consuming, online tools like GeoQuote by Telarus have simplified the process. This automated engine collects pricing from various providers, delivering budgetary quotes for services like T1, ISDN PRI, DS3, and Ethernet connections almost instantly.</description></item><item><title>How Many T1 Lines Do You Need?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 12:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-t1-lines-do-you-need/</guid><description>For small businesses dissatisfied with DSL or Cable broadband, a professional T1 line might seem like the ideal solution. The superior reliability and dedicated bandwidth make T1 lines the popular choice for business voice and data services. However, as your business expands, you might encounter the bandwidth limitations of your once-sufficient T1 line. What then?
Similarly, high-tech businesses, such as Wireless Internet Service Providers (WISPs) or video production companies, might find the 1.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Fiber Needed By Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-fiber-needed-by-business/</guid><description>While many believe fiber optic bandwidth is the way of the future, it&amp;rsquo;s already a smart choice for businesses today.
Traditionally, businesses have depended on copper-based telecom services. The copper wiring integrated during a building&amp;rsquo;s construction becomes the backbone for multi-line phone systems, ISDN digital trunking for PBX systems, and T1 lines connecting offices and providing broadband internet. This infrastructure has been the standard for many small and medium-sized businesses for decades.</description></item><item><title>A Glass Belt to Transform the Rust Belt</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-glass-belt-to-transform-the-rust-belt/</guid><description>Hidden beneath the cornfields of Northern Illinois is a unique triangle, often compared to the Bermuda Triangle, but with a positive twist. Unlike its infamous counterpart, this triangle doesn&amp;rsquo;t make things disappear but instead makes poverty, unemployment, and economic decline vanish. It transforms the remnants of the &amp;ldquo;rust belt&amp;rdquo; into a technological hub for the information age.
This modern marvel comprises a network of fiber optic cables buried alongside three major highways: I-88, I-90, and I-39.</description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers.</description></item><item><title>Twice the T1 Line Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 19:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/twice-the-t1-line-bandwidth/</guid><description>Is your internet connection feeling a little slow? That T1 line that used to be more than enough might be struggling to keep up with your current needs. You&amp;rsquo;re not the only one experiencing this. While T1 bandwidth was sufficient for even large companies a decade ago, today, even small and medium-sized businesses are finding themselves needing more. The shift towards online applications and connectivity, while beneficial for productivity, has led to a significant increase in bandwidth demands.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Bandwidth is Downright Cheap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 18:07:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-bandwidth-is-downright-cheap/</guid><description>Business bandwidth solutions are significantly more expensive than residential options like DSL or Cable. While this is partly due to their guaranteed reliability and dedicated lines, another factor is the complex infrastructure involved. Providing business-grade services often requires collaboration between a long-haul carrier and the local phone company for the final connection.
Despite recent price drops in dedicated T1 connections, high-bandwidth services remain costly, potentially hindering smaller companies needing to transmit large amounts of data.</description></item><item><title>What Is The Real T1 Line Speed?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-real-t1-line-speed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-the-real-t1-line-speed/</guid><description>A T1 line is often described as a 1.5 Mbps dedicated bandwidth connection, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually a bit more nuanced than that. The true speed is 1.544 Mbps, with a usable payload of 1.536 Mbps.
The reason for this difference lies in the T1 line&amp;rsquo;s structure and history. Developed by Bell Labs for telephone companies in the 1950s, T1 lines aimed to improve upon the limitations of analog systems. While utilizing existing copper wiring, T1 lines transmit digital signals, unlike the analog signals used in older phone systems.</description></item><item><title>What Is a DS3 Circuit Or T3 Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line often choose DS3. This article explores DS3, its relationship to T3 lines, and competition from Ethernet over Copper.
DS3, or Digital Signal level 3, follows standards set by Bell Labs for the telephone industry. The smallest unit, DS0, has a 64 Kbps bandwidth, enough for one digitized phone call using the original digital standard, PCM (Pulse Code Modulation). Combining 24 DS0s creates a DS1, which runs on a T1 line.</description></item><item><title>Fractional DS3 Applications</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 23:40:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fractional-ds3-applications/</guid><description>The most popular high-reliability broadband option for businesses, T1 lines, are widely accessible, budget-friendly for most small and medium-sized businesses, and come with various options like PBX telephone lines, dedicated internet, point-to-point electronic data interchange, and Integrated T1 (voice and data combined). The main issue with T1 service is the possibility of outgrowing its capacity.
T1 connections offer 1.5 Mbps full-duplex bandwidth, also known as symmetrical, for internet service, providing 1.</description></item><item><title>The Age Of Managed Networks Is Upon Us</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 16:13:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-age-of-managed-networks-is-upon-us/</guid><description>The business world is changing, and AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s latest move is proof: they&amp;rsquo;re offering free 24/7 network monitoring to their MPLS customers. This means constant oversight and immediate alerts if something goes wrong, even in the dead of night.
This signals a larger trend: managed WAN services are becoming the new normal. For decades, businesses handled their own networks, setting up equipment, monitoring connections, and troubleshooting issues. Large companies needing round-the-clock service had their own dedicated network operations centers.</description></item><item><title>Telecommunication DS3 Affordable For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:40:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telecommunication-ds3-affordable-for-business/</guid><description>Modern businesses need increasing levels of bandwidth to accommodate computer-driven processes that enhance productivity. When a T1 line reaches its capacity, and more bandwidth is necessary, there are options to consider.
A logical next step, if bandwidth needs have gradually increased, is to bond a second T1 line with the first. This doubles the capacity, providing a 3 Mbps WAN connection. Additional T1 lines can be bonded to further multiply the bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Community Builds Infrastructure</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:57:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-community-builds-infrastructure/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a narrative circulating that our infrastructure is failing. While this might be true in some areas, a massive construction project is currently underway to create a robust fiber optic network across the nation. This &amp;ldquo;nervous system&amp;rdquo; for information technology promises practically limitless, low-lag bandwidth for the foreseeable future.
This surge in fiber optic infrastructure isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by failing systems, but rather by existing infrastructure reaching full capacity. The late 20th century witnessed a fiber optic boom, which initially seemed excessive when the tech bubble burst.</description></item><item><title>10 Gbps Dedicated Internet Access Availability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-gbps-dedicated-internet-access-availability/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Previously thought to be an excessive amount of bandwidth only suitable for large telecom companies, 10 Gbps connections are quickly becoming the desired level of connectivity for businesses, local governments, medical facilities, content creators, and online retailers. The good news is this bandwidth level is now attainable at a reasonable cost.
Where Can I Get 10 Gbps Dedicated Internet? 10 Gigabit Ethernet service is now commonly available in most cities due to the widespread adoption of fiber optic infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Gigabit Prices On Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 05:45:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-gigabit-prices-on-demand/</guid><description>Modern businesses are increasing their reliance on bandwidth-intensive applications like video and cloud-based solutions, putting a strain on their Wide Area Networks (WANs). While evaluating bandwidth needs and exploring the best deals seems logical, it can often feel complicated. However, new tools are emerging to simplify this process.
Traditionally, obtaining competitive telecom prices meant identifying local carriers, navigating through voicemail systems, enduring endless phone tag, and deciphering complex quotes to ensure accurate comparisons.</description></item><item><title>Gigabit Wireless For TDM and IP Transport</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 19:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-wireless-for-tdm-and-ip-transport/</guid><description>XO Communications uses BridgeWave Communications&amp;rsquo; FlexPort link to provide gigabit bandwidth services to buildings without a fiber connection. This wireless technology eliminates the need for physical cables and offers high-bandwidth connectivity through the air.
While copper cables and microwave wireless are suitable for moderate bandwidth, fixed wireless systems using millimeter wave transmissions can deliver fiber-like performance without physical fiber optic cables. Laser-based solutions are also available for shorter distances, but BridgeWave excels in connecting networks over several miles.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Internet Is a Reality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-internet-is-a-reality/</guid><description>Internet access has evolved from slow modems, but connecting still requires converting between protocols and Ethernet used in offices. Now, direct Ethernet internet is possible.
Ethernet for internet access is popular in cities, mainly due to cost savings and simpler networking. Called Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet, it extends your network using Ethernet across cities, countries, or to the internet.
Dedicated Internet Access (DIA) is the top choice for businesses, providing exclusive bandwidth unlike shared services like DSL, WiFi, and cable.</description></item><item><title>Fiber - Dark, Lit and Wavelength</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 16:02:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-dark-lit-and-wavelength/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You&amp;rsquo;ve decided that a fiber optic connection is no longer optional for your business; it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for productivity. The next step is determining which type of fiber to get. You might be surprised to learn there&amp;rsquo;s more than one option.
One Strand, Multiple Options
The foundation of all fiber optic connections is the transmission of information through modulated light waves within a glass strand. The fiber cable entering your building will appear the same regardless of the type.</description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services.</description></item><item><title>Get Your Business Bandwidth Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-business-bandwidth-free/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 04:31:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-your-business-bandwidth-free/</guid><description>Telecommunication expenses are a considerable cost for businesses, but there are ways to reduce them significantly. Beyond switching providers, you can eliminate your bandwidth costs entirely through a real estate model.
Imagine renting an apartment where the rent from other units covers your mortgage, allowing you to live there for free. This principle applies to internet connections as well.
You can become your own service provider by ordering a service and router, then leasing out the bandwidth to neighboring businesses.</description></item><item><title>Why 10 Mbps Ethernet is Replacing T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 13:45:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-10-mbps-ethernet-is-replacing-t1/</guid><description>A significant technological shift is affecting small and medium-sized businesses, particularly in how they connect to the internet. The traditional T1 line, a long-time staple, is being phased out and replaced with newer technologies.
T1 lines were the first broadband option for businesses, offering a reliable 1.5 Mbps symmetrical bandwidth, a significant improvement over dial-up and slower digital lines. Its initial purpose, developed by Bell Labs, was to carry phone conversations between switching centers.</description></item><item><title>GigE For Business Not So Far-Fetched</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gige-for-business-not-so-far-fetched/</guid><description>The increasing demands of online technologies, particularly those using graphics and video, are putting pressure on Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. While ordering a T1 line was once a big decision, businesses may soon need to consider Gigabit Ethernet connections.
While Gigabit Ethernet is often associated with large-scale networks, it&amp;rsquo;s becoming increasingly relevant for businesses. With corporate LANs already transitioning to faster speeds, the WAN connection often becomes a bottleneck.</description></item><item><title>What Makes 10 Mbps Ethernet So Popular?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:25:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-makes-10-mbps-ethernet-so-popular/</guid><description>A popular bandwidth solution for businesses today is 10 Mbps Ethernet. This article will explain what it is and its benefits.
We&amp;rsquo;re referring to Metro Ethernet or Carrier Ethernet connections operating at 10 Mbps. These connections can link two business locations, provide dedicated internet access, or connect to a larger cloud network for broader reach.
Why is 10 Mbps a popular choice? It sits in a &amp;ldquo;sweet spot&amp;rdquo; for bandwidth. While T1 lines at 1.</description></item><item><title>Cable is the New Fiber?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 01:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cable-is-the-new-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Coaxial cable, commonly used by cable providers, was once thought to be outdated. People questioned its capacity for handling numerous channels and high internet speeds. However, it turns out coaxial cable can handle significantly more data than initially believed, reaching speeds up to 10 Gbps.
Fiber Optic Integration
The remarkable 10 Gbps speed, comparable to fiber optic standards, is achieved through a hybrid system. While users only see the coaxial cable connecting their modem, it&amp;rsquo;s just a small segment of the infrastructure.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal.</description></item><item><title>WAN Transparency Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</guid><description>The ideal computer network operates so seamlessly that users don&amp;rsquo;t even realize it&amp;rsquo;s there. They don&amp;rsquo;t think about the technical details, just like they don&amp;rsquo;t think about how electricity works. It&amp;rsquo;s simply a service they can rely on. This is called transparency.
Many local area networks (LANs) already achieve this level of transparency. With most network cards supporting high speeds like Fast Ethernet or Gigabit Ethernet, company LANs can easily handle business needs.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Without The Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-without-the-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If you&amp;rsquo;re facing limited bandwidth or the impending loss of your current copper-based internet service, upgrading to fiber optic bandwidth is the ideal solution. However, the lack of nearby fiber optic infrastructure can present a significant obstacle. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there are alternative solutions that can provide comparable performance without requiring a costly fiber installation.
Alternatives to Fiber Optic Internet The key benefit of fiber optic internet lies in its ability to transmit large amounts of data quickly and reliably.</description></item><item><title>HFC Broadband For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 00:40:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hfc-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>Many small businesses don&amp;rsquo;t fit into the &amp;ldquo;residential&amp;rdquo; user category but don&amp;rsquo;t require or can&amp;rsquo;t afford expensive traditional business telecom services like T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper. One solution is HFC, or Hybrid Fiber Coax, broadband services.
You might know this as &amp;ldquo;Cable broadband for business.&amp;rdquo; Many home-based businesses successfully use it to manage websites, access online information, and send and receive emails. However, ordering residential service for a business location usually results in rejection.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Growing By Leaps and Bounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</guid><description>The hottest new access network service is Ethernet over Copper (EoC), with competitive carriers rushing to expand coverage.
What makes EoC so popular? It stems from evolving network needs. Wide Area Networks (WANs) have been dominated by the telephone industry, adapting phone technology for data and video transmission.
T1 lines, using two pairs of copper telephone wires, have been the standard for businesses needing dedicated Ethernet connections. They offer 1.5 Mbps upload and download speeds.</description></item><item><title>Advantages of Dedicated Point to Point Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 06:05:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/advantages-of-dedicated-point-to-point-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
If your business&amp;rsquo;s broadband internet is causing you problems, you might want to consider dedicated point-to-point lines. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore what they are and how they can benefit you.
What Does Dedicated Mean?
Dedicated means you have exclusive access to the bandwidth you pay for.
You might wonder, &amp;ldquo;Isn&amp;rsquo;t all bandwidth dedicated if I&amp;rsquo;m paying for it?&amp;rdquo;
Here&amp;rsquo;s where it gets a little complicated. Broadband providers often advertise services with phrases like &amp;ldquo;bandwidth up to 300 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Why Carriers Are Transforming Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 10:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-carriers-are-transforming-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>Telecommunication companies today seem to have discovered a modern-day philosopher&amp;rsquo;s stone. They are not turning lead into gold, but converting old copper wiring into high-speed fiber optic cables, a transformation proving to be highly profitable.
While copper wire infrastructure has been the backbone of the telecom industry for over a century, its limitations are becoming increasingly apparent in our data-driven world. Although abundant and previously profitable, copper is being outshined by fiber optic technology.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Now Faster and Cheaper Than T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 21:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-now-faster-and-cheaper-than-t1/</guid><description>For a long time, T1 lines have been the top choice for bandwidth for small and medium businesses. They are popular for good reason: they are widely available, reliable, secure, dedicated, adaptable, and relatively affordable.
While T1 services have many advantages, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to get even more value: Ethernet, particularly Ethernet over Copper.
Many people are not familiar with Carrier Ethernet services, as they have only become available recently. Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is primarily found in large cities, as it has a limited reach and requires businesses to be within a few miles of the provider&amp;rsquo;s office.</description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption.</description></item><item><title>Backing Up Broadband</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backing-up-broadband/</guid><description>Over the past few decades, broadband internet has become essential for businesses, with speeds and data usage skyrocketing. This begs the question: what happens if your internet goes down?
We&amp;rsquo;ve Quietly Become Dependent The shift to digital operations has been so gradual that many businesses don&amp;rsquo;t realize the impact of a complete internet outage. You understand the consequences of a power outage, but have you considered how to maintain operations if your internet connection fails?</description></item><item><title>Copper Ethernet Line Prices Instantly!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 22:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/copper-ethernet-line-prices-instantly-/</guid><description>Businesses are increasingly choosing Ethernet over Copper (EoC) for its impressive bandwidth and affordability. If EoC is an option, its value proposition is quite compelling. Curious about the specifics? You can easily find out how much bandwidth is available and the potential cost savings. Explore current Ethernet over Copper prices instantly!
Thanks to the Telarus GeoQuote automated pricing system, you can receive immediate Ethernet quotes whenever you need them. Simply input your information on the user-friendly form at CopperEthernet.</description></item><item><title>Looking For A Lit Building?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:08:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/looking-for-a-lit-building/</guid><description>When seeking high-speed internet for your business, you need more than just a building with lights on at night. You need a &amp;ldquo;lit building&amp;rdquo; – one connected to a fiber optic network.
Fiber optic connectivity is crucial for high bandwidth. While most buildings have copper wiring for traditional phone lines and T1 connections, these offer limited bandwidth (1.5 Mbps per line). Fiber optics, on the other hand, provide significantly faster speeds (10 Gbps or more per fiber) using light to transmit data.</description></item><item><title>Why Ethernet Broadband For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-ethernet-broadband-for-business/</guid><description>When considering broadband, we usually think of DSL, cable internet, or cellular wireless. However, these options are typically consumer-grade and might not be suitable for business needs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why these services might be frustrating for businesses and examine a promising alternative.
Cellular wireless, including 3G and 4G, relies on cell towers with limited bandwidth shared among many users. Smartphones consume significant bandwidth, and a high concentration of devices can overload the network.</description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Broadband Includes Canada &amp; Puerto Rico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 09:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-broadband-includes-canada-puerto-rico/</guid><description>People often associate broadband with wired connections, like T1 lines commonly used by small to medium businesses, or the increasingly popular Ethernet option known for its speed and affordability. While satellite is vital for many chain stores, there&amp;rsquo;s another reliable broadband solution that avoids construction costs and high monthly fees: fixed wireless broadband, now available across the US, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Accel Networks, a leading provider of fixed wireless broadband, leverages existing 2.</description></item><item><title>FastE Is The New DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 20:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-is-the-new-ds3/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than their T1 lines can provide have usually upgraded to DS3. However, a faster and more affordable option, Fast Ethernet (FastE), is now available.
While you might not know Fast Ethernet as a Metro or Carrier bandwidth service, the term is likely familiar. Fast Ethernet refers to 100 Mbps Ethernet, one of the standard LAN speeds alongside 10 Mbps and 1,000 Mbps Ethernet (Gigabit Ethernet or GigE).</description></item><item><title>Colocation Hosting Offers Lower Costs and More</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/colocation-hosting-offers-lower-costs-and-more/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Traditionally, medium to large businesses have relied on their own data centers. While this might still be the best option for some, there are benefits to moving some equipment and data to a colocation hosting facility. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why this could be advantageous.
What Exactly is Colocation?
Colocation implies having multiple operations in a single location, and that&amp;rsquo;s essentially what it is. Initially called carrier hotels, colocation facilities housed equipment from various service providers within a building managed by a carrier or a third party.</description></item><item><title>20 to 100 Mbps Metro Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 12:32:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/20-to-100-mbps-metro-ethernet/</guid><description>Businesses often lease telecommunication lines for private internet access or Wide Area Network (WAN) connections. These WAN links can stretch across cities, states, or even internationally. However, for connecting locations within the same city, a Metropolitan Area Network (MAN) is the solution.
Metropolitan Ethernet, or Metro E, is a new type of MAN. Its highlights include a wide range of bandwidth options, easy scalability, new standardized services, simple LAN integration, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom services.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Service FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 18:53:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-service-faq/</guid><description>Fiber optic internet has rapidly replaced older copper wire connections. Before renewing or signing a new internet contract, review these FAQs to help select the best service option for your business.
Q: Why is fiber optic service preferable to copper?
A: Bandwidth needs have grown significantly in recent years, while fiber optic prices have gone down. You can often obtain higher bandwidth with fiber optic compared to copper at a similar price.</description></item><item><title>Internet Bandwidth Connections For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-bandwidth-connections-for-business/</guid><description>Internet access can be grouped into three main types: consumer broadband for homes, dedicated bandwidth for businesses, and mobile broadband (3G/4G). While mobile broadband caters to both individuals and businesses, fixed wireline connections are generally split between business and consumer use.
This distinction exists because of the trade-off between cost and performance. Consumer internet, including home-based businesses, falls under &amp;ldquo;information services,&amp;rdquo; not &amp;ldquo;telecom services.&amp;rdquo; This means they have less regulation and fewer guarantees for customers.</description></item><item><title>Find The Ethernet Internet Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-the-ethernet-internet-connection/</guid><description>Looking for increased bandwidth for your business without the high price tag? An Ethernet Internet connection might be the solution you need.
Ethernet Internet connections are a newer offering. While we’ve utilized Ethernet in our local area networks for years and the internet itself aligns with LAN Ethernet, connecting the two has involved specialized telecom services.
You likely currently have T1 or DS3 service, which require specific equipment and software for protocol conversion and signal interfacing with standard network Ethernet ports.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Connectivity Options For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</guid><description>Most medium to large businesses, and even some smaller ones with high bandwidth needs, can now afford fiber optic bandwidth. This is due to lower prices and a wider range of options, which is great news for those who need a lot of bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these options that you may not be aware of.
Fiber optic bandwidth services generally fall into two categories: traditional time division multiplexed technology, originating from telephone company research, and newer IP-centric networks offered by both competitive service providers and traditional telecom carriers.</description></item><item><title>Business Gigabit Ethernet Bandwidth Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 18:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-gigabit-ethernet-bandwidth-advantage/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your bandwidth if you&amp;rsquo;re relying on older technologies like bonded T1, DS3, OC3, or OC12 fiber and finding them insufficient. Gigabit service might be a practical and budget-friendly solution if you make informed choices. One option that might be newer than your current contract is Gigabit Ethernet.
You might be wondering why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t just upgrade your existing circuit-switched lines instead of switching to Gigabit Ethernet.</description></item><item><title>Easy Migration from T1 to Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 07:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/easy-migration-from-t1-to-ethernet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many long-time users of T1 lines are finding that the bandwidth is no longer sufficient for their needs. A logical upgrade for most businesses is Ethernet, which is easily and affordably implemented.
Don’t Write Off T1 Yet
Despite its age, the wide availability of T1 lines makes them a convenient option. Originally designed for the telephone industry, T1 lines were later adapted for computer communications. With 1.5 Mbps bi-directional capacity, T1 has long been the standard for small and medium businesses; however, this bandwidth is now considered barely broadband.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Solutions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-solutions/</guid><description>Traditional business bandwidth solutions, typically offering low to moderate speeds, have long relied on T1 lines and their bonded counterparts. However, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) solutions are rapidly replacing these older technologies, delivering enhanced bandwidth at a lower cost.
We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on services ranging from 1 to 20 Mbps, encompassing both dedicated point-to-point private lines and dedicated internet connections. Ethernet standards also enable private LAN services, facilitating connections between multiple business locations.</description></item><item><title>MegaPath Puts Your Complete Office In The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:47:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-puts-your-complete-office-in-the-cloud/</guid><description>You might be interested in cloud services, but the process of ordering and integrating them can be overwhelming. Now, a new solution offers a comprehensive bundle of IT services tailored for small businesses at an affordable price.
](http://www.cloudnetworkingservices.com/)
Small businesses often don&amp;rsquo;t need or can&amp;rsquo;t afford large-scale IT infrastructure. Expensive VoIP phone systems and on-site data centers are impractical for companies with limited staff and resources. While cost savings were previously linked to scale, hosted solutions have revolutionized this.</description></item></channel></rss>