<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IDC on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/idc/</link><description>Recent content in IDC on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/idc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Small and medium-sized enterprises and consumers will reap the rewards as banks increase their focus on innovation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 07:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</guid><description>Several financial institutions in the Asia Pacific region were honored at the Asian Financial Services (AFS) Congress 2014 in Singapore for their innovative banking solutions.
AllianceBank Malaysia received the &amp;ldquo;Asia&amp;rsquo;s Most Customer Friendly Bank&amp;rdquo; award for its BizSmart Academy initiative, which supports young SMEs through business education, coaching, and seed funding. The program is open to both existing and new customers.
The bank provides participants with a year-long curriculum covering management, business, and finance topics...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/small-and-medium-sized-enterprises-and-consumers-will-reap-the-rewards-as-banks-increase-their-focus-on-innovation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Online retailing is becoming increasingly popular for smartphones in China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</guid><description>Want to expand your customer base? Consider partnering with an e-mall, especially in China. A recent IDC Mobile Phone Tracker report indicates a rise in the share of e-tailers, like JD, Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Tmall, and Suning Yigou, in China&amp;rsquo;s smartphone market, from 14% in Q2 2014 to 21% in Q2 2015. This translates to a 58% year-on-year surge in the number of smartphones sold via these online platforms.
Tay Xiaohan, a Senior Market Analyst at IDC Asia/Pacific&amp;rsquo;s Client Devices team, highlights that as operators scale back smartphone subsidies, vendors find more opportunities in the open market, with e-tailers emerging as a crucial channel...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/online-retailing-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-for-smartphones-in-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>According to the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, Singaporean small and medium-sized businesses are leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:23:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</guid><description>Source: Cisco ebook. This Cisco report, the APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index, evaluates digital maturity based on four key aspects.
· Singaporean SMBs achieved the highest ranking on the Cisco APAC SMB Digital Maturity Index.
· Cybersecurity is the primary technology that Singaporean SMBs are investing in, followed by cloud computing and analytics.
· The most significant challenges cited by SMBs across Singapore are a shortage of digital skills and talent within their organizations and a lack of understanding of operational and customer data...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-the-cisco-apac-smb-digital-maturity-index-singaporean-small-and-medium-sized-businesses-are-leading-the-way/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Less expensive smartphones are available for those in developing markets</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</guid><description>To prepare for future growth, smartphone manufacturers are looking beyond China to other emerging markets. Although China represented a third of global smartphone shipments in 2013, the International Data Corporation (IDC) indicates this market is reaching its saturation point.
IDC reports that smartphones constitute over 80% of China&amp;rsquo;s total phone sales. Consequently, they predict that India and Africa will be the primary sources of the next half billion smartphone customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/less-expensive-smartphones-are-available-for-those-in-developing-markets/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC Financial Insights selects the top 50 mobile innovators in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>At the start of 2014, IDC Financial Insights released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Mobilizing Financial Services in Asia/Pacific,&amp;rdquo; which highlighted the most innovative mobile initiatives in the financial services sector. They recently shared an infographic summarizing their findings.
The report identifies Australia, mainland China, Hong Kong, India, South Korea, and Singapore as frontrunners in mobile adoption within the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan).
IDC Financial Insights emphasizes a significant opportunity for mobile commerce growth, fueled by increasing mobile device usage in Asia and a strong consumer interest in mobile payments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-financial-insights-selects-the-top-50-mobile-innovators-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Augmented Reality (AR) and Virtual Reality (VR) are showing potential in the Asia-Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 01:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Spending on augmented reality (AR) and virtual reality (VR) in the Asia Pacific region (excluding Japan), also known as APeJ, is projected to hit $11.1 billion in 2018. This represents a significant increase of over 100% compared to the $4.6 billion spent in the previous year, according to research firm IDC.
IDC&amp;rsquo;s latest Worldwide Semiannual Augmented and Virtual Reality Spending Guide reveals that investments in AR/VR technology have gained substantial momentum in 2018...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/augmented-reality-ar-and-virtual-reality-vr-are-showing-potential-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IDC reveals the preferences of APAC consumers when it comes to mobile devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 05:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</guid><description>The International Data Corporation (IDC) has released an infographic that reveals how consumers in the Asia Pacific region make decisions about mobile devices. Key findings from the Essential Guide to Device Decisions of a Connected Consumer in Asia Pacific report include:
Source: IDC infographic. What consumers like about bigger phone screens.
77% of surveyed consumers reported having a larger smartphone now than their previous device, while only 8% opted for a smaller one...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/idc-reveals-the-preferences-of-apac-consumers-when-it-comes-to-mobile-devices/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year in the Philippines, the focus is on mobile technology</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 05:08:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</guid><description>In the Philippines, technology is synonymous with mobile technology.
According to Jubert Alberto, Research Manager at IDC Philippines, &amp;ldquo;The younger generation is entering the workforce, and they have a strong desire to be connected, informed, and entertained. They also tend to have fewer dependents. These factors indicate a growing demand for all things mobile, including devices, services, and applications.&amp;rdquo; IDC predicts that the Philippines will experience a 22% rise in smartphone spending and a 40% increase in tablet expenditure in 2014, fueled by a positive economic outlook...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-in-the-philippines-the-focus-is-on-mobile-technology/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>