<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Long Distance Calls on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-calls/</link><description>Recent content in Long Distance Calls on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/long-distance-calls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Call Overseas For Pennies From Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>With cell phones now serving as both personal and business lines, affordable landline long distance isn&amp;rsquo;t very useful. The real desire is for better rates on mobile phones. Considering you already have domestic calling and internet, the missing piece is inexpensive international calling.
TEL3 recognized this trend and developed their TEL3Advantage service for mobile users in the US and Canada. Many people need to call contacts internationally, but affordable mobile options have been limited until now...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/call-overseas-for-pennies-from-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Add International Calling To Your Cell Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 16:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</guid><description>Most people primarily use mobile phones, but many US calling plans have limited international options, often with very high rates. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a solution that lets you make affordable international calls without changing your current plan.
This solution is an add-on service called TEL3Advantage. It offers incredibly low rates, such as 1 cent per minute to China, 1.4 cents to Berlin, and less than a penny to Canada. The best part is that this service works on any touch-tone phone, including your landline...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-international-calling-to-your-cell-phone/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Phone Power’s $14.95 A Month VoIP Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 08:50:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</guid><description>Are you thinking about switching to VoIP phone service, but put off by the high prices? That doesn&amp;rsquo;t make sense! VoIP is meant to be a cheaper alternative to traditional landlines. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, there&amp;rsquo;s still hope. Phone Power offers a fully featured residential and home office VoIP service for only $14.95 per month.
That&amp;rsquo;s more like it! Why pay $25 or $35 per month for local and long-distance calling when you can get the same or better service for $14...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/phone-power-s-1495-a-month-voip-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Get a Toll Free Number Instantly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 07:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/</guid><description>When starting a new business or expanding an existing one, a toll-free number can significantly enhance sales and customer service. Contrary to common belief, obtaining a toll-free number doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a lengthy waiting period. Services like Kall8 provide an almost instant setup process, allowing businesses to acquire an 800, 855, 866, 877, or 888 number swiftly.
Kall8 simplifies the process through its online system, which houses a vast selection of pre-established toll-free numbers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-a-toll-free-number-instantly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>