<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>PCI DSS on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pci-dss/</link><description>Recent content in PCI DSS on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 05:34:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/pci-dss/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Do You Need A Managed Security Services Provider?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 05:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-a-managed-security-services-provider/</guid><description>Cybercrime has evolved from mere mischief into a substantial threat focused on financial gain. If your network holds valuable data, cybercriminals will see it as a target, making network security essential.
Protecting your digital assets isn&amp;rsquo;t optional; the choice lies in managing it yourself or outsourcing it to managed security services, also known as Security as a Service (SaaS).
MegaPath, a prominent carrier, provides comprehensive managed security services, including firewalls, intrusion prevention, malware and virus protection, web filtering, anti-spam measures, application control, data leak prevention, log management, vulnerability assessments, security information management, and file integrity monitoring.</description></item><item><title>Windstream’s Enterprise Level Managed Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 06:15:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/windstream-s-enterprise-level-managed-security/</guid><description>As your organization grows, so does the importance of network security. With more assets to protect, more entry points for threats, and a wider impact from breaches, larger organizations face greater scrutiny from regulatory bodies like HIPAA for healthcare and PCI DSS for finance. Simple firewalls, while suitable for smaller entities, lack the capacity and sophistication to handle the complex security needs of organizations with hundreds or thousands of users. Some large organizations opt to build in-house security teams, but many find that managed security services offer a more cost-effective alternative.</description></item></channel></rss>