<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Skincare on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skincare/</link><description>Recent content in Skincare on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/skincare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Herbalife introduces a new skincare line to the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/herbalife-introduces-a-new-skincare-line-to-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Herbalife, a nutrition company, has expanded its product line with the launch of Herbalife SKIN, a new skincare collection available in Asia Pacific markets. This line complements Herbalife&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;outer nutrition&amp;rdquo; range, which focuses on achieving healthy, youthful skin through a blend of natural ingredients, botanicals, extracts, and scientific formulation.
[Image of Herbalife logo]
Herbalife SKIN products are designed to create softer, smoother, and more radiant skin while minimizing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles.</description></item><item><title>LG introduces a new high-end beauty brand for the home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 06:02:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lg-introduces-a-new-high-end-beauty-brand-for-the-home/</guid><description>LG Electronics (LG) has introduced LG Pra.L, its high-end line of at-home beauty devices, in Singapore. The collection includes four devices: the Dual Cleanser, Galvanic Ion Booster, Total Lift Up Care, and Derma LED Mask, each designed to cleanse, nourish, lift, and firm the skin.
Inspired by the idea that beauty comes from within, LG Pra.L aims to elevate skincare routines for quicker, visible results. All four devices prioritize user convenience with features like silicone handles for grip, voice-guided instructions, USB-C charging, and long battery life for portability.</description></item><item><title>Organic cosmetics are becoming increasingly popular</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/organic-cosmetics-are-becoming-increasingly-popular/</guid><description>A new report from TechSci Research, titled Global Organic Cosmetics Market By Product Type, By Point of Sale, By Region, Competition Forecast and Opportunities, 2011 - 2021, reveals that the global organic cosmetics market is expected to experience significant growth through 2021. This growth is driven by rising health concerns and a growing awareness of the negative effects of conventional cosmetic chemicals, coupled with the benefits offered by organic alternatives.</description></item><item><title>Dermatologists have created a one-of-a-kind hand sanitizer</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 03:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dermatologists-have-created-a-one-of-a-kind-hand-sanitizer/</guid><description>● Developed by dermatologists with a deep understanding of skin care and patient requirements.
● Eliminates 99.99% of common household germs and viruses, including SARS-COV-2, upon application.
● Remains effective for 24 hours, even after handwashing, minimizing the need for frequent reapplication.
DS Skin Clinic and its global network of clinics have introduced the DS Skin Clinic All-Day Hand Sanitizer. This innovative product is engineered to outperform existing hand sanitizers available in the market.</description></item><item><title>Adapt your beauty routine to the changing weather conditions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 01:51:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/adapt-your-beauty-routine-to-the-changing-weather-conditions/</guid><description>Mintel Beauty &amp;amp; Personal Care (BPC) has recognized a new global beauty trend: seasonality. This trend reflects how different weather conditions influence beauty routines.
Source: Mintel website.
According to Mintel BPC, product launches related to this trend significantly increased from 9.8% in 2011 to 11.1% in 2014. This is particularly noticeable in facial skincare, where seasonal product launches grew from a mere 0.5% in 2009 to 1.2% in 2014.
Jane Henderson, Global President of Mintel’s Beauty and Personal Care Division, notes a growing consumer awareness of how environmental changes impact their skin and hair.</description></item><item><title>Fenty Skin has been launched worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fenty-skin-has-been-launched-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 20:16:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fenty-skin-has-been-launched-worldwide/</guid><description>Fenty Skin, the skincare line launched by Rihanna, is expanding its reach to 30 countries. The brand is now available at select Sephora and Harvey Nichols locations in the Asia Pacific and Middle East regions. This includes Sephora stores in countries like Australia, Bahrain, and Malaysia, as well as Harvey Nichols in Hong Kong.
Source: Fenty. From left: Total Cleans’r Remove-It-All Cleanser, Fat Water Pore-Refining Toner Serum, Hydra Vizor Invisible Moisturizer Broad Spectrum Spf 30 Sunscreen &amp;amp; Instant Reset Overnight Recovery Gel-Cream.</description></item><item><title>Biotherm Homme releases kite surfing video in collaboration with The Dose skincare</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 04:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/biotherm-homme-releases-kite-surfing-video-in-collaboration-with-the-dose-skincare/</guid><description>Source: L&amp;rsquo;Oréal.
Biotherm Homme, a high-end men&amp;rsquo;s skincare brand, has introduced &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; a product line designed to address the daily needs of men across four areas: feeling refreshed, energized, youthful, and charismatic.
To showcase &amp;ldquo;The Dose,&amp;rdquo; Biotherm Homme has also created an immersive 360° video featuring Youri Zoon, a world champion kitesurfer, as he executes awe-inspiring stunts. Want to learn more? Experience it firsthand.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor reports that skincare is a popular trend</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-reports-that-skincare-is-a-popular-trend/</guid><description>Euromonitor International has reported that the global beauty industry is experiencing growth, particularly in emerging markets, as consumers increasingly adopt more comprehensive beauty routines and upgrade to premium products.
Skincare stands out as the dominant segment in most markets, with global sales projected to exceed US$130 billion by 2019. &amp;ldquo;Consumers are allocating a significant portion of their beauty spending on skincare, averaging US$15 per person annually,&amp;rdquo; notes Irina Barbalova, Head of Beauty and Personal Care at Euromonitor International.</description></item><item><title>Ginvera and Wipro Unza are the top brands on mass-market facial cleanser shelves</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 16:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ginvera-and-wipro-unza-are-the-top-brands-on-mass-market-facial-cleanser-shelves/</guid><description>Numerous facial cleansers are available at supermarkets, with prices starting at S$3.85 for a 100g tube. This article compares a selection of these cleansers to the author&amp;rsquo;s usual Eversoft avocado cleanser. While all the cleansers effectively cleaned the skin, none particularly stood out in terms of oil control, hydration, or other advertised benefits. The author prioritizes cleansers that lather well and don&amp;rsquo;t leave residue, and ultimately, ingredients, price, and fragrance are the deciding factors for repeat purchases.</description></item></channel></rss>