<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OC-3 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc-3/</link><description>Recent content in OC-3 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/oc-3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 Mbps Internet for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</guid><description>For many mid-size businesses, DS3 internet with its 45 Mbps speed has been the standard. It&amp;rsquo;s widely available and offered a significant upgrade from older T1 lines. However, with the rise of video conferencing and cloud-based applications, even DS3 struggles to handle the demands of multiple users. It&amp;rsquo;s time to consider upgrading to 100 Mbps internet access.
The 100 Mbps service level is significant because it aligns with &amp;ldquo;Fast&amp;rdquo; Ethernet, a standard Ethernet LAN speed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-internet-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>Traditional copper leased lines for business connectivity are becoming outdated in the face of increasing demand for bandwidth-intensive applications like big data, HD video, and cloud computing. Fiber optic lines are emerging as the preferred solution, offering lower prices and more choices.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
While large companies and bandwidth-heavy industries have used fiber optic leased lines for a long time, the technology is now becoming more accessible. Historically, most fiber bandwidth relied on SONET (Synchronous Optical NETworking), a standard originating from the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-leased-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Finding The 100 Megabit Connection</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 23:08:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</guid><description>The increasing need for high-bandwidth applications like video streaming, medical image transfer, and cloud computing has made fractional Gigabit connections more prevalent. One such popular service is the 100 Mbps connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the options for delivering this bandwidth.
OC-3, a legacy fiber optic service using SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork), offers 155 Mbps bandwidth. While higher than 100 Mbps, it&amp;rsquo;s a significant jump from the lower tier DS3 service at 45 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-the-100-megabit-connection/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Buildings Offer High Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jan 2024 10:32:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</guid><description>Do you want to upgrade your internet speed from slow copper or fixed wireless connections to the rapid speeds offered by fiber optic cables? Are you trying to avoid the high cost of installing new fiber optic cables? If so, you should consider moving into a fiber building.
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry; a fiber building isn&amp;rsquo;t constructed from exotic materials like carbon fiber. The term &amp;ldquo;fiber&amp;rdquo; refers to the type of telecommunication services already available within the building...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-buildings-offer-high-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Differences Between Fiber and EoC</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</guid><description>Many businesses are analyzing if switching to fiber optic services is worthwhile due to limitations with their current internet and private line bandwidth. However, there&amp;rsquo;s now an additional choice: Ethernet over Copper (EoC).
You might be surprised to learn that EoC&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth and affordability put it in a similar league as fiber optics.
The traditional fiber optic service relies on the SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) standard, created by the telephone industry...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/differences-between-fiber-and-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Shopping For High Speed Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</guid><description>The landscape of business broadband has undergone significant changes. While options were once limited and expensive, today&amp;rsquo;s market offers a variety of affordable high-speed solutions.
For instance, T1 lines, previously exceeding $1,000, now cost around $300 for most locations and offer speeds of 1.5 Mbps or higher with bonding. An alternative, Ethernet over Copper (EoC), provides 2-3 Mbps at a similar price point and allows for easier scalability compared to T1&amp;rsquo;s jump to DS3...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/shopping-for-high-speed-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>California and Nevada Get 200 Mbps Bandwidth over Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</guid><description>The demand for business bandwidth has increased significantly over the past ten years. Companies that once relied on T1 lines (1.5 to 12 Mbps) or DS3 (45 Mbps) now require speeds exceeding 100 Mbps to accommodate high-definition video, large datasets, and cloud-based services.
Obtaining up to 200 Mbps over multiple copper pairs is now much simpler for businesses in California and Nevada. While achieving such speeds with fiber optic connections (SONET or Ethernet over Fiber) is not difficult, the installation of fiber optic cables presents a significant obstacle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/california-and-nevada-get-200-mbps-bandwidth-over-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Is a DS3 Circuit Or T3 Line?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 04:40:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</guid><description>Businesses that need more bandwidth than a T1 line often choose DS3. This article explores DS3, its relationship to T3 lines, and competition from Ethernet over Copper.
DS3, or Digital Signal level 3, follows standards set by Bell Labs for the telephone industry. The smallest unit, DS0, has a 64 Kbps bandwidth, enough for one digitized phone call using the original digital standard, PCM (Pulse Code Modulation). Combining 24 DS0s creates a DS1, which runs on a T1 line...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-ds3-circuit-or-t3-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Private Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 01:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</guid><description>Businesses seeking private line bandwidth exceeding 50 Mbps often find that copper-based options are inadequate. While high-bandwidth wireless solutions might be available in select urban areas, fiber optic services typically become necessary to meet such demands.
A prevalent fiber optic solution for metro and long-distance networks is SONET/SDH (Synchronous Optical NETwork/Synchronous Digital Hierarchy). This technology utilizes a highly synchronized time-division multiplexing (TDM) protocol, offering minimal latency and diverse bandwidth options reaching 40 Gbps and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-private-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Pricing Slashed For Michigan 100 Mbps Business Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:19:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</guid><description>Michigan businesses are facing a common problem: the need for faster internet speeds. Traditional options like T1 lines are no longer sufficient for handling increased data demands from video conferencing, cloud-based applications, and automation. While fiber optic services offer the necessary bandwidth, their high cost often makes them inaccessible.
Comcast Business Class emerges as a potential solution, delivering 100 Mbps download and 10 Mbps upload speeds at a price comparable to T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/pricing-slashed-for-michigan-100-mbps-business-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet over Fiber to Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</guid><description>Many modern businesses rely on data-heavy applications, such as cloud services and video production, which can overwhelm the capacity of traditional internet services. Insufficient bandwidth leads to frustrating consequences, including reduced productivity, delayed file transfers, and disrupted communication. Thankfully, effective solutions are becoming increasingly accessible.
Meeting high bandwidth demands requires high bandwidth solutions. Older technologies like T1 lines and even DS3 bandwidth (45 Mbps) have become insufficient for many businesses. While Ethernet over Copper and fixed wireless offer improved speeds (50-100 Mbps), they too are becoming inadequate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-over-fiber-to-your-door/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Business Fiber Optic Connections Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</guid><description>Is your internet connection slowing down your business? Have you maximized your bandwidth with bonded T1 lines and are now considering fiber optic services? While you might have heard that fiber optic services are expensive and come with high construction costs, this might not be entirely true. Affordable options are available.
Many common beliefs about fiber optics are outdated. These misconceptions prevent businesses from making a seamless transition to options with higher bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-fiber-optic-connections-nearby/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How to Find GigE Connections For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Gigabit Ethernet (GigE) is quickly becoming the preferred bandwidth solution for many organizations. But how do you find and secure the best GigE service? Let&amp;rsquo;s explore.
High-Quality Bandwidth for Businesses
Top-tier GigE services are offered by both established and emerging telecommunications companies. These services utilize dedicated, symmetrical fiber optic lines for high quality, low latency, and minimal data loss. They typically come with Service Level Agreements (SLAs) to guarantee performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-find-gige-connections-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic vs Ethernet over Copper Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:58:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</guid><description>The most common business internet connections are Ethernet over Copper and Fiber Optic connections, which includes Ethernet over Fiber. While copper connections have typically been preferred for their affordability and accessibility, and fiber optic for its high bandwidth and scalability, this is evolving. The increasing affordability and availability of fiber optic connections are making them competitive even at lower bandwidths.
](http://www.fibernetworkquotes.com/)
Copper connections were adopted early on and became widely available due to the FCC&amp;rsquo;s Universal Service policy, which aimed to provide universal access to telephone service using copper lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-vs-ethernet-over-copper-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T3 Bandwidth And Its Competitors</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 13:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</guid><description>When your business outgrows its T1 bandwidth, the next step is often upgrading to T3. But what exactly is T3 bandwidth, and is it always the right choice for businesses seeking more bandwidth?
Both T1 and T3 belong to a group of telecommunications standards known as T-Carrier, a technology developed after World War II to replace analog carrier telephony with digital carriers. Carrier telephony allows multiple conversations to travel over a single pair of telephone wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t3-bandwidth-and-its-competitors/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EoC Takes On Fractional DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</guid><description>Prior to the widespread adoption of Carrier Ethernet, businesses seeking increased bandwidth from T1 lines faced two primary options: upgrading to T3/DS3 for a substantial leap in capacity, or incrementally combining multiple T1 lines through bonding. However, the emergence of Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a compelling alternative for dedicated bandwidth.
T1 lines gained popularity due to their accessibility and sufficient bandwidth for smaller businesses or specialized applications within larger organizations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eoc-takes-on-fractional-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>100 x 100 Mbps Business Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>For many businesses, 100 Mbps bandwidth is no longer optional. This level is necessary for essential functions like remote backups, cloud-based applications, content distribution, and large file sharing (e.g., high-resolution medical images). Older technologies like T1 or DS3 connections are inadequate. So, what options are available and affordable?
OC-3 SONET fiber optic bandwidth is a traditional service offering this capacity, used by large companies for decades. However, high costs previously limited its wider adoption...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-x-100-mbps-business-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>DS3 Bandwidth Alternatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</guid><description>DS3 WAN connections are a popular choice for businesses that need more bandwidth than T1 lines offer but aren&amp;rsquo;t ready for a full OC-3 fiber optic SONET service. However, exploring alternative options might be beneficial due to cost or performance considerations.
There are several bandwidth options available today that might be a better fit than your existing DS3 connection. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some alternatives.
DS3 bridges the gap between copper wireline and fiber optic bandwidth services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ds3-bandwidth-alternatives/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Maps At Your Fingertips</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</guid><description>You might want to upgrade to a faster internet service, but the cost of installing fiber optic cables might seem scary. How can you figure out if upgrading from copper to fiber is affordable?
The easiest way is to compare quotes from different providers in your area. A telecom broker, like Telarus, Inc., can gather these quotes for you quickly and easily. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive a report with pricing from all major providers in your area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-maps-at-your-fingertips/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fiber Connectivity Options For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</guid><description>Most medium to large businesses, and even some smaller ones with high bandwidth needs, can now afford fiber optic bandwidth. This is due to lower prices and a wider range of options, which is great news for those who need a lot of bandwidth. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some of these options that you may not be aware of.
Fiber optic bandwidth services generally fall into two categories: traditional time division multiplexed technology, originating from telephone company research, and newer IP-centric networks offered by both competitive service providers and traditional telecom carriers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-connectivity-options-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Pushes EoC to 400 Mbps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services are constantly achieving higher bandwidth capacities, making businesses reconsider the need for fiber optic installations. MegaPath, for example, now offers EoC speeds up to 400 Mbps.
Many companies use EoC as a cost-effective alternative to T1 lines, obtaining double the bandwidth at the same price. Options like 2x2 Mbps and 3x3 Mbps are particularly favored. Others transition to mid-band Ethernet, offering 10 to 20 Mbps, which exceeds bonded T1 capabilities and suits mid-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-pushes-eoc-to-400-mbps/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>