<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Regulation 1049/2001 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-1049/2001/</link><description>Recent content in Regulation 1049/2001 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/regulation-1049/2001/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClientEarth v Council: A significant win for transparency in accessing documents.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 17:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/clientearth-v-council-a-significant-win-for-transparency-in-accessing-documents/</guid><description>Dimitrios Kyriazis (DPhil, Oxon), Assistant Professor in EU Law at the Law School of the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki.
Photo credit: Bela Geletneky, via Wikimedia Commons
In the combined cases of ClientEarth v Council (T-682/21 and T-683/21), the General Court of the European Union (GC) reviewed a challenge brought by ClientEarth AISBL and Ms. Leino-Sandberg against the Council of the EU. The applicants sought to overturn the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to withhold access to documents they had requested under the Public Access to Documents Regulation and the Aarhus Convention Regulation.</description></item><item><title>The EU has made a decision to increase transparency by allowing access to background documents prepared by consultants.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 02:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-has-made-a-decision-to-increase-transparency-by-allowing-access-to-background-documents-prepared-by-consultants/</guid><description>A Closer Look at EU Transparency: The Mastercard Case and Its Implications Steve Peers
&amp;ldquo;[The plans were] on display in the bottom of a locked filing cabinet stuck in a disused lavatory with a sign on the door saying, &amp;lsquo;Beware of the Leopard&amp;rsquo;!&amp;rdquo;
Arthur Dent, The Hitch-Hiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy
The EU&amp;rsquo;s activities often spark debate. Examples include the trade negotiations with the USA (TTIP), regulations covering diverse products like vacuum cleaners and genetically modified food, and the oversight (or in some cases, control) of Member States&amp;rsquo; financial decisions.</description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans).</description></item><item><title>Access to documents: The Council may choose not to enforce a significant CJEU ruling.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 08:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/access-to-documents-the-council-may-choose-not-to-enforce-a-significant-cjeu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU is frequently criticized for its lack of transparency, particularly concerning its legislative processes. Ideally, these processes should be as open as those in national legislatures, allowing public access to draft legislation.
However, despite a 2001 regulation on public access to documents, EU transparency in this area remains an issue. Within the Council, some Member States prefer to keep their positions confidential during negotiations. This secrecy undermines the idea that citizens, through their national parliaments, can hold their governments accountable for actions taken within the Council.</description></item><item><title>Is it time for the EU to increase transparency in its legislative process, as condemned by the EU Court?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</guid><description>Massimo Frigo, Senior Legal Adviser of the International Commission of Jurist’s Europe Programme*
Occasionally, cases concerning seemingly insignificant administrative matters evolve into pivotal judgments, shaping the continuous development of our democratic legal frameworks. A prime example in the US is Marbury v. Madison, a case initially garnering limited public interest due to its focus on judicial appointment procedures. Nonetheless, it ultimately established the crucial precedent of constitutional review within the US legal system.</description></item></channel></rss>