<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Handbag on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/handbag/</link><description>Recent content in Handbag on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/handbag/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technavio identifies luxury handbag brands worth keeping an eye on</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 04:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</guid><description>This is a picture of the Coach store located in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Raffles City Mall.
Research firm Technavio has identified Burberry, Chanel, Coach, Hermès, Kate Spade, LVMH (Louis Vuitton), Michael Kors, Mulberry, and Prada as the top-performing handbag brands in the Asia Pacific market up to 2019. Currently, popular brands also include Coach, Michael Kors, LVMH, Chanel, D&amp;amp;G, Prada, Gucci, and Christian Dior.
Technavio highlights several factors contributing to the growing demand for handbags in the region, including easy access through specialized retailers, increasing disposable income, and the rise of e-commerce...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technavio-identifies-luxury-handbag-brands-worth-keeping-an-eye-on/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The handbag app reveals the newest handbag options available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</guid><description>Source: Google Play Store.
Swipe Boutique has launched a new fashion app for Android devices called &amp;ldquo;handbag swipe.&amp;rdquo;
The app allows users to explore thousands of the latest handbag designs from over a hundred popular brands, including Topshop, New Look, and Michael Kors.
With a browsing experience resembling Tinder, shoppers can swipe through various handbag options. The app enables users to curate personal wish lists, purchase desired products instantly, or save handbag details for future reference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handbag-app-reveals-the-newest-handbag-options-available/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Handbags will be the focus in India and China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:24:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</guid><description>A new report from Technavio predicts the handbag market in Brazil, Russia, India, and China will experience significant growth between 2014 and 2019. This growth is projected to be over 7.41% in revenue and 7.02% in volume.
Technavio attributes this anticipated growth to the increasing association of handbags with social status among consumers. The introduction of stylish and functional designs, along with attractive colors, finishes, and textures, are making handbags more desirable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/handbags-will-be-the-focus-in-india-and-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Luxury handbags by Jennifer Mak are available for purchase at Tangs in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 02:45:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</guid><description>Jennifer Mak&amp;rsquo;s namesake luxury handbag brand is available on the designer floor of Singapore’s Tangs flagship department store in Orchard Road for a limited time, ending February 28, 2015. The brand uses premium materials like python, ostrich, lizard, stingray, and crocodile skin, creating handbags known for their classic lines, elegance, and one-of-a-kind appeal.
Source: Jennifer Mak. Part of the collection on the second floor at Tang&amp;rsquo;s.
&amp;ldquo;The Jennifer Mak woman doesn&amp;rsquo;t seek attention, but she undoubtedly commands it,&amp;rdquo; says Jennifer Mak, the brand&amp;rsquo;s Founder and CEO...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/luxury-handbags-by-jennifer-mak-are-available-for-purchase-at-tangs-in-singapore/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>