<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>11.11 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/11.11/</link><description>Recent content in 11.11 on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:40:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/11.11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The 11.11 Shopping Festival at Lazada guarantees a more enjoyable experience for everyone involved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s Lazada 11.11 Shopping Festival is breaking records with over 50 million deals, a significant increase from last year&amp;rsquo;s 27 million. The event will involve over 400,000 sellers and brands, almost triple the number from the previous year.
Lazada, a leading e-commerce platform in Southeast Asia, organizes this yearly event to demonstrate the convenience and affordability of online shopping. For 24 hours, starting at midnight on November 11th, shoppers across six countries will have access to incredible deals on a wide range of products, with discounts of up to 90%...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-11-11-shopping-festival-at-lazada-guarantees-a-more-enjoyable-experience-for-everyone-involved/</a></p></description></item><item><title>11 facts about 11.11</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:07:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</guid><description>Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 Global Shopping Festival, beginning on November 11, is generating excitement with its pre-launch preparations. Here are 11 key things shoppers should be aware of:
AI-Powered Multilingual Tools To enhance the shopping experience for global customers, Alibaba has introduced an AI translation tool designed to bridge language gaps between buyers and sellers.
This online chat tool, recently launched on Lazada, enables real-time translation between English and Thai, Vietnamese, and Indonesian...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/11-facts-about-11-11/</a></p></description></item><item><title>This year, Alibaba's 11.11 Global Shopping Festival generated more than $17 billion in sales</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 03:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</guid><description>Alibaba Group reported that on November 11, 2016, its China and international retail marketplaces achieved a gross merchandise volume (GMV) of RMB120.7 billion (US$17.8 billion), settled through Alipay. This represents a 32% growth compared to 2015. Mobile GMV settled through Alipay reached RMB99 billion (US$14.6 billion), making up 82% of the total GMV.
&amp;ldquo;This year&amp;rsquo;s 11.11 provides a glimpse into the future of retail, where entertainment, commerce, and interactive engagement blend seamlessly,&amp;rdquo; said Daniel Zhang, CEO of Alibaba Group...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/this-year-alibaba-s-11-11-global-shopping-festival-generated-more-than-17-billion-in-sales/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>