<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Engagement on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/engagement/</link><description>Recent content in Engagement on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/engagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Encouraging an open workplace culture: the role of leaders</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 02:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</guid><description>Open communication and strong relationships are essential for a thriving workplace. UK-based sales and marketing firm Forrest Bell emphasizes that openness involves respectful and constructive dialogue about needs, opinions, and concerns. It also means actively listening to and considering new ideas, questions, and feedback.
Forrest Bell believes that a culture of openness fosters trust and facilitates collaboration on projects. It also promotes transparency and streamlines processes in dynamic business environments...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/encouraging-an-open-workplace-culture-the-role-of-leaders/</a></p></description></item><item><title>StarHub introduces SmartUC service for businesses in Singapore, powered by Avaya</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 19:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</guid><description>Avaya, a company that provides customer and team engagement solutions, partnered with StarHub, a Singaporean integrated infocommunications company, to launch SmartUC, a business communications service for Singaporean businesses.
This service offers four main advantages: increased productivity, improved customer experience, product and service differentiation, and business expansion. Pamela Tham, Avaya&amp;rsquo;s Singapore Country Leader, highlighted the rapid evolution of customer and business user expectations, emphasizing the demand for mobile solutions, apps, social integration, cloud services, video conferencing, chat features, flexibility, user-friendliness, and instant access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/starhub-introduces-smartuc-service-for-businesses-in-singapore-powered-by-avaya/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>