<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ebola on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ebola/</link><description>Recent content in Ebola on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ebola/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India has implemented measures to prepare for Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 03:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</guid><description>India is actively monitoring the situation to prevent the Ebola virus disease (EVD) from entering the country. Three dedicated helplines (2306 3205, 2306 1469, and 2306 1302) were set up at the Health Ministry on August 9th to address public inquiries.
While India has no confirmed or suspected Ebola cases, the World Health Organization (WHO) alerted the government about an Indian passenger who shared a flight with an Ebola patient traveling from Monrovia (Liberia) to Lagos (Nigeria), both experiencing outbreaks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-has-implemented-measures-to-prepare-for-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Flynas is using Virus Guard to combat MERS and Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:36:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</guid><description>Flynas, a Saudi Arabian low-cost airline, has incorporated Virus Guard disinfectant wipes and sprays into its in-flight hygiene procedures.
Given the concerning rise of MERS cases in the region, with over a thousand reported so far, Flynas aims to prioritize the health of both travelers and staff by mitigating the risk of viral transmission.
Eman Yusuf, Flynas&amp;rsquo; In-flight Services and On-board Product Manager, stated that the airline will utilize these specialized wipes and sprays to disinfect all frequently touched surfaces within the aircraft...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/flynas-is-using-virus-guard-to-combat-mers-and-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore is prepared to take action in response to Ebola</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 14:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Health (MOH) has implemented the World Health Organization&amp;rsquo;s (WHO) recommendations for Ebola virus disease (EVD) preparedness and is going even further. The ministry is prepared to adjust its measures as the situation changes.
One of the recommendations is to educate travelers about the potential dangers of EVD. The MOH is using various channels, such as its website and media releases, to inform the public and potential travelers about the disease...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-prepared-to-take-action-in-response-to-ebola/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The World Health Organization has declared the Ebola outbreak a global public health emergency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</guid><description>The World Health Organization (WHO) declared the West African Ebola outbreak a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) on August 8th.
As of August 4, 2014, there were 1,711 cases (1,070 confirmed, 436 probable, and 205 suspected) of Ebola virus disease (EVD), resulting in 932 deaths. Between August 5th and 6th, 2014, 68 new EVD cases (including confirmed, probable, and suspected) and 29 deaths were reported across Guinea, Liberia, Nigeria, and Sierra Leone...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-health-organization-has-declared-the-ebola-outbreak-a-global-public-health-emergency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WHO dismisses the likelihood of a worldwide Ebola outbreak</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</guid><description>On August 11th, the World Health Organization (WHO) released a statement regarding the Ebola virus disease (EVD) outbreak in West Africa. They emphasized that nations with strong health systems are unlikely to experience an epidemic. This is due to the way the virus spreads and past experiences with outbreaks.
The WHO also noted that while fear has led to increased global vigilance and suspicion of the virus, this heightened awareness makes it more likely that cases will be detected and managed quickly, thus limiting further transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-dismisses-the-likelihood-of-a-worldwide-ebola-outbreak/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>