<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Budget on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/budget/</link><description>Recent content in Budget on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/budget/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accor debuts its first ibis budget hotel in South Korea</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:19:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accor-debuts-its-first-ibis-budget-hotel-in-south-korea/</guid><description>Accor, the leading international hotel operator in the Asia Pacific region and South Korea, has launched its first ibis budget brand hotel in South Korea: the ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
Source: Accor. The Ibis budget Ambassador Seoul Dongdaemun.
This newly constructed hotel offers 195 guest rooms and is situated north of Seoul&amp;rsquo;s Han River. The location is a bustling commercial area known for its blend of traditional markets and modern shopping centers.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is taking steps to enhance its resilience</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 04:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-taking-steps-to-enhance-its-resilience/</guid><description>Concept classroom by dream by WOMBO.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2023 centers around navigating global economic uncertainties by enhancing the country&amp;rsquo;s productivity and competitiveness.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Deputy PM and Finance Minister, Lawrence Wong, highlighted the US ban on advanced chip technology transfer to China and its ripple effects. He stated, &amp;ldquo;We are seeing a fierce competition for dominance in critical technologies, likely to intensify, leading to a concerning trend toward increased economic nationalism and protectionism worldwide.</description></item><item><title>The 2015 Budget of Singapore provides support for businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2015-budget-of-singapore-provides-support-for-businesses/</guid><description>Source: Ministry of Finance, Singapore. Infrastructure investments were also announced as part of Budget 2015.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2015, presented by Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Tharman Shanmugaratnam, included several business initiatives. These encompassed increased training assistance, a gradual reduction in business restructuring aid, a freeze on foreign worker levies (excluding manufacturing and construction), and measures to encourage innovation and expansion.
Training and development
Shanmugaratnam emphasized the government&amp;rsquo;s commitment to continuous investment in Singaporeans&amp;rsquo; skills development.</description></item><item><title>Just under half of Singaporeans believe that Budget 2016 is fair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/just-under-half-of-singaporeans-believe-that-budget-2016-is-fair/</guid><description>A recent poll of 986 Singaporeans by YouGov, a global polling and research company, revealed widespread pessimism regarding the future despite a generally neutral sentiment about the 2016 Budget.
While over a quarter of respondents viewed the current economy positively, a significant majority (over 60%) believed it was either declining or stagnant. This negative outlook was particularly pronounced among older respondents (aged 45-54).
Although half of those surveyed considered the 2016 Budget fair, a significant majority (60%) did not believe it would significantly impact their lives over the next year.</description></item><item><title>Singapore Airlines, Scoot, and Jetstar provide guidance on booking and canceling flights to Thailand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-airlines-scoot-and-jetstar-provide-guidance-on-booking-and-canceling-flights-to-thailand/</guid><description>Sign at the Singapore Airlines counter in Changi Airport
Singapore Airlines is currently running its flights to and from Bangkok as originally planned. However, they are suggesting that passengers get ready for potential traffic delays in the city, which could be caused by street closures or heightened security measures.
&amp;ldquo;We recommend that customers arrange to arrive at the airport no less than four hours before their flight and, if possible, utilize the airport train,&amp;rdquo; stated the airline&amp;rsquo;s website announcement on May 23rd.</description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget provides a significant boost to the commercial sector in various ways</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-provides-a-significant-boost-to-the-commercial-sector-in-various-ways/</guid><description>In yesterday&amp;rsquo;s Budget, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized exploring new ideas and diversity to help Hong Kong citizens achieve their goals.
He stated his commitment to utilizing resources generated by the community, supporting those in need, and promoting sustainable development to ensure that people from all sectors of society and future generations can benefit from economic growth.
The Budget outlines measures for the cultural and creative sector:
An extra HK$400 million will be allocated to the CreateSmart Initiative.</description></item><item><title>The 2021 Budget of Singapore emphasizes resilience and aims for long-term success</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-2021-budget-of-singapore-emphasizes-resilience-and-aims-for-long-term-success/</guid><description>Singapore’s Deputy Prime Minister, Coordinating Minister for Economic Policies, and Minister for Finance Heng Swee Keat presented the Budget 2021: Emerging Stronger Together plan, outlining the government’s strategy for addressing current issues and its vision for a stronger Singapore. The goal is a nation that is economically thriving, socially unified, and environmentally sustainable for all.
Source: Singapore Ministry of Finance.
Cover, Budget Booklet.
To fund Singapore’s regular expenses, the government previously announced in Budget 2018 that the goods and services tax (GST) rate would increase between 2021 and 2025.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is dedicated to developing talent in the infocomm sector</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 13:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-dedicated-to-developing-talent-in-the-infocomm-sector/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, addressed the rising demand for infocomm professionals in the country. This surge is attributed to the growth of the ICT sector and Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Smart Nation initiatives. Dr. Yaacob emphasized the need to fill 30,000 infocomm positions by 2020.
He acknowledged the challenge of meeting this demand solely with local talent, stating that while relying on non-Singaporeans might be necessary, the focus should be on equipping Singaporeans with highly competitive skills.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2017 Budget is on handling uncertainty</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 21:51:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2017-budget-is-on-handling-uncertainty/</guid><description>Source: Singapore Budget website. View of Singapore.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Budget 2017 aimed to prepare the nation for the future amidst significant global economic shifts, presenting both obstacles and prospects. Finance Minister Heng Swee Keat stressed the need for companies and workers to develop robust adaptability to navigate these changing economic structures and technologies. He highlighted that digitalization, innovation, and a highly skilled workforce are key for cities and regions to thrive while maintaining global openness and connectivity.</description></item><item><title>Firefly is back in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/firefly-is-back-in-singapore/</guid><description>Firefly Airlines has resumed flights between Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport in Subang, Malaysia, and Seletar Airport in Singapore.
Source: Firefly. Firefly reinstates Malaysia-Singapore route.
Firefly&amp;rsquo;s first flight on this route to Seletar took place in April 2019, but flights were put on hold in March 2020 due to the pandemic. Now, the airline will offer two flights every day between Kuala Lumpur and Singapore, operating out of Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport and Seletar Airport.</description></item><item><title>Air Asia provides a complimentary Penang travel guide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 09:08:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/air-asia-provides-a-complimentary-penang-travel-guide/</guid><description>The low-cost carrier Air Asia is offering a complimentary travel guide for the island of Penang.
Source: Air Asia e-DM.
Penang, Malaysia is renowned for its distinctive cuisine, the UNESCO World Heritage site of George Town, and its Peranakan culture. The guide, designed to assist event planners organizing trips to Penang, encompasses the following:
Food Art, Heritage, Crafts &amp;amp; Cafés Lifestyle &amp;amp; Nature Getting Around Calendar of Events The guide can be downloaded here.</description></item><item><title>Budget airline flyadeal plans to extend its reach to more destinations in the Middle East in the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budget-airline-flyadeal-plans-to-extend-its-reach-to-more-destinations-in-the-middle-east-in-the-future/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s new low-cost airline, flyadeal, was officially launched on August 23 at King Abdulaziz International Airport in Jeddah. The event showcased flyadeal&amp;rsquo;s first aircraft, named &amp;ldquo;Al-Nayyir&amp;rdquo; (meaning &amp;ldquo;bright star&amp;rdquo;), which arrived from the Airbus delivery center in Hamburg, Germany.
Source: flyadeal. The budget airline flyadeal was inaugurated at a ceremony on August 24. The airline’s colors – a distinct palette of purple and lime – was on full display at the delivery event, along with members of the cabin crew, which gave guests a tour of the unique features onboard.</description></item><item><title>The focus of Singapore's 2018 Budget is on technology, innovation, and building capabilities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-focus-of-singapore-s-2018-budget-is-on-technology-innovation-and-building-capabilities/</guid><description>Source: Budget 2018 site. View of Singapore skyline.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Ministry of Trade and Industry (MTI) anticipates more broad-based economic growth across sectors in 2018, albeit at a moderated pace compared to the heights of 2017, according to Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Financial Minister Heng Swee Keat during his Budget 2018 speech.
Minister Heng emphasized the need for Singapore to adapt to three major shifts in the coming decade:
Asia&amp;rsquo;s increasing global economic influence.</description></item><item><title>Cut Telecom Line Expenses, Not Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:17:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-telecom-line-expenses-not-lines/</guid><description>During economic downturns, businesses often look to cut costs to stay afloat. While eliminating unnecessary expenses is a good start, managers may soon scrutinize even essential budget items.
Instead of panicking and making rash decisions, it&amp;rsquo;s best to proactively identify reasonable cost reductions. This way, you can present well-thought-out proposals and maintain some control over the process.
The key is to maintain productivity while reducing expenses. Instead of completely cutting essential services, focus on achieving the same functionality for less money.</description></item><item><title>BudgetHotels.sg has launched a newly enhanced website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 14:28:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/budgethotels-sg-has-launched-a-newly-enhanced-website/</guid><description>Source: BudgetHotels.sg website.
BudgetHotels.sg, the online guide for finding hotels, recently updated its website to offer a smoother booking experience for affordable accommodations in Singapore.
The redesigned website prioritizes mobile use and faster loading speeds. It allows users to filter hotels by price, ranging from one to four stars. The price categories include:
Less than S$50 S$50 - $79 S$80 - $119 S$120 - $149 More than S$150 Making the website mobile-friendly was a key decision based on the latest trends in the hospitality sector.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has revealed a budget for 2016 that is favorable to small and medium-sized enterprises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 22:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-revealed-a-budget-for-2016-that-is-favorable-to-small-and-medium-sized-enterprises/</guid><description>Source: Budget in Brief document on Singapore Budget website.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Heng Swee Keat, introduced a new program to bolster businesses and industries while stimulating growth through innovation. Building on the Quality Growth Programme from Budget 2013, this initiative, called the Industry Transformation Programme (ITP), seeks to foster innovation and productivity. The goal is to empower Singaporean companies to become more resilient and capitalize on the anticipated global economic upswing.</description></item><item><title>The Hong Kong budget prioritizes innovation to capitalize on opportunities in a changing economic landscape</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 07:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-hong-kong-budget-prioritizes-innovation-to-capitalize-on-opportunities-in-a-changing-economic-landscape/</guid><description>In his 2016-17 Budget address, Hong Kong Financial Secretary John Tsang emphasized the need for the city to adapt to a changing global economy driven by technology and the rise of emerging markets. He highlighted robotics, healthy aging, and smart city initiatives as potential areas for Hong Kong to leverage its strengths.
Tsang announced plans to promote smart production and research in the Tseung Kwan O Industrial Estate, utilizing robotics and IT to advance the entire value chain, from research and development to marketing.</description></item><item><title>Saudi Arabia has announced the release of its 2017 budget</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 06:51:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/saudi-arabia-has-announced-the-release-of-its-2017-budget/</guid><description>Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s King Salman bin Abdulaziz recently announced the nation&amp;rsquo;s budget for 2017. The budget is set at SAR890 billion, representing an 8% rise from the previous year. It is anticipated to significantly reduce the kingdom&amp;rsquo;s deficit by a historic 33%.
King Salman emphasized the strength and resilience of the Saudi economy, stating, &amp;ldquo;Our economy is firm and it has sufficient strength to cope with the current economic and financial challenges.</description></item><item><title>India will be implementing GST and has announced additional training and business initiatives</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 12:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/india-will-be-implementing-gst-and-has-announced-additional-training-and-business-initiatives/</guid><description>India&amp;rsquo;s Finance Minister, Shri Arun Jaitley, announced in his Budget speech that a comprehensive goods and services tax (GST) system will be implemented by April 1, 2016. Additionally, corporate tax rates are expected to be reduced from 30% to 25% gradually over the next four years. These proposals were presented alongside initiatives aimed at enhancing human resource capabilities and fostering innovation nationwide.
Training and Development The Finance Minister stressed the importance of structured skills training, revealing the government&amp;rsquo;s plan to introduce a National Skills Mission.</description></item></channel></rss>