<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Multiplexing on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiplexing/</link><description>Recent content in Multiplexing on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/multiplexing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dark Fiber Gives You Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 07:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Increasing bandwidth requirements are a trend in business IT, impacting local networks and leased lines for broader areas. Beyond just bandwidth, factors like latency, packet loss, and jitter are equally crucial. Security remains paramount, while agility in making changes and deploying resources is key for operational smoothness.
High Bandwidth Demands Necessitate Robust Infrastructure
The need for greater bandwidth has driven a shift from copper to fiber optic cables...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dark-fiber-gives-you-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SONET Rings To Support Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</guid><description>The popular choice for bandwidth right now is Carrier Ethernet, mainly because it&amp;rsquo;s much cheaper than traditional WAN connections. This affordability makes it highly desirable. The main concern for most is availability.
In many cases, Carrier Ethernet is accessible for a couple of key reasons. Firstly, emerging competitors are quickly building their fiber optic networks with IP as the foundation, which is perfect for Carrier Ethernet. This makes it straightforward to connect distant business locations with a point-to-point Ethernet connection, essentially merging their LANs into a single, larger network...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sonet-rings-to-support-ethernet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Wavelength Services vs Dark Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 17:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</guid><description>High-bandwidth fiber optic services are widely used for metropolitan and long-distance connections. These services typically offer speeds ranging from 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps, 40 Gbps, and occasionally even 100 Gbps. However, if these pre-packaged services don&amp;rsquo;t meet your needs, there are alternative options such as leasing dark fiber routes or wavelength services.
Standardized fiber optic bandwidth services provide point-to-point SONET or Ethernet connectivity, similar to private lines. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that you are likely sharing the fiber strand with other customers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wavelength-services-vs-dark-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ISDN PRI For PABX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 18:46:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</guid><description>The preferred phone system for medium and large businesses is the Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX), also called a PBX. Companies big enough for a PABX need multiple outside lines, raising the question of the best technology for these lines.
Smaller businesses needing few lines usually start with analog Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) lines, adding more as needed. Eventually, digital trunks become more practical than numerous separate POTS lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdn-pri-for-pabx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>AboveNet Core Wave Makes Dedicated Wavelength Bandwidth Available</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:49:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</guid><description>When standard bandwidth solutions are insufficient, AboveNet&amp;rsquo;s Core Wave service provides high-capacity bandwidth. This service is designed for sectors with demanding applications, such as finance, media, healthcare, retail, and government, that require the robust capabilities of fiber optic transport.
Many telecom services utilize multiplexing, which combines multiple bandwidth services onto a single fiber optic core network. However, for organizations with exceptionally high bandwidth demands, a dedicated solution may be necessary...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/abovenet-core-wave-makes-dedicated-wavelength-bandwidth-available/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>