<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>AirePBX on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airepbx/</link><description>Recent content in AirePBX on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/airepbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX For Features and Cost Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-for-features-and-cost-savings/</guid><description>Determining if it&amp;rsquo;s the right moment to transition your business phone system to a cloud-based solution is crucial, especially if your current system struggles with capacity, needs frequent fixes, or lacks vendor support. However, even if your current system functions adequately, you might be overlooking opportunities to enhance productivity and reduce communication expenses with modern hosted PBX solutions.
A prime illustration is AireSpring&amp;rsquo;s updated Cloud Hosted IP PBX, AirePBX version 2.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Hosted IP PBX Enables New Telephone Apps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cloud-hosted-ip-pbx-enables-new-telephone-apps/</guid><description>Just like apps revolutionized smartphones, they are now transforming desktop and laptop experiences, moving away from traditional software. And yes, this wave of innovation has reached phone systems too. AireSpring is leading the way with a suite of apps designed for their AirePBX cloud-hosted system.
Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the possibilities. CommPortal acts as your messaging hub, allowing you to manage voicemail, activate a one-number service for seamless device switching, prioritize callers, and utilize click-to-dial functionality.</description></item></channel></rss>