<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Text to Speech on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/text-to-speech/</link><description>Recent content in Text to Speech on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/text-to-speech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The HandySpeech app, which converts handwriting to speech, is now available on Android devices</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 08:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-handyspeech-app-which-converts-handwriting-to-speech-is-now-available-on-android-devices/</guid><description>iSpeak4U, a company known for developing mobile apps for individuals with speech and hearing impairments, has launched an Android version of their app HandySpeech. This app offers a simple and efficient communication tool for those with speech difficulties.
Source: iSpeak4U. HandySpeech running on various devices.
With HandySpeech, users can input text on a device screen using their finger or a stylus, and the device will then vocalize the written words. The app is designed to store frequently used phrases and adapt to the user&amp;rsquo;s handwriting style.</description></item><item><title>Amazon's Kindle Tells Bedtime Stories</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-kindle-tells-bedtime-stories/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 08:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/amazons-kindle-tells-bedtime-stories/</guid><description>Struggling to sleep during a long car ride? Imagine listening to a soothing bedtime story. Facing a day-long drive? Use that time wisely by enjoying audiobooks of popular business titles. This might sound like an advertisement for audiotapes or CDs, but those are outdated. What you need is digitized content, transformed from written text into spoken words, and played on a device the size of a paperback book.
What you need is the new Amazon Kindle 2.</description></item></channel></rss>