<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mesh Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mesh-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Mesh Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mesh-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I, Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 13:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/i-router/</guid><description>An interesting consequence of technological progress is the creation of fabrics capable of producing electricity simply from the wearer&amp;rsquo;s movement. This involves nanowires covered in zinc oxide that transform mechanical energy into electrical energy, illustrating the scientific principle of energy conversion.
The creator of this innovation suggests incorporating it into clothing like shirts and shoes to power devices like iPods or medical implants. Currently, the power density is 80 milliwatts per square meter of fabric, but this could increase significantly in the future, potentially reaching several watts per garment, especially with more vigorous movements.</description></item><item><title>Benefits Of An MPLS Mesh Network</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:01:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-an-mpls-mesh-network/</guid><description>When your company grows to have multiple locations like branches, data centers, or factories, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a way to connect them all on the same network. The best way to do this is with an MPLS Mesh Network.
Smaller companies with only two locations usually start by connecting the locations with a point-to-point T1 or Ethernet line. While this works, using an MPLS network might be more cost-effective depending on the distance between locations and the availability of T1 or Ethernet services.</description></item><item><title>Extending Ethernet over MPLS Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:07:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extending-ethernet-over-mpls-networks/</guid><description>Ethernet has transitioned from a local network protocol to a preferred choice for metropolitan area networks. Its benefits include easy integration with wired and wireless networks, scalable bandwidth without equipment upgrades, and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional telecom options. This begs the question: can Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s success in LAN and MAN be replicated in WAN?
Ethernet WAN is gaining popularity, particularly among businesses with geographically dispersed sites. Dedicated point-to-point Ethernet connections are possible, but Ethernet over MPLS presents a compelling alternative.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Port At Your Door</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 04:41:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-port-at-your-door/</guid><description>You might be surprised to learn that a connection to the outside world could be as simple as an Ethernet port in your telecom closet. This is due to a relatively new technology called Ethernet WAN (Wide Area Network).
Traditionally, organizations have relied on the public switched telephone network (PSTN) for external connections. Technologies designed for phone calls, like T1, DS3, and SONET fiber optic services, were adapted to carry data traffic and internet access.</description></item></channel></rss>