<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Etihad Airways on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etihad-airways/</link><description>Recent content in Etihad Airways on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/etihad-airways/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The inaugural commercial flight of the Etihad Boeing 787 Dreamliner is headed to Germany</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-inaugural-commercial-flight-of-the-etihad-boeing-787-dreamliner-is-headed-to-germany/</guid><description>Source: Etihad.
Etihad Airways, the flag carrier of the UAE, launched its inaugural Boeing 787 Dreamliner commercial flight. The first flight, a Boeing 787-9, flew from Abu Dhabi to Düsseldorf, Germany. Departing at 2:15 a.m. as flight EY23, the seven-hour, 25-minute journey landed at 6:40 a.m. The return leg from Düsseldorf departs at 10:20 a.m., arriving in Abu Dhabi at 7:50 p.m.
James Hogan, Etihad Airways&amp;rsquo; President and CEO, stated that the Boeing 787 is a significant achievement for the airline, calling it the most technologically sophisticated aircraft in its class.</description></item><item><title>Etihad is providing selected transit passengers with a complimentary night's stay in Abu Dhabi</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 02:42:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/etihad-is-providing-selected-transit-passengers-with-a-complimentary-night-s-stay-in-abu-dhabi/</guid><description>Etihad Airways is offering a free overnight stay in Abu Dhabi to Economy Class travelers flying from specific locations, including Pakistan, Saudi Arabia, Jordan, Kuwait, Bahrain, Oman, and Lebanon, whose journeys connect through the UAE&amp;rsquo;s capital.
This offer is valid for travel dates up to September 30, 2018, with bookings available from May 1 to September 15, 2018. Accommodation choices include the Radisson Blu on Yas Island and the Yas Island Rotana.</description></item><item><title>All Boeing 777s operated by Etihad Airways offer mobile and Internet connectivity</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 15:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/all-boeing-777s-operated-by-etihad-airways-offer-mobile-and-internet-connectivity/</guid><description>Etihad Airways has finished installing mobile and internet connectivity on all 24 of its Boeing 777 passenger planes. This allows passengers to stay connected while flying.
Source: Etihad. In-flight connectivity becomes a reality.
The airline plans to have its entire fleet of 89 passenger aircraft connected within the next few months. This will make Etihad Airways the first airline in its region and one of the few globally to offer mobile and internet connectivity on all its planes.</description></item></channel></rss>