<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Radio on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/radio/</link><description>Recent content in Radio on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/radio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Clever D Block Initiative</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 15:56:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</guid><description>During the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction, a small frequency band known as D Block went unsold because it didn&amp;rsquo;t reach its reserve price. This is unfortunate because D Block was supposed to play a crucial role in establishing a nationwide public service network. This plan, which could serve as a model for other initiatives, deserves further consideration, especially in challenging economic times.
The idea for D Block originated after the September 11, 2001, attacks, when communication breakdowns hampered rescue efforts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-clever-d-block-initiative/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hey, Look, More Spectrum!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</guid><description>Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you missed out on the recent 700 MHz spectrum auction and aren&amp;rsquo;t interested in the remaining options. There will be more spectrum becoming available soon.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t about the FCC finding unused frequencies; it&amp;rsquo;s about a secondary market emerging. NextWave Wireless, a company that had acquired licenses for a significant portion of the microwave spectrum, is now divesting those assets to focus on their hardware business.
NextWave&amp;rsquo;s portfolio, encompassing 154 licenses in the AWS bands, 30 in the WCS band, and 22 in the EBS and BRS band, covers a substantial portion of the US population...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hey-look-more-spectrum-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Chumby Kicks the Clock Radio to the Curb</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</guid><description>Are traditional alarm clocks and radios truly effective ways to wake up? Imagine a more modern approach: starting your day with your favorite internet radio station, a quick weather and market update, and a glimpse at your online auctions. You could even catch up on news and sports or play a game. All of this is possible with the Chumby.
What exactly is a Chumby? It&amp;rsquo;s a wireless internet device featuring speakers, a touchscreen, and motion sensors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chumby-kicks-the-clock-radio-to-the-curb/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>