<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mouse on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mouse/</link><description>Recent content in Mouse on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:02:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mouse/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New focus on Kickstarter: A mouse glove as a replacement for traditional computer mice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 17:02:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</guid><description>A new Kickstarter project called the &amp;ldquo;Mouse Glove&amp;rdquo; aims to revolutionize how we interact with technology, potentially replacing touch screens entirely.
Source: Kickstarter website
The creators of the Mouse Glove claim their invention offers a more ergonomic and intuitive user experience compared to traditional mice. By promoting a more natural hand position, they believe it can reduce the risk of repetitive strain injuries like carpal tunnel syndrome.
The glove replicates standard mouse functionalities, including left and right clicks, scrolling, and cursor control...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-focus-on-kickstarter-a-mouse-glove-as-a-replacement-for-traditional-computer-mice/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Basilisk V3 Pro is Razer's most sophisticated mouse yet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:32:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</guid><description>Razer, a leading brand in gaming lifestyle products, has introduced the Basilisk V3 Pro, a wireless gaming mouse designed for high performance and extensive customization. The mouse boasts features like a Razer HyperScroll Tilt Wheel, Razer Optical Mouse Switches Gen-3, more than 10 programmable buttons, a Razer Focus Pro 30K Optical Sensor, and wireless charging capabilities.
Chris Mitchell, the Head of Razer&amp;rsquo;s PC Gaming Division, highlighted the Basilisk V3 Pro as their most feature-packed gaming mouse yet, packed with everything needed to outperform the competition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-basilisk-v3-pro-is-razer-s-most-sophisticated-mouse-yet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Duracell batteries provide six times the power</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</guid><description>Source: Duracell. To commemorate five decades of providing portable power, Duracell has partnered with TRANSFORMERS: AGE OF EXTINCTION, the fourth film in director Michael Bay&amp;rsquo;s globally recognized franchise, in a battle of good and evil.
Duracell, the renowned battery manufacturer, is observing 50 years of providing portable power solutions. Although the traditional battery design remains largely unchanged, battery technology advancements have significantly extended battery life.
Duracell&amp;rsquo;s latest CopperTop AA and AAA batteries, equipped with Duralock Power Preserve Technology, are ideal for devices like wireless mice and keyboards...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/duracell-batteries-provide-six-times-the-power/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>