<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Laser on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/laser/</link><description>Recent content in Laser on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/laser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lexmark introduces seven innovative laser multifunction models with groundbreaking features</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</guid><description>Lexmark has introduced seven new A4 color laser and smart multifunction printers (MFPs). These MFPs feature Kofax TotalAgility from Lexmark to improve omnichannel capture strategies and boost business efficiency.
Amy Machado, Research Manager at IDC, highlighted the strong growth of the A4 color MFP market, projecting a 10.5% increase throughout the forecast period, according to the Worldwide Hardcopy Peripherals Format Forecast from Q3 2015.
These new models, powered by a quad-core processor, boast leading print and copy speeds for their class...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/lexmark-introduces-seven-innovative-laser-multifunction-models-with-groundbreaking-features/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WDM Wavelength Services Offer Expandability</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 05:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</guid><description>For those seeking high bandwidth, security, and adaptable network solutions, wavelength services present an attractive option, going beyond typical fiber optic bandwidth.
Fiber optic transmission offers nearly limitless bandwidth—a stark contrast to copper wireline services. However, even with fiber optic services, users typically select a fixed bandwidth level. This limits them, as upgrading often becomes the only way to obtain additional bandwidth when needed. In reality, these services utilize only a fraction of the fiber&amp;rsquo;s total capacity...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wdm-wavelength-services-offer-expandability/</a></p></description></item><item><title>BenQ has recently introduced a new series of digital laser projectors that offer precise color accuracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</guid><description>The BenQ LU9715 digital laser projector.
BenQ, a leading brand in digital light processing (DLP) and interactive displays, has introduced a new series of laser projectors designed for large venues in corporate, professional, and academic settings.
BenQ highlights that the 24/7 operational capabilities will be particularly valuable in large business settings, museums, exhibition spaces, and boardrooms. Daren Low, Senior Product Manager at BenQ Singapore, emphasized the advantage of minimal maintenance, especially since these projectors are often mounted in high, hard-to-reach locations where scaffolding would be necessary for each maintenance session...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benq-has-recently-introduced-a-new-series-of-digital-laser-projectors-that-offer-precise-color-accuracy/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>