<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Auto on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/auto/</link><description>Recent content in Auto on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 05:48:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/auto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GoTripy Car Rentals is now available in 11 cities across India</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 05:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gotripy-car-rentals-is-now-available-in-11-cities-across-india/</guid><description>Source: GoTripy Car Rentals&amp;rsquo; website.
GoTripy Car Rentals currently operates in 11 cities across India. Their updated website makes online booking easier than ever before.
GoTripy offers a variety of budget-friendly and luxury vehicles, along with professional drivers, in cities like Mumbai, Pune, Nashik, Ahmednagar, Aurangabad, Shirdi, Kolhapur, Delhi, Gurgaon, Bangalore, and Ahmedabad. Their car rental services cater to diverse needs such as local transportation, day trips within a city, sightseeing excursions, airport and railway station transfers, inter-city travel, weekend getaways, business trips, and multi-city journeys.</description></item><item><title>Singapore has relaxed its requirements for car loans</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 08:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-has-relaxed-its-requirements-for-car-loans/</guid><description>The Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) announced adjustments to loan regulations for motor vehicles. The maximum loan-to-value (LTV) ratios and allowable loan durations will be relaxed, but some limitations will remain indefinitely.
These changes come after three years of sustained moderation in Certificate of Entitlement (COE) premiums and related inflationary pressures.
Financial institutions&amp;rsquo; motor vehicle loan restrictions were implemented in 2013 to control car and COE demand and reduce inflationary pressures.</description></item><item><title>Google is revealing how it plans to increase your productivity in the coming year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 13:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/google-is-revealing-how-it-plans-to-increase-your-productivity-in-the-coming-year/</guid><description>Google&amp;rsquo;s annual developer conference, I/O, brought a wave of announcements for Apps, Android, Chromebooks, and the Cloud Platform.
As highlighted on the official Google blog, Android now boasts a staggering one billion users who send an estimated 20 billion text messages and 93 million selfies daily. Key introductions include:
Android Wear
Expanding Android&amp;rsquo;s reach to wearable devices, Android Wear allows users to perform tasks or ask questions simply by saying &amp;ldquo;Ok Google.</description></item></channel></rss>