<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hangzhou on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hangzhou/</link><description>Recent content in Hangzhou on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hangzhou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hainan Airlines is now offering flights from China to France</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</guid><description>Hainan Airlines has introduced a fifth European route to its network, joining existing services to Moscow, Saint Petersburg, Brussels, and Berlin. The inaugural flight, HU7907, departed Hangzhou International Airport on September 3rd, with a stopover at Xi&amp;rsquo;an Xianyang International Airport before continuing to Paris&amp;rsquo; Roissy-Charles de Gaulle Airport.
Source: Hainan Airlines. The ribbon-cutting ceremony for the first flight on September 3.
This new service aims to enhance political, economic, and cultural ties between China and France, especially as 2014 marks the 50th anniversary of diplomatic relations between the two nations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hainan-airlines-is-now-offering-flights-from-china-to-france/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Hong Kong Airlines introduces new flights to Okinawa, Hangzhou, and Ho Chi Minh</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:46:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</guid><description>On March 19th, Hong Kong Airlines launched new flights for its Hong Kong-Okinawa and Hong Kong-Hangzhou routes to meet the increasing demand from business and leisure travelers. The airline celebrated the occasion with events at Hong Kong International Airport and both destination airports.
Alex Wu, Hong Kong Airlines General Manager of the Hong Kong Sales Office, welcomed passengers on the inaugural Okinawa flight HX678 with model airplanes. At the gate, passengers received certificates acknowledging their support for the new route...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hong-kong-airlines-introduces-new-flights-to-okinawa-hangzhou-and-ho-chi-minh/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>