<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Electronic Medical Records on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-medical-records/</link><description>Recent content in Electronic Medical Records on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 19:06:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/electronic-medical-records/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Medical Records Head To The Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 19:06:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>The medical field is transitioning to electronic records to control rising costs. Verizon is at the forefront of this shift with its cloud-based service, Verizon Health Information Exchange. This service provides a platform for storing patient records in a standardized format, enabling healthcare providers to share information seamlessly via web-based access.
Verizon&amp;rsquo;s entry into this domain could lead to the establishment of industry standards for electronic medical records, much like IBM did for personal computers...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/medical-records-head-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Electronic Medical Records and Connectivity Boost Healthcare Efficiency</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 18:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</guid><description>A crucial factor in controlling rising healthcare costs and enhancing patient care is transitioning from paper-based methods to automated systems and electronic medical records (EMRs). The advantage of EMRs lies in their ability to be stored, copied, and shared more efficiently and cost-effectively than paper documents. EMRs provide healthcare providers with more complete patient information compared to traditional paper records.
Electronic medical records encompass prescriptions, diagnoses, patient details, and electronic imaging files like X-rays, CT scans, PET scans, MRI results, and ultrasounds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/electronic-medical-records-and-connectivity-boost-healthcare-efficiency/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Competitive Fiber Optic Service Nearby</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 17:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</guid><description>Does your company use a lot of bandwidth? We&amp;rsquo;re talking 100 Mbps to 10 Gbps or more of reliable, commercial-grade bandwidth. If so, bonded T1 lines or Ethernet over Copper won&amp;rsquo;t cut it. You need fiber optic service. But is competitive fiber optic bandwidth an option in your area? Let&amp;rsquo;s find out&amp;hellip;
The reality is that buildings equipped for fiber optic service are appearing faster than ever. Why? Because today&amp;rsquo;s data-heavy applications need increasingly faster network speeds...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/competitive-fiber-optic-service-nearby/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>