<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fiber Optic Ring on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-ring/</link><description>Recent content in Fiber Optic Ring on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fiber-optic-ring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Level 3 Network Connections Into Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 05:49:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</guid><description>Businesses operating in Mexico or multinational companies with a significant Mexican presence are receiving positive news from Level 3 Communications. The company has initiated a major project to provide high-bandwidth packet network services to businesses across Mexico.
Level 3 identifies a business opportunity in Mexico that other carriers, except the incumbent Telemex, may overlook. Level 3&amp;rsquo;s recent acquisition of Global Crossing, an international bandwidth competitor with significant network connectivity in Latin America, is highly advantageous...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-network-connections-into-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>You’ll Believe This MAN Can Fly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 13:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</guid><description>Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are growing in significance for businesses operating within the same city or its surrounding suburbs, especially for franchises or companies with numerous branch offices like banks, insurance agencies, and gas stations. While network connection speeds were previously a limiting factor, MANs now offer high-speed solutions.
Bridging the gap between Local Area Networks (LANs) and Wide Area Networks (WANs), MANs play a crucial role in transmitting voice, data, and video traffic within a specific geographic area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-ll-believe-this-man-can-fly/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>