<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Energy on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/energy/</link><description>Recent content in Energy on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/energy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the Essent ruling a new milestone in the legal precedent for the free movement of goods?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 20:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-essent-ruling-a-new-milestone-in-the-legal-precedent-for-the-free-movement-of-goods/</guid><description>A Reassessment of Proportionality and Discrimination in Light of the Essent Case Filippo Fontanelli, Lecturer in International Economic Law, University of Edinburgh
Introduction
The September 11, 2014, Essent case (Joined Cases C-204 to C-208/12) judgment by the Court of Justice of the EU presents a nuanced analysis of proportionality, weighing factors such as promoting free energy trade, safeguarding the environment and human health, adhering to international emission reduction agreements, bolstering local employment, and encouraging energy self-sufficiency.</description></item><item><title>REPowerEU: Expanding Europe's financial capacity post-pandemic</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:29:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/repowereu-expanding-europe-s-financial-capacity-post-pandemic/</guid><description>Rosalba Famà, PhD student in EU law, Bocconi University
Photo credit: ThibaultC, via wikicommons media
In response to the energy crisis stemming from the Russian invasion of Ukraine, the European Union is implementing REPowerEU. Presented in May 2022, the comprehensive REPowerEU strategy encompasses proposals to modify existing energy directives and an ambitious industrial policy program aimed at achieving energy independence. This analysis will focus on the latter, referred to as the REPowerEU plan.</description></item><item><title>Airswift Holdings, a global recruiting company, operates in 57 locations worldwide</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 05:20:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/airswift-holdings-a-global-recruiting-company-operates-in-57-locations-worldwide/</guid><description>Source: Airswift Holdings. From left, Duncan Gregson, CEO of Air Energi; Janette Marx, COO, Airswift, Ian Langley, Chairman, Airswift; Peter Searle, CEO, Airswift; and Tobias Reed, CEO of Swift Worldwide Resources.
Air Energi Group and Swift Worldwide Resources combined to establish Airswift Holdings, a global staffing company. Airswift specializes in placing contract and permanent employees, providing resource consultation, assisting with global mobility, and developing managed solutions for companies in the energy, process, and infrastructure sectors.</description></item><item><title>The World Bank will provide assistance for a geothermal energy project in Indonesia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-world-bank-will-provide-assistance-for-a-geothermal-energy-project-in-indonesia/</guid><description>The World Bank is providing $55.25 million in grants to bolster Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s Geothermal Energy Upstream Development Project, which promotes investment in geothermal energy production.
The Clean Technology Fund (CTF) is supplying $49 million for infrastructure and exploratory drilling, while the Global Environment Facility (GEF) is providing an extra $6.25 million to build geothermal exploration expertise, including due diligence safeguards. The Indonesian Ministry of Finance and PT Sarana Multi Infrastruktur, a state-owned infrastructure financing firm, will match the CTF funding.</description></item><item><title>Opinion of Advocate General Szpunar on the compatibility of the Energy Charter Treaty with the Treaties and the jurisdiction of the CJEU in Case C-741/19.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:53:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinion-of-advocate-general-szpunar-on-the-compatibility-of-the-energy-charter-treaty-with-the-treaties-and-the-jurisdiction-of-the-cjeu-in-case-c-741-19/</guid><description>Hannes Lenk, an Assistant Professor in Law at Aarhus University, examines a September 24, 2019 request by the French Cour d’appel de Paris. The court asked the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) to interpret &amp;ldquo;investment&amp;rdquo; as used in Article 1.6 of the Energy Charter Treaty (ECT). The intersection of the ECT and EU law, especially following the Achmea judgment against investor-state dispute settlement (ISDS) provisions in bilateral investment treaties (BITs) between EU Member States, has drawn scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Malaysia to identify energy-efficient government buildings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 21:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/malaysia-to-identify-energy-efficient-government-buildings/</guid><description>Malaysia&amp;rsquo;s Energy Commission, under the Ministry of Energy, Science, Technology, Environment and Climate Change (MESTECC), has introduced the National Building Energy Intensity (BEI) Labelling for Government Buildings.
This program strives to enhance energy efficiency in government-owned buildings within Malaysia, encouraging building owners to prioritize and improve energy conservation. Buildings are assigned a star rating based on their energy efficiency, with a five-star rating indicating the highest level of efficiency.
The initial phase, concluding in late 2018, encompasses 100 buildings belonging to ministries, departments, and agencies under MESTECC and the Prime Minister&amp;rsquo;s Department.</description></item><item><title>In 2020, Canopy Power is making Southeast Asia more environmentally friendly</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2020-canopy-power-is-making-southeast-asia-more-environmentally-friendly/</guid><description>Source: Canopy Power. This image shows solar panels installed on the roof of a beachfront pavilion at Batu Batu resort. This installation was part of a larger project by Canopy Power.
Despite the economic downturn of 2020, Canopy Power has announced several accomplishments within the Asia Pacific region.
One such accomplishment was the completion of a renewable energy microgrid in the third quarter of 2020. This microgrid, located on Batu Batu, a sustainable island resort 16 km from Mersing, Malaysia, will allow the 22-villa resort to decrease its reliance on diesel and lower carbon emissions.</description></item><item><title>How can legislation empower Europe? By phasing out fossil fuels and implementing the Sustainability Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 02:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-can-legislation-empower-europe-by-phasing-out-fossil-fuels-and-implementing-the-sustainability-directive/</guid><description>Ewan McGaughey, Reader in Law, King’s College London
Photo credit: Geopolitical Intelligence Services, via Wikicommons
Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine has prompted initiatives like RePowerEU and similar UK programs, aiming to eliminate reliance on Russian fossil fuels. President Biden has even called for a complete end to fossil fuel use, arguing that dependence on any authoritarian regime for energy is no longer acceptable. This shift recognizes the need to transition to renewable energy sources rapidly, acknowledging everyone&amp;rsquo;s fundamental right to benefit from scientific advancements.</description></item><item><title>Protecting data and smart meters: GDPR and the EU clean energy law's 'winter package'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giulia Pizza, FratiniVergano, European Lawyers - a Brussels-based law firm specialising in European and international law
Introduction
In late 2016, the European Commission introduced the “Clean Energy for All Europeans” legislative package to modernize Europe&amp;rsquo;s electricity market and encourage cleaner energy solutions. This push for &amp;ldquo;decentralization&amp;rdquo; is seen as a way to drive innovation and shift the focus to a demand-driven energy policy. The goal is to give consumers the tools they need to actively participate in this change.</description></item></channel></rss>