<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Corroded on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/corroded/</link><description>Recent content in Corroded on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/corroded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Replacing the original DIN or RCA plugs is a crucial step when restoring a Beogram 4002. The old plugs often show corrosion due to the lack of gold plating. Upgrading to modern, all-metal plugs with gold-plated terminals is recommended. This upgrade minimizes electromagnetic interference and ensures optimal signal transfer to the amplifier by maintaining low contact resistance, especially important for the delicate MMC20 cartridge signals.
The original RCA plugs on a Beogram 4002 (5513) being restored were in poor condition...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</guid><description>Over time, many Beogram devices have developed corroded DIN or RCA plugs. It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to replace these old connectors with new, gold-plated ones. This specific Beogram 4002 (5513) came with RCA connectors.
I typically use large, modern, high-quality metal plugs for replacements. However, this project had a unique requirement: the Beogram needed to connect to a Beolab 5000. The Beolab 5000 has a compact compartment for its connectors, which creates limitations on plug size...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold-Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4000 restoration continued with gold-plating the carriage position switch terminals to address a common issue. In my experience, about 90% of problems with this B&amp;amp;O model stem from oxidized switch terminals. These switches are critical because they inform the digital control system about the carriage&amp;rsquo;s position. Malfunctioning switches lead to a confused control system, so gold-plating is recommended for its resistance to oxidation, ensuring long-term reliability.
While not the worst I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in these models, the black spots indicate some oxidation was present...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): New Gold Plated DIN Plug</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</guid><description>During the ongoing refurbishment of a Beogram 4002 (5513) turntable, a corroded DIN5 plug was replaced after a new output relay had been installed. The original plug showed significant signs of wear.
A high-quality Rean DIN5 plug with gold-plated terminals was chosen as a replacement. Photos document the preparation of the cable and the installation process. The author notes the limited space inside the DIN5 plug, making it difficult to separate the signal and ground connections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-new-gold-plated-din-plug/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Replacing the Original DIN5 Plug with a Modern All-Metal Gold Plated Unit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 09:43:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</guid><description>To fully restore a 4002, replacing the often corroded DIN5 connector is essential. The delicate low-voltage signals need optimal contact. Gold is an ideal material due to its resistance to oxidation, ensuring a strong and long-lasting connection. The pictures illustrate this process, showing the old connector&amp;rsquo;s condition, preparing the cable for the new connector, the soldering process, and finally, the pristine new gold-plated connector installed. This upgrade is a significant step towards bringing the Beogram back to its former glory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-replacing-the-original-din5-plug-with-a-modern-all-metal-gold-plated-unit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5514): Installation of a New DIN5 Plug With Gold Coated Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 16:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</guid><description>My Beogram 4002 (5514) restoration is coming along nicely. I believe a key part of revitalizing these turntables is installing a new, all-metal DIN 5 plug with gold-plated contacts. The old plugs often suffer from corrosion, which hinders the delicate signal transfer from the MMC cartridge. For example, here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the old plug with tarnished terminals:
This image showcases the soldering work within the updated plug:
And finally, the finished product:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5514-installation-of-a-new-din5-plug-with-gold-coated-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoring the Carriage Position and Solenoid Driven Switches</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</guid><description>Following the keypad cluster rebuild on this Beogram 4000 turntable, the next step was to address the mechanical switches that control its operation. These switches are grouped into two clusters: one set located under the carriage that dictates tonearm positioning, and another positioned near the solenoid. The solenoid-activated switches are critical for engaging the tracking mechanism, initiating output when the stylus is in the groove, and regulating the solenoid power upon the arm&amp;rsquo;s descent...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoring-the-carriage-position-and-solenoid-driven-switches/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5503): Installation of a New All-Metal DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Contacts</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 15:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</guid><description>I believe that any restoration of a Beogram 4002 isn&amp;rsquo;t truly finished until the old output plugs, which are often corroded, are replaced with modern, all-metal ones featuring gold-plated terminals. High-quality analog signals deserve the best possible connections. Here are some photos documenting the DIN5 plug replacement I completed on a Beogram 4002 (5503) restoration:
The original DIN5 plug is shown here:
This photo shows the &amp;ldquo;under the hood&amp;rdquo; soldering work:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5503-installation-of-a-new-all-metal-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-contacts/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Upgrade of Signal Path with New DIN5 Plug and a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 22:49:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The DIN5 plug on the Beogram 4000 being restored was heavily oxidized and needed replacement. A new, fully metal plug with gold-plated terminals was installed.
To improve the signal output, a switch was added to connect the signal and system grounds. This feature is beneficial when using a DIN5 to RCA adapter, as RCA cables lack a system ground. Connecting the system ground to the signal ground on the Beogram can reduce humming...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-upgrade-of-signal-path-with-new-din5-plug-and-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Gold Plating of Keypad Contact Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 01:20:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</guid><description>A key feature of the Beogram 400x series is its use of mechanical switches in the control systems. These switches utilize spring-loaded contact terminals, activated either by the user or, in the Beogram 4000, by the carriage movement during playback. The functionality of these switches is crucial for these Beograms to operate correctly. Due to the prevalence of control problems stemming from oxidized terminals in the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s switches, electrochemical gold plating of these terminals is now offered as a service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-gold-plating-of-keypad-contact-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5501): Gold Plating of the Carriage Position Switch Spring Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 20:41:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring an early model Beogram 4002 (5501) turntable, and it&amp;rsquo;s captivating to trace the evolution of its design from the original Beogram 4000. Having already tackled the arm lowering mechanism, I&amp;rsquo;ve shifted my focus to the carriage position switches, a particularly interesting aspect of the 4002&amp;rsquo;s design.
While the design echoes that of the 4000, it features some notable refinements. The 4000&amp;rsquo;s 7&amp;quot; record set-down point switch, for instance, was a break switch prone to issues stemming from oxidation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5501-gold-plating-of-the-carriage-position-switch-spring-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Plating of Carriage Position Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:37:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the restoration of the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control panel (keypad), the next step was to focus on the carriage position switches. These switches are vital for the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s digital control system, and even one faulty switch can render the entire device unusable. Similar to the keypad switches, these are prone to oxidation, making gold plating a reliable solution to prevent future contact problems. The image below displays the circuit board with the switches after detaching the carriage position indicator component...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-plating-of-carriage-position-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Keypad Assembly - Gold Plated Switch Terminals and Light Bulbs Replaced with LEDs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 18:46:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</guid><description>Following the repair of the arm&amp;rsquo;s lowering and tracking systems, the next step was to focus on the Beogram 4000&amp;rsquo;s control center: the keypad assembly. This unit houses an early digital control system that manages inputs from the keypad&amp;rsquo;s keys. The mechanical switches connected to these keys are a common source of problems and should be gold-plated to ensure reliable, long-term operation after restoration.
The keypad cluster was removed from the Beogram and opened, revealing a missing light bulb in the position indicator scale...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-keypad-assembly-gold-plated-switch-terminals-and-light-bulbs-replaced-with-leds/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Gold Coating of Solenoid Activated Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 22:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 has a set of four switches, activated by the solenoid, which control its operation when the tonearm is lowered. These switches, like others in the keypad and under the carriage, are prone to oxidation and can cause malfunctions. One crucial switch manages the solenoid current as the tonearm lowers, and if oxidized, it prevents the arm from lowering. It&amp;rsquo;s highly recommended to have these switches gold-plated for optimal performance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-gold-coating-of-solenoid-activated-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Replacement of Corroded RCA Plugs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:51:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) currently under restoration was equipped with RCA plugs and a grounding wire instead of the typical DIN 5 connector. The plugs and grounding terminal were noticeably dirty and corroded.
The RCA plugs were switched out for all-metal gold-plated ones, and a new grounding terminal was installed.
These compact RCA plugs lack color coding, so 3D-printed inserts were created. These inserts enclose the back of the plugs and provide a visual distinction between the left and right channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-replacement-of-corroded-rca-plugs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: Restoration of the Control Panel - LEDs and Gold Plating of Switch Terminals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 07:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</guid><description>Following the enhancement of the carriage position switches, the control panel restoration of a Beogram 4000 turntable commenced. The project involved a typical upgrade of incandescent bulbs to LED assemblies and gold plating of switch terminals for enhanced longevity and performance.
The initial stage revealed significantly oxidized keypad switch terminals:
The terminals were carefully removed:
Following oxidation removal using a fiberglass pen, the terminals were gold-coated:
An oversight led to one terminal being missed initially:..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-restoration-of-the-control-panel-leds-and-gold-plating-of-switch-terminals/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000: A New DIN 5 Plug and Installation of a Grounding Switch</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:48:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</guid><description>The Beogram 4000 I&amp;rsquo;m currently restoring had a severely corroded and improperly installed DIN 5 plug, clearly not the original. The attached photos illustrate its poor condition.
One of the pictures highlights a loose black wire, potentially a makeshift attempt to address humming issues (unsurprising given the plug&amp;rsquo;s installation). Adding to the problem, a poorly executed soldering job had left one of the signal leads disconnected.
I removed the old plug and prepared the wires for a new one, as shown in the photo...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4000-a-new-din-5-plug-and-installation-of-a-grounding-switch/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5513): Installation of New DIN5 Plug with Gold Plated Pins</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 07:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</guid><description>A gold-plated plug is the finishing touch for a fully restored signal path. Here&amp;rsquo;s the process on a Beogram 4002(5513) I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on:
Above is the original plug in rough shape due to oxidation.
The new Rean plug offers a neat and tidy internal layout.
Placing the metal enclosure back results in an even more visually appealing look. That&amp;rsquo;s the Beolove!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5513-installation-of-new-din5-plug-with-gold-plated-pins/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>