<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fabric on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fabric/</link><description>Recent content in Fabric on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/fabric/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Four fashion trends from New York Fashion Week</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 10:09:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/four-fashion-trends-from-new-york-fashion-week/</guid><description>Milanoo.com, an online retailer for apparel and other goods, has recently highlighted the major trends observed during February&amp;rsquo;s New York Fashion Week.
Source: Milanoo website.
One trend was wrapped skirts that sit above the knee. This is a departure from the more revealing styles seen in past fashion events, which Milanoo refers to as &amp;ldquo;the consistent sexy style.&amp;rdquo; The company observed, &amp;ldquo;Skirts have been very popular these years. But things are changing.</description></item><item><title>The Avex Group introduces high-quality hemp fabric as part of the majotae brand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:57:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-avex-group-introduces-high-quality-hemp-fabric-as-part-of-the-majotae-brand/</guid><description>Avex Group Holdings, a Japanese entertainment company, has introduced &amp;ldquo;majotae,&amp;rdquo; a fabric brand reviving taima-fu, a traditional natural hemp fabric.
The photo above features (from left) Shigekazu Takeuchi, Representative Director of Avex Group Holdings; Masato Matsuura, CEO of Avex Group Holdings; Shinichiro Yoshida, natural fabric expert; Genbei Yamaguchi, obi artisan; and Hiroshi Onishi, CEO of Isetan Mitsukoshi Holdings. They were attending the opening reception for the &amp;ldquo;majotae: The Forgotten Fabric&amp;rdquo; exhibition at Daikanyama Hillside Forum on October 22, 2014, in Tokyo, Japan.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean fashion designers are displaying their collections that have been digitally printed by Epson</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-fashion-designers-are-displaying-their-collections-that-have-been-digitally-printed-by-epson/</guid><description>Source: Epson Singapore. Display, Wai Yang.
Epson, a printing technology company, partnered with designers based in Singapore for FashionisTech, a showcase at the recent FUZE Fashion Technology 2017 event in Singapore. The designers used Epson&amp;rsquo;s digital printing technology to create their collections.
Organized by Textile and Fashion Federation (TAFF), the summit was the first of its kind in Singapore. It promoted advancements in materials and highlighted creative uses of technology by Singaporean fashion brands.</description></item></channel></rss>