<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>European Parliament on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-parliament/</link><description>Recent content in European Parliament on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/european-parliament/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 1: The Legal Framework - Should the EU impose sanctions on its Member States for violations of the rule of law and human rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
As an EU law and human rights professor for over two decades, the topic of sanctioning Member States for human rights violations was once straightforward. The enforcement procedure (Article 7 TEU) was never used, making in-depth discussions unnecessary. My focus remained on practical issues like arrest warrants and asylum seekers.
However, the landscape has shifted. Like Article 50, which also addresses the EU&amp;rsquo;s relationship with Member States, Article 7 seems hastily drafted without considering its practical application, possibly because its creators never anticipated its use...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-1-the-legal-framework-should-the-eu-impose-sanctions-on-its-member-states-for-violations-of-the-rule-of-law-and-human-rights/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU revives the old 'third pillar' with the EU Zombie Law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
In 1993, the Maastricht Treaty&amp;rsquo;s implementation brought about the EU&amp;rsquo;s adoption of criminal law and policing measures under a unique system known as the &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo; of EU law. Although modified by the Treaty of Amsterdam in 1999 and facing multiple attempts at its abolishment over the following decade, it persisted until the Treaty of Lisbon, which formally ended it upon coming into effect on December 1, 2009, albeit with a five-year transitional period...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-revives-the-old-third-pillar-with-the-eu-zombie-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU Return Directive has been implemented by the European Parliament to bring the EU expulsion policy in line with recommendations from UN human rights expert mechanisms.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:52:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</guid><description>Izabella Majcher, PhD in International Law; Senior Legal Officer, ECRE*
*The views expressed in the post are those of the author and do not necessarily reflect the position of ECRE In December 2020, the European Parliament issued a Resolution regarding the implementation of the Return Directive (a 2008 directive concerning the rules for returning undocumented migrants). This Resolution resulted from the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s failure to assess the Directive&amp;rsquo;s implementation, a task they were supposed to perform every three years starting in 2013...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-return-directive-has-been-implemented-by-the-european-parliament-to-bring-the-eu-expulsion-policy-in-line-with-recommendations-from-un-human-rights-expert-mechanisms/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it appropriate for the outcome of the European Parliament elections to dictate the selection of the next President of the European Commission, or are there valid concerns about this democratic process?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 21:55:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s doubtful the European Court of Justice will decide the next European Commission President. Election laws typically set the stage but don&amp;rsquo;t directly determine the winner, although there are notable exceptions like the 2000 US election.
The 2014 Commission President election is unique because the rules changed, and their interpretation is debated. Previously, the European Council appointed the President after European Parliament approval. The Treaty of Lisbon introduced new rules, applied for the first time, stating the Parliament &amp;ldquo;elects&amp;rdquo; the President based on the Council&amp;rsquo;s nomination, &amp;ldquo;taking account&amp;rdquo; of Parliament election results...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-appropriate-for-the-outcome-of-the-european-parliament-elections-to-dictate-the-selection-of-the-next-president-of-the-european-commission-or-are-there-valid-concerns-about-this-democratic-process/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU establishes significant limitations on the Commission's power to initiate actions.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</guid><description>Steve Peers
It is a fundamental principle of EU law, as taught to every student of the subject, that the Commission has a near-monopoly on proposing new EU legislation - it is the &amp;lsquo;motor&amp;rsquo; of EU integration. This near-monopoly is often called the Commission&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;right of initiative&amp;rsquo;. But does this right also imply a right to withdraw proposals? And if it does, are there any limitations to this power? These questions were addressed by the CJEU in a significant ruling...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-establishes-significant-limitations-on-the-commission-s-power-to-initiate-actions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the EU here to rescue legal aid, or to put it to rest? Evaluating discussions on the proposed Directive.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 08:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</guid><description>by Claire Perinaud (FREE Group Trainee)
Access to legal aid is crucial for individuals facing criminal charges, enabling them to mount a proper defense. The EU is developing legislation to address this right, but its impact remains uncertain.
Progress of the Procedural Rights Roadmap
EU legislation concerning the procedural rights of suspects and accused individuals in criminal cases has been developing gradually since late 2009, following years of unsuccessful attempts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-here-to-rescue-legal-aid-or-to-put-it-to-rest-evaluating-discussions-on-the-proposed-directive/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Questions for two Commission Vice-Presidents on EU foreign policy, human rights, and institutional reform.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</guid><description>By Emilio DE CAPITANI, Henri LABAYLE and Steve PEERS
This week, Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) will continue interviewing candidates for the next European Commission to decide on its confirmation. MEPs have already posed written questions and received responses. However, the upcoming oral hearings offer MEPs a crucial opportunity to understand the Commissioners&amp;rsquo; intentions and secure key political promises.
This blog post proposes questions for MEPs to ask two potential Commission Vice-Presidents: the High Representative for the Common Foreign and Security Policy and Commission Vice President for external relations (Mogherini), and the Commissioner for Better Regulation, Fundamental Rights and the Rule of Law (Timmermans)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/questions-for-two-commission-vice-presidents-on-eu-foreign-policy-human-rights-and-institutional-reform/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Prisoner voting is now a legal issue under EU legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 05:28:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</guid><description>Jo Shaw, Salvesen Chair of European Institutions
Article 39(2) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights states:
‘European Parliament members shall be chosen through direct, universal suffrage in a free and secret ballot.’
The Grand Chamber of the Court of Justice, in a concise and understated judgment in Delvigne (Case C-650/13; ECLI:EU:C:2015:648) delivered on October 6, 2015, provided further definition to this provision. It found that national policies determining voter eligibility in European Parliament elections fall under EU law&amp;rsquo;s purview, as they implement EU law according to Article 51(1) of the Charter of Fundamental Rights...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/prisoner-voting-is-now-a-legal-issue-under-eu-legislation/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the new Directive on immigration for students and researchers a minor advancement or a significant stride?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 21:38:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU has been working for many years to attract highly skilled individuals from non-EU countries. However, the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s reports indicate that the existing legislation, specifically the 2005 Researchers&amp;rsquo; Directive and the 2004 Students&amp;rsquo; Directive, have not significantly increased the number of students and researchers coming to the EU.
As a result, in 2013, the Commission recommended a complete overhaul of these laws. The European Parliament (EP) and the Council recently reached an agreement on the content of this proposal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-directive-on-immigration-for-students-and-researchers-a-minor-advancement-or-a-significant-stride/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Farewell and gratitude for the fish: CJEU provides clarity on international law and institutional matters related to fisheries.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:25:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s fisheries policy generates disagreement both within and outside the EU because of its effects on fish populations and the economic well-being of fishing communities. Prior to the Treaty of Lisbon, its implementation was essentially under the sole authority of the Council. Although the European Parliament (EP) attempted to gain shared control over some of the policy&amp;rsquo;s external aspects by asserting its consent was required for international fisheries agreements that significantly impacted the EU budget, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) dismissed this claim...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/farewell-and-gratitude-for-the-fish-cjeu-provides-clarity-on-international-law-and-institutional-matters-related-to-fisheries/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The CJEU guarantees the fundamental democratic and judicial oversight of the EU's foreign policy.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) confirmed in its recent decision in European Parliament v Council that the EU&amp;rsquo;s Common Foreign and Security Policy (CFSP) is subject to a minimum standard of democratic and judicial oversight.
The case involved a challenge by the European Parliament (EP) to the Council&amp;rsquo;s decision to sign and ratify a treaty between the EU and Mauritius. This treaty pertained to the EU&amp;rsquo;s military operations against pirates operating in the Indian Ocean...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-guarantees-the-fundamental-democratic-and-judicial-oversight-of-the-eu-s-foreign-policy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it time for the EU to increase transparency in its legislative process, as condemned by the EU Court?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</guid><description>Massimo Frigo, Senior Legal Adviser of the International Commission of Jurist’s Europe Programme*
Occasionally, cases concerning seemingly insignificant administrative matters evolve into pivotal judgments, shaping the continuous development of our democratic legal frameworks. A prime example in the US is Marbury v. Madison, a case initially garnering limited public interest due to its focus on judicial appointment procedures. Nonetheless, it ultimately established the crucial precedent of constitutional review within the US legal system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-for-the-eu-to-increase-transparency-in-its-legislative-process-as-condemned-by-the-eu-court/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is there a difference this time? The Commission's work programme for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently released its yearly plan, outlining a different approach than previous years. Beyond the typical policy revisions, this Commission aims to introduce fewer new EU initiatives and withdraw more pending proposals.
Is this approach truly different from past Commissions? Comparing this year&amp;rsquo;s plan to those of previous Commissions offers insights.
In 2005, the incoming Barroso Commission put forward 32 pages of proposals, without mentioning any withdrawals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-there-a-difference-this-time-the-commission-s-work-programme-for-2015/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Exploring the European Parliament's Closed Reading Rooms: Shedding Light on Transparency in the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 09:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Dr Vigjilenca Abazi
Assistant Professor of European Law
Maastricht University
Documents related to various topics, such as Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (TTIP) negotiations, EU Food Safety Authority oversight, and tax justice, share a common factor: accessing them requires select Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to participate in closed reading rooms. This blog post will examine how this departure from transparent parliamentary oversight is becoming increasingly common and question its potential impact on public access to documents requests...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/exploring-the-european-parliament-s-closed-reading-rooms-shedding-light-on-transparency-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Imprisoning bankers: the latest EU Directive on enforcing criminal penalties for market abuse</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</guid><description>Steve Peers
EU politicians likely feel a sense of relief as they&amp;rsquo;ve discovered a group even less popular than themselves: bankers. This unpopularity has only intensified as the global financial crisis and resulting austerity measures continue to impact ordinary citizens across numerous Member States. Politicians understand that targeting disliked groups rarely hurts them in the polls, leading EU institutions to enact legislation that could imprison bankers for specific wrongdoings...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/imprisoning-bankers-the-latest-eu-directive-on-enforcing-criminal-penalties-for-market-abuse/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is Juncker capable of being a reformist Commission President, like Nixon was in going to China?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 22:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A common saying in American politics, &amp;ldquo;only Nixon could go to China,&amp;rdquo; suggests that only a politician with a well-established reputation can persuade their base to accept a major policy shift. Nixon, a staunch anti-Communist, was able to convince American conservatives that engaging with Communist China was in their best interest. This principle might apply to the European Union as well. The recent European Parliament (EP) elections saw a rise in support for anti-EU parties in several Member States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-juncker-capable-of-being-a-reformist-commission-president-like-nixon-was-in-going-to-china/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Guide for Law Students: Understanding EU Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</guid><description>Catherine Barnard, Trinity College, Cambridge*
EU law is a captivating field of study that offers something for everyone, particularly those interested in politics, visionary thinking, and pragmatic solutions. Even if these aren&amp;rsquo;t your primary interests, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to study EU law due to its mandatory nature. However, it&amp;rsquo;s unlike any other legal system you may have encountered, defying categorization and fitting into no single box.
Before diving in, it&amp;rsquo;s helpful to reflect on your existing political perspectives on the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/guide-for-law-students-understanding-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Legal Foundation and Democratic Discussion of Indian Ocean Piracy</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 20:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While crucial in EU law, legal base arguments are often confusing for those outside the realm of EU legal experts, especially when there&amp;rsquo;s agreement on the issue itself. Take the example of piracy in the Indian Ocean. Everyone agrees it&amp;rsquo;s a problem, except perhaps the pirates, and that the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision to combat it with military force is necessary.
Disagreement arises regarding what to do with captured pirates...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-legal-foundation-and-democratic-discussion-of-indian-ocean-piracy/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Council is making initial progress in reforming EU data protection law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 19:05:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s 1995 data protection rules, laid out in a Directive, are undergoing a major transformation. The Commission has proposed a new Regulation, sparking discussions since early 2012. While negotiations continue, June saw a significant step forward: the Council (composed of EU Member States&amp;rsquo; justice ministers) agreed on its stance regarding the proposal&amp;rsquo;s application outside the EU. This agreement, though partial, provides valuable insight into the negotiation&amp;rsquo;s trajectory...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-council-is-making-initial-progress-in-reforming-eu-data-protection-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>If the UK remains a member of the EU past May 22nd, it will be necessary for the country to hold European Parliament elections in order to uphold democratic principles.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</guid><description>Professor Eleanor Spaventa, Bocconi University
The UK&amp;rsquo;s political climate surrounding Brexit is highly unstable. Prime Minister May&amp;rsquo;s strategy of delaying a decision may or may not work, but it seems to have created a situation where extending Article 50 of the Treaty on European Union is unavoidable. If Parliament approves the Withdrawal Agreement this week, the UK will need more time to implement the necessary legislation before leaving the EU...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/if-the-uk-remains-a-member-of-the-eu-past-may-22nd-it-will-be-necessary-for-the-country-to-hold-european-parliament-elections-in-order-to-uphold-democratic-principles/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Regarding knowledge as power: the transparency of procedures for making EU laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 00:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</guid><description>Päivi Leino (University of Helsinki)
A key promise made during the adoption of the Lisbon Treaty was increased transparency in EU law-making. However, this has not yet been realized. Access to documents related to EU legislative processes, especially &amp;ldquo;trilogues&amp;rdquo; (informal meetings between the European Parliament, the Council, and the Commission), has become a significant concern. This issue is highlighted in the new Interinstitutional Agreement (IIA) on Better Regulation, the European Ombudsman&amp;rsquo;s public consultation on trilogue transparency, and a legal appeal by a former LIBE Committee Secretariat head against the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s refusal to grant full access to legislative documents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regarding-knowledge-as-power-the-transparency-of-procedures-for-making-eu-laws/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Briefing 3: Is there a lack of democracy in the EU?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</guid><description>Laurent Pech, Professor of Law, Middlesex University
Steve Peers, Professor of Law, University of Essex
The European Union is frequently criticized for being undemocratic or suffering from a &amp;ldquo;democratic deficit.&amp;rdquo; One common assertion is that all EU decisions are made by the unelected bureaucrats of the European Commission. This post will demonstrate why this criticism is fundamentally flawed. It stems from a misunderstanding of both the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s actual powers within the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making processes and how the European Commission is appointed...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/briefing-3-is-there-a-lack-of-democracy-in-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The EU legislature enforces the principle of ineffectiveness to combat counterfeiting of the euro.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Court of Justice has worked to solidify the principle of effectiveness in EU criminal law through significant rulings like Pupino and those on environmental crime legislation. However, the EU legislature&amp;rsquo;s recent adoption of a new Directive on euro counterfeiting seems to contradict this, illustrating a principle of ineffectiveness.
Background
Currently, euro counterfeiting is addressed through various measures, notably a 2000 pre-Lisbon Framework Decision. This Decision, part of the former &amp;rsquo;third pillar&amp;rsquo;, establishes substantive criminal law rules on currency counterfeiting, including the euro...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-legislature-enforces-the-principle-of-ineffectiveness-to-combat-counterfeiting-of-the-euro/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for Thomas Piketty to bring about reform in both capitalism and democracy within the European Union?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 02:08:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</guid><description>Steve Peers
French economist Thomas Piketty unexpectedly became a prominent intellectual figure, especially in the UK and US, with his book &amp;ldquo;Capital,&amp;rdquo; which presents a new perspective on the relationship between capitalism and democracy.
Maintaining his engagement with current issues, Piketty has contributed to a proposal for EU reform, connecting his academic work to practical solutions.
The EU, once adept at managing capitalism but less so democracy, now struggles with both...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-thomas-piketty-to-bring-about-reform-in-both-capitalism-and-democracy-within-the-european-union/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Additional research is required to further explore the EU's efforts to attract a greater number of non-EU researchers and students.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU member states, similar to other economically advanced nations, require a growing number of highly skilled workers. Current EU regulations have not significantly increased the influx of students and researchers from other countries, prompting the Commission to propose revisions in 2013. Both the European Parliament (EP) and the Council have agreed on their respective stances for the proposed law and are preparing to negotiate a final version...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/additional-research-is-required-to-further-explore-the-eu-s-efforts-to-attract-a-greater-number-of-non-eu-researchers-and-students/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Extension and elections: It is important to discuss Article 50.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</guid><description>Professors Catherine Barnard (University of Cambridge) and Steve Weatherill (University of Oxford) explore the implications of Article 50, the exit clause for leaving the European Union. While brief and seemingly straightforward, Article 50 leaves much open to interpretation.
The authors begin by outlining the process for extending the two-year withdrawal period, noting that an extension would require unanimous agreement from all EU member states. They suggest that an extension is likely to be granted if requested by the UK, as it would provide additional time for the UK to either pass the necessary legislation to implement the Withdrawal Agreement or prepare for a &amp;ldquo;no-deal&amp;rdquo; Brexit...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/extension-and-elections-it-is-important-to-discuss-article-50/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Overview of the European Democracy Action Plan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 04:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
The European Democracy Action Plan (EDAP) is one piece of a larger effort to regulate the online world. Unveiled as a key initiative by Commission President von der Leyen, it joins upcoming legislation like the Digital Services Act (DSA) and Digital Markets Act (DMA). These measures signal a change in how the EU approaches internet regulation and raise questions about the EU&amp;rsquo;s authority in this space...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/overview-of-the-european-democracy-action-plan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Should there be increased use of majority voting in EU social policy decisions? Evaluating the Commission's suggestion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 12:57:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</guid><description>Ane Aranguiz, PhD Candidate, University of Antwerp
In April 2019, the European Commission initiated a discussion on streamlining the EU&amp;rsquo;s decision-making in social policy. The goal was to enhance efficiency by utilizing &amp;ldquo;passerelle&amp;rdquo; clauses, which permit a shift from unanimous voting to qualified majority voting (QMV) and from special to ordinary legislative procedures. This change, while requiring unanimous approval from Member States, aims to bypass the complexities of Treaty revisions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-there-be-increased-use-of-majority-voting-in-eu-social-policy-decisions-evaluating-the-commission-s-suggestion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can a person be a member of both a national parliament and the European Parliament at the same time?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 13:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recently, Geert Wilders, the leader of the Dutch PVV party and a newly elected Member of the European Parliament (MEP), declared his intent to pursue legal action to maintain his position as both an MEP and a member of the Dutch national parliament. This begs the question: does such a right exist?
The crux of the matter lies in Article 39 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, which states that every EU citizen possesses the right to vote in and stand as a candidate for European Parliament elections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-a-person-be-a-member-of-both-a-national-parliament-and-the-european-parliament-at-the-same-time/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>