<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Third-Country Nationals on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/third-country-nationals/</link><description>Recent content in Third-Country Nationals on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/third-country-nationals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CS and Rendón Marín: Are Union Citizens and their Third-Country National Parents Experiencing a Revival of the Ruiz Zambrano Ruling?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 19:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</guid><description>Maria Haag, PhD Researcher, European University Institute (Florence, Italy) &amp;amp; Michigan Grotius Research Scholar, University of Michigan Law School (Ann Arbor, Michigan)
Background
Five years ago, a significant ruling in the case of C-34/09 Ruiz Zambrano was delivered by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The court found that national measures that hinder EU citizens from genuinely enjoying their rights as citizens are prohibited under Article 20 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cs-and-rend-n-mar-n-are-union-citizens-and-their-third-country-national-parents-experiencing-a-revival-of-the-ruiz-zambrano-ruling/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Staying connected with the (Turkish) family: the integration criteria for family reunification in Genc</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</guid><description>Silvia Adamo, Postdoctoral Fellow, bEUcitizen – Barriers to European Citizenship/Faculty of Law, University of Copenhagen
This piece examines the expectations for integration placed on Turkish citizens residing in EU Member States seeking family reunification. While the EU Directive on family reunification allows Member States to establish integration requirements, the 2015 CJEU judgment in K and A clarified the limitations of these requirements. Additionally, the 2014 Dogan judgment addressed the standstill clause in the EU-Turkey Association Agreement concerning family reunification for self-employed Turkish nationals...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/staying-connected-with-the-turkish-family-the-integration-criteria-for-family-reunification-in-genc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice resolves the issue of posting third-country workers within the EU.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 11:06:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</guid><description>Amedeo Arena, Assistant Professor of European Law - University of Naples &amp;ldquo;Federico II&amp;rdquo; School of Law
Judgment of the court (Second Chamber) of 11 September 2014, Essent Energie Productie BV v. Minister van SocialeZaken en Werkgelegenheid, Case C-91/13.
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) has consistently maintained that, in contrast to workers from EU Member States, Turkish nationals do not possess the right to freedom of movement within the European Union...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-resolves-the-issue-of-posting-third-country-workers-within-the-eu/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Citizens' Family Reunion: A third-country national family member who is separated from an EU citizen can obtain permanent residency status.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 11:31:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</guid><description>Chiara Berneri, Lecturer at BPP Law School
Article 16(2) of the EU citizens’ Directive (Directive 2004/38) outlines that non-EU family members of EU citizens residing in another EU country can obtain permanent residency, which provides stronger protection against deportation, if they have lived legally with the EU citizen continuously for five years. This article examines whether this right applies if the couple separates and enters new relationships before the five-year period ends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-citizens-family-reunion-a-third-country-national-family-member-who-is-separated-from-an-eu-citizen-can-obtain-permanent-residency-status/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brexit's Irony in Immigration Control</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 23:11:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</guid><description>Daniel Thym, Professor of Public, European and International Law at the University of Konstanz
Immigration was a key issue during the Brexit debate, with &amp;ldquo;taking back control&amp;rdquo; becoming a central theme. In her January speech in Lancaster, Theresa May emphasized that controlling immigration was a primary goal of the Brexit negotiations. She stressed the public&amp;rsquo;s message that Brexit must equate to managing the influx of people from Europe to Britain...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-irony-in-immigration-control/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Understanding the Requirements for Family Reunion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</guid><description>Georgios Milios
PhD candidate on immigration law at the Faculty of Law, University of Barcelona
This piece examines two cases, Dogan and Noorzia, which prompted opinions from Advocate General Paolo Mengozzi on April 30, 2014. These cases center around interpretations of Directive 2003/86, concerning family reunification. Specifically, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) was tasked with determining if proof of basic language proficiency in a Member State could be a prerequisite for granting residency to a third-country national&amp;rsquo;s family member...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/understanding-the-requirements-for-family-reunion/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Will the new Directive on intra-corporate transferees improve the safeguarding of third-country nationals and bolster EU competitiveness?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</guid><description>Lucia Brieskova, PhD candidate at Oxford Brookes University
This post examines the new EU Intra-Corporate Transfers Directive (ICTD) concerning legal economic migration. This analysis is divided into three parts. First, it explains the background and motivation behind introducing this Directive and its connection to other EU directives on economic migration. Second, it outlines the key changes this Directive brings. Finally, it highlights potential issues that will be analyzed in future posts...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-directive-on-intra-corporate-transferees-improve-the-safeguarding-of-third-country-nationals-and-bolster-eu-competitiveness/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Irreconcilable Disagreements: The Impact of Divorce and Departure of EU Citizens According to the Citizens' Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 18:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A complex situation arises when an EU citizen, residing in another Member State, divorces a non-EU spouse after the EU citizen has left that Member State. The EU Citizens’ Directive provides rules for divorce and departure, but these rules seem contradictory. An Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion in the significant Singh case tackles these issues, as does a pending reference from the UK. However, this opinion is fundamentally flawed, and the Court of Justice should consider a different approach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/irreconcilable-disagreements-the-impact-of-divorce-and-departure-of-eu-citizens-according-to-the-citizens-directive/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>