<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sales on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sales/</link><description>Recent content in Sales on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Imperial Hotel in Japan is targeting visitors from Southeast Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</guid><description>Source: Imperial Hotel website.
The established Imperial Hotel of Japan has launched its inaugural full-service sales office in Southeast Asia to bolster its marketing endeavors within the ASEAN region. Imperial Hotel, Ltd., the company behind the globally acclaimed Imperial Hotel in Tokyo (established in 1890), the recently opened Imperial Hotel in Osaka, and other smaller hotels, along with a mountain resort in the Japan Alps, is expanding its reach...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-imperial-hotel-in-japan-is-targeting-visitors-from-southeast-asia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo reveals worldwide fascination with mobile commerce</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 18:01:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance advertising, has released its Q1 2014 Mobile Flash report, highlighting new consumer e-commerce trends. The report examines the browsing and shopping habits of over 920 million global internet users reached by Criteo&amp;rsquo;s ads, emphasizing the growing importance of mobile devices in consumer engagement.
[Image]
Source: Criteo Mobile Flash Report.
The report reveals that mobile devices are increasingly crucial for reaching consumers:
Mobile platforms achieve greater click-through rates (CTRs) compared to PCs across most industry sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-reveals-worldwide-fascination-with-mobile-commerce/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Criteo provides three suggestions for increasing sales conversions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 23:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</guid><description>Criteo, a company specializing in digital performance display advertising, offers advice based on its collaborations within the travel industry on converting leads into customers. This guidance is relevant across all sectors.
Tip #1: Strategically Time Your User Acquisition
Travel app downloads peak during summer (June-September), providing a window before peak season to engage a larger active user base*. Capitalize on your customers&amp;rsquo; planning and buying cycles by aligning download promotions for optimal new customer acquisition, Criteo recommends...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/criteo-provides-three-suggestions-for-increasing-sales-conversions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless for Point of Sale Authorizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:11:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</guid><description>Credit card processing is essential for modern businesses, so having a fast and reliable authorization terminal is crucial. While dial-up terminals might have been sufficient in the past, their slow speed can frustrate customers and reflect poorly on your business. Upgrading to a broadband connection is a worthwhile investment.
T1 lines have become more affordable, making them a popular choice for businesses. However, they can still be expensive for smaller companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-for-point-of-sale-authorizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>A digital sales training platform that enables users to engage in role-playing exercises</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 19:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</guid><description>Role-playing is crucial for sales training, allowing two people to act out real-life sales scenarios.
While businesses utilize meeting software for training remote sales teams, this technology often lacks features for practicing pitches online.
uniRow&amp;rsquo;s TrainingCloud.com is designed specifically to facilitate online role-playing during sales training. Trainers can conduct, record, and share role-plays for evaluation and learning purposes.
Nimit Kumar, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of uniRow, emphasizes the importance of hands-on practice in sales training...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-digital-sales-training-platform-that-enables-users-to-engage-in-role-playing-exercises/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HubSpot for Startups simplifies the onboarding process for new businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</guid><description>HubSpot, a company that provides marketing and sales technology, has launched a new program called HubSpot for Startups. This program is specifically designed to support startups that are working with accelerators, incubators, and entrepreneurial organizations.
The program aims to help these small businesses gain momentum in their marketing and sales efforts by offering a substantial 90% discount on HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s products. These products include tools for customer relationship management (CRM), sales, and marketing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-for-startups-simplifies-the-onboarding-process-for-new-businesses/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gulf Air expands its direct presence to four cities in Northern Pakistan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 03:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</guid><description>Source: Gulf Air.
Bahrain&amp;rsquo;s national airline, Gulf Air, has established four new sales offices in the northern Pakistani cities of Islamabad, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Gulf Air currently operates 23 weekly flights between Bahrain and several cities in Pakistan, including Islamabad, Karachi, Lahore, Peshawar, and Sialkot. Travelers can book flights to and from Pakistan through various channels, including the airline&amp;rsquo;s website (gulfair.com), their 24/7 Worldwide Contact Centre (+973 1737 3737), any Gulf Air sales office, or authorized travel agents...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gulf-air-expands-its-direct-presence-to-four-cities-in-northern-pakistan/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Jumei expands its online beauty offerings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</guid><description>Source: Jumei website.
Jumei International Holding, a Chinese online retailer specializing in beauty products, has formed several strategic alliances with international brands. The company revealed that Max Factor and OPI Products have joined its Authentic Beauty Product Alliance (ABPA) and that it has established a partnership with American fashion designer Jill Stuart.
Through its website and mobile app, the company provides a variety of products, including branded beauty items, fashionable apparel, and other lifestyle goods...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jumei-expands-its-online-beauty-offerings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>HubSpot uncovers the true desires of buyers when it comes to salespeople</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</guid><description>HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s recent report, Asia Pacific Buyers Have Spoken: Sales Needs to Evolve, reveals what Asia Pacific buyers desire in a sales experience, from initial call topics to the best time for sales interactions.
The report suggests that sales isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily becoming more challenging, but rather traditional sales strategies are losing their effectiveness. The mismatch between current sales tactics and buyer expectations is the root of the problem. HubSpot asserts that conversions will increase if salespeople align their approach with buyer preferences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hubspot-uncovers-the-true-desires-of-buyers-when-it-comes-to-salespeople/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Warrior Forum has introduced a new e-marketplace that leverages the existing reach of its members</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:07:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</guid><description>Warrior Forum, a prominent online community and marketplace for internet marketers, has introduced Warrior Payments. This comprehensive platform aims to revolutionize online sales by combining payments, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution tools.
Matt Barrie, CEO of Freelancer.com, which acquired Warrior Forum in 2014, highlights the platform&amp;rsquo;s value for entrepreneurs and startups looking to launch and sell products or services online.
Warrior Payments streamlines the sales process by integrating payment processing, digital product delivery, analytics, affiliate marketing, and distribution...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-warrior-forum-has-introduced-a-new-e-marketplace-that-leverages-the-existing-reach-of-its-members/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>