<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Border Controls on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/border-controls/</link><description>Recent content in Border Controls on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:45:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/border-controls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The discussion on drones in the UK and its impact on the European Union</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 05:45:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-discussion-on-drones-in-the-uk-and-its-impact-on-the-european-union/</guid><description>By Chris Jones
A new report, Back from the battlefield: domestic drones in the UK, investigates the use of drones by public and private entities in the UK. It focuses on law enforcement and border control agencies, examining the laws, regulations, and public and private funding surrounding drone technology development. The report analyzes the current situation and potential future applications, advocating for public discussion and decision-making before widespread drone use, particularly for surveillance, becomes commonplace.</description></item><item><title>Is the European Border and Coast Guard a completely new entity or just a revamped version of Frontex?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 19:39:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-european-border-and-coast-guard-a-completely-new-entity-or-just-a-revamped-version-of-frontex/</guid><description>Herbert Rosenfeldt, Research Assistant and PhD candidate, University of Passau
Introduction
Celebrating the new European Border and Coast Guard Agency, also known as Frontex, at the Bulgarian external border with Turkey might seem like an odd festivity. However, last Thursday, high-ranking EU and Member State officials gathered at Bulgaria&amp;rsquo;s Kapitan Andreevo Border Checkpoint for this inauguration. This event marked the implementation of the European Border and Coast Guard Regulation, a significant step towards strengthening external border control in the wake of recent migration challenges.</description></item><item><title>Strategy on immigration policy in the EU by the Commission</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strategy-on-immigration-policy-in-the-eu-by-the-commission/</guid><description>This is an unofficial preview of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s communication on the EU migration agenda, scheduled for release on May 13th. Please be aware that the content may change before publication and may be incomplete.
I. Introduction
Migration has been a constant throughout human history, driven by a range of factors such as political oppression, war, poverty, opportunity, and family reunification. Each migrant&amp;rsquo;s story is unique, and their movement has diverse impacts on society, necessitating a variety of responses.</description></item><item><title>UK/EU immigration post-Brexit: Moving beyond blue passports</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 18:19:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/uk-eu-immigration-post-brexit-moving-beyond-blue-passports/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Recent discussions about the UK&amp;rsquo;s post-Brexit return to blue passports have been marked by misinformation. Contrary to some claims, the passport change won&amp;rsquo;t incur additional costs, as the contract was already up for renewal. Additionally, the EU never mandated the burgundy color; it was merely a non-binding suggestion.
While some view the color change as symbolic of Brexit, the true measure of a passport lies in the rights it affords, not its appearance.</description></item><item><title>Comparing and evaluating the immigration policy proposals of candidates for Commission President.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 12:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/comparing-and-evaluating-the-immigration-policy-proposals-of-candidates-for-commission-president/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Much like fans of Fantasy Football, European Union politics enthusiasts can engage in a similar thought experiment: envisioning the potential impact of different candidates for Commission President if they were elected.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to remember that the European Council&amp;rsquo;s willingness to nominate the candidate from the leading political party after the May 25th elections remains uncertain. Additionally, the European Parliament&amp;rsquo;s reaction to a nomination they disagree with is unclear, despite having the power to elect the President.</description></item><item><title>Accountability of Frontex: a challenging journey</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 22:27:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/accountability-of-frontex-a-challenging-journey/</guid><description>Laura Salzano, PhD student in Constitutional Law, Barcelona University
Since its establishment in 2004, Frontex&amp;rsquo;s role and duties have been heavily scrutinized by the EU and human rights advocates. This attention stems from various concerns, including allegations of power abuse, opacity, and lack of cooperation. These concerns have been raised by diverse voices, such as policy experts, legal professionals, academics, activists, and NGOs.
Critiques of Frontex originate from both within and outside the EU.</description></item><item><title>Regaining Control: British Travel to the EU Post-Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:23:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regaining-control-british-travel-to-the-eu-post-brexit/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*linked to research on the upcoming 5th edition of EU Justice and Home Affairs Law
Photo credit: John Fielding, via Wikimedia Commons
It&amp;rsquo;s self-evident that the UK leaving the EU has changed travel and residency rules for British citizens within the EU. This change mirrors the altered regulations for EU citizens traveling to and residing in the UK, a specific demand from the Leave campaign.</description></item><item><title>Doctor U? The CJEU balances the right to a name with passport security.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/doctor-u-the-cjeu-balances-the-right-to-a-name-with-passport-security/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While many individuals possess a flexible understanding of their personal identity, this concept clashes with the perspective of law enforcement agencies. These organizations aim to establish a fixed identity for each person they gather information on to ensure absolute certainty.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently addressed these contrasting viewpoints in a case involving an individual identified as &amp;lsquo;U.&amp;rsquo; This case was among several during that week where plaintiffs were identified solely by letters, a practice the author suggests moving away from in favor of using pseudonyms for clarity and ease of reference.</description></item><item><title>Will the new EU regulations on maritime surveillance be effective in preventing fatalities and push-backs in the Mediterranean?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 18:36:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-the-new-eu-regulations-on-maritime-surveillance-be-effective-in-preventing-fatalities-and-push-backs-in-the-mediterranean/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Introduction
A recently published EU Regulation establishes new guidelines for maritime surveillance and rescue missions coordinated by Frontex, the EU&amp;rsquo;s border agency. This piece examines the potential impact of these rules on migrant deaths in the Mediterranean and the handling of asylum claims from those rescued at sea.
These new regulations are a direct response to ongoing criticisms that the EU shares responsibility for the migrant deaths in the Mediterranean.</description></item><item><title>Balancing EU free movement regulations with UK border controls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:38:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/balancing-eu-free-movement-regulations-with-uk-border-controls/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s recent opinion in the McCarthy case brings up significant issues concerning the reach of EU free movement laws and how they interact with EU and national regulations on border control and visas. The case involves Mr. McCarthy, a dual UK and Irish citizen residing in Spain with his Colombian wife (a third-country national) and their child (also a dual UK and Irish citizen).
The family currently needs to secure a &amp;lsquo;family visa&amp;rsquo; for Mr.</description></item><item><title>Responsibility in Joint Returns after WS and Others v Frontex: Letting the Active By-Stander Off the Hook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 23:14:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/responsibility-in-joint-returns-after-ws-and-others-v-frontex-letting-the-active-by-stander-off-the-hook/</guid><description>A Missed Opportunity for Accountability: Examining the General Court&amp;rsquo;s Ruling in WS and others v Frontex This analysis delves into the General Court&amp;rsquo;s September 6, 2023, decision in the case of WS and others v Frontex, where a Syrian refugee family&amp;rsquo;s claim for damages against Frontex was dismissed. The family, seeking refuge in the EU during the Syrian war, was returned to Turkey under questionable circumstances involving a joint return operation between Greece and Frontex.</description></item><item><title>European Union Migration Agencies: Frontex, EASO, and Europol's Operations and Collaborations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:58:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-union-migration-agencies-frontex-easo-and-europol-s-operations-and-collaborations/</guid><description>Dr. David Fernández-Rojo, Universidad de Deusto - davidfrojo@deusto.es
The recent surge in migration, often called the “refugee crisis,” highlighted the urgent need to strengthen both the Schengen area and the Common European Asylum System (CEAS). It also underscored the need to support EU member states dealing with large numbers of migrants and to consistently apply EU policies on migration, asylum, and border control. EU agencies such as Frontex, EASO, and Europol have become central to these efforts.</description></item><item><title>Is the EU's new law on travel authorization for non-EU citizens creating a brave new world?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-eu-s-new-law-on-travel-authorization-for-non-eu-citizens-creating-a-brave-new-world/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Introduction
A new European Union (EU) law regarding travel authorization for non-EU citizens visiting the EU was recently announced. This new law will impact millions of travelers annually, potentially including British citizens post-Brexit. This law, though not immediately applicable, holds significant future implications. This explanation aims to clarify its reach and functionality. (Update: the final law was officially published in September 2018).
Basics of the system</description></item><item><title>Summary of a new report: Is Restoring the Borderless Schengen Area an Impossible Mission?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/summary-of-a-new-report-is-restoring-the-borderless-schengen-area-an-impossible-mission/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: BlueMars, via Wikimedia Commons
A new report I wrote for the Swedish Institute of European Policy Studies (SIEPS) analyzes the potential effects of the recently approved changes to the Schengen Borders Code. This blog post summarizes the key findings of the report.
The report addresses concerns regarding the increasing trend of Schengen countries reinstating border checks within the zone for extended periods.</description></item><item><title>A leaked document discloses that the EU is considering suspending the Schengen agreement for a period of two years.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-leaked-document-discloses-that-the-eu-is-considering-suspending-the-schengen-agreement-for-a-period-of-two-years/</guid><description>Commentary by Steve Peers
This is Council document 14300/15, from December 1, 2015, called &amp;ldquo;Integrity of the Schengen area,&amp;rdquo; and sent to Coreper (representatives of EU member states) and the Council - likely the Justice and Home Affairs ministers meeting December 3rd and 4th. (An official version of the document is available here).
The first three sections are relatively standard (see here for discussion), but section 4 proposes initiating a process to formally permit the reinstatement of internal border controls within the Schengen zone for a duration of up to two years.</description></item><item><title>An Unassuming Suggestion: Preventing a Standstill on the Irish Border in the Brexit Negotiations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:59:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-unassuming-suggestion-preventing-a-standstill-on-the-irish-border-in-the-brexit-negotiations/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The Brexit withdrawal agreement negotiations are in danger of collapsing due to disagreements on managing the Irish border. The UK government&amp;rsquo;s lack of concrete proposals for customs away from the border is concerning. Additionally, the UK Foreign Secretary&amp;rsquo;s inability to differentiate between a simple congestion charge and the complexities of border control is disappointing.
In anticipation of the European Commission&amp;rsquo;s upcoming proposals, I have drafted a text (Annex 1) addressing the Irish border in the withdrawal agreement.</description></item><item><title>The EU Migration Strategy: Anticipating a Major Advancement</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 01:28:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-migration-strategy-anticipating-a-major-advancement/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The European Commission recently unveiled its immigration strategy. Pending the release of the final text, this analysis examines an earlier leaked version, highlighting potential discrepancies if the final strategy deviates significantly.
Content
The strategy is structured in three parts: immediate responses to the migrant fatality crisis, an immigration management agenda covering irregular immigration, border control, asylum, and legal migration, and lastly, some long-term goals.
Immediate action
The immediate action section largely expands on the strategy already outlined by EU leaders regarding Mediterranean migrant deaths.</description></item></channel></rss>