<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UTM on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/utm/</link><description>Recent content in UTM on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/utm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Network Monitoring Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:18:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-network-monitoring-services/</guid><description>The increasing reliance on electronic transactions, online services, and cloud technologies has made networks essential for businesses. This dependence requires IT departments to prioritize network monitoring, either through in-house solutions or external providers.
While companies have traditionally monitored their internal networks, extending this practice to telecom connections is crucial. This includes dedicated lines, public internet connections, and VPNs. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to enhance network monitoring processes.
Smaller businesses often face challenges with network monitoring outside of business hours.</description></item><item><title>Secure To The Core Cloud Hosting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 01:50:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/secure-to-the-core-cloud-hosting/</guid><description>An increasing number of companies are discovering the advantages of cloud-based solutions. The cloud offers scalability, vast resources, high performance, reduced maintenance, and cost-effectiveness. However, the question of cloud security persists.
MegaPath, a prominent name in private networking and hosted IT, aims to address these security concerns with its &amp;ldquo;secure to the core&amp;rdquo; approach. But what does this mean, and how can it benefit your business?
While most cloud providers emphasize data center security with certifications like SAS 70 Type II and SSAE 16, alongside physical security measures, these primarily focus on reliability rather than comprehensive security.</description></item></channel></rss>