<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MPLS VPN Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-vpn-networks/</link><description>Recent content in MPLS VPN Networks on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/mpls-vpn-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise SIP Trunking Consolidates Phone Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 19:29:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/</guid><description>When was the last time you examined your telephone network? And I don&amp;rsquo;t mean just looking at your bills for excessive long-distance usage or disconnected lines. I&amp;rsquo;m talking about a thorough review of your phone system&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure and its connections.
If you have multiple locations, you might unknowingly be tangled in a web of connections that drain your budget every month. This is especially common for companies that have expanded through acquisitions, where each site might have a completely different setup, leading to unnecessary expenses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-sip-trunking-consolidates-phone-lines/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>