<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Theft on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/theft/</link><description>Recent content in Theft on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:28:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/theft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Checkpoint Systems in Hong Kong is dedicated to preventing shoplifting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 09:28:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/checkpoint-systems-in-hong-kong-is-dedicated-to-preventing-shoplifting/</guid><description>Checkpoint Systems, a leading provider of retail merchandise availability solutions, has introduced innovative loss prevention and RFID solutions tailored for Hong Kong retailers. These solutions aim to safeguard valuable merchandise from loss and theft across the entire supply chain, from the manufacturer to the store shelf.
Checkpoint&amp;rsquo;s enhanced Merchandise Visibility Solution utilizes cutting-edge labeling and RFID technology, allowing manufacturers to apply RFID tags cost-effectively at the point of manufacture. These tags enable real-time tracking and location identification of individual products throughout the supply chain.</description></item><item><title>Global Crossing Ups Ante On Network Security</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/global-crossing-ups-ante-on-network-security/</guid><description>Organizations often overlook the significant expense of security breaches. Frequent news reports reveal compromised user accounts and credit card information, highlighting the immediate financial burden of these breaches. However, the long-term damage to customer trust and potential loss of business can be even more costly.
Beyond these publicized incidents, espionage and intellectual property theft occur discreetly, posing a severe threat to businesses. Competitors can quickly neutralize a company&amp;rsquo;s advantage by obtaining trade secrets and client data.</description></item><item><title>Undercover Laptop Sleeve Computer Cloaking Device</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 18:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/undercover-laptop-sleeve-computer-cloaking-device/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a legendary product in computer security that&amp;rsquo;s not a fancy gadget but a simple, low-tech solution: a dirty old bag disguised as a laptop sleeve. This &amp;ldquo;Undercover Laptop Sleeve&amp;rdquo; from Lazybone uses clever disguise as its security mechanism.
The sleeve&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness lies in its unappealing appearance. To a potential thief, it looks like an ordinary, grubby mailing envelope, not a valuable laptop&amp;rsquo;s hiding place. This is crucial considering the potential loss of expensive hardware and sensitive data stored on most laptops.</description></item></channel></rss>