<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Protection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection/</link><description>Recent content in Data Protection on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/data-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Google Spain ruling by the CJEU: a lack of equilibrium between privacy and freedom of speech</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 09:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-google-spain-ruling-by-the-cjeu-a-lack-of-equilibrium-between-privacy-and-freedom-of-speech/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive was established in 1995 during the early days of the internet, before the rise of major internet companies. Notably, Google, founded in 1998, emerged just as EU countries were implementing this Directive.
Despite its age and ongoing debates surrounding a proposed revision, this legislation still governs the modern internet. Years of debate about the Directive&amp;rsquo;s application to aspects like social media, search engines, and cookies culminated in the CJEU&amp;rsquo;s GoogleSpain judgment, focusing on search engines.</description></item><item><title>The extent of the 'household exception' to EU data protection law: Is it like Big Brother's Little Brother?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:27:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-extent-of-the-household-exception-to-eu-data-protection-law-is-it-like-big-brother-s-little-brother/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, co-author of &amp;ldquo;EU Law&amp;rdquo; by Steiner and Woods, examines a case about data protection and CCTV use.
Introduction
The Czech Supreme Administrative Court referred a question to the Court of Justice regarding the &amp;ldquo;household activity&amp;rdquo; exception in the EU Data Protection Directive. This case, Ryneš, involved CCTV footage capturing images beyond the operator&amp;rsquo;s property, raising questions about the exception&amp;rsquo;s scope, especially since the Directive states data processing must be &amp;ldquo;exclusively&amp;rdquo; for personal and household purposes.</description></item><item><title>The European Union should consider the UK police's use of live facial recognition technology when developing regulations for law enforcement.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-union-should-consider-the-uk-police-s-use-of-live-facial-recognition-technology-when-developing-regulations-for-law-enforcement/</guid><description>Divergent Approaches to Regulating Live Facial Recognition Dr. Asress Adimi Gikay, a Senior Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law at Brunel University London, explores the contrasting approaches to regulating live facial recognition (LFR) in the UK and the European Union.
Recent suggestions by UK officials to use LFR for searching national passport databases to combat shoplifting have sparked debate, particularly as London, a city with a high concentration of CCTV cameras, grapples with AI safety concerns.</description></item><item><title>A new approach by the Bundesverfassungsgericht regarding constitutional complaints: balancing conflicting rights and applying Union law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 22:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/a-new-approach-by-the-bundesverfassungsgericht-regarding-constitutional-complaints-balancing-conflicting-rights-and-applying-union-law/</guid><description>Lucia Serena Rossi, Judge at the Court of Justice of the European Union*
* Personal opinions expressed in this article are not representative of the Court&amp;rsquo;s views.
** Originally published in Italian as ‘Il “nuovo corso” del Bundesverfassungsgeright nei ricorsi diretti di constituzionalità: bilanciamento fra diritti confliggenti e applicazione del diritto dell’Unione’ on Federalismi.it, February 5, 2020, ISSN 1826-3534.
Table of contents:
Balancing Competing Fundamental Rights in the EU&amp;rsquo;s Multilevel System.</description></item><item><title>Analysis 3: The Impact of Human Rights on the EU/UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement in Brexit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:33:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analysis-3-the-impact-of-human-rights-on-the-eu-uk-trade-and-cooperation-agreement-in-brexit/</guid><description>Human Rights and the EU-UK Trade and Cooperation Agreement Introduction
The UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union (EU) did not affect its participation in the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR). However, the relationship between human rights and EU law has changed for the UK. This blog post will explore the new connections between human rights and the Trade and Cooperation Agreement (TCA) now in effect between the EU and the UK.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of a Hard Brexit? Transforming Britain's £24 billion worth of unicorns.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 15:47:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/benefits-of-a-hard-brexit-transforming-britain-s-24-billion-worth-of-unicorns/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
The pro-Brexit group &amp;ldquo;Change Britain&amp;rdquo; recently released a statement claiming significant financial benefits for the UK following a &amp;ldquo;hard Brexit,&amp;rdquo; where the UK leaves both the EU&amp;rsquo;s single market and customs union. This claim was widely circulated in the media despite being fundamentally flawed.
While the report attempts to offer a thorough analysis, it highlights the poor quality of the overall Brexit debate. The report&amp;rsquo;s claim of a £24 billion benefit originates from three key areas: ending contributions to the EU budget, potential savings from reduced regulation, and the anticipated benefits of new trade agreements.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU makes a ruling on data protection laws and home CCTV: Bringing Data Protection to Your Home</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-makes-a-ruling-on-data-protection-laws-and-home-cctv-bringing-data-protection-to-your-home/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Law, University of Essex
A recent decision by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ryneš v. Úřad pro ochranuosobníchúdajů addressed whether EU data protection law applies to home CCTV cameras. The CJEU agreed with the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s earlier opinion on the matter, though it avoided addressing some of the more complex issues.
This judgment is significant for two reasons. Firstly, its implications extend beyond stationary surveillance systems and could impact how recording devices are used in public areas, even by private citizens.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK data protection authority granting big tech giants a free pass?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-data-protection-authority-granting-big-tech-giants-a-free-pass/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 10:45:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-data-protection-authority-granting-big-tech-giants-a-free-pass/</guid><description>Asress Adimi Gikay (PhD), Senior Lecture in AI, Disruptive Innovation and Law (Brunel University London)
Photo credit: howtostartablogonline.net Online, the phrase &amp;ldquo;we value your privacy&amp;rdquo; often rings hollow. Despite promises, businesses lack the motivation to truly prioritize data privacy. This holds true even within the European Union (EU) and its comprehensive data protection law, the GDPR. Businesses frequently disregard these rules while regulators struggle to enforce them or simply overlook infractions.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU enhances public availability of legal counsel on international agreements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 17:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-enhances-public-availability-of-legal-counsel-on-international-agreements/</guid><description>A Taste of Transparency: The CJEU Rules on Access to Legal Advice in Treaty Negotiations Introduction
Data protection remains a point of contention between the EU and the USA. Disagreements existed even before Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about US surveillance practices, particularly regarding access to passenger data and financial transactions. These disputes were ultimately settled through treaties regulating US access for programs like the Terrorist Finance Tracking Program (TFTP). Notably, the European Parliament initially rejected the first TFTP agreement, only approving a revised version after amendments.</description></item><item><title>Workplace Privacy: The Strasbourg Grand Chamber Provides Clarity on Legal Standards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/workplace-privacy-the-strasbourg-grand-chamber-provides-clarity-on-legal-standards/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The Bărbulescu case examined the permissible extent of employer monitoring of employee communications, including internet usage, particularly when private conversations might be mixed with work-related ones. An employee, dismissed for violating a company policy prohibiting personal use of work equipment, sued his employer in Romania. He lost and appealed under Article 8 of the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), which protects privacy rights, arguing that his employer&amp;rsquo;s monitoring of his communications violated the precedent set by Copland v UK.</description></item><item><title>At the oral hearing on the PNR directive at the Court of Justice of the European Union, the focus was on flights, rock concerts, and finding a needle in a haystack.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/at-the-oral-hearing-on-the-pnr-directive-at-the-court-of-justice-of-the-european-union-the-focus-was-on-flights-rock-concerts-and-finding-a-needle-in-a-haystack/</guid><description>Christian Thönnes, Research Associate at the Max Planck Institute for the Study of Crime, Security and Law in Freiburg, Department of Public Law.
July 13, 2021, marked a crucial moment for the future of privacy and security in the European Union. On this day, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) held a hearing regarding its preliminary ruling procedure C-817/19. This procedure was initiated after the Constitutional Court of Belgium submitted ten questions to the CJEU, prompted by a legal challenge from the Belgian NGO Ligue des Droits Humains.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU missed an opportunity to address mass hacking and fundamental rights.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 03:01:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-missed-an-opportunity-to-address-mass-hacking-and-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Hugo Partouche, a Paris Bar Attorney-at-law (avocat), and Chloé Berthélémy, a Senior Policy Advisor at EDRi, collaborated on this piece.
Photo credit: hacker-silhoutte, via Wikimedia commons
*This article initially appeared in French in Actualité Juridique (AJ) Pénal, Dalloz Revues. You can find it here.
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) issued its decision on the ‘EncroChat’ case on April 30, 2024.
This case arose from large-scale European police operations targeting organized crime.</description></item><item><title>Is the UK's new data retention bill in violation of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2024 19:20:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-uk-s-new-data-retention-bill-in-violation-of-the-eu-charter-of-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Despite the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidating the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive in April, the UK government is pushing for continued data retention authority. This piece examines whether the proposed law aligns with EU law and if it violates the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights.
The connection to EU law lies in Article 15(1) of the EU&amp;rsquo;s e-privacy Directive. This article allows Member States to restrict certain rights concerning communication confidentiality for safeguarding national security and other serious matters.</description></item><item><title>Do national data retention laws fall under the jurisdiction of the Charter?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-national-data-retention-laws-fall-under-the-jurisdiction-of-the-charter/</guid><description>By Steve Peers
After the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) invalidated the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive, a crucial question emerged: do those same rules affect national data retention laws? This post will explain why that&amp;rsquo;s the case.
We begin with Article 51 of the EU&amp;rsquo;s Charter of Fundamental Rights. It states that the Charter applies to EU institutions and bodies, but to Member States &amp;lsquo;only&amp;rsquo; when &amp;lsquo;implementing&amp;rsquo; EU law.</description></item><item><title>The Data Retention Directive's content and implementation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 07:48:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-data-retention-directive-s-content-and-implementation/</guid><description>EU Data Retention Directive: A Closer Look By Chris Jones, Statewatch researcher
This article, the second in a series examining the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, dives into the Directive&amp;rsquo;s details and its implementation across EU member states. It builds upon the background information presented in the first post and precedes a final post focusing on legal challenges.
Dissecting the Directive
Article 1 outlines the Directive&amp;rsquo;s goal: harmonizing data retention laws across member states to aid investigations of serious crime, with each country defining &amp;ldquo;serious crime&amp;rdquo; individually.</description></item><item><title>Is Europol's Joint and Several Liability Regime Transforming Responsibility for EU Fundamental Rights?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 03:32:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europol-s-joint-and-several-liability-regime-transforming-responsibility-for-eu-fundamental-rights/</guid><description>Dr Joyce de Coninck, University of Ghent
Photo credit: Oseveno Introduction The Europol Regulation introduces a shared responsibility framework for the EU concerning unlawful data processing that violates Articles 7 and 8 of the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This developing system of liability is at the center of the Marián Kočner v Europol case, highlighting the need for clarity regarding joint responsibility for human rights violations when EU agencies and Member States collaborate.</description></item><item><title>Has workplace privacy become obsolete? Thoughts on the Barbulescu ruling</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/has-workplace-privacy-become-obsolete-thoughts-on-the-barbulescu-ruling/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The question of when employers can access employee emails, texts, or internet usage is crucial for both parties involved. A recent judgment in the case of Barbulescu v Romania tackled this issue, but unfortunately, misleading headlines like &amp;ldquo;EU court allows employers to read all employee e-mails&amp;rdquo; have emerged. This is inaccurate for two reasons: the ruling originates from the European Court of Human Rights, not an EU court, and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t grant employers unrestricted access to employee emails.</description></item><item><title>How many EU treaties infringe upon the rights to privacy and data protection due to the Domino Effect?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 11:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-many-eu-treaties-infringe-upon-the-rights-to-privacy-and-data-protection-due-to-the-domino-effect/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) recently made significant rulings on data privacy. In the Digital Rights case, the court struck down the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention directive, deeming it mass surveillance lacking adequate safeguards. They also ruled against Google in the &amp;ldquo;right to be forgotten&amp;rdquo; case. These decisions have prompted questions about their broader implications. For instance, an Irish court has referred the &amp;ldquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rdquo; case to the CJEU, questioning the compatibility of the EU-US &amp;ldquo;Safe Harbour&amp;rdquo; data protection arrangement in light of the Snowden revelations.</description></item><item><title>The Tele 2 and Watson case: Human Rights and National Data Retention Law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-tele-2-and-watson-case-human-rights-and-national-data-retention-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The Advocate General recently issued an opinion on two cases referred by national courts. These cases stem from the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) decision in Digital Rights Ireland, which invalidated the Data Retention Directive. Both cases examine whether the mass retention of communications data aligns with EU law, raising a critical question: can such broad data retention ever truly comply with human rights?</description></item><item><title>Schrems II and the Transfer of Personal Data: You Were Only Meant to Blow the Bloody Doors Off!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/schrems-ii-and-the-transfer-of-personal-data-you-were-only-meant-to-blow-the-bloody-doors-off/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
The European Court of Justice (ECJ) recently issued its highly anticipated decision regarding the legitimacy of standard contractual clauses (SCCs) for transferring personal data outside the European Union. This decision is part of a larger effort to challenge the “surveillance capitalism” model employed by many online businesses. While this case significantly impacts SCCs and Facebook&amp;rsquo;s operations, it also reveals the ECJ&amp;rsquo;s stance against mass surveillance, a recurring theme in European jurisprudence.</description></item><item><title>The ECJ ruling in Joined Cases C-203/15 and C-698/15 Tele2 and Watson (Grand Chamber) on data retention and national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecj-ruling-in-joined-cases-c-203-15-and-c-698-15-tele2-and-watson-grand-chamber-on-data-retention-and-national-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent court decision examined the legality of national data retention laws from a human rights standpoint. These laws remained in effect even after the Data Retention Directive was struck down in the Digital Rights Ireland case due to its disproportionate impact on Articles 7 and 8 of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights (EUCFR). This judgment clarifies the interpretation of Articles 7 and 8 within EU law, particularly in the context of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Directive, and may impact the UK&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the EU post-Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Live. Die. Repeat. Is the 'Privacy Shield' deal stuck in a never-ending cycle of repeating the same mistakes like in the movie 'Groundhog Day'?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/live-die-repeat-is-the-privacy-shield-deal-stuck-in-a-never-ending-cycle-of-repeating-the-same-mistakes-like-in-the-movie-groundhog-day/</guid><description>Steve Peers
While the USA is globally recognized, some of its customs remain perplexing. Take &amp;ldquo;Groundhog Day,&amp;rdquo; where the presence or absence of a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s shadow on February 2nd supposedly predicts six more weeks of winter. Beyond the USA, it&amp;rsquo;s more famous as a film where Bill Murray relives the same day, striving for perfection and Andie MacDowell&amp;rsquo;s affections. This concept has inspired others: Tom Cruise battling aliens and wooing Emily Blunt in Edge of Tomorrow, and Peter Capaldi&amp;rsquo;s efforts to breach a diamond wall and resurrect Jenna Coleman in Doctor Who&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Hell Bent.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU provides clarification on police powers in relation to mobile phone theft and EU eprivacy law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:08:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-provides-clarification-on-police-powers-in-relation-to-mobile-phone-theft-and-eu-eprivacy-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
A recent judgment from the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) in the case of Ministerio Fiscal contributes to the understanding of the ePrivacy Directive, specifically Article 15, which allows Member States to make exceptions to the confidentiality of communications for certain purposes. This article played a role in the legal framework surrounding the mass retention of communications data from the Digital Rights Ireland case, where the CJEU established that data retention is justified only in cases of &amp;ldquo;serious crime,&amp;rdquo; as per the Tele2/Watson case.</description></item><item><title>Is the new e-Privacy Regulation a threat to human rights? Exploring the implications of Tele2 and Watson.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 09:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-new-e-privacy-regulation-a-threat-to-human-rights-exploring-the-implications-of-tele2-and-watson/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
Introduction
This post follows up on a previous one from last Christmas, which discussed data retention in the context of the proposed Regulation on Privacy and Electronic Communications (e-Privacy Regs). The European Commission released the official version of the e-Privacy Regs on January 10, 2017. Like the leaked version, the official proposal does not have specific provisions for data retention (para 1.3). The proposal allows Member States to maintain or create their own data retention laws.</description></item><item><title>Challenging mass surveillance in the EU's Court of Justice: The Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 05:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/challenging-mass-surveillance-in-the-eu-s-court-of-justice-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This post discusses the EU&amp;rsquo;s data retention Directive and the Advocate-General&amp;rsquo;s opinion on its validity, particularly in light of the &amp;ldquo;Day We Fight Back&amp;rdquo; against mass surveillance.
Overall context
These cases, brought before the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) by Irish and Austrian courts, present a significant opportunity for the court to issue a landmark judgment on the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, unlike the 2011 Test-Achats judgment, which lacked a thorough examination of key issues.</description></item><item><title>Opinions of the Attorney General on recent CJEU cases regarding national data retention laws</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/opinions-of-the-attorney-general-on-recent-cjeu-cases-regarding-national-data-retention-laws/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
Advocate General Campos Sanchez-Bordana has presented his opinions on three cases concerning data retention: SpaceNet and Telekom Deutschland, GD v Commissioner of the Garda Síochána, and VD and SR. These opinions are the latest development in a series of legal challenges related to data retention that began with an Irish challenge to the Data Retention Directive.
The Data Retention Directive, which allowed for the retention of communications data under certain exceptions to privacy principles, was invalidated in the Digital Rights Ireland case.</description></item><item><title>The EU Data Retention Directive provides the context for the background.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-eu-data-retention-directive-provides-the-context-for-the-background/</guid><description>By Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
As the Snowden leaks continue to make waves, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) is set to rule on a case (Digital Rights Ireland, Seitlinger and Others) that could potentially invalidate the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive in its present form. This directive mandates that private companies retain large amounts of their users&amp;rsquo; telecommunications data, just in case law enforcement needs it for criminal or terrorism investigations.</description></item><item><title>Brexit's Impact on UK's Participation in EU Policing and Criminal Law: EU Referendum Brief 5</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:12:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brexit-s-impact-on-uk-s-participation-in-eu-policing-and-criminal-law-eu-referendum-brief-5/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers
This piece examines the relationship between EU membership and UK policing and criminal law, exploring potential impacts of Brexit.
Summary
The UK held veto power over EU laws in this domain before the Treaty of Lisbon (enacted December 1, 2009). Subsequently, the UK secured two opt-out mechanisms: the ability to opt into (or out of) any new EU law in this area post-Treaty, and the option to retroactively opt out of pre-existing EU laws.</description></item><item><title>Returning to the past: Revisiting fundamental data protection principles in the proposed Data Protection Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:27:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/returning-to-the-past-revisiting-fundamental-data-protection-principles-in-the-proposed-data-protection-regulation/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The year 2015 is not living up to the futuristic vision presented in the Back to the Future films, particularly with the absence of hoverboards (drones are a disappointing alternative). Instead of establishing a data protection framework suitable for 2015, the Council seems poised to agree on maintaining the core legal principles from 1995 – which are outdated in the context of technology law.
Background
Negotiations regarding the EU&amp;rsquo;s proposed General Data Protection Regulation appear to be nearing their final stages within the Council.</description></item><item><title>An open letter regarding the UK's Data Retention and Investigatory Powers Bill</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:42:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/an-open-letter-regarding-the-uk-s-data-retention-and-investigatory-powers-bill/</guid><description>Tuesday 15th July 2014
To all Members of Parliament,
Re: An open letter from UK internet law academic experts
The Coalition Government, with support from the Opposition, introduced the Data Retention and Investigatory Powers Bill (&amp;ldquo;DRIP&amp;rdquo;) on July 10th. The bill was presented as a simple extension of existing data retention powers under the EU Data Retention Directive. This Directive was recently found incompatible with European human rights law by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU).</description></item><item><title>Backup and Recovery For All Businesses</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 18:39:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/backup-and-recovery-for-all-businesses/</guid><description>Businesses are exposed to various risks, not just economic fluctuations or environmental factors. Your data, whether on your computer or in your data center, might be your biggest vulnerability. Without backup and recovery solutions, you&amp;rsquo;re one mishap away from major problems.
Your data is the most valuable asset at risk. While paper records were once the norm, with fire as a primary threat, today&amp;rsquo;s electronic records face risks like corruption and deletion.</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Commission's Proposal to Enhance Europol's Authority: A Review of the Amendment to Regulation (EU) 2016/784 (Europol Regulation)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/assessing-the-commission-s-proposal-to-enhance-europol-s-authority-a-review-of-the-amendment-to-regulation-eu-2016-784-europol-regulation/</guid><description>Niovi Vavoula and Valsamis Mitsilegas, Queen Mary University
Introduction The European Union Agency for Law Enforcement Cooperation (Europol) plays a crucial role in supporting EU Member States&amp;rsquo; cross-border police cooperation, as defined by Regulation (EU) 2016/794 (Europol Regulation). Referred to as the EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;criminal information hub,&amp;rsquo; Europol facilitates information exchange between Member States, Europol itself, other EU bodies, international organizations, and third countries. It also generates criminal intelligence using information from various sources, including Member States and partners.</description></item><item><title>Whistleblower Protection: The Latest EU Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:04:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/whistleblower-protection-the-latest-eu-directive/</guid><description>Vigjilenca Abazi, Assistant Professor of EU Law, Maastricht University &amp;amp; Fellow, Yale Law School
*The author co-authored the model Directive presented at the European Parliament in May 2016.
On April 16th, the European Parliament overwhelmingly voted to approve a new law protecting whistleblowers within the European Union. This Directive establishes high standards and exemplifies how collaborative efforts between civil society organizations, NGOs, trade unions, journalists, academics, whistleblowers, and the European Parliament can produce progressive legislation that strengthens the safeguards for upholding the rule of law in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Is Europe v Facebook the start of the end for NSA surveillance of EU citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:58:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-europe-v-facebook-the-start-of-the-end-for-nsa-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>The &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; Case: Challenging US Data Surveillance in Europe Since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations about the NSA&amp;rsquo;s extensive spying activities, concerns have grown about the effectiveness of US data protection, particularly for EU citizens who benefit from stronger protections under the Data Protection Directive. One concern is the NSA&amp;rsquo;s ability to access communications processed by US-based social media companies like Facebook.
The Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s recent decision to refer questions in the &amp;lsquo;Europe v Facebook&amp;rsquo; case to the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) could potentially lead to the end of NSA access to EU citizens&amp;rsquo; data.</description></item><item><title>Is it an early Christmas gift or a disappointment? Examining data retention and the leaked ePrivacy Regulation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 09:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-an-early-christmas-gift-or-a-disappointment-examining-data-retention-and-the-leaked-eprivacy-regulation/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
The leak of a draft ePrivacy Regulation on December 12, 2016, has sparked discussions about its implications for data retention. This post will examine this aspect of the draft regulation.
The Article 29 Data Protection Working Party (A29DPWP) had previously advised against introducing new European data retention requirements. This recommendation, reflecting concerns about the existing ePrivacy Directive&amp;rsquo;s allowance for national data retention regimes, is echoed in the leaked draft Regulation.</description></item><item><title>Is the Commission's draft EU-US Privacy Shield adequacy decision a new shield for transatlantic privacy or just more of the same?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:39:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-commission-s-draft-eu-us-privacy-shield-adequacy-decision-a-new-shield-for-transatlantic-privacy-or-just-more-of-the-same/</guid><description>Dr. Maria Tzanou (Lecturer in Law, Keele University)
In October 2015, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) ruled in the Schrems case that the US Safe Harbor framework did not adequately protect personal data transfers from the EU. The court found that US mass electronic surveillance practices violated fundamental EU privacy rights.
To address this, the European Commission and the US agreed on a new framework called the EU-US Privacy Shield.</description></item><item><title>Regardless of the CJEU's decision, data retention could potentially continue to exist under national law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/regardless-of-the-cjeu-s-decision-data-retention-could-potentially-continue-to-exist-under-national-law/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University
A central question regarding internet privacy is whether governments should be allowed to store data about everyone&amp;rsquo;s online and phone activities in the name of fighting terrorism and serious crime. This issue, known as &amp;ldquo;data retention,&amp;rdquo; raises crucial questions about balancing privacy and security, both nationally and within the European Union. Initially, the EU&amp;rsquo;s electronic privacy (e-Privacy) Directive offered member states the choice to implement data retention rules, deviating from the usual rule of communication confidentiality outlined in the directive.</description></item><item><title>Data Retention is still a permanent fixture, at least for the time being.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 04:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/data-retention-is-still-a-permanent-fixture-at-least-for-the-time-being/</guid><description>Matthew White, Ph.D candidate, Sheffield Hallam University.
Introduction
On January 30, 2018, the human rights organization Liberty announced on Twitter that the Court of Appeal found the UK government to be acting illegally. The government was gathering internet and phone records from the entire country and allowing public bodies to access them without any suspicion of serious crime or independent approval.
This referred to the Court of Appeal&amp;rsquo;s (CoA) decision in the case of Tom Watson and Others v Secretary of State for the Home Department concerning access to communication data under the Data Retention and Investigatory Power Act 2014 (DRIPA 2014).</description></item><item><title>The CJEU ruling on data retention: Mass surveillance is prohibited.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-ruling-on-data-retention-mass-surveillance-is-prohibited/</guid><description>Steve Peers
On July 7, 2005, a relative of mine was on her way to work on a London tube train when terrorists detonated bombs on her train and three others across the city. While my relative was unharmed, dozens of people tragically lost their lives.
This event, along with the prior attacks on 9/11 and in Madrid, understandably fueled public anxiety around terrorism and spurred the EU to introduce additional anti-terrorism measures.</description></item><item><title>National legal challenges to the Data Retention Directive</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 09:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/national-legal-challenges-to-the-data-retention-directive/</guid><description>Chris Jones, Researcher for Statewatch
This article delves into the numerous legal obstacles faced by the EU&amp;rsquo;s Data Retention Directive, both at national and EU levels. This is the third installment in a series examining this controversial legislation, which has recently been overturned by the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU). The information presented is a result of research conducted by Statewatch as part of the SECILE project, which focuses on the impact, legitimacy, and effectiveness of counter-terrorism measures in securing Europe.</description></item><item><title>The European Court of Human Rights highlights the significance of encryption in the case of Podchasov v. Russia.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 20:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-human-rights-highlights-the-significance-of-encryption-in-the-case-of-podchasov-v-russia/</guid><description>Mattis van ’t Schip &amp;amp; Frederik Zuiderveen Borgesius*
*Both authors work at the iHub and the Institute for Computing and Information Sciences, Radboud University, The Netherlands - mattis.vantschip[at]ru.nl &amp;amp; frederikzb[at]cs.ru.nl
Photo credit: Gzen92, on wikimedia commons A February 2024 ruling by the European Court of Human Rights in the case of Podchasov v. Russia highlighted the crucial role of encryption in safeguarding privacy rights. This judgment comes at a time when encryption is at the heart of many global legal discussions.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU's confusion on biometric data and data protection law</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 14:02:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-s-confusion-on-biometric-data-and-data-protection-law/</guid><description>Growing concerns about the protection of biometric data have led the EU to propose a data protection regulation classifying such data as sensitive, thus providing it with a higher level of protection. However, until this proposal is enacted, existing EU regulations address this issue, although not always effectively, as demonstrated by the recent CJEU ruling in the Willems case, which falls short in its application of existing regulations to biometric data.</description></item><item><title>Recent rulings from the European Court of Justice (ECJ) and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) have addressed issues related to privacy and data protection in universities.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/recent-rulings-from-the-european-court-of-justice-ecj-and-the-european-court-of-human-rights-ecthr-have-addressed-issues-related-to-privacy-and-data-protection-in-universities/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
Privacy and data protection are distinct legal concepts originating from different legal frameworks and adjudicated by separate European courts. However, these concepts often intersect, and the relevant courts, namely the European Court of Justice (ECJ) interpreting EU data protection laws and the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) interpreting the right to privacy within the European Convention on Human Rights (ECHR), sometimes reference each other&amp;rsquo;s legal precedents and texts.</description></item><item><title>Protecting data and smart meters: GDPR and the EU clean energy law's 'winter package'</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:29:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/protecting-data-and-smart-meters-gdpr-and-the-eu-clean-energy-law-s-winter-package/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giulia Pizza, FratiniVergano, European Lawyers - a Brussels-based law firm specialising in European and international law
Introduction
In late 2016, the European Commission introduced the “Clean Energy for All Europeans” legislative package to modernize Europe&amp;rsquo;s electricity market and encourage cleaner energy solutions. This push for &amp;ldquo;decentralization&amp;rdquo; is seen as a way to drive innovation and shift the focus to a demand-driven energy policy. The goal is to give consumers the tools they need to actively participate in this change.</description></item><item><title>The ECtHR Grand Chamber makes a ruling on mass surveillance in the case of Big Brother Watch v UK.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 12:02:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ecthr-grand-chamber-makes-a-ruling-on-mass-surveillance-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-v-uk/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, an expert in internet law from the University of Essex, provides an in-depth analysis of a significant ruling by the Grand Chamber of the European Court of Human Rights (ECtHR) concerning the United Kingdom&amp;rsquo;s surveillance regime, specifically its Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA).
This ruling is the culmination of a series of legal challenges against the UK&amp;rsquo;s surveillance practices, brought to light by revelations of extensive government surveillance programs.</description></item><item><title>Analyzing the negotiation positions for the future UK/EU relationship in Justice and Home Affairs.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 09:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/analyzing-the-negotiation-positions-for-the-future-uk-eu-relationship-in-justice-and-home-affairs/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex
The EU and the UK have established their negotiating positions for their future relationship, including the UK&amp;rsquo;s exit from EU regulations (as discussed here). The UK&amp;rsquo;s position can be found here. Many commentators have analyzed the economic implications of the future relationship. This post focuses on justice and home affairs, including immigration, asylum, civil cooperation, and judicial and police cooperation.
This analysis will objectively critique both sides&amp;rsquo; positions.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU interprets the e-commerce Directive regarding Facebook's responsibility for defamatory posts.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 08:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-interprets-the-e-commerce-directive-regarding-facebook-s-responsibility-for-defamatory-posts/</guid><description>Over the past few weeks, several legal decisions have addressed how individuals can control their information online. Two cases, GC et al and Google v CNIL, focused on how search engines should interpret their obligations under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). This post will focus on a third case, Glawischnig-Piesczek v Facebook, which examined how the e-Commerce Directive&amp;rsquo;s prohibition on general monitoring applies to &amp;ldquo;stay down&amp;rdquo; notices. The case raises a broader question about the consistency of different internet regulations, including those related to intellectual property, child exploitation, and terrorism.</description></item><item><title>The draft adequacy decisions: Data Protection in the UK and the EU</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 03:10:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-draft-adequacy-decisions-data-protection-in-the-uk-and-the-eu/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Background
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Law Enforcement Directive (LED) have strict rules about transferring personal data outside the EU. Adequacy decisions are the simplest way to ensure these transfers are safe. Currently, twelve countries have received full or partial adequacy decisions, including Japan, which has additional safeguards in place. The US previously held an adequacy status, but the Court of Justice overturned this in the Schrems II case.</description></item><item><title>Examining the ECtHR ruling in the case of Big Brother Watch: part 1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/examining-the-ecthr-ruling-in-the-case-of-big-brother-watch-part-1/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
A recent court decision tackles the increasingly relevant issue of secret surveillance, a topic that has gained more attention since Edward Snowden&amp;rsquo;s revelations. This extensive ruling examines three cases against the UK&amp;rsquo;s Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 (RIPA), now largely revoked. These cases, brought by Big Brother Watch, the Bureau of Investigative Journalism and Alice Ross, and 10 Human Rights Organisations, challenged RIPA&amp;rsquo;s provisions on bulk interception of communications, acquisition of communications data, and data sharing between the UK and the US.</description></item><item><title>The CJEU affirms that data protection authorities are independent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-cjeu-affirms-that-data-protection-authorities-are-independent/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent judgment on data protection, while not as impactful as a prior ruling, is still significant. In Commission v Hungary, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) expanded on earlier decisions in Commission v Germany and Commission v Austria concerning the independent operation of data protection authorities. The judgment&amp;rsquo;s implications, however, reach beyond this specific area.
Background
The EU&amp;rsquo;s data protection Directive mandates that data protection authorities be established to uphold the Directive&amp;rsquo;s regulations, in addition to individual legal action.</description></item><item><title>Consent and Cookies in EU Data Privacy Law— One Click is Enough</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consent-and-cookies-in-eu-data-privacy-law-one-click-is-enough/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:37:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consent-and-cookies-in-eu-data-privacy-law-one-click-is-enough/</guid><description>Dr Asress Adimi Gikay (PhD, SJD, LLM), Lecturer in AI, Disruptive Innovation, Law Brunel Law School (Brunel University London); Twitter: @DrAsressGikay
Consent and Data Protection in the European Union
The foundation of data protection law in the European Union lies in the concept of data privacy as a basic human right, a principle reinforced by the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Consequently, handling personal data requires strict adherence to legal standards.</description></item><item><title>Is the Passenger Name Record Directive legally valid? Thoughts on the upcoming CJEU case.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-passenger-name-record-directive-legally-valid-thoughts-on-the-upcoming-cjeu-case/</guid><description>Douwe Korff, a legal expert in human rights and data protection, believes the EU Court of Justice should examine whether the PNR Directive aligns with the Charter of Fundamental Rights. This follows a similar inquiry by Belgium&amp;rsquo;s Constitutional Court.
Korff suggests that any large-scale surveillance, such as that under the PNR Directive, needs to meet two criteria. First, there should be strong proof from the European Commission and EU member states that these measures genuinely help combat crimes related to PNR.</description></item><item><title>The case of Elgizouli v Secretary of State for the Home Department [2020] UKSC 10 involves issues related to data protection, the death penalty, and mutual legal assistance in criminal law.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-elgizouli-v-secretary-of-state-for-the-home-department-2020-uksc-10-involves-issues-related-to-data-protection-the-death-penalty-and-mutual-legal-assistance-in-criminal-law/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 15:07:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-of-elgizouli-v-secretary-of-state-for-the-home-department-2020-uksc-10-involves-issues-related-to-data-protection-the-death-penalty-and-mutual-legal-assistance-in-criminal-law/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Introduction
The Elgizouli case marks the first UK Supreme Court ruling on the Data Protection Act 2018 (DPA). The key takeaway is that simply mostly complying with the Act&amp;rsquo;s requirements isn&amp;rsquo;t enough to legalize data transfers to other countries. This judgment centers around Part Three of the DPA, which puts the Law Enforcement Directive into action and emphasizes procedural safeguards. However, the court&amp;rsquo;s methodology might have broader consequences for how UK courts interpret the DPA and the GDPR, particularly regarding the protection of individual rights outlined in the European Court of Human Rights (ECHR).</description></item><item><title>Rights for data protection and administrative procedures</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rights-for-data-protection-and-administrative-procedures/</guid><description>Steve Peers
A recent Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) decision in the cases of YS and M and S clarified data protection rights for asylum-seekers. This judgment could also have wider implications for accessing documents in administrative procedures.
Two asylum-seekers in the Netherlands wanted to see file notes related to their cases. Instead of relying on the EU’s asylum procedures Directive, which grants access to reasons for negative decisions and interview reports but not all documents, they invoked the data protection Directive.</description></item><item><title>Is the End Near for American Mass Surveillance of EU Citizens?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:57:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-end-near-for-american-mass-surveillance-of-eu-citizens/</guid><description>Steve Peers
This blog post is dedicated to the memory of the great privacy campaigner Caspar Bowden, who recently passed away. It is tragic that he didn&amp;rsquo;t live to witness the developments in this case. To support his work, donations can be made to the Caspar Bowden Legacy Fund here.
A bright university student challenges the inflexible establishment – and achieves a remarkable victory. This was Mark Zuckerberg, creating Facebook in 2002.</description></item><item><title>European Data Protection Authorities should reconsider their approach to Facial Recognition Technology in schools due to power imbalances and issues of consent.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-data-protection-authorities-should-reconsider-their-approach-to-facial-recognition-technology-in-schools-due-to-power-imbalances-and-issues-of-consent/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 01:45:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/european-data-protection-authorities-should-reconsider-their-approach-to-facial-recognition-technology-in-schools-due-to-power-imbalances-and-issues-of-consent/</guid><description>Dr. Asress Adimi Gikay, a lecturer specializing in AI, Disruptive Innovation, and Law at Brunel Law School, Brunel University London, focuses his research on Artificial Intelligence, Law, and Policy. He also teaches courses on Artificial Intelligence and the Law, and Law, Policy and Governance of Artificial Intelligence (https://www.brunel.ac.uk/people/asress-gikay). Twitter: https://twitter.com/DrAsressGikay
Facial Recognition Technology in Schools
In the digital age, large technology companies like Facebook, Google, and Apple exert significant control over our personal information and privacy.</description></item><item><title>Should we opt for the European Digital Identity Wallet? Privacy concerns in the current legislative discussion.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-we-opt-for-the-european-digital-identity-wallet-privacy-concerns-in-the-current-legislative-discussion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 13:48:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/should-we-opt-for-the-european-digital-identity-wallet-privacy-concerns-in-the-current-legislative-discussion/</guid><description>Alessandra Fratini and Giorgia Lo Tauro – FratiniVergano, European Lawyers
Photo credit: Martin Firrell, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
In June 2021, during the review of the eIDAS Regulation, the European Commission put forth a proposal to create a European Digital Identity framework. This framework would include a &amp;ldquo;European Digital Identity Wallet,&amp;rdquo; or EUDI Wallet. Seen as a major element of this proposal, the Wallet aims to address the increasing use of digital services across borders, both public and private.</description></item><item><title>Consumer law and the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR): Case C-319/20 involving Facebook Ireland - Advocate General's opinion</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 05:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consumer-law-and-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr-case-c-319-20-involving-facebook-ireland-advocate-general-s-opinion/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Facts
The Federation of German Consumer Organisations initiated legal proceedings in German courts against Facebook. They claimed that Facebook violated data protection rules by failing to provide sufficient information about data collection practices related to free, third-party games offered on its platform. The Federation argued that this also infringed upon unfair competition and consumer protection regulations. The case reached the Bundesgerischtshof, which raised concerns about the Federation&amp;rsquo;s legal standing to bring the action following the implementation of the GDPR.</description></item><item><title>The Attorney General's opinion in the Schrems II case: Facebook, national security, and laws on data protection.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 05:02:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-attorney-general-s-opinion-in-the-schrems-ii-case-facebook-national-security-and-laws-on-data-protection/</guid><description>Lorna Woods, Professor of Internet Law, University of Essex
Recently, a CJEU Advocate-General presented an opinion on the Schrems II case, which centers on the legality of US national security regulations regarding personal data transfers from the EU, specifically through Facebook. This case follows the impactful Schrems I ruling that invalidated the EU-US data transfer agreement due to insufficient protections against surveillance under US law. While companies shifted to alternative mechanisms, like Standard Contractual Clauses (SCCs), Schrems II (Data Protection Commissioner v.</description></item><item><title>Inquiries for potential Commissioners of Home Affairs and Justice</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 01:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/inquiries-for-potential-commissioners-of-home-affairs-and-justice/</guid><description>Steve Peers, Emilio de Capitani, and Henri Labayle present a series of questions for Members of the European Parliament (MEPs) to pose to the candidates for Commissioners of Immigration and Home Affairs and Justice. These questions aim to understand the candidates&amp;rsquo; plans and secure commitments on crucial matters.
Immigration and Asylum
Given the Commission&amp;rsquo;s stance on framing migration policy with the non-binding Global Approach to Migration and Mobility Partnerships, would the candidate propose a legally binding basis for agreements with relevant nations, based on Articles 77, 78, and 79 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union (TFEU)?</description></item><item><title>The UK is now part of the Schengen Information System, bringing the Panopticon Home.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 09:20:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-uk-is-now-part-of-the-schengen-information-system-bringing-the-panopticon-home/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The idea of a &amp;ldquo;Panopticon,&amp;rdquo; a prison where guards could potentially see any inmate at any point, was conceived over two centuries ago by British philosopher Jeremy Bentham. He believed that the constant threat of observation would motivate prisoners to act appropriately. This concept is now often used to illustrate contemporary patterns in widespread monitoring and societal control.
The European Union&amp;rsquo;s (EU) initial move in this direction was the establishment of the Schengen Information System (SIS) during the 1990s.</description></item></channel></rss>