<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CPE on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cpe/</link><description>Recent content in CPE on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cpe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What Ethernet over Copper Is All About</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is an innovative business bandwidth service that surpasses traditional options like T1 and DS3 lines in terms of cost and performance. Businesses currently using these older services should consider switching to EoC due to its significant advantages.
EoC leverages the Ethernet standard, widely used in local area networks, and extends it for metropolitan and wide area network transmission. Unlike traditional telecom services based on telephone technology, EoC utilizes a protocol directly compatible with computer networks, eliminating the need for complex interface cards and protocol conversions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-ethernet-over-copper-is-all-about/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Ethernet Port Scales WAN Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 18:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</guid><description>Upgrading your business internet bandwidth from copper to fiber or from OC-3 SONET can feel overwhelming. How much bandwidth should you commit to? An Ethernet port strategy provides flexibility and cost-efficiency for your future needs.
Traditional telecom services lack scalability. Upgrading from a T1 to a T3 line or an OC-3 requires completely different interfaces, connectors, and even router changes. Each upgrade often means new hardware and potential service disruptions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-ethernet-port-scales-wan-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Ports In a Data Storm</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:42:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</guid><description>Businesses are finding it increasingly challenging to forecast their WAN network needs, especially during uncertain economic times. The traditional long wait times for telecom upgrades add to this uncertainty. What&amp;rsquo;s needed is a solution that allows businesses to pay only for the bandwidth they currently use while retaining the ability to swiftly increase capacity as needed.
Ethernet service ports offer this flexibility. Service providers install these ports, often as RJ45 jacks or fiber optic connectors, on a managed router at the customer&amp;rsquo;s location...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-ports-in-a-data-storm/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 and EoC When There Is No Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</guid><description>The future of business undoubtedly lies in fiber optic bandwidth, particularly given the surge in video content and the increasing shift towards cloud computing. While copper infrastructure is still prevalent, it is gradually becoming outdated. So, how can businesses adapt during this transitional period?
One practical approach is to maximize the use of existing copper infrastructure while it remains viable. Many assume that relying on copper limits bandwidth, but this is not necessarily true...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-and-eoc-when-there-is-no-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Software Defined Network Comes to Austin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 01:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Software Defined Network (SDN) has arrived, shifting away from the abstract and promising practical improvements for businesses. Here&amp;rsquo;s how SDN can benefit your company.
Why Software?
SDN aims to replace fixed hardware functions with adaptable software. While this may seem like simplification, it involves intricate coding on more generic hardware like microprocessors. The advantage lies in the easy replication and remote modification of software components.
The Idea of Virtualization..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-software-defined-network-comes-to-austin/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing T1 Speed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</guid><description>For decades, T1 lines have been the standard for business network connections, offering ample bandwidth initially. However, like computer advancements, what was sufficient before is now inadequate. While upgrading to fiber is an option, it&amp;rsquo;s not the only solution.
Many companies opt for the traditional upgrade path from T1 (1.5 Mbps) to T3 (45 Mbps) speeds. This offers a significant speed increase at a premium, though T3 costs have decreased...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-t1-speed/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Port Sets Your Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:19:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As MAN and WAN telecom service users, we understand the limitations of our contracted bandwidth. What was once sufficient can become restrictive, impacting application performance and productivity. What can be done to increase bandwidth and eliminate this congestion?
Connection Speed Limits
While you can utilize less than the maximum capacity of a line, exceeding it is not possible. The maximum speed is determined by factors such as the type of transmission medium (e...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-port-sets-your-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>