<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Safe Countries of Origin on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/safe-countries-of-origin/</link><description>Recent content in Safe Countries of Origin on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/safe-countries-of-origin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Is the draft EU/Turkey agreement on migration and refugees legally sound?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 18:19:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-draft-eu-turkey-agreement-on-migration-and-refugees-legally-sound/</guid><description>Steve Peers
Recent legal debates have arisen concerning the proposed EU/Turkey agreement on refugees. While general points were discussed last month, a leaked draft of the final deal necessitates a closer examination before the finalizing summit.
The agreement, framed as an EU-Turkey statement, builds upon the March 7, 2016, statement with added elements. It is crucial to note that as a statement, it won&amp;rsquo;t be legally binding, requiring no formal EU or national approval beyond the summit&amp;rsquo;s endorsement.</description></item><item><title>Evaluating the new proposal on "Safe countries of origin</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evaluating-the-new-proposal-on-safe-countries-of-origin/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission recently introduced several new immigration and asylum initiatives. Three proposals, in particular, suggest binding measures: a temporary relocation measure for asylum-seekers, a permanent relocation system for asylum-seekers, and a regulation establishing a common list of &amp;ldquo;safe countries of origin.&amp;rdquo; This list would include Western Balkan countries and Turkey. This article will focus on the &amp;ldquo;safe country of origin&amp;rdquo; rules.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the UK, Ireland, and Denmark are not subject to these measures.</description></item></channel></rss>