<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Online Sales on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-sales/</link><description>Recent content in Online Sales on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/online-sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hosted Social Commerce Apps For Facebook</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 08:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hosted-social-commerce-apps-for-facebook/</guid><description>E-commerce is no longer a novelty; it&amp;rsquo;s a cornerstone of modern business. The next big shift, social commerce, is already underway. This evolution utilizes social media platforms, primarily Facebook and Twitter, to connect with customers where they are most active. The question for businesses is how to best harness this power.
While older methods like DIY websites, email campaigns, and blogs still exist, they are becoming outdated. The solution lies in hosted solutions, with Facebook as the foundation.</description></item><item><title>Stress Testing For Your Website</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 19:55:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/stress-testing-for-your-website/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;ve successfully launched your website and initiated a marketing campaign. However, what happens when your website crashes during a surge in visitor traffic? This situation is preventable through stress testing. Many companies neglect this step and suffer the consequences, especially during peak seasons like holidays.
Don&amp;rsquo;t let this happen to you. Load testing allows you to assess your website&amp;rsquo;s capacity and make necessary improvements. BrowserMob, a cloud-based service, provides affordable load testing for businesses of all sizes.</description></item><item><title>US and UK Shopping Cart Software</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-and-uk-shopping-cart-software/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 03:42:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/us-and-uk-shopping-cart-software/</guid><description>Are you an online seller or aspiring to be one? Affiliate programs handle order processing and tracking, but if you sell your own products like books, crafts, or components, a shopping cart is essential. Without one, you&amp;rsquo;ll lose sales.
What does a shopping cart offer? It allows customers to browse your products, make selections, and purchase multiple items in a single transaction. Without it, customers are limited to one product per order.</description></item></channel></rss>