<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Net Neutrality on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/net-neutrality/</link><description>Recent content in Net Neutrality on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/net-neutrality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?</description></item><item><title>New EU Regulatory Guidelines for Net Neutrality</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:54:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/new-eu-regulatory-guidelines-for-net-neutrality/</guid><description>Professor Lorna Woods, University of Essex
New EU regulations designed to ensure equal treatment of internet traffic were enacted in the fall of 2015 and implemented in April 2016. These net neutrality rules were intended to prevent discrimination by internet service providers and promote innovation, but their effectiveness was debated.
The regulations stipulate that internet providers should treat all traffic the same, regardless of the source, content, or device. However, the vague language and exceptions within the regulations led to uncertainty regarding the level of protection for users and permitted provider activities.</description></item><item><title>Unlimited Internet's Days are Numbered</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/unlimited-internets-days-are-numbered/</guid><description>Remember the golden age of air travel? You could stroll into an airport right before your flight, effortlessly purchase a ticket, and enjoy luxurious treatment onboard. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a different story. We endure long lines and cramped seats, a far cry from the preferential treatment of the past. Sadly, this shift from luxury to cattle car is coming soon to the internet.
You might be skeptical. After all, the internet has felt limitless for over a decade.</description></item></channel></rss>