<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Analog Television on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analog-television/</link><description>Recent content in Analog Television on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/analog-television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Dark Side of Spectrum Renewal</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dark-side-of-spectrum-renewal/</guid><description>Half a century ago, the government embraced urban renewal, demolishing and rebuilding deteriorated urban areas for housing projects or highways leading to suburbs. Similarly, today, we&amp;rsquo;re witnessing &amp;ldquo;spectrum renewal,&amp;rdquo; where sections of the radio frequency spectrum are deemed too valuable for older technologies like analog TV and cell phone service, despite their widespread use.
This isn&amp;rsquo;t driven by lack of public demand. Millions of analog TV sets and cell phones are still functional.</description></item><item><title>Time to Move to HD Video Cameras</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:23:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/time-to-move-to-hd-video-cameras/</guid><description>The familiar sound of &amp;ldquo;Taps&amp;rdquo; softly playing from your TV symbolizes the end of an era: analog television. From its start with Herbert Hoover to its abrupt conclusion, marked by TV stations switching off their analog transmitters, this technology has reached its end. The outdated 4:3 video format should disappear alongside it, but strangely, it&amp;rsquo;s still present.
Observe TV broadcasts throughout the day, and you&amp;rsquo;ll find many programs, including network shows and local news, still framed by black bars on the sides.</description></item><item><title>700 MHz Groundhogs Look For DTV Shadow</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/700-mhz-groundhogs-look-for-dtv-shadow/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 14:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/700-mhz-groundhogs-look-for-dtv-shadow/</guid><description>Every year, like clockwork, attention turns to predicting the future, and this year is no different. While many await a groundhog&amp;rsquo;s weather forecast, the telecom industry is focused on a different kind of prediction: the upcoming decision on user rights within the 700 MHz UHF TV band. This decision has significant implications for the future of television broadcasting. One outcome ushers in the era of digital television (DTV), while the other prolongs the use of analog television (ATV) for another 16 weeks.</description></item></channel></rss>