<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>1889JPBG4002 on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1889jpbg4002/</link><description>Recent content in 1889JPBG4002 on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/1889jpbg4002/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Complete Functional Restoration and Installation of Commander Remote Control System</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-complete-functional-restoration-and-installation-of-commander-remote-control-system/</guid><description>This article details the restoration process of a Beogram 4002 (5523) turntable, aiming for like-new performance.
The restoration began with addressing the DC platter motor, a common area of concern in these models. The motor was carefully removed and disassembled, and its bearings, often found dry, underwent a revitalization process. This involved immersing them in motor oil and applying a vacuum to draw out air and facilitate oil penetration.
Simultaneously, the carriage and arm-lowering mechanisms were cleaned and re-lubricated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): Repair of an Intermittent Sensor Arm Light Source</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 22:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-repair-of-an-intermittent-sensor-arm-light-source/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 turntable, which I had previously restored in May 2022, recently came back to my workshop due to a malfunctioning sensor arm LED. This was concerning because I had implemented a redesigned LED assembly for this particular unit.
To my relief, the LED functioned correctly when I powered up the turntable in my workshop. This suggested an intermittent problem that resolved itself during transport.
I tried manipulating the plugs and cables, but the LED remained illuminated.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002 (5523): A New Arrival from Colorado - First Impressions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 08:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-5523-a-new-arrival-from-colorado-first-impressions/</guid><description>A Beogram 4002 (Type 5523) turntable arrived from Colorado for restoration, carefully packaged in a specialized box. The outer cover had several scratches but could potentially be polished to an acceptable condition. The hinges seemed fine, and the aluminum underneath the cover appeared to be in good shape. The control keypad showed only minor signs of wear.
The corners of the turntable&amp;rsquo;s base were almost pristine. However, upon inspection, the metal frames attached to the plinth were loosening, a common issue caused by deteriorating glue.</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4000/2/4: Update of Sensor Arm LED Assembly. No More Crumbly Flex-PCB Mess!</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 12:11:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-400024-update-of-sensor-arm-led-assembly-no-more-crumbly-flex-pcb-mess-/</guid><description>I recently redesigned the sensor arm LED assembly for Beogram 4000, 4002, and 4004 because the prior flexible PCB design was too difficult for some users to install. My new design utilizes a small, rigid PCB that fits perfectly within the bulb housing and includes an insert to ensure accurate LED placement. This ensures the LED sits roughly where the original lightbulb filament was positioned.
This image displays the new components:</description></item><item><title>Beogram 4002: Plexiglass Hood Restoration</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 18:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/beogram-4002-plexiglass-hood-restoration/</guid><description>The Beogram 4002 (5523) I recently refurbished had a very scratched lid. Fortunately, the hinges were undamaged, and the inside of the lid was in good condition, with only a few minor cleaning marks. This made it worthwhile to try to restore the lid to an acceptable condition. The photo below shows the condition of the lid when I received the Beogram:
Because some scratches were deep enough to feel with a fingernail, I began by using 400-grit sandpaper to smooth the surface:</description></item></channel></rss>