<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VAR on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/var/</link><description>Recent content in VAR on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/var/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TalkSwitch Supports both VoIP and Legacy PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talkswitch-supports-both-voip-and-legacy-pbx/</guid><description>Choosing between a traditional phone system (analog or digital TDM PBX) and a newer VoIP system can be tough. TalkSwitch offers a solution by supporting both technologies.
For example, the TalkSwitch 244vs desktop PBX handles 2 incoming lines, 4 extensions for analog phones, and features like voicemail and music on hold. It also supports 10 remote extensions, allowing cell phones, home phones, and phones on other systems to connect by dialing a 3-digit extension.</description></item><item><title>We're Looking For Successful IT Consultants</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:40:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/were-looking-for-successful-it-consultants/</guid><description>Are you an experienced IT professional looking to expand your consulting business? If you specialize in voice and data network design, implementation, and troubleshooting, and perhaps even hold certifications with equipment vendors, we have an opportunity for you.
We&amp;rsquo;re offering a chance to grow your business with minimal effort. Gain access to new clients in your area and expand your service offerings without any upfront costs or extensive training. This is a simple way to boost your existing business.</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider.</description></item><item><title>Who Says You Can't Sell T1 Lines?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 02:41:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/who-says-you-cant-sell-t1-lines/</guid><description>While your business thrives by selling business phone systems or computer networking services, you might be missing out on providing clients a complete package. This missing piece? PBX trunk lines or WAN network connections. You&amp;rsquo;d definitely want a share of this profitable market.
You might assume this area belongs solely to phone companies. They prefer you think that way. When businesses see an available &amp;ldquo;T1&amp;rdquo; jack, they often contact their local phone provider directly.</description></item><item><title>Expand Your Telecom Services Line Card</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 22:18:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/expand-your-telecom-services-line-card/</guid><description>Instead of physical cards, a &amp;ldquo;line card&amp;rdquo; in telecommunications sales refers to the range of products and services your company provides. Expanding this range can attract new customers and increase sales but often involves higher inventory costs, franchise fees, or sales quotas. However, there&amp;rsquo;s a way to expand your offerings without these burdens, specifically within the professional telephone and enterprise network sectors.
This opportunity involves selling wireline telecom services. While you might already provide clients with handsets, PBX systems, network equipment, installation, and training, they might be purchasing telecom services elsewhere at a higher cost.</description></item><item><title>Telephone Installers Business Networking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 08:37:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telephone-installers-business-networking/</guid><description>For businesses selling or installing business telephone systems, there&amp;rsquo;s a valuable networking service to know about. It can provide you with more warm leads and expand your product offerings without any extra cost.
This service is the VAR Partner Network, an online platform run by Telarus, Inc. Telarus is a master agency that works with many different voice and data carriers. But it offers much more than that. Through its VAR Network, Telarus actively connects with businesses seeking not just communication services, but also equipment sales and installation.</description></item><item><title>Fiber Optic Cable Gets Limber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 05:38:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fiber-optic-cable-gets-limber/</guid><description>Fiber optic and copper cable are competing to be the main wiring used in communication setups, whether for renovations, improvements, or brand new projects. However, fiber is already recognized as the superior long-term option. Copper persists due to its widespread implementation and compatibility with existing switches and routers.
A significant installation obstacle has hindered the widespread adoption of fiber optic cabling: limited fiber bending flexibility. Exceeding this limit not only risks snapping the delicate strands but also creates functional issues.</description></item><item><title>Cisco's New Terabit Monster Router</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ciscos-new-terabit-monster-router/</guid><description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest edge router, the ASR 9000, significantly increases network bandwidth capacity. This powerful router can handle a massive 6.4 Tbps with a 400 Gbps per slot configuration. While not necessary for small businesses, the ASR 9000 targets large service providers dealing with the ever-growing demand for video content.
The surge in internet video consumption, from platforms like YouTube to embedded video content, is pushing service providers to their limits in bandwidth provisioning.</description></item></channel></rss>