<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dublin System on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dublin-system/</link><description>Recent content in Dublin System on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/dublin-system/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Under EU Law, asylum seekers who are subject to 'Dublin procedures' have the right to work.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</guid><description>Liam Thornton, Associate Professor, UCD Law School*
*Reblogged with permission from Liam Thornton’s blog.
Last week, the Court of Justice of the European Union determined in the K.S decision that Ireland&amp;rsquo;s 2018 Reception Regulations are not in line with the 2013 EU Reception Conditions Directive. Specifically, individuals involved in a potential transfer under the Dublin system possess the right to work in Ireland under these circumstances:
When a decision on their primary protection claim (separate from the Dublin transfer) hasn&amp;rsquo;t been reached within nine months...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/under-eu-law-asylum-seekers-who-are-subject-to-dublin-procedures-have-the-right-to-work/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can the Dublin III Regulation strengthen family reunification? The CJEU's ruling on the ability to appeal denials of take charge requests.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:26:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</guid><description>Mark Klaassen, Leiden University
Photo credit: DFID
Unaccompanied minors can appeal a receiving EU member state&amp;rsquo;s denial of a request to assume responsibility for their asylum case. This conclusion from the Court of Justice of the EU (CJEU) comes from its judgment in the I. &amp;amp; S. case. Interestingly, the District Court of Haarlem in the Netherlands initially posed the question because the Dublin III Regulation, which governs such transfers, doesn&amp;rsquo;t explicitly provide for this appeal right...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-the-dublin-iii-regulation-strengthen-family-reunification-the-cjeu-s-ruling-on-the-ability-to-appeal-denials-of-take-charge-requests/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initial examination of the European Union's latest asylum suggestions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 02:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Law School, University of Essex*
The EU Commission recently released a new set of proposals regarding asylum and non-EU migration. These proposals include draft legislation, non-binding agreements, renewed discussions on unresolved proposals, and plans for future measures. This article provides a summary of these new proposals and offers initial impressions. While the package could result in an agreement on updated asylum laws, this might come at the expense of weaker human rights protections...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initial-examination-of-the-european-union-s-latest-asylum-suggestions/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The European Court of Justice's initial decision on detaining asylum-seekers within the Dublin system and its implications for the rule of law in immigration detention.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 02:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</guid><description>Tommaso Poli, LL.M. candidate in Human Rights and Humanitarian Law at the University of Essex, School of Law.
The detention of those seeking asylum is a contentious issue within immigration law. While not initially covered by the European Common Asylum System (CEAS), it is now addressed in several of the second-phase CEAS measures. These measures include the Asylum Procedures Directive, the Reception Conditions Directive, the Qualification Directive, the Dublin Regulation, and the EURODAC Regulation...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-european-court-of-justice-s-initial-decision-on-detaining-asylum-seekers-within-the-dublin-system-and-its-implications-for-the-rule-of-law-in-immigration-detention/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Creating Discontent: Questions and Answers about the legal concerns of asylum-seekers crossing the Channel.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 23:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, University of Essex*
*Supported by an ESRC Priority Brexit Grant on &amp;lsquo;Brexit and UK and EU Immigration Policy&amp;rsquo;.
Some politicians are trying to create unnecessary fear and outrage over a relatively small number of people crossing the English Channel. This situation does bring up important legal questions. While the legal aspects have been discussed elsewhere, such as in the Free Movement blog, this post aims to clarify some of these legal issues in a straightforward question-and-answer format...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/creating-discontent-questions-and-answers-about-the-legal-concerns-of-asylum-seekers-crossing-the-channel/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Dublin system: Balancing Mutual Trust and Human Rights Protection in the ECJ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 20:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</guid><description>By Cecilia Rizcallah, Research Fellow at the Belgian National Fund for Scientific Research affiliated to the Centre of Interdisciplinary Research in Constitutional Law of Saint-Louis University (USL-B) and the Centre of European Law of the Free University Brussels (ULB). The author wishes to thank the Professors E. Bribosia and S. Van Drooghenbroeck for their valuable advice.
Introduction
On February 16th, the European Court of Justice (ECJ) issued a significant judgment in the case of C...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-dublin-system-balancing-mutual-trust-and-human-rights-protection-in-the-ecj/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Part 6 of the new EU asylum laws: The updated Dublin regulations regarding the accountability for asylum-seekers.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:25:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway, University of London
Photo credit: Ggia, via Wikimedia Commons
(last updated 10 June 2024: changed text marked by an asterisk)
Shortly before Christmas 2023, the European Parliament and the Council finalized an agreement on five crucial components of EU asylum law. These components address asylum procedures, the &amp;lsquo;Dublin&amp;rsquo; system for determining responsibility for asylum applications, the supporting &amp;lsquo;Eurodac&amp;rsquo; database, migrant/asylum seeker screening, and crisis derogations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-6-of-the-new-eu-asylum-laws-the-updated-dublin-regulations-regarding-the-accountability-for-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Three main points about the EU's New Pact on Migration and Asylum</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</guid><description>Lilian Tsourdi, Assistant Professor, University of Maastricht
*Photo credit: Délmagyarország/Schmidt Andrea
The EU&amp;rsquo;s New Pact on Migration and Asylum, along with its accompanying legislative proposals, represents the latest policy framework for asylum, migration, and border management. Its stated goal is to create streamlined migration procedures and stronger governance. Since September 2020, negotiations on the Pact&amp;rsquo;s legislative components have been underway.
Recently, both the European Parliament (April 2023) and the Council of the European Union (June 2023) have adopted negotiating positions on two significant instruments: the Asylum Procedures Regulation (APR), which updates regulations on determining asylum and related rights, and the Asylum and Migration Management Regulation (AMMR), which reforms the EU&amp;rsquo;s system for allocating responsibility for processing asylum requests and establishing a solidarity framework...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/three-main-points-about-the-eu-s-new-pact-on-migration-and-asylum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EU Law and Policy on the Relocation of Asylum-Seekers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</guid><description>Steve Peers recently discussed the legal aspects of the refugee crisis, focusing on international law. This post will examine the relocation of asylum-seekers within the EU, a topic that has sparked considerable debate. The EU recently passed a second decision on this matter, facing opposition from several member states. This decision follows an earlier one from September. Both are temporary measures, effective for two years, but there is a proposal for a permanent system...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eu-law-and-policy-on-the-relocation-of-asylum-seekers/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is it possible for the UK to choose not to participate in the mandatory EU refugee quotas?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</guid><description>Steve Peers
The EU Commission is anticipated to unveil a new immigration and asylum agenda on May 13th. A pressing issue within this agenda is whether the UK can opt out of mandatory refugee quotas, a question this article will examine.
Leaked portions of the Commission&amp;rsquo;s paper suggest a more ambitious approach to refugee resettlement than EU leaders recently agreed upon. Specifically, the Commission intends to propose mandatory rules for relocating asylum-seekers already within the EU and resettling refugees currently residing in non-EU countries...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-possible-for-the-uk-to-choose-not-to-participate-in-the-mandatory-eu-refugee-quotas/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The impact of the Rwanda Policy on the Common Travel Area in a low trust context with high trust arrangements.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</guid><description>Professor Colin Murray, University of Newcastle, and Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Zairon, via [Wikimedia Commons](Photo credit: Zairon, via Wikimedia Commons )
Introduction
Recent disagreements between the UK and Ireland concerning the ramifications of the UK&amp;rsquo;s Rwanda asylum policy highlight the complex interplay between EU law and Common Travel Area (CTA) agreements that now govern immigration policies between the two nations. This analysis examines these interactions and the Irish Government&amp;rsquo;s legislative proposals following the Irish High Court&amp;rsquo;s decision in A v Minister for Justice...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-impact-of-the-rwanda-policy-on-the-common-travel-area-in-a-low-trust-context-with-high-trust-arrangements/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tarakhel v Switzerland: Is this the end of the Dublin system?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 05:19:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</guid><description>Dublin System Challenged Again: Tarakhel v Switzerland Introduction
Despite aiming for high human rights protection standards, the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin system, which assigns responsibility for each asylum-seeker to one Member State, has repeatedly encountered human rights issues. The recent European Court of Human Rights (&amp;lsquo;ECtHR&amp;rsquo;) judgments in Tarakhel v Switzerland and Sharifi v Italy and Greece further highlight the difficulties in aligning this system with ECHR obligations. Notably, the Tarakhel judgment goes beyond previous rulings by demonstrating that the Court of Justice of the European Union&amp;rsquo;s (CJEU) interpretation of the Dublin rules also conflicts with the ECHR...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tarakhel-v-switzerland-is-this-the-end-of-the-dublin-system/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the recent asylum case law of the CJEU a distinction, integration, or extension from 'Mainstream' EU law?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Luxofluxo, via Wikimedia Commons
Introduction
While the focus has been on revising EU asylum law, as explored in my upcoming article and blog series, the Court of Justice of the European Union (CJEU) has been issuing significant judgments on asylum law matters. This post reviews these judgments, recent Advocate-General opinions, and potential impacts of the new EU asylum laws. It also examines how EU asylum law interacts with broader EU law principles...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-recent-asylum-case-law-of-the-cjeu-a-distinction-integration-or-extension-from-mainstream-eu-law/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Story of the Administrative Agreement on Asylum-Seekers between Greece and Germany: Is it a case of "paraDublin activity"?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 06:20:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</guid><description>Stathis Poularakis, Legal advisor - Advocacy Officer Médecins du Monde – Greece*
* Reposted from the EDAL blog. A previous version of this article was published in Greek on the immigration.gr blog. The opinions in this article belong to the author and don&amp;rsquo;t represent the official stance of Médecins du Monde – Greece. Thank you to Evangelia Tzironi, PhD Candidate at the Law School of the National and Kapodistrian University of Athens, for proofreading...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-story-of-the-administrative-agreement-on-asylum-seekers-between-greece-and-germany-is-it-a-case-of-paradublin-activity/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is the Dublin Regulation coming to an end? Where should unaccompanied children seek asylum?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</guid><description>Steve Peers*
Recent events have sparked debate concerning the EU&amp;rsquo;s Dublin III Regulation, which dictates where asylum seekers must apply for asylum within the EU. A British court ruled that the UK is responsible for the asylum claims of unaccompanied children in France, particularly those in Calais, if they have family in the UK. Additionally, a press release suggested the Commission may soon propose significant changes to the Dublin rules...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-the-dublin-regulation-coming-to-an-end-where-should-unaccompanied-children-seek-asylum/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Resistance is useless: examining the new Eurodac Regulation – part 4 of the analysis of recent EU asylum legislation.</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 18:10:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</guid><description>Professor Steve Peers, Royal Holloway University of London
Photo credit: Rachmaninoff, via Wikimedia Commons
This blog post has been amended since its initial publication, with asterisks marking the changes.* The most recent update was on June 18, 2024.
Shortly before Christmas, the European Parliament and the Council, the EU body representing ministers from Member States, agreed on five crucial aspects of EU asylum law. These aspects include asylum procedures, the ‘Dublin’ system for determining responsibility for asylum claims, the ‘Eurodac’ database that supports the Dublin system, the screening process for migrants and asylum seekers, and derogations during crises...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/resistance-is-useless-examining-the-new-eurodac-regulation-part-4-of-the-analysis-of-recent-eu-asylum-legislation/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>