<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Ethernet on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-ethernet/</link><description>Recent content in Business Ethernet on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/business-ethernet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Business Ethernet Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 12:56:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-ethernet-vs-t1/</guid><description>For decades, small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) have relied heavily on T1 lines. However, a new service called Business Ethernet is emerging as a strong competitor, offering comparable performance at a lower cost.
Business Ethernet, also referred to as Metro Ethernet, Ethernet over Copper, or Ethernet over Fiber, provides advantages such as scalable bandwidth options, reduced cost per Mbps, and wider availability. Its name emphasizes that Ethernet is no longer limited to Local Area Networks (LANs) and carriers, as it&amp;rsquo;s rapidly being adopted by SMBs.</description></item><item><title>FastE Fiber as MetroE for Business Ethernet Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 10:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/faste-fiber-as-metroe-for-business-ethernet-service/</guid><description>As businesses increasingly rely on data, the need for high-speed data transfer is becoming crucial. Fast Ethernet, a readily available and budget-friendly solution, offers a reliable way to achieve this over existing fiber optic networks. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into how Fast Ethernet operates and its role in optimizing bandwidth strategies.
You&amp;rsquo;ve likely utilized Fast Ethernet (FastE) on your network for years. FastE, synonymous with 100 Mbps Ethernet, surpasses standard Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 10 Mbps and falls short of Gigabit Ethernet&amp;rsquo;s 1,000 Mbps.</description></item><item><title>Will Elastic Bandwidth Help Your Company?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/will-elastic-bandwidth-help-your-company/</guid><description>Traditional telecom services such as T1 lines and SONET provided consistent bandwidth, but lacked flexibility. Today&amp;rsquo;s technology requires bandwidth that can adapt to changing needs. Enter &amp;ldquo;elastic bandwidth,&amp;rdquo; a service distinct from the variable bandwidth of DSL and Cable.
While DSL and Cable&amp;rsquo;s performance depends on overall network traffic, elastic bandwidth empowers users to directly control their connection capacity. This allows for scaling bandwidth up or down in real-time.
tw telecom&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Capacity service exemplifies this by allowing users to adjust bandwidth instantly via a self-service portal, even scheduling changes in advance.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item></channel></rss>