<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Festive on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/festive/</link><description>Recent content in Festive on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/festive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experience the flavors of an Italian Christmas at Casa Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jan 2024 17:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/experience-the-flavors-of-an-italian-christmas-at-casa-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>This year, Ferrero, the maker of Ferrero Rocher chocolates, has brought a touch of Italian Christmas magic to Singapore. Casa Ferrero, their only Southeast Asian pop-up shop, exudes elegance. The shop&amp;rsquo;s design echoes the gold of the classic Ferrero Rocher praline, enhanced by sparkling crystal chandeliers, the inviting aroma of espresso, and the distinct essence of roasted hazelnuts.
Located outside the Wisma Atria mall along Orchard Road in Singapore, Casa Ferrero is even larger than last year&amp;rsquo;s pop-up, Pasticceria Ferrero.</description></item><item><title>Chinese ranked as the top holiday spenders for 2015 according to Adobe Digital Index</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 17:49:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/chinese-ranked-as-the-top-holiday-spenders-for-2015-according-to-adobe-digital-index/</guid><description>A new Adobe Digital Index report predicts that online holiday spending in the Asia Pacific (APAC) region will be led by China, reaching an estimated US$150 billion.
China is expected to represent 55% of the region&amp;rsquo;s total online spending. Almost half (49%) of Chinese consumers surveyed anticipate increasing their online spending this holiday season. The average Chinese internet user is projected to spend US$210 online in November and December, contributing to 20% of the entire year&amp;rsquo;s online sales.</description></item><item><title>Singtel is celebrating Lunar New Year by offering free unlimited mobile data and previews of Singtel TV</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:43:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singtel-is-celebrating-lunar-new-year-by-offering-free-unlimited-mobile-data-and-previews-of-singtel-tv/</guid><description>Source: Singtel.
To celebrate the Year of the Monkey, Singtel is offering special promotions to its customers. For two days, from 12 am on February 7th to 11:59 pm on February 8th, all Singtel postpaid customers will receive free unlimited mobile data. Additionally, Singtel TV customers can access free previews of over 150 channels for a longer period, starting from 12 am on February 5th and ending at 11:59 pm on February 14th.</description></item><item><title>Add some festive flowers to the office to celebrate Chinese New Year and bring some brightness</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:17:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/add-some-festive-flowers-to-the-office-to-celebrate-chinese-new-year-and-bring-some-brightness/</guid><description>Starting January 19, 2015, Viva La Fleur will debut a new collection of long-lasting bouquets and table arrangements. The color palette for this collection features predominantly red, orange, and yellow tones, symbolizing love, luck, and fortune, perfectly aligning with the festive season.
This arrangement, part of Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s new collection, showcases deep red roses, hydrangeas, and caspia accented with brown twigs. You can find this arrangement in Viva La Fleur&amp;rsquo;s online shop here.</description></item><item><title>During the festive season, you can find exclusive Ferrero Rocher pralines at Pasticceria Ferrero in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 03:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/during-the-festive-season-you-can-find-exclusive-ferrero-rocher-pralines-at-pasticceria-ferrero-in-singapore/</guid><description>Celebrities Qi Yu Wu and Joanne Peh are pictured at the event.
Ferrero Rocher has opened its first Southeast Asia store, Pasticceria Ferrero, at Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Wisma Atria on Orchard Road. This unique boutique is the only one in the world and will be open for the holiday season.
A sneak peek before the official opening.
The shop offers a unique experience, allowing customers to personalize chocolate boxes with limited-edition Ferrero pralines available only during this special time of year.</description></item><item><title>Capella Singapore introduces exciting promotions for Chinese New Year</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/capella-singapore-introduces-exciting-promotions-for-chinese-new-year/</guid><description>Capella Singapore is celebrating the Year of the Rooster with special menus at their Cantonese restaurant, Cassia, from January 28th, 2017. They are also offering a three-night retreat package during this festive period.
Source: Capella Singapore. Capella Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起).
Cassia&amp;rsquo;s Prosperity Lou Hei (百花齐放捞起), a Lunar New Year staple, is back. Executive Chef Lee Hiu Ngai has carefully chosen each ingredient for this dish, which includes a variety of fresh greens, salmon, and a homemade passion fruit sauce for a refreshing twist.</description></item><item><title>Observe the fireworks display on February 11 at the Regent Hong Kong</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/observe-the-fireworks-display-on-february-11-at-the-regent-hong-kong/</guid><description>For the Lunar New Year, The Regent Hong Kong offers various culinary experiences:
Hong Kong Cuisine 1983
Celebrate with symbolic à la carte dishes (HK$468 to HK$980) like Lohei (HK$580) for prosperity, prawns in salted egg yolk (HK$580) for wealth, and braised Wagyu beef cheek (HK$980) for strength. Their HK$438 Good Fortune Turnip Cake Gift Box contains two 800g turnip cakes, one traditional and one smoked with tea leaves, sugarcane, imperatae, and brown sugar.</description></item><item><title>Goodwood Park Hotel is ringing in the Lunar New Year with a wide array of delicious treats</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 23:29:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/goodwood-park-hotel-is-ringing-in-the-lunar-new-year-with-a-wide-array-of-delicious-treats/</guid><description>Goodwood Park Hotel is celebrating the arrival of spring and Lunar New Year with a variety of festive treats, including yu sheng platters and savory specials, with a focus on the pineapple, a symbol of fortune.
Among the delicious takeaway options are the Duo of Prosperity Fish, featuring mango with pomelo and sago, and durian pudding. The hotel&amp;rsquo;s pastry team has also created an impressive Auspicious Golden Pineapple vanilla pound cake and a large Huat!</description></item></channel></rss>