<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Study on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/study/</link><description>Recent content in Study on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 01:00:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/study/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Consider pricing and marketing strategies for successful product launches in the Asia Pacific region</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 01:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</guid><description>Almost 75% of new products launched in the Asia-Pacific region fail. This rate surpasses other global regions, according to a study by strategy consultants Simon Kucher &amp;amp; Partners. The study, Global Pricing Study 2014, was conducted in partnership with the Professional Pricing Society (PPS).
[Image of watches for sale in a shopping district]
Globally, the ability to implement price increases is declining. While companies in 2012 could successfully implement 50% of planned price increases, that number has fallen to about 33% in 2014...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/consider-pricing-and-marketing-strategies-for-successful-product-launches-in-the-asia-pacific-region/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Initiating a discussion with real-time Tableau visualizations</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 23:41:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</guid><description>David Murphy, Google&amp;rsquo;s Head of TV Attribution (APAC), illustrates the stark contrast between working with data &amp;ldquo;before Tableau&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;after Tableau.&amp;rdquo; He first encountered Tableau in 2010.
In his presentation &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Fear the Data&amp;rdquo; at the &amp;ldquo;Tableau on Tour&amp;rdquo; conference in Singapore, Murphy argues that large datasets become manageable with the right tools. He highlights how discovering Tableau&amp;rsquo;s visualization software revolutionized his work.
Prior to Tableau, he relied on spreadsheets for chart creation, a process he dreaded altering...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/initiating-a-discussion-with-real-time-tableau-visualizations/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singaporeans have the opportunity to apply for government grants to assist with their studies in infocomm, media, and design</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 12:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</guid><description>Singaporeans working in Infocomm, Media, and Design can apply for the SkillsFuture Study Awards until June 14, 2016.
Announced during the Ministry of Communications and Information’s Committee of Supply Debate for 2016, the SkillsFuture Study Award encourages Singaporeans to enhance their skills in sectors crucial for future economic growth. Minister for Communications and Information, Dr. Yaacob Ibrahim, stated that 310 awards will be granted to Singaporeans in the early or middle stages of their careers who are looking to advance their skills in these sectors...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-have-the-opportunity-to-apply-for-government-grants-to-assist-with-their-studies-in-infocomm-media-and-design/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Various approaches to talent management in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: ECN.
Attracting and retaining skilled managers in Asia has become increasingly crucial for business leaders.
A recent survey by the Economist Corporate Network (ECN) of 550 member companies in Asia revealed that 95% of CEOs actively engage in talent management practices. However, their level and type of involvement differ significantly.
The report, Aligned for Success? Strategy, talent management and the role of the CEO in Asia, indicates that CEOs primarily focus on the strategic aspects of human capital, such as forecasting future workforce needs and organizational design...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/various-approaches-to-talent-management-in-asia/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>