<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>VoIP Telephony on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip-telephony/</link><description>Recent content in VoIP Telephony on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/voip-telephony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dedicated Bandwidth vs Cable</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-bandwidth-vs-cable/</guid><description>Businesses choose dedicated internet services, like T1 lines and Ethernet over Copper, when they prioritize consistent performance and service guarantees, or when shared options aren&amp;rsquo;t available. Cable broadband, on the other hand, attracts businesses with its high bandwidth for a lower cost. Although cable lacks service guarantees, its proven track record and widespread availability, especially during business hours, make it appealing.
The term &amp;ldquo;dedicated&amp;rdquo; in this context signifies that a specific bandwidth amount is exclusively allocated to the user.</description></item><item><title>Is Voice Over MPLS The New PSTN?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:32:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-voice-over-mpls-the-new-pstn/</guid><description>Packet-switched networks are undeniably replacing circuit-switched networks, so much so that the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN) might be phased out by the FCC. This signals the potential end of the century-old telephone system, raising the question of what will replace it. VoIP is a strong contender, but not in its current form.
VoIP&amp;rsquo;s strengths lie in its established standards for coding, signaling, and its compatibility with Ethernet data networks. However, its widespread adoption is hampered by incompatible implementations, concerns from wireless carriers about network overload, and inconsistent voice quality on the internet.</description></item><item><title>How to Get Your Business Phones For Free</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 06:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-to-get-your-business-phones-for-free/</guid><description>Upgrading your phone system might seem unnecessary if your current one still works, but you could be missing out on valuable features and integration with wireless devices. While this might seem like a luxury, your competitors could be gaining an advantage while you fall behind.
Believe it or not, you can access these advanced features without spending a fortune upfront. Cloud-based communication services provide a cost-effective alternative to traditional phone systems, allowing you to pay for what you use monthly.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Fast Ethernet for your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:32:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-fast-ethernet-for-your-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are your sophisticated business applications, such as cloud services, big data, VoIP telephony, video conferencing, or even simple video downloads, suffering due to insufficient bandwidth? If so, it might be the perfect time to consider upgrading to a 100 x 100 Mbps Fast Ethernet service. For a quick overview of Fast Ethernet, take a look at this video:
Fast Ethernet, offering speeds of 100 Mbps, is just one of many options provided by Carrier Ethernet providers.</description></item><item><title>Take a Bow For The SIP Revolution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:27:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/take-a-bow-for-the-sip-revolution/</guid><description>A significant change is happening in businesses of all sizes. It&amp;rsquo;s not related to politics, social issues, or processes. It&amp;rsquo;s a subtle change that most employees aren&amp;rsquo;t aware of, a change that isn&amp;rsquo;t easily noticeable and doesn&amp;rsquo;t require anyone to alter their work methods. It simply provides enhanced capabilities and cost savings. This is the SIP revolution.
What is SIP, and why is it so transformative? Watch this brief introduction to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>VoIP Compatible High Speed Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 13:45:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-compatible-high-speed-internet/</guid><description>The increasing popularity of Voice over IP (VoIP) among businesses is undeniable, primarily due to its advanced features and cost-effectiveness compared to traditional phone services. However, the transition to VoIP raises a crucial question: how to handle existing phone lines.
This question arises because the traditional phone system, deeply rooted in analog technology, has long relied on copper wiring for transmission. While smaller companies might still use analog lines, larger businesses have often transitioned to digital transmission methods like ISDN PRI (also known as T1 PRI).</description></item><item><title>Business Phone Goes Hosted</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 07:14:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-phone-goes-hosted/</guid><description>The evolution of business phone systems has progressed from basic single-line setups to intricate PBX systems accommodating numerous phones. However, the latest advancement isn&amp;rsquo;t about bigger in-house systems but rather a shift towards hosted solutions.
Hosted business phone, also known as cloud-based phone service, involves a provider managing your phone system on their equipment. Essentially, the responsibility of operating the PBX and connecting to the public phone network shifts from your company to the provider.</description></item><item><title> When Only T1 Will Do</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 10:17:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/-when-only-t1-will-do/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While gigabit fiber connections are becoming the norm, T1 lines are still a relevant and useful option for bandwidth needs. T1 service remains popular and could be a perfect fit for your requirements, balancing speed and affordability.
Why Consider T1 Lines?
T1 is a well-established and widely available telecom service. Although Plain Old Telephone Service (POTS) was once the standard, it&amp;rsquo;s being replaced by VoIP and cloud-based systems in many businesses.</description></item><item><title>TDM vs VoIP - Why Not Both?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:02:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tdm-vs-voip-why-not-both/</guid><description>Feeling stuck between choosing a traditional phone system or a modern one? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many businesses hesitate between sticking with their reliable but potentially outdated PBX system and switching to a VoIP system, unsure of the financial implications. The good news is that you have more choices than you might realize. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to commit to one system completely. You can have a mix of analog, digital, or IP phones at each desk, and you can choose between TDM or VoIP for outside calls.</description></item><item><title>Residential and Small Business VoIP Rates Crushed</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/residential-and-small-business-voip-rates-crushed/</guid><description>In recent years, VoIP telephony, also known as broadband phone service, has transformed from a niche computer application into a major competitor to traditional telephone services. This shift is largely due to the widespread adoption of broadband internet and its increased availability to small businesses. As a result of increased broadband access, there&amp;rsquo;s been a surge in VoIP providers, with Phone Power emerging as a major player. Phone Power is disrupting the industry by offering unlimited residential and small home-based business service plans for less than $15 per month.</description></item><item><title>How Does a VoIP Call Work?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 06:27:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-does-a-voip-call-work/</guid><description>VoIP is often called a network service, not a phone service, which matters for technical folks and business owners, but less so for everyday users. After all, a phone is a phone; you expect it to work the same way.
The aim with VoIP has been to closely replicate the experience of traditional landlines. Now that this is largely accomplished, the focus is shifting towards making VoIP calls sound even better than traditional calls, aiming for what&amp;rsquo;s called HD or high-definition voice.</description></item><item><title>What Is VoIP For Business?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-voip-for-business/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of talk about the benefits of switching from traditional phone services to VoIP, and for good reason. Businesses can gain a lot from enterprise VoIP solutions. However, there are potential downsides to watch out for to ensure a smooth transition. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by clarifying what VoIP is and how it compares to your current phone service.
One thing that often causes confusion about VoIP is the name itself.</description></item><item><title>You Pay Too Much For Your Business Phone</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/you-pay-too-much-for-your-business-phone/</guid><description>The telephone industry has undergone significant changes, even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t updated your phone system in a while. Sticking with outdated technology could mean you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying and missing out on valuable features.
What has changed? While phones might seem simple, their technology has evolved. In the past, all phones were standardized because they came from a single provider, the local telephone company. These phones were basic devices connected to a central switching system.</description></item><item><title>Fonality Call Center in a Box</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 01:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fonality-call-center-in-a-box/</guid><description>Thinking about starting a call center but worried about the initial expenses and complex setup? While a large-scale call center requires significant investment, there are solutions for businesses looking to add call center capabilities or start small and gradually expand. Fonality offers a &amp;ldquo;call center in a box&amp;rdquo; solution, providing a simplified yet robust system.
This solution utilizes an off-the-shelf PC tower functioning as a Linux server, with the option to upgrade to a rack-mount server for increased capacity.</description></item></channel></rss>