<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wide Area Networks on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wide-area-networks/</link><description>Recent content in Wide Area Networks on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/wide-area-networks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet In The First Mile Advantages</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 20:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-in-the-first-mile-advantages/</guid><description>Metropolitan and Wide Area Networks can send your data anywhere you want. To access these networks, you need a connection known as &amp;ldquo;first mile&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;last mile&amp;rdquo; connectivity. Ethernet offers advantages for this first mile link.
Several technologies, such as T1 lines, DSL, SONET fiber optic services, and even microwave or 3G/4G wireless, work well for first mile connections. These options connect your building to your service provider or a gateway to their network.</description></item><item><title>Can You Get To The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing and storage are becoming increasingly popular, and many believe they will soon be the standard for computer use. There are many benefits to using the cloud, such as not needing to buy or maintain software, having data automatically backed up, accessing tools and data from anywhere on any device, and being able to use smaller, more portable computers, like netbooks, cellphones, and tablets. However, one concern remains: reliable access to the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Future Proofing Your WAN With Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/future-proofing-your-wan-with-ethernet/</guid><description>Wide area networks (WANs) are changing. While once reliant on telephone technology, core networks are shifting towards packet-switched services to handle the increasing dominance of data and video traffic over voice. This shift raises questions for businesses about adapting their connections to stay current.
Many organizations face growing bandwidth demands. As their service contracts near renewal, they are reevaluating options, considering newer Ethernet services as alternatives to traditional T1 lines.</description></item><item><title>The Multiple Data Center Dilemma</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-multiple-data-center-dilemma/</guid><description>The increasing number of mergers and acquisitions has left many companies with a surplus of data centers. Instead of choosing one data center to become the central hub, companies should consider the unique characteristics of each facility, such as equipment, applications, and staffing. Furthermore, consolidating data centers necessitates a reassessment of connectivity.
While internal network traffic often surpasses external traffic, the rising reliance on cloud services demands greater Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Domination</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-domination/</guid><description>In the near future, Ethernet may become the sole networking standard.
Previously, local networking involved choices like Token Bus or Token Ring. Today, almost every Network Interface Card (NIC) uses Ethernet, with speeds ranging from 10 to 1,000 Mbps, and 10 Gbps becoming increasingly affordable. Local Area Networks (LANs) predominantly use switched Ethernet over twisted pair copper wiring with RJ-45 connectors, although fiber optics is becoming a competitor.
Cost drives this standardization.</description></item><item><title>Are Your WAN Circuits Monitored For Quality?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-your-wan-circuits-monitored-for-quality/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As businesses shift from traditional phone systems and in-house data storage to cloud-based solutions, the reliability of their Wide Area Network (WAN) connections becomes paramount. Network issues that were once minor annoyances can now lead to significant drops in productivity or even complete business disruptions. Ensuring optimal performance of every network connection, whether copper or fiber optic, is crucial. But how can businesses guarantee this level of reliability?</description></item><item><title>Ethernet Replacements For SONET</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:59:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-replacements-for-sonet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
High-bandwidth fiber optic Wide Area Networks (WANs) are based on SONET, a decades-old telephone company standard. While dependable, SONET&amp;rsquo;s high cost is leading to its replacement by Ethernet WAN. The increasing demand for business bandwidth makes Ethernet an attractive option for long-distance connections.
Why SONET Was Dominant for So Long
SONET (Synchronous Optical Network) emerged from a growing need for increased traffic capacity, specifically for long-distance phone calls.</description></item><item><title>WAN Transparency Via Ethernet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:33:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-transparency-via-ethernet/</guid><description>The ideal computer network operates so seamlessly that users don&amp;rsquo;t even realize it&amp;rsquo;s there. They don&amp;rsquo;t think about the technical details, just like they don&amp;rsquo;t think about how electricity works. It&amp;rsquo;s simply a service they can rely on. This is called transparency.
Many local area networks (LANs) already achieve this level of transparency. With most network cards supporting high speeds like Fast Ethernet or Gigabit Ethernet, company LANs can easily handle business needs.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Growing By Leaps and Bounds</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 07:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-growing-by-leaps-and-bounds/</guid><description>The hottest new access network service is Ethernet over Copper (EoC), with competitive carriers rushing to expand coverage.
What makes EoC so popular? It stems from evolving network needs. Wide Area Networks (WANs) have been dominated by the telephone industry, adapting phone technology for data and video transmission.
T1 lines, using two pairs of copper telephone wires, have been the standard for businesses needing dedicated Ethernet connections. They offer 1.5 Mbps upload and download speeds.</description></item><item><title>Why The Smart WAN Beats A Dumb Pipe</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-the-smart-wan-beats-a-dumb-pipe/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) are traditionally built using &amp;ldquo;dumb pipes,&amp;rdquo; which are simple bandwidth connections between two points. These connections are efficient at their primary function: transferring data packets. However, as IT requirements become more complex, there&amp;rsquo;s a growing need for more intelligent solutions. This can be achieved by either enhancing your internal IT capabilities or outsourcing these needs as a service.
Level 3 Communications, a leading provider of fiber network services, recognizes this shift from basic to high-performance networking demands.</description></item><item><title>WANs That Act Like LANs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:43:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wans-that-act-like-lans/</guid><description>Local Area Networks (LANs) are so commonplace in businesses that they often go unnoticed, much like the electrical outlets we use daily. They provide a standardized way to connect devices, making them function seamlessly without users needing to consider technical details.
Networks vs Utilities LANs can be compared to electricity: reliable and readily available. Just as we don&amp;rsquo;t think about voltage variations, we expect LANs to work without needing to understand the intricacies of Ethernet standards.</description></item></channel></rss>