<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telephone on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone/</link><description>Recent content in Telephone on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telephone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cut Your Telecommunications Costs 50%?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s uncertain economic climate, finding cost savings is more crucial than ever. What if you could save significantly on your monthly telecom bills without compromising quality? This might be easier than you think.
This article assumes your business uses at least a T1 line for phone and/or internet, which is common for most businesses beyond small offices or home setups. While many companies rely on traditional telecom providers, they may not be the most cost-effective option anymore...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cut-your-telecommunications-costs-50-/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You ARE Overpaying For Your Phone and Data Lines</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With economic uncertainty looming, businesses must prioritize survival. Focusing on expense reduction is crucial when future income is unpredictable. Telecom expenses, including data, phone, and internet services, often represent a significant monthly cost. It&amp;rsquo;s highly probable that you&amp;rsquo;re overpaying for these services.
Who’s Gouging Me?
You&amp;rsquo;re likely not being cheated. Think of it like those hidden costs that drain your budget without you realizing it.
First, Get Rid of the Waste..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-are-overpaying-for-your-phone-and-data-lines/</a></p></description></item><item><title>MegaPath Duet Combines Voice and Data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 05:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</guid><description>Small and mid-sized businesses need both phone and internet services. Their phone systems often start small and expand over time, adding lines as needed. Similarly, internet service might begin with dial-up, transition to DSL, and eventually upgrade to dedicated connections for better reliability.
This piecemeal approach often leads to businesses overspending on telecommunications. Optimizing these systems could potentially cut costs by up to 50%.
The key to saving money is bundling services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/megapath-duet-combines-voice-and-data/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Yes, You can Still Get a T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:59:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While T1 lines were the preferred connectivity choice during the early days of the internet and business migration to the Web, they have since been surpassed by business cable broadband and fiber, offering significantly higher bandwidth and lower costs per Mbps. However, T1 lines remain a suitable option for certain locations and applications. The question is, can you still find them?
Why Would You Want To?
Introduced by the Bell system in 1962, the T1 standard is deeply rooted in phone systems, particularly for small and medium-sized businesses...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/yes-you-can-still-get-a-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 PRI is More Than Caller ID</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:24:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</guid><description>T1 lines are the most common way to link PBX phone systems to the telephone network. T1 PRI service is often the preferred choice because it can transmit Caller ID information to business phones or call centers. However, there are additional ways that T1 PRI can offer the most budget-friendly phone line trunking.
T1 PRI is a highly specialized telecom service. T1 lines have been in use for over half a century to carry phone calls, and more recently, for point-to-point data, dedicated internet service, and connections to private networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-pri-is-more-than-caller-id/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Contact Center Telecom Service Savings</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 22:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</guid><description>Contact centers manage various communication methods like phone calls, faxes, emails, and mail for businesses and organizations. These centers often use a lot of telecommunications technology, making them a significant expense for the company. A typical center might have analog phone lines, digital phone lines (T1 or DS3), SIP trunking for VoIP, dedicated internet, and private lines for specific needs.
Contact center managers need voice and data services that reduce costs without sacrificing performance or reliability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contact-center-telecom-service-savings/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Landlines Flourish in Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 06:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</guid><description>While consumers are rapidly switching away from landlines, they are still essential for businesses of all sizes. Why is this the case?
Unlike individual consumers, businesses often have multiple employees and a central office location. These factors make landline-based PBX telephone systems, which connect to the outside world via landlines, the preferred choice for business communication.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t just mean traditional copper phone wires. Modern business landlines can include T1 lines, which combine multiple lines into a single digital cable, or SIP trunks, which use internet protocol for both voice and data transmission...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/landlines-flourish-in-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Technicians at Your Beck and Call</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</guid><description>Smaller businesses may find it difficult to afford a full-time technical expert, especially in a tough economy. However, this doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you have to postpone necessary telephone and network upgrades or settle for under-qualified technicians. You can get the expertise you need by hiring contractors.
Focus on finding pre-screened professionals with experience in your required services instead of just any contractor. You only pay for the specific work done, often as part of a package deal that includes equipment, installation, setup, and training at a special price...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/technicians-at-your-beck-and-call/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Conference Bridge to Everywhere</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-bridge-to-everywhere/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 22:46:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-bridge-to-everywhere/</guid><description>Conference bridges connect multiple phone lines, allowing people in different locations to talk together. While large companies might buy this equipment, it&amp;rsquo;s more affordable for others to pay as they go.
CogniConference is a budget-friendly service for organizing and participating in conference calls. It works well for audio-only calls using speakerphones or handsets. Additionally, it can provide audio for web conferences using tools like GotoMeeting.
While managed teleconferencing can be pricey, CogniConference aims for affordability, flexibility, and high-quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-bridge-to-everywhere/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/conference-bridge-to-everywhere/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Free International Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 12:14:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</guid><description>During tough economic times, everyone appreciates a good deal, especially free offers. Phone Power is offering free international calls through 2008 to promote its competitive business and residential VoIP services. This is a great opportunity for anyone who makes a lot of international calls. Even after the promotion ends, Phone Power&amp;rsquo;s rates remain very affordable.
This holiday season, you can call landlines in the following countries for free: United Kingdom (44), Spain (34), Ireland (353), Israel (972), Germany (49), Singapore (65), France (33), Denmark (45), Greece (30), Italy (39), and China (86)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/free-international-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Low Cost 800 Numbers Are Here</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:09:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/</guid><description>Considering an 800 number for your business? It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to encourage calls from potential customers, as they won&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to reach out if it&amp;rsquo;s toll-free. However, the cost of such a service might be a concern. Fortunately, there are affordable solutions available.
While &amp;ldquo;800 number&amp;rdquo; is a common phrase, various toll-free options exist, including 866, 877, and 888. These numbers function identically, allowing callers to connect without incurring charges, even for long-distance calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/low-cost-800-numbers-are-here/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Two Internet Connections For Consistent Phone Calls</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</guid><description>The way businesses use phone systems is evolving. Traditional analog and PBX systems are being replaced by mobile, computer-integrated, and cloud-based solutions. While these new features offer significant advantages, maintaining high-quality, reliable voice communication is crucial. The challenge lies in leveraging advanced technologies without compromising service quality, a balance we must strike as there&amp;rsquo;s no turning back from this technological evolution.
Staying with outdated analog or ISDN PRI systems is no longer sustainable...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/two-internet-connections-for-consistent-phone-calls/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The VoSKY is the Limit</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:53:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</guid><description>Skype, known for free international calls, has become a major player with over 300 million users and a growing presence in the corporate world.
While some might think Skype is just for techies, it has evolved significantly since eBay acquired it in 2005. Beyond basic computer-to-computer calls, a range of hardware now complements Skype, resembling traditional phone setups.
VoSKY, a California-based company, exemplifies this trend, catering to both home users and large companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-vosky-is-the-limit/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ultra Conference Dual Conference Calling Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/</guid><description>When your teleconferencing needs expand beyond small, local groups, it&amp;rsquo;s time to explore conference call solutions. While some phone systems offer conference bridges to connect multiple phones, outsourced conferencing solutions can accommodate significantly more participants from various locations.
Ultra Conference provides a robust and affordable conferencing solution suitable for a wide range of applications. It offers flexible pricing options with both fixed and per-minute rates.
Training calls are a popular use for Ultra Conference...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ultra-conference-dual-conference-calling-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is ISDN and Why Do I Want It?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</guid><description>You might have encountered the term ISDN in the context of phone services. What does it mean and how can it benefit you?
ISDN stands for Integrated Services Digital Network, a technical term for a digital phone service that adheres to specific standards.
The concept of ISDN emerged when dial-up modems using analog phone lines were the norm for internet access. ISDN aimed to combine phone and internet services on a single line with three channels...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-isdn-and-why-do-i-want-it/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Private Branch Exchange Connections</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</guid><description>PBX telephone systems are the preferred business phone technology for medium and large businesses, though recent advancements have made them affordable for smaller companies as well, replacing outdated hardwired or key systems. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering a new PBX system, reaching out to VAR Network can provide insights into pricing and available options.
Beyond hardware, PBX systems require connectivity, with various options offering different cost and performance benefits. The most basic connection is an FXO, or analog phone line, connecting to a central office...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/private-branch-exchange-connections/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Have The Instinct For Covert Ops?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:55:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</guid><description>Ever imagine yourself as a secret agent like Jack Bauer from the show &amp;ldquo;24&amp;rdquo;? The Samsung Instinct phone, especially in sleek black, is your gateway to that world. Packed with features, it&amp;rsquo;s the ultimate device for any aspiring operative.
The large, high-resolution touchscreen provides crystal-clear visuals and even vibrates slightly when you touch it, ensuring precise navigation. Its powerful 2.0 Megapixel camera captures high-quality photos and videos suitable for sharing or printing...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-have-the-instinct-for-covert-ops/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The AccuConference Cost Advantage</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s challenging economy, audio teleconferencing, video conferencing, and web conferencing are gaining popularity. These tools effectively cut costs and boost productivity without resorting to layoffs or facility closures. This demonstrates how technology is replacing outdated and unsustainable business practices. Electronic conferencing helps businesses thrive during economic slowdowns by connecting teams, accelerating progress, and eliminating costly travel expenses. A frontrunner in this domain is AccuConference.
AccuConference stands out from competitors by offering a comprehensive suite of solutions, including conventional audio conference calls, video conferencing, and web conferences...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-accuconference-cost-advantage/</a></p></description></item><item><title>VoIP Land Lines Complement Wireless</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:55:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</guid><description>Traditional analog phone lines are commonly referred to as &amp;ldquo;landlines.&amp;rdquo; This term can also apply to digital services like T1 lines. Both analog and digital telephony have relied on buried copper wire pairs since the beginning of telephone service two centuries ago. The term &amp;ldquo;landline&amp;rdquo; distinguishes these copper wire-based telecom services from satellite and cellular wireless services.
While landlines and wireless services may seem entirely distinct, they can be combined to offer significant advantages...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/voip-land-lines-complement-wireless/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Enterprise VoIP Moves to the Cloud</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 16:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>by: John Shepler
For decades, enterprise VoIP has been taking the place of traditional analog business phone systems. While PBX systems evolved into IP PBX, they remained hardware and software bound to a physical location. Now, those telecom rooms are becoming vacant as business VoIP transitions to the cloud and evolves into Unified Communications.
What’s Cloud Got To Do With It? Initially, businesses set up their own phone switching systems when the limited buttons on desk phones became insufficient...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/enterprise-voip-moves-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Pros and Cons for Business PBX</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</guid><description>The evolution of business telephone lines has been remarkable, from analog landlines to digital T1 CAS trunks, ISDN PRI, and finally SIP packet-based networks. Interestingly, all these technologies are still in use. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the two most common configurations for multi-line PBX business phone systems.
ISDN PRI (Primary Rate Interface)
ISDN PRI, often shortened to PRI or ISDN PRI, stands for Integrated Services Digital Network Primary Rate Interface.
This standard telecom service is based on the earlier T1 line specification...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-pros-and-cons-for-business-pbx/</a></p></description></item><item><title>QT Talk is Both VoIP and Dial-Around</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 03:23:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</guid><description>Many people are interested in VoIP phone service because of its features and affordability, but they also want the freedom of mobile calling. QT Talk offers a solution that combines the advantages of VoIP with the flexibility of cellular service.
QT Talk provides a feature-rich VoIP service, including their popular North America Plus plan. For a low monthly fee, users enjoy unlimited calls to the U.S., Canada, and Puerto Rico, along with a reduced rate to select international destinations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/qt-talk-is-both-voip-and-dial-around/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Tips To Reduce Your Telecom Costs</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:16:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Businesses are facing a challenging time as they grapple with the fluctuating economic landscape brought on by the Covid-19 crisis. While growth was once the primary focus, survival has now taken center stage, making cost control paramount. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore some immediate steps you can take to reduce expenses without jeopardizing operations.
Are You Paying For Unused Services?
It might seem improbable, but both individuals and businesses frequently pay for services they don&amp;rsquo;t utilize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tips-to-reduce-your-telecom-costs/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Integrated T1 Gives You Phone and Internet</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 16:42:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</guid><description>Small businesses need high-quality telecom services without the high price tag of large corporations. While you might not need the same capacity as a major company, you can still access reliable phone and internet services tailored to your needs.
Achieving this involves using a T1 line, a standard for voice and data transmission. While medium-sized companies might have multiple T1 lines, a single line can suffice for smaller businesses by combining phone and internet access...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/integrated-t1-gives-you-phone-and-internet/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>