<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Challenge on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/challenge/</link><description>Recent content in Challenge on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/challenge/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The RYDE Carpool Challenge will begin in April</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 19:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-ryde-carpool-challenge-will-begin-in-april/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s carpooling app, RYDE, has teamed up with Cycle &amp;amp; Carriage for the RYDE Carpool Challenge. The grand prize? A Mitsubishi Attrage.
The eight-month campaign, which began on April 1, 2016, aims to have RYDE users complete a collective carpool distance of 1,000,000km, thus reducing carbon emissions by 200,000kg. By encouraging carpooling, RYDE hopes to promote a more environmentally friendly mode of transportation.
Each month, RYDE will select two winners: the rider and driver with the highest number of successful carpools.</description></item><item><title>Avaya has pinpointed areas where the guest experience can be improved</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 10:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/avaya-has-pinpointed-areas-where-the-guest-experience-can-be-improved/</guid><description>Avaya, a telecommunications company, recently released the results of their first annual Hospitality Industry Survey. The survey, which polled 72 global hotel brands, revealed key market trends and areas for improvement within the hospitality industry.
Three major areas stood out as opportunities for hotels to enhance guest experiences: guest engagement, communication, and services. The survey revealed that many companies recognize the potential of mobile, multichannel communication for both guests and staff and are looking to upgrade in-room technology with new applications and features.</description></item><item><title>Singaporean CFOs are struggling to manage an overwhelming amount of data</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 10:22:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporean-cfos-are-struggling-to-manage-an-overwhelming-amount-of-data/</guid><description>Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Chief Financial Officers (CFOs) face difficulties due to evolving stakeholder expectations and reporting timelines. CFOs anticipate changes in how reporting operates. CFOs are finding it difficult to provide boards with timely and accurate insights due to the increasing amount and speed of data. This issue is highlighted in a new report by EY Financial Accounting and Advisory Services (FAAS): 66% of global respondents say this significantly impacts corporate reporting effectiveness, up from 57% in 2015.</description></item><item><title>Brand Alliance is set to release a new book highlighting the achievements of influential brands in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 18:05:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/brand-alliance-is-set-to-release-a-new-book-highlighting-the-achievements-of-influential-brands-in-asia/</guid><description>Brand Alliance, a brand consulting firm, is releasing its inaugural book, &amp;ldquo;Influential Brands: A documentary of their heroic rise.&amp;rdquo; This book launch coincides with the firm&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;2014 Influential Brands&amp;rdquo; conference, themed &amp;ldquo;Celebrating brand leadership and Asia brand heroes&amp;rdquo;, taking place on November 7, 2014, at the Suntec City Convention Centre.
Source: Brand Alliance. Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s brand story is in the book.
The book offers never-before-seen insights into the development of well-known brands, particularly those from Singapore.</description></item><item><title>Singapore is known for having one of the most competitive talent markets in Asia</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-is-known-for-having-one-of-the-most-competitive-talent-markets-in-asia/</guid><description>Source: Randstad Sourceright website. Global figures.
Randstad Sourceright, a global staffing agency, has released its 2016 Talent Trends Report, a guide highlighting 30 significant trends influencing talent, employees, and businesses this year.
The report incorporates insights from almost 400 HR, talent, and business leaders representing over 60 countries. Randstad Sourceright identified the lack of essential skills and its subsequent impact on businesses, leadership, and succession planning as the most significant talent management challenge today.</description></item><item><title>Jabra discusses the obstacles of maintaining productivity in a workplace</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/jabra-discusses-the-obstacles-of-maintaining-productivity-in-a-workplace/</guid><description>Source: Jabra research report.
According to audio and communications company Jabra, modern workplaces face difficulties in fostering productivity due to common hurdles employees experience daily. These include distractions, poorly structured meetings, and technology that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work as intended.
Jabra&amp;rsquo;s 2015 research report, Productivity at the Office – Challenges, highlights that while companies invest in resources and tools to help office workers collaborate and focus, employees still encounter obstacles. These include constant distractions, unproductive meetings, and challenges utilizing technology meant to enhance their output.</description></item><item><title>The Canon PhotoMarathon is scheduled to take place in Singapore in November</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 14:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-canon-photomarathon-is-scheduled-to-take-place-in-singapore-in-november/</guid><description>Source: Canon eDM. Now in its 12th year, the Canon PhotoMarathon 2014 is the biggest photography competition in the region. Taking place in Indonesia, Malaysia, Singapore, Vietnam, India, Thailand, and Cambodia, the competition offers a fantastic chance for companies to form teams and compete in the Corporate Challenge category.
Companies can participate by assembling a team of at least three individuals who register as a group. In contrast to the open and student divisions, corporate teams are evaluated collectively.</description></item><item><title>Tata Communications announces Global Scrapbook Challenge ahead of upcoming Formula 1 race</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:28:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tata-communications-announces-global-scrapbook-challenge-ahead-of-upcoming-formula-1-race/</guid><description>Tata Communications, a global communications company, has launched its second technology challenge offering US$50,000 in prizes. This challenge focuses on harnessing innovative connectivity solutions, a key aspect of Formula 1 racing.
Leading up to the FORMULA 1 GRAN PREMIO D’ITALIA 2014, Tata Communications is challenging the public to create a digital scrapbook celebrating the history of the Mercedes-Benz Silver Arrows in Formula 1. This Global Scrapbook Challenge aims to build a virtual museum, a captivating online archive of stories, memories, and intrigue for fans of the sport.</description></item><item><title>Euromonitor examines consumer opportunities for individuals aged 60 and above</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 12:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/euromonitor-examines-consumer-opportunities-for-individuals-aged-60-and-above/</guid><description>Source: Euromonitor website.
Market research firm Euromonitor International has published a new report on the growing market of older consumers. Though businesses have often overlooked this demographic— individuals aged 60 and above— due to perceptions of low spending, limited income, and resistance to marketing, this group is expanding rapidly.
In 2014, the global population aged 60 and over reached 912 million, accounting for 12.6% of the total. By 2030, this segment is projected to increase to 1.</description></item></channel></rss>