<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Future on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/future/</link><description>Recent content in Future on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Asia Pacific region is experiencing advancements in IT that are preparing it for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 04:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-asia-pacific-region-is-experiencing-advancements-in-it-that-are-preparing-it-for-the-future/</guid><description>Businesses can be categorized into four groups based on their future readiness: Current Focused, Future Aware, Future Focused, and Future Creators. Future Creators have a significant advantage over their Current Focused counterparts when evaluating key performance indicators. Companies in the Asia Pacific region that are the most future-ready show improvements across eight different business metrics.
Source: Dell infographic. The four things that future-ready organisations are more likely to do.
Dell recently released findings from a global study conducted by IDC, an analyst firm.</description></item><item><title>Cisco has found that technology is influencing the way we work</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cisco-has-found-that-technology-is-influencing-the-way-we-work/</guid><description>The 2014 Cisco Connected World Technology Report (CCWTR) reveals that employers are adapting their policies to accommodate the growing desire for flexible work styles among Generation X (born 1960s-1980s) and Millennial (born 1980s-2000s) employees.
This year&amp;rsquo;s CCWTR expands on its usual exploration of young workers&amp;rsquo; mindsets and behaviors by examining how Gen X and HR professionals value connectivity, perceive their work availability, and influence IT policies, product design, and business competitiveness.</description></item><item><title>Singaporeans will receive increased support for SkillsFuture</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 00:48:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singaporeans-will-receive-increased-support-for-skillsfuture/</guid><description>Source: SkillsFuture Singapore. Minister Puthucheary watches on as Ng (left) and Kevin Wo, Country GM, Microsoft Singapore (right) sign the MoU.
To better equip Singapore&amp;rsquo;s workforce and businesses for a digital-centric economy, SkillsFuture Singapore (SSG) has launched new initiatives. These include a partnership with Microsoft and enhancements to the national SkillsFuture for Digital Workplace program.
Dr. Janil Puthucheary, Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Senior Minister of State for the Ministry of Transport and Ministry of Communications and Information, announced these developments at the first SkillsFuture Festival X Smart Nation (SFFXSmart Nation) event.</description></item><item><title>Five hotel design trends that travelers should keep an eye out for</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 23:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/five-hotel-design-trends-that-travelers-should-keep-an-eye-out-for/</guid><description>Source: Hotel Suppliers Show website. Hotels in the future will have a drastically different look and feel compared to what we are accustomed to.
The Hotel Suppliers Show, the largest hospitality trade show in the Philippines, highlights five key hospitality design trends expected to shape the industry&amp;rsquo;s future:
Guest Room Reimagined
The popularity of alternative lodging options like Airbnb has pushed traditional hotels to rethink their interior design, especially for guest rooms.</description></item><item><title>Part 12: 2023's Work Trends</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:22:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/part-12-2023-s-work-trends/</guid><description>Source: Deel playbook. 12 work
trends for 2023.
Deel, a provider of payroll and compliance solutions for global teams, has identified twelve emerging workplace trends for 2023:
Overemployed
Deel found that remote workers are increasingly taking on multiple jobs simultaneously, leveraging flexible schedules and asynchronous communication tools.
The Chief Remote Officer (CRO)
The role of CRO is gaining traction, with companies seeking individuals to oversee all aspects of remote work, including in-person events, time-zone management, compensation, and communication tools.</description></item><item><title>In the new application economy, leaders can quickly fall behind and become laggards</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 23:32:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-the-new-application-economy-leaders-can-quickly-fall-behind-and-become-laggards/</guid><description>Lim May-Ann, Managing Director of TRPC, presented the findings of the 2016 CA Technologies Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan Application Economy Index.
Singapore currently holds the top spot in the Asia Pacific and Japan region regarding the application economy. However, it faces a potential decline to fourth place in future potential, according to the inaugural Asia Pacific &amp;amp; Japan (APJ) Application Economy Index (AEI) 2016. This index assesses the readiness of 10 APJ markets to thrive in the digital age.</description></item><item><title>Cognizant: Training programs are not keeping up with evolving realities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:36:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-training-programs-are-not-keeping-up-with-evolving-realities/</guid><description>Businesses and higher education institutions (HEIs) need to prepare workers for jobs that don&amp;rsquo;t even exist yet, according to a new report by Cognizant.
The Future of Learning report, based on a survey of business executives and HEI leaders, found that while both groups recognize the need to prepare students for a workplace transformed by digital technologies, they are struggling to adapt. Although the majority of businesses (80%) and HEIs (72%) understand the importance of equipping workers with the skills needed for this new environment, there is a gap between awareness and action.</description></item><item><title>Deliveroo predicts future food trends in Asia with "Snack to the Future"</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 17:22:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/deliveroo-predicts-future-food-trends-in-asia-with-snack-to-the-future/</guid><description>Deliveroo, a food delivery platform, has released a report titled &amp;ldquo;Snack To The Future Report&amp;rdquo; predicting how technology and evolving consumer habits will shape food consumption patterns in the region by 2040.
The report, developed by Deliveroo in collaboration with Singaporean food specialists Yip Hon Mun and Luke Tay, along with other global experts, identifies emerging food trends driven by technological advancements and changing consumer behaviors. Key predictions include personalized dietary recommendations based on breath analysis (&amp;ldquo;Breath-prints&amp;rdquo;), AI-powered customized diets (&amp;ldquo;Me-ganism&amp;rdquo;), and immersive dining experiences using augmented reality (&amp;ldquo;FOODGASMS&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Cognizant outlines three key strategies for remaining employed in the coming decade</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 02:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cognizant-outlines-three-key-strategies-for-remaining-employed-in-the-coming-decade/</guid><description>Cognizant&amp;rsquo;s Jobs of the Future Report highlights a three-part theme, Coaching, Caring, and Connecting, which prioritizes human skills and predicts their importance in the future job market, regardless of technological advancements.
Coaching Coaches can transform work by making it more engaging, humane, and meaningful. Individuals with a knack for mentoring and helping others improve in areas like finance or personal well-being should focus on developing these skills further.
Caring Future-oriented organizations will prioritize employee well-being alongside technological advancement.</description></item><item><title>Dell considers Singapore to be one of the 50 economies worldwide that are prepared for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 10:50:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dell-considers-singapore-to-be-one-of-the-50-economies-worldwide-that-are-prepared-for-the-future/</guid><description>Dell recognized Singapore as one of 50 economies worldwide prepared to flourish in an evolving, globalized future through technological integration. The _Dell Future-Ready Economies Model*, the foundation for this ranking, assesses large, rapidly growing global metropolitan areas on characteristics that allow individuals and businesses to utilize innovative tools and concepts. These factors contribute to improved connectivity, superior economic performance, and a greater capacity to attract talent.
The ranking evaluated the Global 50 cities based on three key aspects:</description></item></channel></rss>