<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Interconnection on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/interconnection/</link><description>Recent content in Interconnection on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/interconnection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Telx Minimizes Latency WIth Colocation Near Carriers</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:56:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/telx-minimizes-latency-with-colocation-near-carriers/</guid><description>For applications sensitive to delays, proximity to service providers is crucial. Regardless of your equipment&amp;rsquo;s speed, signal propagation sets the minimum latency. This speed is about a millisecond per 186 miles in a vacuum and increases with copper or fiber cables, further compounded by routers and switches. Being directly connected to your provider minimizes this distance. Telx offers a solution.
Telx specializes in colocation, connecting customers and providers physically. With 15 strategically located centers in 9 states, they offer proximity to media hubs, cable landings, fiber paths, and exchanges.</description></item><item><title>Business Booming For Telx Interconnection and Colocation</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 05:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/business-booming-for-telx-interconnection-and-colocation/</guid><description>Despite the current economic downturn, data center provider Telx is experiencing a surge in construction at their main Chicago facility. This might seem counterintuitive during a recession, but it makes sense considering the ongoing technological transformation in business and finance.
Companies have shifted from manual processes to computer-based systems, leading to a client-server model that boosted efficiency and productivity. Now, forward-thinking companies are seeking new strategies for a competitive edge.</description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area.</description></item></channel></rss>