<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Chair on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chair/</link><description>Recent content in Chair on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/chair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Increase your productivity by installing a treadmill at your desk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 13:22:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</guid><description>A recent study featured in the journal Plos One found that using a treadmill desk could lead to higher productivity compared to a traditional desk setup.
[Image of a treadmill desk]
Source: Plos One
This study, titled &amp;ldquo;Treadmill Workstations: The Effects of Walking while Working on Physical Activity and Work Performance&amp;rdquo;, was conducted by researchers from the University of Minnesota-Twin Cities, University of Texas-Arlington, Mayo Clinic, and Arizona State University. Over 12 months, they observed the impact of treadmill desks on physical activity and work output at a financial services company...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increase-your-productivity-by-installing-a-treadmill-at-your-desk/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Focus of Kickstarter campaign: Sitting cross-legged on a CrossChair</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 21:16:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</guid><description>Dave McClintock designed a chair that lets you comfortably rest with your legs up. Its unique design is so flexible, it even allows for the sukhasana yoga pose while seated.
McClintock explained that the chair caters to millions of workers who experience fatigue, back pain, and stiff muscles from prolonged sitting. While crossing your legs can alleviate these issues, traditional office chairs lack the ergonomics. The CrossChair solves this by enabling various sitting positions, including cross-legged, promoting movement and reducing discomfort...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/focus-of-kickstarter-campaign-sitting-cross-legged-on-a-crosschair/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Singapore customers can test products before making a purchase with Flokk</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 22:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/</guid><description>Flokk, a Norwegian company known for producing high-quality seating furniture, has joined forces with W. Atelier to introduce Flokk&amp;rsquo;s brands to the Singapore market.
Source: Flokk. HÅG chairs in an office.
Flokk is recognized for its ergonomic and sustainable designs, with all products developed, produced, and manufactured in Europe. Each of Flokk&amp;rsquo;s eight brands represents the highest quality, as demonstrated in W. Atelier&amp;rsquo;s Henderson showroom, where HÅG, RBM, and RH are exclusively featured...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/singapore-customers-can-test-products-before-making-a-purchase-with-flokk/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>