<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ethernet Bandwidth on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-bandwidth/</link><description>Recent content in Ethernet Bandwidth on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/ethernet-bandwidth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Last Mile Connections That Make Sense</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 23:17:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</guid><description>The US is covered in a network of competing telecom companies, reaching into every major city. Businesses of all sizes are drawn to their advanced IP networks, fiber optic infrastructure, and significantly lower prices. But how can businesses connect to these networks?
The final connection to a customer&amp;rsquo;s location, often called the &amp;ldquo;last mile,&amp;rdquo; is frequently the most critical, expensive, and limiting part of a wide area network. It gets its name from the typical distance between a business and the nearest carrier Point of Presence (POP)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/last-mile-connections-that-make-sense/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Level 3 Shows How The Converged Business Network Saves Money</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 17:19:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</guid><description>Larger organizations have been moving towards network convergence since IP became the standard network protocol. However, smaller companies, often lacking substantial IT departments, haven&amp;rsquo;t adopted this approach as readily. This is changing. Convergence is now a viable option for businesses of all sizes.
What&amp;rsquo;s driving this shift? The answer, as always, is cost savings. In today&amp;rsquo;s business climate, reducing expenses is crucial. The real game-changer is the availability of managed convergence services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/level-3-shows-how-the-converged-business-network-saves-money/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Insatiable Demand For Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 22:20:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>10 Gbps used to be a bandwidth amount so large that only major telecommunications companies needed it. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer true, as businesses are now using that much WAN bandwidth and wanting even more.
Beyond internet providers, who could need 10 Gbps? According to Carrier Ethernet News, the finance, streaming entertainment, and medical industries are leading the demand for high bandwidth. Some are even hoping for 40 Gbps and 100 Gbps!..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/insatiable-demand-for-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Instant Ethernet Fiber Network Quotes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 17:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/</guid><description>The need for fiber optic bandwidth has never been greater. Businesses are producing and sharing more video content, medical imaging has transitioned to digital platforms, and cloud-based IT relies heavily on bandwidth. However, finding available fiber services and their costs can be a tedious and time-consuming process.
Imagine getting instant online quotes for fiber optic services. It might seem too good to be true, but it&amp;rsquo;s now a reality. The Telarus GeoQuote bandwidth search engine has been enhanced to provide instant online quotes for Ethernet over Fiber, with bandwidth options ranging from 10 Mbps to 1 Gbps (GigE)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-ethernet-fiber-network-quotes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Point of Presence Locator</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re interested in getting more bandwidth for your money, and finding an Ethernet Point of Presence (POP) Locator can help. But what is a POP and how can it save you money?
Essentially, a POP is a carrier&amp;rsquo;s service location, such as a central office with termination equipment for their fiber optic network. Think of it as a station for accessing high-speed data and voice services. POPs aren&amp;rsquo;t always in carrier offices; they can be in colocation centers, shared facilities housing servers and offering resources like bandwidth, security, and backup power...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-point-of-presence-locator/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Cuts Costs, Expands Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</guid><description>In the business world, we often face tough decisions where we must choose between two desirable options. But what if we didn&amp;rsquo;t have to choose? What if we could have it all? That&amp;rsquo;s precisely the advantage that Ethernet service offers.
Ethernet provides a win-win situation: increased bandwidth at a lower cost. You might wonder how that&amp;rsquo;s possible. The answer lies in technological progress and the emergence of ambitious new providers determined to revolutionize telecommunications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-cuts-costs-expands-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>