<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>T1 Line on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line/</link><description>Recent content in T1 Line on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/t1-line/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Get Ready For The Recovery With Bandwidth on Demand</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>The economy is recovering, benefiting some businesses while others struggle. Maintaining earnings through cost-cutting instead of increased sales won&amp;rsquo;t be sustainable. When the economy fully recovers, rapid adaptation will be crucial, but increased expenses are only justifiable with increased revenue. Bandwidth on demand offers a solution.
Bandwidth on demand allows businesses to access and pay for only the bandwidth they currently need, scaling usage up or down as required. This differs from the traditional approach of installing full capacity in advance, which poses financial risks if projected growth doesn&amp;rsquo;t materialize...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/get-ready-for-the-recovery-with-bandwidth-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet Over Copper Vs T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 05:09:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</guid><description>The T1 line is a widely available and dependable business bandwidth solution. It provides dedicated bandwidth at a reasonable cost, making it a reliable choice. However, another service called Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining popularity as a viable alternative.
EoC is an Ethernet WAN connection that can connect multiple business locations or provide a dedicated high-speed Ethernet connection. It can also serve as an access point to private cloud networks, including national and international MPLS networks...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-vs-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>600,000 Inquiries, No Waiting</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</guid><description>Purchasing important items can be a hassle, especially telecommunications services. It&amp;rsquo;s a maze of confusing calls, endless hold music, and tedious forms with long wait times.
But imagine getting a price for a T1 line or finding nearby Metro Ethernet services in under a minute, any time, day or night. That&amp;rsquo;s where GeoQuote (tm) comes in. This innovative telecom pricing application is changing how businesses buy voice and data services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/600-000-inquiries-no-waiting/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Is It Time To Go Fiber Optic Internet?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you found that your internet service, once reliable, can no longer keep up with your growing business? If a slow connection is impacting productivity and increasing frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. But what are your options?
More Choices, Less Cost
Shopping for internet access may seem daunting, especially if your last experience was limited and expensive. You might have settled for a T1 line, DSL from the phone company, or business cable from your TV provider...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-it-time-to-go-fiber-optic-internet/</a></p></description></item><item><title>10 Mbps, 100 Mbps, 1000 Mbps Internet Upgrades</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:29:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Are you frustrated with your company&amp;rsquo;s slow internet speeds? It&amp;rsquo;s understandable. Today&amp;rsquo;s applications are much more demanding than the simple websites and text-based emails common when T1 lines were first introduced. A 10 Mbps connection is now the bare minimum for most businesses, and it&amp;rsquo;s reasonable to need 100 Mbps or even 1000 Mbps. So, how can you upgrade effectively?
Upgrading Your Connection
One option is to gradually increase your bandwidth as your needs grow...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/10-mbps-100-mbps-1000-mbps-internet-upgrades/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Bandwidth Windfall</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 07:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</guid><description>When budgets are strained, expanding into new markets and generating much-needed revenue often depends on increasing Wide Area Network (WAN) bandwidth. However, more bandwidth usually means higher expenses, creating a difficult situation.
It&amp;rsquo;s generally accepted that increasing bandwidth leads to increased costs. For instance, 10 Mbps will likely cost more than 1 Mbps, although there might be a volume discount. But is it possible to get more bandwidth while paying less overall?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/bandwidth-windfall/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Providers Bandwidth Service Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</guid><description>Having a reliable internet connection is crucial for modern businesses. There are many options available, so it’s important to understand what’s on the market and how to find the best prices.
Wide Area Networks (WANs) and Metropolitan Area Networks (MANs) are how businesses connect to each other and their customers, essentially extending the reach of a Local Area Network (LAN). While traditionally dominated by telecom companies, the WAN market has seen an influx of new providers offering competitive services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-providers-bandwidth-service-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Increasing Bandwidth By Pair Bonding</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:08:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</guid><description>When your T1 line starts reaching its bandwidth limit, upgrading to a DS3 line might seem like the next step, but it comes with challenges. DS3 often requires fiber optic cable instead of the copper used for T1, and the cost difference is significant.
A simpler solution for a moderate bandwidth boost is adding another T1 line and using &amp;ldquo;pair bonding.&amp;rdquo; This technique combines two lines into one, effectively doubling your bandwidth to 3 Mbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/increasing-bandwidth-by-pair-bonding/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What’s The Best Business Internet Service?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 03:42:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</guid><description>Is your new business in need of internet service for the first time, or does your existing business require better access? You might suspect you could be getting more for your money, and you&amp;rsquo;d probably be right. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the current business internet service options to determine the best fit for you.
The long-standing favored business internet connection for professionals has been the T1 line, recognized for its high reliability and consistent 1...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-s-the-best-business-internet-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Why Choose Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:07:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
The Internet has transitioned from a novelty to a necessity, as indispensable as electricity or heat. However, its unreliability can be a source of frustration, especially given its immense potential for businesses. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore how to enhance Internet stability and dependability.
Internet vs Internet
Internet experiences are not universal, despite discussions about net neutrality claiming otherwise. While some enjoy superior performance, others face limitations. How is this possible?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/why-choose-dedicated-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What Replaces DSL, T1, ISDN PRI, EoC?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Have you noticed that your copper-based telecom services are becoming more expensive? You might have even received a notice that your service will be discontinued. This is a growing trend as telecommunications companies phase out their old copper wire systems and replace them with newer technology like fiber optics and wireless. It&amp;rsquo;s time to think about upgrading your service.
A Different Type of Copper Network
The traditional analog copper telephone lines are the ones being phased out...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-replaces-dsl-t1-isdn-pri-eoc/</a></p></description></item><item><title>EVPL Ethernet Virtual Private Line Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 15:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re likely aware of private line services used by businesses. These lines provide exclusive use, like dedicated analog phone lines or T1 lines for voice and data. Now, there&amp;rsquo;s a new option: the Virtual Private Line (VPL).
Telephone lines weren&amp;rsquo;t always private. Shared lines, known as party lines, connected multiple households. Picking up the phone meant potentially overhearing neighbors&amp;rsquo; conversations, a form of pre-Twitter entertainment.
This lack of privacy is gone from phone lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/evpl-ethernet-virtual-private-line-service/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T-1 Bandwidth Suits the SMB</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</guid><description>Small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs), despite being independently owned, are no longer isolated entities. They rely heavily on the internet, from small insurance offices to quick-service restaurants (QSRs). This reliance stems from the cost-effectiveness of internet-based solutions.
The T1 line is widely used by SMBs for digital communication. This business-grade telecommunication service has become more affordable in recent years due to increased competition and demand. Costs for T1 services have been cut by more than half in some instances...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t-1-bandwidth-suits-the-smb/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can SIP Trunking Supplant ISDN PRI?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 21:54:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</guid><description>Businesses that require multiple phone lines can benefit from digital trunks. While previously only large companies with numerous lines saw advantages with digital trunks, advancements in technology now make them a viable option for businesses with just a few lines and internet access.
What exactly constitutes a telephone trunk? Essentially, it is a collection of phone lines bundled together. Unlike individual analog lines, which consist of a twisted pair of copper wires, a trunk combines multiple lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-sip-trunking-supplant-isdn-pri/</a></p></description></item><item><title>WAN Network Connections From Copper to Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As the demand for more bandwidth increases, so do LAN, MAN, and WAN speeds. This puts pressure on both copper and fiber-based telecommunication networks to upgrade their speeds more frequently. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine the options for both traditional TDM (Time Division Multiplexing) and IP (Internet Protocol) networks.
Traditional Copper Telecom Lines
Copper wiring has been the foundation of electronic communication since the telegraph and telephone networks. While the telegraph is obsolete, the telephone is transitioning technologically, with voice becoming a converged network service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/wan-network-connections-from-copper-to-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Asymmetric Bandwidth is Hot for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 14:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Business-grade internet bandwidth has typically been symmetrical, meaning the upload and download speeds are equal. However, new services are emerging that offer asymmetrical bandwidth, where upload and download speeds differ. Let&amp;rsquo;s examine this trend and its potential benefits for your business.
Symmetrical bandwidth originated from telecommunication services dating back to the advent of digital transmission roughly 50 years ago. Bell Labs, the creator of the T-Carrier standards (including the widely used T1 line), focused on serving telephone companies...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/asymmetric-bandwidth-is-hot-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Boost Ethernet over Copper Speed in 60 Minutes</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</guid><description>Modern Carrier Ethernet services offer superior scalability compared to older technologies like T-Carrier and SONET. Bandwidth increases will soon be achievable within an hour, simply through a phone call or online portal.
Business today demands agility. Traditional planning cycles struggle to match the unpredictable and constantly shifting commercial landscape. The rapid growth of cloud computing highlights this need for adaptability. Cloud services go beyond just reducing staffing and capital expenditures; they offer on-demand scalability...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/boost-ethernet-over-copper-speed-in-60-minutes/</a></p></description></item><item><title>3 Mbps to 6 Mbps Bonded Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 19:54:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</guid><description>Reliable and fast business internet access is crucial for customer interaction and order processing. While you aim for a stable connection with sufficient bandwidth, you also need a budget-friendly option. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore ways to incrementally boost your internet speed in line with your business requirements.
](http://www.T1Rex.com/)
Dedicated internet access used to be limited to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line or a 45 Mbps T3 line (DS3 bandwidth). Shared bandwidth services offer more choices, but their performance and availability can fluctuate...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/3-mbps-to-6-mbps-bonded-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>What is a PRI in VoIP?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</guid><description>While we often view VoIP as a modern phone service separate from the traditional public switched telephone network (PSTN), the reality is that the PSTN is still relevant. Larger organizations with numerous outside phone lines should consider ISDN PRI to connect phones outside their VoIP system.
](http://www.enterprisevoip.com/)
PRI, or Primary Rate Interface, is a standard within ISDN (Integrated Services Digital Network). ISDN was initially intended to replace analog phone lines with digital ones but lost momentum with the rise of broadband internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/what-is-a-pri-in-voip/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Replace T1 Line With 10 Mbps Fiber at Same Cost</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</guid><description>Are telecommunications companies pushing you to replace your outdated T1 line? See this as a positive change! You might be able to upgrade from a 1.5 Mbps T1 line to a 10 Mbps fiber optic service for about the same price. Moreover, fiber optic allows for easy bandwidth increases as your needs grow.
What&amp;rsquo;s Happening to Traditional Phone Lines?
Bell Labs created T1 lines as the first digital telecommunications service to carry multiple phone calls...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/replace-t1-line-with-10-mbps-fiber-at-same-cost/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Can You Get To The Cloud?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 03:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</guid><description>Cloud computing and storage are becoming increasingly popular, and many believe they will soon be the standard for computer use. There are many benefits to using the cloud, such as not needing to buy or maintain software, having data automatically backed up, accessing tools and data from anywhere on any device, and being able to use smaller, more portable computers, like netbooks, cellphones, and tablets. However, one concern remains: reliable access to the cloud...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/can-you-get-to-the-cloud/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Local Telephone Service Provider Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:21:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</guid><description>All homes and businesses require some form of local phone service. While this was once as simple as calling the phone company, more choices are now available, requiring careful consideration for the best deal.
Traditional analog phone service, or &amp;ldquo;dial tone&amp;rdquo; service, uses century-old technology. With its established infrastructure and widespread availability, customers can still walk into a local phone company for service. However, exploring offers from both traditional and newer competitive carriers can lead to better options...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/local-telephone-service-provider-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How Your Internet Connectivity Works</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes of the internet? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to imagine it as a vast cloud, and while that&amp;rsquo;s partially true, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to it. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the technical side of the internet using this informative infographic from Telex.
Connecting Your Business to the Web
To fully utilize the internet&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, your business needs a reliable link to its core infrastructure. This is where Tier 1 service providers come in...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-your-internet-connectivity-works/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1, T3 and Ethernet Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 21:50:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When upgrading your business internet, you have several high-performance options available, including T1 lines, T3 (DS3) lines, and Ethernet options delivered via copper or fiber optic cables.
T1 Lines
T1 lines have been a reliable business internet solution for decades. While their use has become more specialized, they remain a strong option, especially in areas without many choices. The primary advantage of T1 lines is their reliance on existing copper telephone wiring, making them accessible in locations with standard landline service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-t3-and-ethernet-bandwidth/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Line as an On Ramp</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</guid><description>You might know about T1 lines as dedicated connections for digital data or PBX phone lines, but they also serve as excellent access points for various other services. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore why.
Most businesses maintain a Local Area Network (LAN) and a Wide Area Network (WAN) to connect with the wider world. Your WAN connection often acts as an entry point to larger public or private networks.
A prime example is &amp;ldquo;T1 dedicated Internet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-as-an-on-ramp/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Line With Instant Wireless Backup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 13:06:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</guid><description>Losing business broadband during a crucial moment can be incredibly frustrating. This is why many companies choose dedicated T1 lines instead of standard DSL or cable internet, despite the higher reliability of T1, they can still experience outages. Issues like equipment malfunctions or accidents can unexpectedly cut your connection.
To prevent downtime, some companies opt for diverse T1 service, ordering two lines from separate providers. However, this solution isn&amp;rsquo;t foolproof, as both lines often use the same physical infrastructure owned by the Incumbent Local Exchange Carrier (ILEC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-line-with-instant-wireless-backup/</a></p></description></item><item><title>SIP Trunking and Internet On a T1</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 20:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</guid><description>Many smaller companies utilize T1 lines for dedicated internet access, opting for this solution after experiencing unreliable or unavailable consumer-grade broadband options. T1 lines offer these businesses dependable, robust bandwidth at increasingly affordable prices. However, many are unaware that they can bundle their broadband and telephone services onto a single T1 line.
Traditional T1 lines offer various service options. The original format, designed for the telephone industry, provides 24 channels of digitized telephone service over two pairs of twisted copper phone wires...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-trunking-and-internet-on-a-t1/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gaining Ethernet Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:58:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s widely known that using the internet for business purposes offers cost and bandwidth benefits over traditional telecommunications methods. To explore Ethernet Internet access, a useful tool is the Ethernet Internet Finder.
You&amp;rsquo;ll likely discover multiple options for Ethernet Internet service, although availability may vary based on location. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this is a business-specific service. For residential or home office broadband needs, resources like &amp;ldquo;Can I Get DSL?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gaining-ethernet-internet-access/</a></p></description></item><item><title>CAS vs PRI Voice Channels</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:38:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</guid><description>T1 telephone trunk lines are commonly used with PBX and IP PBX phone systems because most modern equipment can connect directly to them without a separate CSU/DSU box. There are two main types of T1 lines: CAS and PRI (also called ISDN PRI).
The original T1 line design, T1 CAS, is divided into 24 channels, each carrying a 64 Kbps digitized phone call. This digital conversion process, known as PCM, ensures clear voice quality...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cas-vs-pri-voice-channels/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Types of Bandwidth for Wide Area Networks</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 23:18:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</guid><description>Wide Area Networks (WANs) connect your business to the outside world, encompassing private networks across various locations. These connections, often called &amp;ldquo;long haul circuits&amp;rdquo;, form the foundation of wide area networking.
Connecting your local area network (LAN) to a WAN usually involves a router and a specialized interface corresponding to the WAN circuit type.
A common WAN connection is a T1 line, terminating at a &amp;ldquo;smart jack&amp;rdquo; in your telecom closet...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/types-of-bandwidth-for-wide-area-networks/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 Lease Costs Reduced Again</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</guid><description>In the past, T1 lines were a costly telecommunication option accessible only to large companies and the telecom sector. While competition has significantly lowered prices since then, there&amp;rsquo;s been another recent plunge. But what&amp;rsquo;s driving this trend?
Originally, T1 lines, part of the T-Carrier telephony standard, were trunk lines connecting central offices within telephone companies. Later, corporate telecom departments adopted them for PBX phone systems and internet service. They became crucial for local internet providers, particularly dial-up services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-lease-costs-reduced-again/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Find A T1 Line For Your Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 12:43:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re unsatisfied with your current internet options like DSL or Cable due to fluctuating speeds, frequent outages, or location limitations, and find Satellite internet&amp;rsquo;s lag, bandwidth restrictions, and weather-related disruptions unacceptable, there&amp;rsquo;s a better solution: T1 lines.
T1 lines, the gold standard for business wireline services, provide a reliable solution with consistent upload and download speeds, high reliability, quick problem resolution, and widespread availability. They offer secure connections between business locations and digital phone line options for PBX systems, features absent in other digital services...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/find-a-t1-line-for-your-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Gigabit Metro Fiber Ethernet Means Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 21:43:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
As data-heavy applications consume more bandwidth, businesses are struggling to keep up. Is there a solution, or are companies destined to lose the bandwidth battle?
More Bandwidth to the Rescue Today&amp;rsquo;s business environment demands more bandwidth than ever before. Older technologies like X.25 and T1 lines are no longer sufficient. Even Ethernet over Copper is just a temporary fix. The optimal solution is connecting to the world through fiber optic bandwidth...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gigabit-metro-fiber-ethernet-means-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Triple Play For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</guid><description>A popular trend in consumer telecommunications, the &amp;ldquo;residential triple play,&amp;rdquo; bundles television, telephone, and broadband internet services. This package is offered at a lower cost than purchasing these services individually from separate providers. Cable companies are well-positioned to provide this bundle due to the high bandwidth capacity of their Hybrid Fiber Cable (HFC) infrastructure, although telephone and wireless providers also offer similar packages.
Businesses also benefit from triple play bundles. Comcast, a major provider known for its cable TV and broadband services, also ranks as the third largest phone company in the United States...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/triple-play-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Swap Your Old T1 Line For Fiber</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 12:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Your reliable T1 line may have been a steadfast companion for years, but its 1.5 Mbps speed, once impressive, now feels outdated in the age of cloud services and video streaming. While you recognize the need for an upgrade, you might be surprised to learn that you could potentially boost your bandwidth without increasing your expenses.
Why You Need to Make a Change
The issue isn&amp;rsquo;t with your T1 line itself, but rather its limited bandwidth for today&amp;rsquo;s demands...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/swap-your-old-t1-line-for-fiber/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Do You Need Bandwidth on Demand?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 01:23:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
When subscribing to bandwidth, you&amp;rsquo;re usually expected to understand your network&amp;rsquo;s needs and pick the optimal service. But what if your needs are unclear or fluctuate? What about transitioning from in-house IT to cloud-based services? What are the consequences of an incorrect choice?
Traditional Bandwidth Services Fall Short
Conventional line contracts offer fixed bandwidth for a predetermined period, like a DS3 connection providing 45 Mbps constantly. While this guarantees consistent speed, you pay even when it&amp;rsquo;s idle...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/do-you-need-bandwidth-on-demand/</a></p></description></item><item><title>ISDN's Primary Rate Interface</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 06:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</guid><description>The Integrated Services Digital Network (ISDN) is a digital telephone standard that provided widespread voice and data services before Enterprise VoIP and MPLS networks. Notably, ISDN&amp;rsquo;s Primary Rate Interface remains in high demand due to its seamless integration with existing telephone trunk lines, which are nearly ubiquitous.
The development of ISDN was driven by the increasing use of modems on analog telephone lines for long-distance data transmission. Analog telephone networks, designed for limited voice bandwidth, only allowed for data speeds up to 56 Kbps...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/isdns-primary-rate-interface/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Fixed Wireless Moving To 4G</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</guid><description>Fixed wireless broadband for businesses has two main forms. The first, found primarily in downtown areas of major cities, uses licensed microwave services. While this method offers high bandwidth, it has a limited coverage area of a few thousand feet and requires a clear line of sight. The second approach utilizes existing 3G cellular broadband networks to provide wider coverage, comparable to a T1 line&amp;rsquo;s bandwidth, wherever there&amp;rsquo;s a cell phone signal...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/fixed-wireless-moving-to-4g/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cure The Bulging T1 Line</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</guid><description>Not too long ago, you got your first T1 line. It was impressive with its 1.5 Mbps speed for both uploading and downloading. The connection was reliable, and there was a guarantee for quick assistance if any issues arose. Though a bit pricey, it was worth it, and you believed it would last forever. However, lately, that once-speedy connection has slowed to a crawl. So, what now?
Many businesses are facing the issue of overloaded T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cure-the-bulging-t1-line/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Plain Old Telephone Service For Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 02:36:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s business world, what&amp;rsquo;s the best way to get a reliable phone service? Surprisingly, it might be POTS – Plain Old Telephone Service.
While the name might sound outdated, POTS offers dependable, high-quality phone service at an affordable price. Why is this the case?
POTS, technically known as analog telephone service over copper wiring, is a direct descendant of the original telephone system. This system, developed and refined over a century by companies like the Bell Telephone System, became incredibly efficient and standardized...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/plain-old-telephone-service-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Connecting Offices Between the US and Mexico</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 05:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many businesses operate in both the United States and Mexico. While numerous carriers cater to each country, finding consistent service quality for both markets can be challenging.
International Connections Businesses operating across borders require telecommunication solutions that extend internationally. Fortunately, several carriers provide international line services, including connections between US and Mexican cities.
Modern options encompass voice, data, and video services, enabling connections between two locations or the creation of a vast virtual LAN encompassing all North American business locations and beyond...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/connecting-offices-between-the-us-and-mexico/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Rural Doesn’t Mean Broadband Wasteland Anymore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 20:54:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Securing reliable and affordable broadband internet access is a common challenge for businesses located in rural areas or business parks outside city limits, unlike their urban counterparts.
Is The Broadband Service I Need Available? Just a few years ago, businesses could operate effectively with only phone lines and electricity. However, in today&amp;rsquo;s world, broadband internet access is crucial for serving even local customers. The required internet performance depends on the nature and size of your business...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/rural-doesn-t-mean-broadband-wasteland-anymore/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Reduce Expense of T3 or DS3</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 06:06:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re currently using or thinking about getting 45 Mbps service via T3 or DS3, it&amp;rsquo;s worth exploring cost-saving options before renewing or signing a new contract.
While often considered the same, T3 and DS3 have distinct meanings. T3, a Bell Labs creation, is a specific T-carrier system capable of handling 45 Mbps of full-duplex data transmission or 672 simultaneous phone calls. As a point of reference, a T3 line can accommodate 28 T1 lines...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/reduce-expense-of-t3-or-ds3/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Your Broadband Isn’t Stable Enough For VoIP Phones</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 01:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
You might get laughed at for sticking with your old-school analog phone lines. &amp;ldquo;Still using a rotary phone?&amp;rdquo; they&amp;rsquo;ll joke. But here&amp;rsquo;s the thing: those old-fashioned phone lines were built for clear sound and unwavering reliability. Sure, they might deteriorate over time, leading to static and eventually dropped calls. A quick fix from the phone company, though, and you&amp;rsquo;re back in business for years to come.
The modern approach is using the internet for phone calls, combining your phone and internet services onto one broadband connection...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-your-broadband-isn-t-stable-enough-for-voip-phones/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Dedicated Leased Lines for Business</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 22:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Leased lines, a technology dating back to the telegraph, have evolved to offer businesses speeds ranging from 1.5 Mbps to 100 Gbps. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve into the characteristics of leased lines and how they stand apart from conventional broadband.
What is a Leased Line?
Similar to leasing a property, leased lines involve an agreement and regular payments that grant you exclusive access to a dedicated communication line.
In its simplest form, a leased line consists of a pair of copper wires, linking your location to your provider, often through a local telephone company (ILEC)...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/dedicated-leased-lines-for-business/</a></p></description></item><item><title>T1 is Your Rural Broadband Solution</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:17:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
While metropolitan areas have many choices for broadband internet, rural areas often only have access to limited options like mobile 4G or satellite internet. However, there&amp;rsquo;s another option that is often overlooked but may be a perfect fit for rural businesses and remote work: T1 dedicated internet access.
T1 is Everywhere T1 lines are widely available, often wherever standard phone lines exist. This is because T1 utilizes the same copper wiring infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/t1-is-your-rural-broadband-solution/</a></p></description></item><item><title>The Case For Telecom Copper</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:49:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</guid><description>Major telephone corporations are considering decommissioning their existing copper wire infrastructure, partly to reduce competition and partly to transition to fiber optic technology. However, the question arises: should the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) allow the removal of this copper, or should it be preserved as a valuable national asset?
While copper might not initially seem like a national treasure compared to gold or silver, its worth stems from the significant investment in time, effort, and resources used to install it across the country...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-case-for-telecom-copper/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Price Your Telecom Lines Before You Move</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 08:17:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</guid><description>When choosing a location for your new or relocating business, telecommunications costs are an important factor to consider. While factors like foot traffic might be more critical for retail businesses, telecom expenses can vary significantly depending on your location and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be ignored.
It might seem unusual, but factoring in bandwidth costs when choosing a business address is crucial. Even the cost of a basic T1 line can double in areas with limited infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/price-your-telecom-lines-before-you-move/</a></p></description></item><item><title>How MPLS Network Bursting Provides Flexibility</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 19:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</guid><description>The standard method of ordering bandwidth for last-mile connections or MPLS networks involves committing to a specific rate or line speed. For instance, a T1 line provides a constant 1.5 Mbps, while a 10 Mbps Ethernet service delivers precisely that speed. In multi-tenant networks like MPLS VPNs, you purchase a committed information rate representing the maximum speed your connection will achieve. However, what happens if business needs change or your initial estimate is inaccurate?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/how-mpls-network-bursting-provides-flexibility/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 01:52:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</guid><description>The number of business bandwidth choices has grown a lot lately. One popular newcomer is Ethernet over Copper (EoC). If you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about a new or renewed connectivity contract, check out these EoC FAQs.
Q: What is Ethernet over Copper service?
A: Ethernet over Copper (EoC) uses existing telephone lines to carry Ethernet signals. Basically, it extends your local network across cities and wider areas.
Q: How does EoC compare to T1 lines?..<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq/</a></p></description></item><item><title>When Broadband is Hard to Find</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:38:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</guid><description>For businesses in bustling city centers, finding network and telecom services is usually not a problem. The challenge is finding the best deals on connectivity, trunk lines, and cloud services, as there might be lesser-known options available.
However, for businesses in rural areas or home offices, options might seem limited and expensive. Surprisingly, there might be more bandwidth choices than you realize.
Traditional Telecommunications Services Businesses with commercial addresses can typically access services like POTS phone service and T1 lines, using existing copper cable infrastructure...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/when-broadband-is-hard-to-find/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Are T1 Lines Still Used?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 14:27:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
With today&amp;rsquo;s advanced technology like gigabit fiber optic and cable broadband, discussing twisted copper pair lines for WAN networking or Internet access might seem outdated. However, the traditional T1 line is still used today. The question is, why would anyone choose this older technology?
Who Needs a T1 Line?
Ideally, we would have a wide range of networking options. While this is true in commercial areas of major U...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/are-t1-lines-still-used/</a></p></description></item><item><title>5G Fixed Wireless Fills the Copper Gap</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
For about 150 years, twisted pair copper wiring has been the standard way to deliver telecom services. This includes everything from traditional phone service to T1 lines for internet access and private connections. However, copper wiring is becoming outdated. Even if you haven&amp;rsquo;t reached the bandwidth limits of copper yet, you might face issues if your local telephone company (which owns the copper lines) decides to stop service...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/5g-fixed-wireless-fills-the-copper-gap/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>