<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Peering on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/peering/</link><description>Recent content in Peering on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/peering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internet Wholesale Bandwidth Options</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</guid><description>Two main types of organizations buy internet bandwidth: end users and resellers. End users, such as businesses, need access for their employees. Resellers, also known as Internet Service Providers (ISPs), purchase large amounts of bandwidth and divide it among numerous individuals and businesses, aiming to profit from the difference between wholesale and retail prices.
The biggest networks, called Tier 1, are integral to the internet&amp;rsquo;s core and don&amp;rsquo;t purchase access. Instead, they exchange traffic equally with other Tier 1 networks through a process called peering, which benefits all without financial transactions...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/internet-wholesale-bandwidth-options/</a></p></description></item><item><title>GTT Expands Ethernet Footprint With PacketExchange</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:52:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</guid><description>GTT, a global telecommunications company, is expanding its Ethernet services globally by acquiring PacketExchange, an Ethernet provider. PacketExchange, based in London, boasts a substantial 10 Gigabit fiber optic IP network spanning Europe, the United States, and Asia, largely acquired through its acquisition of MZIMA Networks in 2010. This combined infrastructure offers private line services, MPLS, VPLS networking, and peering capabilities.
This acquisition highlights the growing dominance of Carrier Ethernet in telecommunications...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/gtt-expands-ethernet-footprint-with-packetexchange/</a></p></description></item><item><title>E-NNI Helps Ethernet Go Global</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 05:47:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet is rapidly gaining popularity. This is understandable given that, compared to traditional telecom services, it typically provides greater bandwidth at reduced costs. Additionally, it offers features like virtual private lines and LAN services that were previously unavailable. As businesses increasingly use Ethernet in their wide area networks (WANs), they naturally want to leverage their Metro Ethernet connections for comprehensive connectivity.
The term &amp;ldquo;metro&amp;rdquo; in Metro Ethernet signifies its intended use within a metropolitan area...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/e-nni-helps-ethernet-go-global/</a></p></description></item><item><title>IP Transit vs Peering vs DIA</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 01:26:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</guid><description>The internet relies on a complex system of interconnected networks. While it appears as a single entity to users, it&amp;rsquo;s actually a collection of networks working together to transmit data.
At the top are Tier 1 networks, massive international systems with global reach. These networks connect through &amp;ldquo;peering,&amp;rdquo; a mutually beneficial arrangement where they exchange traffic equally without fees, effectively expanding their reach.
Smaller Tier 2 networks, with limited capacity, can connect to Tier 1 networks for a fee known as &amp;ldquo;IP transit,&amp;rdquo; compensating for the traffic imbalance...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ip-transit-vs-peering-vs-dia/</a></p></description></item><item><title>International Dedicated Internet Access</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</guid><description>Businesses that rely heavily on the internet require dependable internet access, especially multinational companies that need consistent connectivity across all their locations.
The internet&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure allows data to travel globally. If one path fails, the network automatically reroutes traffic. Performance issues often stem from local access networks rather than the internet&amp;rsquo;s core.
While the internet excels in many areas, real-time processes like video conferencing can be affected by its inherent limitations...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/international-dedicated-internet-access/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>