<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hiring on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hiring/</link><description>Recent content in Hiring on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/hiring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In 2021, digitalization will be the driving force behind recruitment in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/in-2021-digitalization-will-be-the-driving-force-behind-recruitment-in-singapore/</guid><description>Randstad Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 2021 Market Outlook Report examines the economic and hiring trends anticipated for 2021.
Jaya Dass, Managing Director for Randstad Malaysia and Singapore, emphasizes that digital transformation will be a key driver of talent demand in 2021. She predicts a surge in demand for tech professionals and digitally skilled individuals across various sectors. While acknowledging the cautious optimism of businesses in the wake of the pandemic, Dass highlights the need for agility and innovation to adapt to the evolving landscape.</description></item><item><title>Robert Walters reports that there is still a high demand for talent in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/robert-walters-reports-that-there-is-still-a-high-demand-for-talent-in-singapore/</guid><description>Robert Walters, a recruitment firm, has published its Asia Job Index for the first quarter of 2015, highlighting that finding and hiring local talent remains a top concern in Singapore. The Asia Job Index monitors the number of job postings for professional roles across major job sites and national newspapers in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Malaysia, and Singapore.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, noted that recruitment in Singapore is primarily driven by competition for a limited pool of candidates, making it challenging to attract the most qualified individuals for the right positions.</description></item><item><title>Job Forward introduces the Startup Essence referral tool for startups and small to medium enterprises (SMEs)</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-forward-introduces-the-startup-essence-referral-tool-for-startups-and-small-to-medium-enterprises-smes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 01:44:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/job-forward-introduces-the-startup-essence-referral-tool-for-startups-and-small-to-medium-enterprises-smes/</guid><description>Source: Job Forward.
Job Forward, the first online social recruitment platform in Singapore, has introduced Startup Essence. This new addition to their referral-based platform helps startups and small to medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) by allowing them to build recruitment pages that attract and engage potential employees. The company aims to create a new avenue for these businesses to connect with individuals who are a good fit for their company culture.</description></item><item><title>Is your company using mobile for recruiting?</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 11:29:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/is-your-company-using-mobile-for-recruiting/</guid><description>Mobile interaction is crucial for successful recruitment in India. In 2014-15, almost half of companies surveyed by TimesJobs reported receiving 10-20% of job applications via mobile phones, significantly up from the previous year.
With mobile phones widespread, 65% of organizations in India now have mobile recruitment strategies, a 10% increase from the previous year, according to a TimesJobs.com survey.
Jobseeker behavior has shifted dramatically, with 85% of online job searching now done on smartphones.</description></item><item><title>Glassdoor has released a list of the top 10 workplaces in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 02:13:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/glassdoor-has-released-a-list-of-the-top-10-workplaces-in-singapore/</guid><description>The job and recruiting website Glassdoor has revealed the winners of its annual Employees’ Choice Awards, which included a category for Singapore for the first time.
These awards recognize the Best Places to Work in 2020 across nine countries, including Singapore. The rankings are determined by the input of employees who anonymously share their experiences through company reviews on Glassdoor. This feedback encompasses their job, work environment, and employer over the past year.</description></item><item><title>Zhaopin in China introduces chat feature to Highpin recruitment platform</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 06:24:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/zhaopin-in-china-introduces-chat-feature-to-highpin-recruitment-platform/</guid><description>Source: Highpin.cn website.
Zhaopin, a Chinese career platform, has introduced Highpin Chat, a desktop-based instant messaging feature for its executive recruitment site, Highpin.cn.
This new chat feature aims to streamline the hiring process on Highpin.cn. Recruiters and employers can now directly connect with candidates, enabling better candidate evaluation and efficient job matching. Similarly, job seekers can use the chat to ask recruiters and employers about specific roles and follow their application status in real time.</description></item><item><title>Finding good people is still a challenge, according to ManpowerGroup</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:20:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-good-people-is-still-a-challenge-according-to-manpowergroup/</guid><description>Source: ManpowerGroup infographic.
Around the world, the most difficult positions to fill are in skilled trades (particularly chefs, bakers, butchers, mechanics, and electricians), sales, engineering (mechanical, electrical, and civil), technician roles, and drivers (especially heavy vehicle operators), according to workforce experts ManpowerGroup.
The situation in Singapore is somewhat different. While engineers are among the top five hardest roles to fill, as elsewhere, the other four are accounting and finance professionals, sales representatives, secretaries (including receptionists and administrative assistants), and marketing, public relations, and communications specialists.</description></item><item><title>The practice of recruiting and retaining skilled individuals</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-practice-of-recruiting-and-retaining-skilled-individuals/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 01:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-practice-of-recruiting-and-retaining-skilled-individuals/</guid><description>Innovative talent acquisition strategies are helping some companies secure the best possible candidates.
Mei-lynn Chan, Head of Organizational Development, Group Human Capital at Maybank, emphasizes the need for HR departments to approach hiring from a business perspective. This involves quantifying HR activities into tangible business metrics.
She argues that while budget constraints may have traditionally limited HR&amp;rsquo;s hiring choices, a new perspective allows for hiring the right talent if the business can absorb the cost until the hire generates a return on investment.</description></item><item><title>Digital recruitment is becoming increasingly popular, with HireVue leading the way</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 18:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/digital-recruitment-is-becoming-increasingly-popular-with-hirevue-leading-the-way/</guid><description>HireVue, a leading digital recruiting platform, facilitates thousands of interviews daily. The company&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Mark Newman, highlights the global employment paradox: millions of professionals are unemployed while companies struggle to fill open positions. HireVue aims to bridge this gap by streamlining the hiring process and creating a level playing field for all candidates, regardless of background. The company emphasizes the importance of allowing candidates to showcase their skills and connect with potential employers effectively.</description></item><item><title>Corporate India is facing challenges in recruiting women candidates for job positions</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/corporate-india-is-facing-challenges-in-recruiting-women-candidates-for-job-positions/</guid><description>MyParichay, a Facebook-based recruiting platform, states that social recruiting is no longer optional. They report that 90% of recruiters believe a social media-based hiring tool would offer a competitive edge in hiring a gender-diverse workforce.
Source: MyParichay
A company-wide survey in India conducted by MyParichay revealed that 85% of companies surveyed believe diversity is critical for workplace innovation. However, MyParichay found that 75% of recruiters struggle to find qualified female candidates to meet the gender diversity goals set by leadership.</description></item><item><title>Crowdsourcing In Lieu of Outsourcing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 20:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/crowdsourcing-in-lieu-of-outsourcing/</guid><description>Over recent years, outsourcing has become increasingly popular as a way to meet business needs. However, since the Great Recession, crowdsourcing has emerged as a new and growing trend. This approach leverages the collective talent of a group to find solutions for specific tasks.
Crowdsourcing provides a decentralized approach to problem-solving, unlike traditional methods of assigning tasks to employees or contractors. Imagine needing a building sold – you&amp;rsquo;d hire a real estate agent.</description></item><item><title>The demand for jobs in Singapore is being driven by digitization, according to Robert Walters</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:12:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/the-demand-for-jobs-in-singapore-is-being-driven-by-digitization-according-to-robert-walters/</guid><description>Source: Robert Walters. Click on the
image to view a larger version.
According to the international recruitment firm Robert Walters, the increasing presence of digital technology was the main driver of recruitment in Singapore during the second quarter of 2015. These insights were published in the company’s Asia Job Index for Q2 2015.
Toby Fowlston, Managing Director of Robert Walters Southeast Asia, acknowledged the anticipated decrease in job advertisements during this quarter.</description></item><item><title>SEEK's Jobstreet introduces a new employment platform powered by artificial intelligence</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seek-s-jobstreet-introduces-a-new-employment-platform-powered-by-artificial-intelligence/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/seek-s-jobstreet-introduces-a-new-employment-platform-powered-by-artificial-intelligence/</guid><description>Jobstreet by SEEK, a leading career and talent platform, has launched a new and improved employment platform powered by SEEK’s AI technology. This upgrade aims to create a better experience for both job seekers and employers by improving job matches and providing more in-depth insights.
This initiative is a component of SEEK’s ongoing efforts to unify its online employment platforms across the Asia Pacific region, including SEEK in Australia and New Zealand, Jobstreet in Singapore, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Indonesia, and JobsDB in Hong Kong and Thailand.</description></item><item><title>Strong job market in Hong Kong for 2015</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/strong-job-market-in-hong-kong-for-2015/</guid><description>A new report by recruitment firm REED indicates that 78% of employees in Hong Kong received a pay raise in the last year. The report, titled REED 2015 Salary Survey and Market Insight, covers 14 countries across Asia, Australia, Europe, and the Middle East.
REED predicts that Hong Kong&amp;rsquo;s thriving job market will continue to grow in 2015, driven by substantial foreign investments. The financial, digital marketing, e-commerce, and sales &amp;amp; marketing industries are expected to be particularly strong.</description></item><item><title>80% of Singaporeans living abroad are interested in returning to work in their home country</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 07:18:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/80-of-singaporeans-living-abroad-are-interested-in-returning-to-work-in-their-home-country/</guid><description>A new report from Robert Walters, a professional recruitment firm, suggests that competition for skilled workers in Singapore will increase in 2016. This demand will likely lead to more attempts to recruit Singaporeans working abroad. Hiring managers believe that these experienced professionals could help alleviate the tight labor market, benefiting both companies and the &amp;ldquo;Fair Consideration Framework,&amp;rdquo; which promotes local hiring.
Returning Singaporeans are desirable candidates because they often have international experience and a broader range of skills compared to their counterparts who haven&amp;rsquo;t worked overseas.</description></item><item><title>Contract positions are the perfect solution for companies in Singapore</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:14:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/contract-positions-are-the-perfect-solution-for-companies-in-singapore/</guid><description>A recent survey by Robert Walters, a global recruitment firm, indicates a rise in contract employment in Singapore. The Singapore Contracting Survey reveals that hiring managers are increasingly turning to skilled contract workers due to difficulties in obtaining approval for permanent positions. Many companies are implementing hiring freezes, often mandated by their headquarters, leading managers in Singapore to seek adaptable, temporary staffing solutions.
The survey, which polled over 300 professionals in Singapore with contracting experience, explored the advantages and disadvantages of contract work.</description></item><item><title>Foo See Yang has been appointed as the Vice President and Country General Manager for Singapore at Kelly Services</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foo-see-yang-has-been-appointed-as-the-vice-president-and-country-general-manager-for-singapore-at-kelly-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 23:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/foo-see-yang-has-been-appointed-as-the-vice-president-and-country-general-manager-for-singapore-at-kelly-services/</guid><description>Source: Kelly Services.
Foo.
Kelly Services appointed Foo See Yang to the position of Vice President and Country General Manager for Singapore, starting January 1st of this year. With over 15 years in the recruitment field, Foo will manage over 150 consultants for the global staffing and recruitment company in Singapore.
“See Yang has been with Kelly Services for over 13 years. As a Singaporean with deep knowledge of this market, he has provided valuable local perspectives on Singapore&amp;rsquo;s dynamic talent landscape and has proven himself to be a successful and respected leader,” stated Natalia Shuman, Senior Vice President and General Manager for Kelly Services, EMEA and APAC regions.</description></item><item><title>Helping individuals with disabilities transition from training programs to meaningful employment opportunities</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/helping-individuals-with-disabilities-transition-from-training-programs-to-meaningful-employment-opportunities/</guid><description>Individuals with disabilities should be placed in jobs where they can acquire skills on the job, rather than receiving training without a clear path to employment. Christy Lynch, CEO of KARE Ireland, an organization supporting individuals with intellectual disabilities and their families, emphasized the importance of collaborating with both individuals with disabilities and employers to create truly empowering opportunities. He spoke at the &amp;ldquo;Towards an Inclusive Workforce 2015&amp;rdquo; event, co-organized by SPD and supported by SG Enable and the Singapore Workforce Development Agency (WDA).</description></item><item><title>TalentBin by Monster searches through social networks to find potential candidates for recruitment</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/talentbin-by-monster-searches-through-social-networks-to-find-potential-candidates-for-recruitment/</guid><description>Source: Monster website.
Monster recently launched its TalentBin platform across multiple regions to help businesses locate and engage skilled professionals. Functioning as a specialized search engine for talent, the software grants recruiters access to a pool of potential candidates who might not be easily discoverable through traditional methods. This is achieved by analyzing and leveraging professional information individuals share on various social media platforms.
TalentBin not only automates and simplifies the process of identifying potential candidates through site monitoring, data interpretation, and profile matching but also makes hiring more efficient, allowing recruiters to achieve more in less time.</description></item><item><title>According to LinkedIn, 65% of employees in Singapore are planning to change jobs in 2023</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/according-to-linkedin-65-of-employees-in-singapore-are-planning-to-change-jobs-in-2023/</guid><description>Although hiring in Singapore experienced a significant drop of 34% in December 2022 compared to the previous year, and despite economic uncertainties, professionals are adopting a forward-thinking approach to their careers. They are investing in skill development and actively pursuing opportunities for advancement. LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s research indicates that a considerable 65% of professionals are contemplating job changes in 2023.
The desire for enhanced financial stability amidst rising living costs is a primary driver behind this job search trend.</description></item><item><title>Hilton ranks among the top three employers in the hospitality industry in Greater China</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:40:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/hilton-ranks-among-the-top-three-employers-in-the-hospitality-industry-in-greater-china/</guid><description>Source: Hilton. Hilton earned the title of Best Hospitality Company to Work For in Greater China.
For the second year in a row, Hilton has secured a spot among the top three companies to work for in Greater China, according to the global research and consulting firm Great Place To Work Institute. Holding the highest position among hospitality companies on the 2016 list, Hilton also received recognition from 51job Inc.</description></item><item><title>Companies are focusing on ensuring that their workforces are prepared for the future</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 13:24:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/companies-are-focusing-on-ensuring-that-their-workforces-are-prepared-for-the-future/</guid><description>- The Asia-Pacific region is seeing a high demand for professionals with a mix of skills, especially those with expertise in technology and the ability to adapt to new situations. This trend is driven by the increasing adoption of digital technologies across various sectors.
- To attract and keep skilled workers, companies are refining their hiring strategies to identify individuals who are not only experts in their fields but also adaptable and possess a global perspective.</description></item></channel></rss>