<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cybercriminal on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybercriminal/</link><description>Recent content in Cybercriminal on 0x000216</description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/cybercriminal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Before you decide to check out Ronaldo, reconsider your decision</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 01:52:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</guid><description>A study by McAfee, a part of Intel Security, reveals that cybercriminals often use popular figures like Cristiano Ronaldo to lure unsuspecting users to malicious websites. These websites, designed to look like legitimate fan pages, can infect devices with malware capable of stealing personal information. McAfee&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Red Card Club&amp;rdquo; list highlights the top eleven footballers whose names are most frequently used in these scams, with Ronaldo topping the list, followed by Lionel Messi and Iker Cassillas...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/before-you-decide-to-check-out-ronaldo-reconsider-your-decision/</a></p></description></item><item><title>Cybercriminals have a strong affinity for Donnie Yen and Jackie Chan</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:57:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</guid><description>Donnie Yen, known for his martial arts expertise, has been identified as the riskiest celebrity to search for online in Singapore, according to Intel Security&amp;rsquo;s annual study.
Cybercriminals exploit public interest in popular figures, creating websites that appear legitimate but actually contain malware. These malicious sites can steal personal information, such as passwords, from unsuspecting users. The study, focusing on Singapore, revealed that searches for martial arts legends, established actresses, and musicians often expose users to a higher risk of viruses and malware...<p>Read The Full Article :<a href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/">https://Nexus-Security.github.io/cybercriminals-have-a-strong-affinity-for-donnie-yen-and-jackie-chan/</a></p></description></item></channel></rss>