<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telecom Technology on 0x000216</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-technology/</link><description>Recent content in Telecom Technology on 0x000216</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Nexus-Security.github.io/tags/telecom-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Instant Metro Ethernet Provider Maps</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/instant-metro-ethernet-provider-maps/</guid><description>Metro Ethernet (Metro E) offers significant benefits like enhanced bandwidth, cost savings, and advanced features such as interconnected WAN setups. However, finding the right Metro E service for your business requires understanding its availability. This is where a Metro Ethernet provider map becomes essential.
Why is mapping Ethernet availability crucial? Unlike established services like T1 lines, Metro Ethernet is relatively new and not universally accessible. Your current provider might not offer it or cover your location yet.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper Data Service</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 19:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-data-service/</guid><description>While traditional data services rely on technologies like T1 lines, DS3 bandwidth, OC-3, SONET fiber optics, Frame Relay, and MPLS networks for connectivity, Ethernet over Copper (EoC) presents a modern alternative for the last mile. Although not available coast-to-coast, EoC provides a cost-effective, high-performance solution, especially for connecting businesses to larger private or public networks.
EoC leverages existing copper infrastructure, eliminating the need for costly fiber optic installations or dealing with line-of-sight issues encountered with fixed wireless solutions.</description></item><item><title>100 Mbps Business Ethernet vs OC3 SONET Bandwidth</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:59:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/100-mbps-business-ethernet-vs-oc3-sonet-bandwidth/</guid><description>By: John Shepler
Many tech companies and large corporations adopted fiber optic bandwidth service, specifically OC3 SONET, years ago. While some have upgraded to faster SONET options, others have continued using their reliable OC3 service.
However, the emergence of 100 Mbps and faster Ethernet MAN and WAN bandwidth is challenging SONET&amp;rsquo;s dominance. Long-time users are exploring alternatives, while new customers are carefully considering their options.
SONET (Synchronous Optical NETwork) within the SDH (Synchronous Digital Hierarchy) became the foundation for most metropolitan, wide area, and international networks in recent decades.</description></item><item><title>Ethernet over Copper FAQ - Part 2</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:38:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/ethernet-over-copper-faq-part-2/</guid><description>Ethernet over Copper (EoC) is gaining traction as a business connectivity solution, rivaling traditional options like T1, DS3, and OC3. To determine if EoC is a good fit for your business, consider these frequently asked questions.
Q: How does EoC&amp;rsquo;s cost compare to other services?
A: EoC often provides significant cost savings compared to other business bandwidth services. A 3 Mbps Ethernet connection might be priced similarly to a 1.5 Mbps T1 line, with even greater savings at higher bandwidths.</description></item><item><title>Finding Information on PBX Telephone Systems Pricing</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 15:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/finding-information-on-pbx-telephone-systems-pricing/</guid><description>Planning a new office building or hotel? Upgrading your old business phone system? Finding the right PBX system at the right price is essential for a smart decision.
Instead of searching endlessly, utilize an online clearinghouse like the VAR Network. This platform connects businesses with qualified PBX and network equipment vendors.
The VAR Network focuses on these two interconnected technologies. Most businesses rely on both for internal communication and internet access.</description></item><item><title>SIP vs PRI Telephone Trunking</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 16:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/sip-vs-pri-telephone-trunking/</guid><description>Telephone trunking allows multiple phone conversations to happen simultaneously over long distances using a single line. While older analog methods have been replaced by digital ones using time division multiplexing (TDM), a newer technology called SIP trunking is emerging as a challenger.
The rise of SIP trunking is driven by the shift from traditional circuit-switched telephone systems to packet-switched systems like VoIP. However, T1 lines are still widely used, even with the newest IP PBX systems.</description></item><item><title>EoDS1 Extends Ethernet over Copper Distance</title><link>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 02:38:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Nexus-Security.github.io/eods1-extends-ethernet-over-copper-distance/</guid><description>The high demand for Ethernet over Copper (EoC) services has surpassed its availability, partly due to the limited presence of necessary equipment in central offices and distance constraints. MegaPath, a major carrier, offers a solution called EoDS1 (Ethernet over DS1).
Both EoC and EoDS1 utilize existing copper telephone wiring and increase bandwidth by combining multiple pairs. However, they differ in their distance limitations. EoC outperforms traditional T1 lines (1.5 Mbps) by providing higher bandwidth options, ranging from 3 Mbps to 100 Mbps, using existing copper infrastructure.</description></item></channel></rss>